[
	{
		"answer":"15\u70B9-17\u70B9",
		"indexes":"grysedzbsytdsegscmgsclgxssszdssmsj",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u7528\u5341\u4E8C\u5730\u652F\u8868\u793A\u4E00\u5929\u7684\u5341\u4E8C\u4E2A\u65F6\u8FB0\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u65F6\u8FB0\u4E24\u4E2A\u5C0F\u65F6\uFF0C\u7533\u65F6\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":17156
	},
	{
		"answer":"F1",
		"indexes":"xxlzjygangkjjdkjm",
		"question":"\u60F3\u4FEE\u70BC\u81EA\u5DF1,\u5E94\u8BE5\u6309\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u6253\u5F00\u754C\u9762?",
		"id":17157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"klOKxqyng",
		"question":"\u5361\u62C9OK\u5174\u8D77\u4E8E\u54EA\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":17158
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C88\u9CD7",
		"indexes":"wwyyqxxwwjsylsxetkgedmwwynzdwwydxmssmm",
		"question":"\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C\u56E0\u5176\u5F62\u50CF\u5A03\u5A03\uFF0C\u53EB\u58F0\u53C8\u7C7B\u4F3C\u5C0F\u513F\u557C\u54ED\uFF0C\u6545\u800C\u5F97\u540D'\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C'\u3002\u60A8\u77E5\u9053'\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C'\u7684\u5B66\u540D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"lhgjkwzzzbsznl",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u6559\u79D1\u6587\u7EC4\u7EC7\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":17160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u540D",
		"indexes":"mlsszdsssyg",
		"question":"\u540D\u843D\u5B59\u5C71\u4E2D\u7684'\u5B59\u5C71'\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A",
		"id":17161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"wggdwxmzsgyyzszlyggwgzljqlzdqdyxxxzgyxss",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u6587\u5B66\u540D\u8457<\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49>\u4E2D\u5851\u9020\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u8FC7\u4E94\u5173\u65A9\u516D\u5C06,\u5343\u91CC\u8D70\u5355\u9A91\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u5F62\u8C61,\u8FD9\u4E2A\u82F1\u96C4\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":17163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u7EA6\u9EC4\u660F\u540E",
		"indexes":"yslstdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6708\u4E0A\u67F3\u68A2\u5934\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"jyswgnyghdsydnh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5EFA\u5143\u201D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":17165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u6866",
		"indexes":"mrsdxms",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u4EBA\u6811\u7684\u5B66\u540D\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67CF\u6797",
		"indexes":"xmngcszdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u5FB7\u56FD?",
		"id":17167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"sgyyssdzz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8457\u4F5C",
		"id":17168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"kmsz",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u662F\u6307",
		"id":17169
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49",
		"indexes":"ggzjdsslhtjyxsfcbztkqsyjzjdxyhzswgnbwxgdmzdkpc",
		"question":"\u6EDA\u6EDA\u957F\u6C5F\u4E1C\u901D\u6C34,\u6D6A\u82B1\u6DD8\u5C3D\u82F1\u96C4.\u662F\u975E\u6210\u8D25\u8F6C\u5934\u7A7A.\u9752\u5C71\u4F9D\u65E7\u5728,\u51E0\u5EA6\u5915\u9633\u7EA2...\u8FD9\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u90E8\u6587\u5B66\u53E4\u5178\u540D\u8457\u7684\u5F00\u7BC7\u8BCD",
		"id":17170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"syqjjdssdyxgs",
		"question":"\u6C34\u6DF9\u4E03\u519B\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u6545\u4E8B\uFF1F",
		"id":17171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"yryhsjdssyccdzdgs",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u4E0E\u66F9\u64CD\u6597\u667A\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":17172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u3001\u8700\u3001\u5434",
		"indexes":"txsfsztxflwnjg",
		"question":"'\u5929\u4E0B\u4E09\u5206'\u662F\u6307\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u88C2\u4E3A\u54EA\u51E0\u56FD",
		"id":17173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"szqrsgmlhqqmhjdsdgs",
		"question":"\u820C\u6218\u7FA4\u5112\u3001\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u548C\u4E03\u64D2\u5B5F\u83B7\u8BB2\u7684\u8C01\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":17174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"csbzdxdzlbbxz",
		"question":"<\u51FA\u5E08\u8868>\u4E2D\u7684'\u5148\u5E1D'\u6307\u5218\u5907,'\u965B\u4E0B'\u6307",
		"id":17175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C82\u5A75",
		"indexes":"lbwlssdz",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u4E3A\u4E86\u8C01\u6740\u8463\u5353",
		"id":17176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4",
		"indexes":"mchxzqsspyxjsrqjwllyssjybxrszsssdssgyyzlbhccdydgszggss",
		"question":"\u52C9\u4ECE\u864E\u7A74\u6682\u6816\u8EAB,\u8BF4\u7834\u82F1\u96C4\u60CA\u715E\u4EBA.\u5DE7\u5C06\u95FB\u96F7\u6765\u63A9\u9970,\u968F\u673A\u5E94\u53D8\u4FE1\u5982\u795E>\u8FD9\u9996\u8BD7\u8BF4\u7684\u662F<\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49>\u4E2D\u5218\u5907\u548C\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E00\u6BB5\u6545\u4E8B.\u8FD9\u4E2A\u6545\u4E8B\u662F",
		"id":17177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"cywsjbzqdfsgjsgyydsmzyzzydjhgccyqdzbhlzqnbdhcxcyddfdgsyheld",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED'\u4E07\u4E8B\u4FF1\u5907,\u53EA\u6B20\u4E1C\u98CE'\u662F\u6839\u636E<\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49>\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79\u4E2D'\u5468\u745C\u5B9A\u8BA1\u706B\u653B\u66F9\u64CD,\u4E00\u5207\u90FD\u51C6\u5907\u597D\u4E86,\u53EA\u7F3A\u80FD\u628A\u5927\u706B\u5439\u5411\u66F9\u8425\u7684\u4E1C\u98CE.'\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u6F14\u5316\u800C\u6765\u7684.",
		"id":17178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"zglyzylszhdycyssddzl",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0E\u5468\u745C\u8054\u624B\u6307\u6325\u7684\u4E00\u573A\u4EE5\u5C11\u80DC\u591A\u7684\u6218\u4F8B",
		"id":17179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A00\u8FC7\u5176\u5B9E\uFF0C\u671F\u671F\u827E\u827E",
		"indexes":"yxnlgsysggsygdcyhsy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E24\u4E2A\u662F\u4E0E\u4E09\u56FD\u6545\u4E8B\u6709\u5173\u7684\u6210\u8BED\u6216\u4FD7\u8BED",
		"id":17180
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8857\u4EAD\u5931\u5B88",
		"indexes":"zglhlzmssywhs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6325\u6CEA\u65A9\u9A6C\u8C21\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u4F55\u4E8B.",
		"id":17181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5141",
		"indexes":"dcdyfss",
		"question":"\u8C82\u5A75\u7684\u4E49\u7236\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"dmcbszdfbyzlbtqcsseqdjzxdssmzy",
		"question":"\u675C\u7267<\u8D64\u58C1>\u8BD7\u4E2D'\u4E1C\u98CE\u4E0D\u4E0E\u5468\u90CE\u4FBF,\u94DC\u96C0\u6625\u6DF1\u9501\u4E8C\u4E54'\u7684\u53E5\u5B50\u5199\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79;.",
		"id":17183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6253\u795D\u5BB6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlgszbssgyyzdyxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6545\u4E8B\u4E2D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u9879\u662F:",
		"id":17184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"tysjyzsdjljxd",
		"question":"\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u5BB6\u91CC\u8FDB\u884C\u7684",
		"id":17185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u5929",
		"indexes":"zywmhzglyqqzjtnzcswzj",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u4E3A\u8C0B\u5BB3\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\uFF0C\u8981\u6C42\u5176\u5728\u51E0\u5929\u5185\u9020\u51FA\u5341\u4E07\u652F\u7BAD\uFF1F",
		"id":17186
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5341\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"ccjjsmzccyjsdsr",
		"question":"\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u65F6\uFF0C\u6BCF\u652F\u8349\u8239\u6709\u519B\u58EB\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":17187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"cszdrzzldsyxnw",
		"question":"\u5E38\u5C71\u771F\u5B9A\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5B57\u5B50\u9F99\u7684\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":17188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u5343\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zglhsxysmgglbdsrqbhsltmf",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u706B\u70E7\u65B0\u91CE\u65F6\uFF0C\u547D\u5173\u516C\u9886\u5175\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\u53BB\u767D\u6CB3\u4E0A\u6D41\u5934\u57CB\u4F0F",
		"id":17189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"tqtzmwhrsq",
		"question":"\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0\u4E4B\u540D\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u53D6\uFF1F",
		"id":17190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"ydxxkhraqxrkzdss",
		"question":"\uFF02\u4E00\u4EE3\u67AD\u96C4\uFF0C\u5BBD\u539A\u4EC1\u7231\uFF0C\u6C42\u8D24\u82E5\u6E34\uFF02\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":17191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgyyztysjydsdxfbssgjdmmszbsmqdmmhsqlyyddmrzsrycs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u7684\u4E09\u5F1F\u5144\u5206\u522B\u662F\u53CC\u80A1\u5251\u7684\u67D0\u67D0\uFF0C\u4F7F\u4E08\u516B\u86C7\u77DB\u67AA\u7684\u67D0\u67D0\u548C\u4F7F\u9752\u9F99\u5043\u6708\u5200\u7684\u67D0\u4EBA\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E09\u4EBA\u4F9D\u6B21\u662F",
		"id":17192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u52AD",
		"indexes":"rnygsyplrwdmsplccwzsznclszjxcmss",
		"question":"\u6C5D\u5357\u6709\u4E2A\u5584\u4E8E\u8BC4\u8BBA\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u540D\u58EB\uFF0C\u8BC4\u8BBA\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\uFF1A\u201C\u6CBB\u4E16\u4E4B\u80FD\u81E3\uFF0C\u4E71\u4E16\u4E4B\u5978\u96C4\u201D\uFF0C\u6B64\u540D\u58EB\u662F",
		"id":17193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"zzhzhdxzqzgzyrwxqxjsrzyjzjgjczds",
		"question":"\uFF02\u667A\u8005\u548C\u667A\u6167\u7684\u8C61\u5F81\uFF0C\u6E05\u5FE0\u803F\u76F4\uFF0C\u7528\u4EBA\u552F\u8D24\uFF0C\u8C26\u865A\u3001\u8C28\u614E\u3001\u8BA4\u771F\u53C8\u5C3D\u804C\u3001\u97A0\u8EAC\u5C3D\u7601\uFF02\uFF0C\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u548C\u620F\u66F2\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"sgyydzzlgzsymmcd",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u662F\u5143\u672B\u660E\u521D\u7684",
		"id":17195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u672B\u660E\u521D",
		"indexes":"zzlgzssmcddr",
		"question":"\u4F5C\u8005\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u4EBA",
		"id":17196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74",
		"indexes":"sgyyjdssmsqdsq",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E8B\u60C5",
		"id":17197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u548C\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"sgyyznlwrwqmzjlyx",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E24\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u9752\u6885\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\uFF1F",
		"id":17198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD\u3001\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u3001\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzyrwzbcsjjjzjyjycs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u4E3B\u8981\u4EBA\u7269\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0\u201C\u4E09\u7EDD\u201D\uFF1A\u201C\u5978\u7EDD\u201D\u3001\u201C\u667A\u7EDD\u201D\u3001\u201C\u4E49\u7EDD\u201D\u4F9D\u6B21\u662F",
		"id":17199
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"sqqlrjz",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5A36\u4EB2\u8DEF\u4EBA\u7686\u77E5",
		"id":17200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u4E54",
		"indexes":"zydqzs",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u7684\u59BB\u5B50\u662F",
		"id":17201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"lbwlmstxlwydhsls",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u4E3A\u4E86\u7F8E\u8272\uFF0C\u542C\u4FE1\u4E86\u738B\u5141\u7684\u8BDD\u6740\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":17202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"dzrjhsmlmjsyfsdlxddqdlssbz",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u5165\u4EAC\u540E\u6536\u4E70\u4E86\u731B\u5C06\u8C01,\u53C8\u5E9F\u5C11\u5E1D,\u7ACB\u732E\u5E1D,\u5927\u6743\u72EC\u63FD,\u5B9E\u65BD\u66B4\u653F\u3002",
		"id":17203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C42\u8D24\u4EE4\u300B",
		"indexes":"ccwlxbgddrcdplyjfjdxhmdgdrygldbztclwcsjdyrfzygy210nctxlydsm",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\u4E86\u9009\u62D4\u66F4\u591A\u7684\u4EBA\u624D,\u6253\u7834\u4E86\u4F9D\u636E\u5C01\u5EFA\u5FB7\u884C\u548C\u95E8\u5F1F\u9AD8\u4F4E\u4EFB\u7528\u5B98\u540F\u7684\u6807\u51C6,\u63D0\u51FA\u4E86'\u552F\u624D\u662F\u4E3E'\u7684\u7528\u4EBA\u65B9\u9488,\u4E8E\u516C\u5143210\u5E74\u6625\u5929\u4E0B\u4E86\u4E00\u9053\u4EC0\u4E48.",
		"id":17204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u7433",
		"indexes":"cjtysqcxwmlccdzzsdyssbhgjccds",
		"question":"\u66FE\u7ECF\u66FF\u8881\u7ECD\u8D77\u8349\u6A84\u6587,\u9A82\u4E86\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u7956\u5B97\u4E09\u4EE3.\u8881\u7ECD\u5931\u8D25\u540E\u5F52\u964D\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u4E0B\u5F52\u664B",
		"indexes":"sgyyxlsggjdxssctysjyzsggjgjllwdsqbshjzldzzlqxgjgdzzcbzzsftxhsm",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5199\u4E86\u4E09\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u5174\u8870\u53F2,\u4ECE\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u81F3\u4E09\u56FD\u5F52\u664B\u5171\u7ECF\u5386\u4E86\u4E94\u5927\u65F6\u671F,\u4FBF\u662F\u9EC4\u5DFE\u4E4B\u4E71,\u8463\u5353\u4E4B\u4E71,\u7FA4\u96C4\u5272\u636E(\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218,\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218),\u4E09\u5206\u5929\u4E0B\u548C\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"zglrwmrsqlesqzsbzjqtexqdsbyrwqnhyfgcrs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u8BA4\u4E3A\u67D0\u4EBA\uFF1A\u98DF\u5176\u7984\u800C\u6740\u5176\u4E3B\uFF0C\u662F\u4E0D\u5FE0\uFF1B\u5C45\u5176\u571F\u800C\u732E\u5176\u5730\uFF0C\u662F\u4E0D\u4E49\uFF0C\u8BA4\u4E3A\u5176\u8111\u540E\u6709\u53CD\u9AA8\uFF0C\u6B64\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":17207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06",
		"indexes":"zglqlxclgxssjygzcfw",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u53D6\u4E86\u897F\u5DDD\uFF0C\u8BBA\u529F\u884C\u8D4F\u65F6\uFF0C\u5C06\u6709\u529F\u4E4B\u81E3\u5C01\u4E3A",
		"id":17208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"yxsbszglfdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5C01\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":17209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"zglzwzyjdhsstfszcqjgz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F\u4EA4\u4EE3\u540E\u4E8B\u65F6\uFF0C\u6258\u4ED8\u8C01\u4E3B\u6301\u5168\u5C40\u5DE5\u4F5C",
		"id":17210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"zglzwzyjdhssbbqjjls",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F\u4EA4\u4EE3\u540E\u4E8B\u65F6\uFF0C\u628A\u5175\u6743\u4EA4\u7ED9\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":17211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5CB1",
		"indexes":"wyfhslsjhcdzdyyyqsyyzhhsyyhshlzlwy",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5EF6\u653E\u706B\u70E7\u4E86\u8700\u519B\u56DE\u64A4\u7684\u6808\u9053\uFF0C\u626C\u8A00\u8981\u64D2\u6740\u6768\u4EEA\uFF0C\u6700\u540E\u8FD8\u662F\u6768\u4EEA\u548C\u8C01\u5408\u529B\u65A9\u4E86\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"id":17212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD\u3001\u8D75\u4E91\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u9A6C\u8D85\u3001\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"yxnxrswhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u4EBA\u662F\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06",
		"id":17213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C60\u6237",
		"indexes":"sgmjzfzydssmcs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u731B\u5C06\u5F20\u98DE\uFF0C\u5B57\u7FFC\u5FB7\uFF0C\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u51FA\u8EAB",
		"id":17214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"szhsxslbhshxslbssrnldzjygszxcbljrjwxfflpzbkby",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5B57\u6C49\u5347\uFF0C\u5148\u4E8B\u5218\u8868\uFF0C\u540E\u4E8B\u97E9\u7384\u3002\u867D\u4E24\u9B13\u971C\u8272\uFF0C\u4ECD\u80FD\u62A1\u5200\u65A9\u5C06\uFF0C\u5F15\u5F13\u5C04\u8D3C\uFF0C\u76F8\u4F20\u81C2\u529B\u60CA\u4EBA\uFF0C\u7BAD\u65E0\u865A\u53D1\uFF0C\u975E\u5EC9\u9887\u4E4B\u8F88\u53EF\u6BD4\u4E5F\u3002",
		"id":17215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8083",
		"indexes":"ccjjszypsqdtzgldxs",
		"question":"\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u65F6\uFF0C\u5468\u745C\u6D3E\u8C01\u53BB\u6253\u63A2\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u865A\u5B9E",
		"id":17216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zglgglmyhbxyyxesldglzdgljghscq",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u201C\u8EAC\u8015\u9647\u4EA9\u201D\u4E8E\u6E56\u5317\u8944\u9633\u4EE5\u897F\u4E8C\u5341\u91CC\u7684\u53E4\u9686\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5EA6\u8FC7\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u5BD2\u6691\u6625\u79CB\u3002",
		"id":17217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"ssxlbdtjlzgl",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u5218\u5907\u7684\u63A8\u8350\u4E86\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"id":17218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5341\u4E03\u5C81",
		"indexes":"lbmzlddyhhdxswlzxnfesqsdzglqjtytxddjslbdd",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5192\u7740\u9686\u51AC\u7684\u4E25\u5BD2\u548C\u5927\u96EA\uFF0C\u4E09\u5F80\u9686\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5411\u5E74\u65B9\u4E8C\u5341\u4E03\u5C81\u7684\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u8BF7\u6559\u7EDF\u4E00\u5929\u4E0B\u7684\u5927\u8BA1\u65F6\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u591A\u5927",
		"id":17219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"kcjszglysbcdxz",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0E\u8C01\u6446\u51FA\u7684\u865A\u62DB",
		"id":17220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u897F\u57CE",
		"indexes":"kcjszglzsmdfssdyzhbzj",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\u5B9E\u65BD\u7684\u4E00\u62DB\u7F13\u5175\u4E4B\u8BA1",
		"id":17221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"lbdctmzhclsdzq",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u7684\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\u6700\u540E\u6210\u4E86\u8C01\u7684\u5EA7\u9A91",
		"id":17222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"dmszsdzbsmzx",
		"question":"\u9093\u8302\u6B7B\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u4E08\u516B\u86C7\u77DB\u4E4B\u4E0B",
		"id":17223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8700\u56FD",
		"indexes":"djszyhzsngdzj",
		"question":"\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u6218\u5F79\u9EC4\u5FE0\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7684\u4E3B\u5C06",
		"id":17224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u5BFF",
		"indexes":"ymmclgzzhmjcshxqhbyjjhsdsgzhpszzdslwclsgyy",
		"question":"\u5143\u672B\u660E\u521D\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u7EFC\u5408\u6C11\u95F4\u4F20\u8BF4\u548C\u620F\u66F2\u3001\u8BDD\u672C\uFF0C\u4EE5\u53CA\u7ED3\u5408\u8C01\u7684\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u5FD7\u300B\u548C\u88F4\u677E\u4E4B\u6CE8\u7684\u53F2\u6599\u5B8C\u6210\u4E86\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49",
		"id":17225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732E\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"cchsxcslsytcydgsslyzlzrs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8C01\u8BB8\u660C\u72E9\u730E\u65F6\uFF0C\u7528\u4ED6\u66FE\u7528\u7684\u5F13\u5C04\u6740\u4E86\u4E00\u53EA\u9E7F\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":17226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u968B\u5510\u5FD7\u4F20\u300B",
		"indexes":"lgzczysgyywhzy",
		"question":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u9664\u8457\u6709\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5916\u8FD8\u8457\u6709",
		"id":17227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u864E\u5C06",
		"indexes":"yxngbslbdcw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5218\u5907\u7684\u79F0\u8C13",
		"id":17228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u6C99\u6538\u53BF",
		"indexes":"hzyzjzjflbhxrzzljylbczlpgshd",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u5728\u8346\u5DDE\u519B\u9600\u5218\u8868\u9EBE\u4E0B\u4EFB\u804C\u4E2D\u90CE\u5C06\uFF0C\u4E0E\u5218\u8868\u4ECE\u5B50\u5218\u78D0\u5171\u5B88\u4F55\u5730",
		"id":17229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u9675",
		"indexes":"cbzzhlbzjnsjzstshxgytszfjlltsyjhctsjxyktj",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u540E\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u5F81\u8346\u5357\u56DB\u90E1\u3002\u957F\u6C99\u592A\u5B88\u97E9\u7384\u3001\u6842\u9633\u592A\u5B88\u8D75\u8303\u53CA\u96F6\u9675\u592A\u5B88\uFF0C\u4EE5\u53CA\u4F55\u5904\u592A\u5B88\u91D1\u65CB\u4E00\u5757\u6295\u964D",
		"id":17230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"lbzsm",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u78D0",
		"indexes":"hzywlbsxshsytzszs",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u4E3A\u5218\u8868\u624B\u4E0B\u65F6\u548C\u8C01\u4E00\u540C\u9547\u5B88\u957F\u6C99",
		"id":17232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"gy201nccygddzzdbsjengrn",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143201\u5E74\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u4E8E\u5B98\u6E21\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u5927\u8D25\u8C01\uFF0C\u8FDB\u800C\u5357\u653B\u6C5D\u5357",
		"id":17233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u80DC",
		"indexes":"hjbshdkghdxcshjdzzzsjwsdhd",
		"question":"\u4F55\u8FDB\u5907\uFF0C\u8700\u6C49\u7684\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u76F8\u4F20\u662F\u6C49\u666F\u5E1D\u4E4B\u5B50\u4E2D\u5C71\u9756\u738B\u8C01\u7684\u540E\u4EE3\u3002",
		"id":17234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u7384",
		"indexes":"whjzydhzyssdsx",
		"question":"\u4E94\u864E\u5C06\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u624B\u4E0B",
		"id":17235
	},
	{
		"answer":"207\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lbsgmlqdzgljrdclzddzlfzdgszgydsn",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u8BF7\u5F97\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u52A0\u5165\uFF0C\u5F97\u51FA\u9686\u4E2D\u5BF9\u7684\u6218\u7565\u65B9\u9488\uFF0C\u5927\u6982\u662F\u5728\u516C\u5143\u591A\u5C11\u5E74",
		"id":17236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9879\u7FBD\u5C04\u7BAD\uFF0D\u767E\u53D1\u767E\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xmnjxhybzq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u53E5\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E",
		"id":17237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B59\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"jdsrjsccrysyshptzsywzl",
		"question":"\u501F\u5200\u6740\u4EBA\u8BA1\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u8BA9\u8881\u6C0F\u4E0E\u8C01\u706B\u62FC\uFF0C\u4ED6\u5750\u6536\u6E14\u7FC1\u4E4B\u5229",
		"id":17238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58F0\u4E1C\u51FB\u897F\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"ccxbtfzxjgnycbxysccmsbzhjxgczbzjqjzcxbjrczyqjxkdqcysjjjjwzxxsyjzjs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u5174\u5175\u8BA8\u4F10\u5F20\u7EE3\uFF0C\u4E45\u653B\u5357\u9633\u57CE\u4E0D\u4E0B\u3002\u4E8E\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u547D\u58EB\u5175\u505A\u597D\u7EE7\u7EED\u653B\u57CE\u51C6\u5907\uFF0C\u81EA\u5DF1\u5374\u5047\u88C5\u4ECE\u897F\u5317\u89D2\u5165\u57CE\u3002\u8FD9\u4E00\u5207\u8D3E\u8BE9\u770B\u5F97\u6E05\u695A\uFF0C\u4E8E\u662F\u5C06\u8BA1\u5C31\u8BA1\u4E3A\u5F20\u7EE3\u732E\u4E0A\u4E00\u8BA1\uFF0C\u8FD9\u8BA1\u662F",
		"id":17239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u9042",
		"indexes":"ljjsccylljmcysd",
		"question":"\u79BB\u95F4\u8BA1\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u7528\u6765\u79BB\u95F4\u9A6C\u8D85\u4E0E\u8C01\u7684",
		"id":17240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u8FDB",
		"indexes":"dhmnwqyhgzdyqgtnlxlddzsdsmqjjjjdmlyybj",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74\uFF0C\u5916\u621A\u4E0E\u5BA6\u5B98\u4E89\u6597\uFF0C\u5F15\u8D77\u5BAB\u5EF7\u5185\u4E71\u3002\u897F\u51C9\u7684\u8463\u5353\u6536\u5230\u8C01\u547D\u5176\u8FDB\u4EAC\u6551\u9A7E\u7684\u5BC6\u4EE4\uFF0C\u72B9\u8C6B\u4E0D\u51B3",
		"id":17242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5112",
		"indexes":"dhmngtnlsdzdmsslqdzyfzjjwmcjjjdqzq",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74\u5BAB\u5EF7\u5185\u4E71\u65F6\uFF0C\u8463\u5353\u7684\u8C0B\u58EB\u8C01\uFF0C\u529B\u529D\u8463\u5353\u4EE5\u201C\u5949\u8BCF\u6551\u9A7E\u201D\u4E3A\u540D\uFF0C\u8D81\u673A\u8FDB\u4EAC\u593A\u53D6\u653F\u6743\u3002",
		"id":17243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C03\u864E\u79BB\u5C71",
		"indexes":"ccdbzxhmtzxxzlbrgzmylbjsjsqsyhssczzszytjccdcdcgyyhjddbbxrdmd",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6253\u8D25\u5F20\u7EE3\u540E\uFF0C\u77DB\u5934\u6307\u5411\u5F90\u5DDE\u5415\u5E03\uFF0C\u5982\u679C\u6B63\u9762\u4E0E\u5415\u5E03\u4EA4\u624B\u5373\u4F7F\u53D6\u80DC\u4E5F\u4F1A\u635F\u5931\u60E8\u91CD\u3002\u8FD9\u65F6\u65E9\u5DF2\u6295\u964D\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u9648\u767B\u6210\u529F\u8FD0\u7528\u4F55\u8BA1\uFF0C\u8FBE\u5230\u5175\u4E0D\u8840\u5203\u7684\u76EE\u7684\u3002",
		"id":17244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u4EBA\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"stwykddzlbjshsztysqssmjrdcljdzlbcerqfzlrhb",
		"question":"\u53F8\u5F92\u738B\u5141\u770B\u5230\u8463\u5353\u3001\u5415\u5E03\u7686\u662F\u597D\u8272\u4E4B\u5F92\uFF0C\u4E8E\u662F\u5DE7\u4F7F\u4EC0\u4E48\u8BA1\uFF0C\u8BA9\u8C82\u8749\u79BB\u95F4\u8463\u5353\u5415\u5E03\uFF0C\u4ECE\u800C\u8BA9\u5176\u7236\u5B50\u4E24\u4EBA\u706B\u5E76",
		"id":17245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u5E72",
		"indexes":"sddwyszybzyjjjjsccsscmzysjldd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5230\u4E1C\u5434\u6E38\u8BF4\u5468\u745C\uFF0C\u88AB\u5468\u745C\u5C06\u8BA1\u5C31\u8BA1\uFF0C\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u6740\u6B7B\u8521\u7441\u5F20\u5141\u6C34\u519B\u4E24\u90FD\u7763\uFF0C",
		"id":17246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"zyyshylyckrjlrcczjwhldhscclxhmgl",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u4E0E\u8C01\u5408\u6F14\u4E86\u4E00\u573A\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1\u6765\uFF0C\u8BA9\u66F9\u64CD\u4E2D\u8BA1\uFF0C\u4E3A\u540E\u6765\u7684\u706B\u70E7\u66F9\u8239\u7ACB\u4E0B\u6C57\u9A6C\u529F\u52B3\u3002",
		"id":17247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"dsjgzdwysptbjltjptqjs",
		"question":"\u5F53\u65F6\u848B\u5E72\u5728\u4E1C\u5434\u9047\u4E0A\u5E9E\u7EDF\uFF0C\u5E76\u6781\u529B\u63A8\u8350\u5E9E\u7EDF\u53BB\u89C1\u8C01",
		"id":17248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"ptyxrdwylbqsxjccrcjjmzcyhlszycbrlpdcjs",
		"question":"\u5E9E\u7EDF\u6709\u5FC3\u8BA9\u4E1C\u5434\u4E0E\u5218\u5907\u53D6\u80DC\uFF0C\u732E\u8BA1\u66F9\u64CD\uFF0C\u8BA9\u66F9\u519B\u5C06\u6BCF\u53EA\u8239\u7528\u73AF\u8FDE\u4E0A\uFF0C\u8FD9\u6837\u66F9\u5175\u5982\u5C65\u5E73\u5730\uFF0C\u6B64\u8BA1\u662F",
		"id":17249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"yxngzysylccjjlhjkrjjdfljjddgjc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u6218\u5F79\u4F7F\u7528\u4E86\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u3001\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1\u3001\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1\u3001\u501F\u4E1C\u98CE\u3001\u79BB\u95F4\u8BA1\u7B49\u591A\u4E2A\u8BA1\u7B56",
		"id":17250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u6B63",
		"indexes":"yydljssjgddjssstcdjm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u9038\u5F85\u52B3\u8BA1\u662F\u8700\u519B\u653B\u6253\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u65F6\uFF0C\u8C01\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\u8BA1\u8C0B",
		"id":17251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6843\u56ED\u7ED3\u4E49",
		"indexes":"sgyydyhjdjssmgs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u7B2C\u4E00\u56DE\u8BB2\u7684\u5C31\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":17252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20",
		"indexes":"zfdbbxsm",
		"question":"\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u7238\u7238\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"mzctrzqzhssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u9A6C\u4E2D\u8D64\u5154\uFF0C\u4EBA\u4E2D\uFF1F\u201D\u5176\u4E2D?\u53F7\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C21",
		"indexes":"hlzmSUSUzzmx",
		"question":"\u6325\u6CEA\u65A9\u9A6CSU\uFF0CSU\u5B57\u600E\u4E48\u5199",
		"id":17255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4F10\u65F6\u75C5\u6B7B\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F",
		"indexes":"kmszmsd",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u662F\u600E\u4E48\u6B7B\u7684",
		"id":17256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E0\u4E3A\u4ED6\u8BA4\u4E3A\u66F9\u64CD\u793A\u610F\u201C\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u53E3\u9165\u201D",
		"indexes":"yxwhbccdyhsyzjsfcl",
		"question":"\u6768\u4FEE\u4E3A\u4F55\u628A\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u4E0E\u4F17\u5C06\u58EB\u5206\u5403\u4E86",
		"id":17257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u4E91",
		"indexes":"yxzdbsgyds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u4E91\u957F",
		"indexes":"shmcwdyzdcqswnfwrygzwtrxrjcqybyzrqgbzgsfxdss",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u201C\u6C49\u672B\u624D\u65E0\u654C\uFF0C\u4E91\u957F\u72EC\u51FA\u7FA4\uFF0C\u795E\u5A01\u80FD\u594B\u6B66\uFF0C\u5112\u96C5\u66F4\u77E5\u6587\uFF0C\u5929\u65E5\u5FC3\u5982\u955C\uFF0C\u300A\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u4E49\u8584\u4E91\uFF0C\u662D\u7136\u5343\u53E4\uFF0C\u4E0D\u6B62\u51A0\u4E09\u5206\u201D\u5199\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":17259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"yxzdbszglds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u572D",
		"indexes":"zgldfqj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u53EB",
		"id":17261
	},
	{
		"answer":"27\u5C81",
		"indexes":"lbsgmlszgldss",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u65F6\uFF0C\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u591A\u5C11\u5C81",
		"id":17262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6210\u90FD",
		"indexes":"lbznjllshzq",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5728\u54EA\u5EFA\u7ACB\u4E86\u8700\u6C49\u653F\u6743",
		"id":17263
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u519B",
		"indexes":"184nhjmbbfsdsrzspsszzlbzzqybgszjtfsmj",
		"question":"184\u5E74\uFF0C\u9EC4\u5DFE\u6C11\u53D8\u7206\u53D1\uFF0C\u53D7\u5230\u5546\u4EBA\u5F20\u4E16\u5E73\u3001\u82CF\u53CC\u8D44\u52A9\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8D77\u4E49\u5175\uFF0C\u8DDF\u968F\u90B9\u9756\u8BA8\u4F10\u4EC0\u4E48\u519B",
		"id":17264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"cjhgyzfxdlrddbfsxddywjw",
		"question":"\u66FE\u7ECF\u548C\u5173\u7FBD\uFF0C\u5F20\u98DE\u5144\u5F1F\u4E24\u4EBA\u6253\u7684\u4E0D\u5206\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B66\u5C06\u4E3A?",
		"id":17265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"hjzczywhrss",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u8D3C\u7A0B\u5FD7\u8FDC\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u6740?",
		"id":17266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"cbzzzsxczjcc",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8C01\u732E\u7B56\u8BC8\u964D\u66F9\u64CD?",
		"id":17267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0",
		"indexes":"ccyrjxyjxwlsdzddjlyzjtqmw",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u56E0\u4EBA\u8FDB\u732E\u4E00\u5409\u7965\u7269\uFF0C\u52B3\u5E08\u52A8\u4F17\u7684\u642D\u5EFA\u4E86\u4E00\u5EA7\u5DE8\u53F0\uFF0C\u5176\u540D\u4E3A?",
		"id":17268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4E15",
		"indexes":"lsfqzlssyzsdqz",
		"question":"\u300C\u6D1B\u795E\u8D4B\u300D\u5176\u4E2D\u6D1B\u795E\u662F\u610F\u6307\u8C01\u7684\u59BB\u5B50?",
		"id":17269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4E08\u539F",
		"indexes":"kmzhycbfsbsznl",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u6B21\u5317\u4F10\u65F6\u75C5\u6B7B\u5728\u54EA\u91CC?",
		"id":17270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"zzzzyjbljszsfjmxbkqebyjcdds",
		"question":"\u5728\u4F5C\u6218\u4E2D\u773C\u775B\u88AB\u6D41\u7BAD\u5C04\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8BF4\uFF1A\u300C\u7236\u7CBE\u6BCD\u8840\u4E0D\u53EF\u5F03\u300D\u800C\u628A\u773C\u775B\u5403\u6389\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u96CD",
		"indexes":"sqcdhxlhzbrmcx",
		"question":"\u5B59\u6743\u79F0\u5E1D\u540E\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4F55\u8005\u88AB\u4EFB\u547D\u4E1E\u76F8?",
		"id":17272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8E\u7981",
		"indexes":"ccwyjjzcmzznzbjlrbrlszfbwssgzmjhyjzzwhr",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u8C13\u66F0\u300C\u5C06\u519B\u5728\u5306\u5FD9\u4E4B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u80FD\u6574\u5175\u575A\u5792\uFF0C\u4EFB\u8C24\u4EFB\u52B3\uFF0C\u4F7F\u4E4B\u53CD\u8D25\u4E3A\u80DC\u867D\u53E4\u4E4B\u540D\u5C06\uFF0C\u4F55\u4EE5\u52A0\u5179\u8005!\u300D\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA?",
		"id":17273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"sgsqcwddghyxdss",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u4ECE\u672A\u5F97\u5230\u8FC7\u6C49\u7389\u73BA\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795D\u878D",
		"indexes":"kmznmscqqqzmhmhdfrj",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u5F81\u5357\u86EE\u65F6\u66FE\u4E03\u64D2\u4E03\u7EB5\u5B5F\u83B7\uFF0C\u5B5F\u83B7\u7684\u592B\u4EBA\u53EB\uFF1F",
		"id":17275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"gydyzss",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u517B\u5B50\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u575A",
		"indexes":"nywjzlbmyqtk",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u4F4D\u541B\u4E3B\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u6CA1\u6709\u53BB\u6295\u9760?",
		"id":17277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"qbcsds",
		"question":"\u4E03\u6B65\u6210\u8BD7\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54ED\u51FA\u6765\u7684",
		"indexes":"xhylbdjss",
		"question":"\u6B47\u540E\u8BED--\u5218\u5907\u7684\u6C5F\u5C71\u662F?",
		"id":17279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u4E13\u6740\u4E49\u7236",
		"indexes":"dccqdlbxswyzslbjlsmyslbbs",
		"question":"\u5F53\u66F9\u64CD\u64D2\u5F97\u5415\u5E03\u60F3\u6536\u4E3A\u4E49\u5B50\u65F6\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u5EFA\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48\u8A00\u4F7F\u5415\u5E03\u88AB\u6740?",
		"id":17280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u8D21",
		"indexes":"ssxccbgscxqxdzxhbscss",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u62A5\u544A\u5B59\u7B56\u88AD\u53D6\u8BB8\u90FD\u4E4B\u5FC3\uFF0C\u540E\u88AB\u5B59\u7B56\u6240\u6740?",
		"id":17281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u900D\u9065\u6D25\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"szlcmdzygssm",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u5F20\u8FBD\u6210\u540D\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u5404\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u677F\u6865\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"szycmdzygssm",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u8D75\u4E91\u6210\u540D\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u5404\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BA1\u4EF2",
		"indexes":"zglyjscbzjbz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u9690\u5C45\u65F6\u5E38\u628A\u81EA\u5DF1\u6BD4\u4F5C?",
		"id":17284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"qwcjdglbjsddfqsshr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u66FE\u7ECF\u5F53\u8FC7\u5218\u5907\u519B\u5E08\u7684\u300C\u5355\u798F\u300D\u5176\u5B9E\u662F\u4F55\u4EBA?",
		"id":17285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u6027",
		"indexes":"xhdbhrsqyy",
		"question":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7\u88AB\u4F55\u4EBA\u5C04\u53BB\u4E00\u773C?",
		"id":17286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E54\u56FD\u516C",
		"indexes":"zyqdxqssdne",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u5A36\u7684\u5C0F\u4E54\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u5973\u513F?",
		"id":17287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E25\u989C",
		"indexes":"cszydtjjwjjjdsdzhhstjzfdjls",
		"question":"\u79F0\u8700\u4E2D\u6709\u65AD\u5934\u5C06\u519B\uFF0C\u65E0\u964D\u5C06\u519B\uFF0C\u4F46\u662F\u5230\u6700\u540E\u8FD8\u662F\u6295\u964D\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u5C06\u9886\u662F?",
		"id":17288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6062",
		"indexes":"sstlbsjlmc",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u66FF\u5218\u5907\u8BF4\u964D\u4E86\u9A6C\u8D85?",
		"id":17289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwkmjwdfhyhrjyebgzyprzs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5B54\u660E\u501F\u5B8C\u4E1C\u98CE\u540E\u7531\u4F55\u4EBA\u63A5\u5E94\uFF0C\u800C\u907F\u8FC7\u5468\u745C\u6D3E\u4EBA\u8FFD\u6740?",
		"id":17290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"cbzzddgcymzlzcds",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u7684\u5927\u529F\u81E3\uFF0C\u6709\u300C\u7F8E\u5468\u90CE\u300D\u4E4B\u79F0\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwzsxrdzjaddss",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u53EA\u8EAB\u9677\u5165\u654C\u9635\u6551\u963F\u6597\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E03\u64D2\u4E03\u7EB5",
		"indexes":"kmjqjzmh",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u51E0\u64D2\u51E0\u7EB5\u5B5F\u83B7?",
		"id":17293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"gylccsdzhw",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u79BB\u66F9\u64CD\u65F6\u5E26\u8D70\u4F55\u7269?",
		"id":17294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9E\u7EDF",
		"indexes":"sdlbrtxdjxdqyzds",
		"question":"\u8BF4\u52A8\u5218\u5907\uFF0C\u8BA9\u4ED6\u4E0B\u5B9A\u51B3\u5FC3\u593A\u53D6\u76CA\u5DDE\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u4E11",
		"indexes":"wsmptbbsqzy",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E9E\u7EDF\u4E0D\u88AB\u5B59\u6743\u91CD\u7528?",
		"id":17296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"dwssjsjccd",
		"question":"\u5178\u97E6\u662F\u8C01\u4ECB\u7ECD\u7ED9\u66F9\u64CD\u7684?",
		"id":17297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5CB1",
		"indexes":"wyzfjgsyhrss",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5EF6\u9020\u53CD\u7ED3\u679C\u6B7B\u4E8E\u4F55\u4EBA\u624B\u4E0A?",
		"id":17298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F92\u624B\u640F\u864E",
		"indexes":"whxcjhc",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4F55\u8BB8\u891A\u53EB\u864E\u75F4?",
		"id":17299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u742C",
		"indexes":"zglshsgnzyhrdz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6B7B\u540E\uFF0C\u8700\u56FD\u5185\u653F\u7531\u4F55\u4EBA\u4EE3\u4E4B?",
		"id":17300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4E2A\u9526\u56CA",
		"indexes":"lbdwgqxnszgljtsmdx",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5230\u5434\u56FD\u300C\u5A36\u65B0\u5A18\u300D\u65F6\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7ED9\u4ED6\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E1C\u897F?",
		"id":17301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"bmhjwwtjjds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u7962\u8861\u8BA5\u4E3A\u300C\u5B8C\u4F53\u5C06\u519B\u300D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwcyhssdjdsxmnwjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u6D51\u8EAB\u662F\u80C6\u201D\u5C06\u7684\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":17303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"sgyyzcrdbmjszbnwjssp",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\uFF0C\u66F9\u4EC1\u7684\u516B\u95E8\u91D1\u9501\u9635\u88AB\u54EA\u4F4D\u519B\u5E08\u6240\u7834?",
		"id":17304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u826F",
		"indexes":"rcmswcbmzlszds",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u79F0\u300C\u9A6C\u6C0F\u4E94\u5E38\uFF0C\u767D\u7709\u6700\u826F\u300D\u6240\u6307\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u5DE2",
		"indexes":"xyxjccjysjdjlczcyjsjqwysdlcsz",
		"question":"\u8BB8\u6538\u732E\u8BA1\u66F9\u64CD\uFF0C\u5C06\u8881\u7ECD\u519B\u56E4\u79EF\u7CAE\u8349\u4E4B\u5904\u4E00\u4E3E\u70E7\u5C3D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8881\u7ECD\u7684\u7CAE\u4ED3\u662F\u5728?",
		"id":17306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u8303",
		"indexes":"yjsgdndszfsjyzydqrdzydnds",
		"question":"\u6B32\u5C06\u5B88\u5BE1\u591A\u5E74\u7684\u5AC2\u5B50\u6A0A\u6C0F\u5AC1\u4E0E\u8D75\u4E91\uFF0C\u4F46\u5374\u60F9\u5F97\u8D75\u4E91\u5927\u6012\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u5E72",
		"indexes":"qwzylyhrsccslcmzyer",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5468\u745C\u5229\u7528\u4F55\u4EBA\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u6740\u4E86\u8521\u7441\uFF0C\u5F20\u5141\u4E8C\u4EBA?",
		"id":17308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u8499",
		"indexes":"rgydysjzddwjlw",
		"question":"\u8BA9\u5173\u7FBD\u5927\u610F\u5931\u8346\u5DDE\u7684\u4E1C\u5434\u5C06\u9886\u4E3A?",
		"id":17309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"zglshszdzzs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6B7B\u540E\u8700\u4E2D\u7684\u652F\u67F1\u662F?",
		"id":17310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5367\u9F99\u5148\u751F",
		"indexes":"zglrc",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4EBA\u79F0?",
		"id":17311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"xlwhjzngzzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E94\u864E\u5C06\u4E2D\u90A3\u4E2A\u6700\u65E9\u6B7B?",
		"id":17312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u4ED3",
		"indexes":"xzmzsxjzzwggybblpydjsgpzbhlcddzsggbjs",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5728\u5E99\u4E2D\u795E\u50CF\uFF0C\u5C45\u4E2D\u8005\u4E3A\u5173\u516C\uFF0C\u53F3\u8FB9\u767D\u8138\u6367\u5370\u7684\u5C31\u662F\u5173\u5E73\uFF1B\u5DE6\u8FB9\u9ED1\u8138\u6301\u5200\u7684\uFF0C\u5219\u662F\u5173\u516C\u90E8\u5C06\u8C01?",
		"id":17313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"dhmnccxctzylzhjzdtzsz",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74\uFF0C\u300C\u66F9\u64CD\u631F\u6301\u5929\u5B50\u4EE5\u4EE4\u8BF8\u4FAF\u300D\uFF0C\u53E5\u4E2D\u7684\u300C\u5929\u5B50\u300D\u662F\u6307?",
		"id":17314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BCD\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"cczlxsdngqryxgy",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6293\u4E86\u5F90\u5EB6\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EB2\u4EBA\u8981\u631F\u5F52\u4F9D\uFF1F",
		"id":17315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"jdcchyszbsfdgjzys",
		"question":"\u51B3\u5B9A\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8881\u7ECD\u4E89\u9738\u80DC\u8D1F\u7684\u5173\u952E\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":17316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"dgxssdszn",
		"question":"\u300A\u77ED\u6B4C\u884C\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BD7\u4F5C\u5462?",
		"id":17317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53BF\u4EE4",
		"indexes":"lbzxpjptdzws",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u6700\u5148\u6D3E\u7ED9\u5E9E\u7EDF\u7684\u804C\u4F4D\u662F?",
		"id":17318
	},
	{
		"answer":"208",
		"indexes":"cbzzsyxyjn",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u59CB\u4E8E\u897F\u5143\u51E0\u5E74?",
		"id":17319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"ggdzqctmybssysd",
		"question":"\u5173\u516C\u7684\u5750\u9A91\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\u539F\u672C\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8C01\u7684?",
		"id":17320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8D85",
		"indexes":"cyzfxcdzebfsfdxlmjs",
		"question":"\u66FE\u4E0E\u5F20\u98DE\uFF0C\u8BB8\u891A\u5927\u6218\u800C\u4E0D\u5206\u80DC\u8D1F\u7684\u897F\u51C9\u731B\u5C06\u662F?",
		"id":17321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"kmqswgdjsss",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u6C14\u6B7B\u5434\u56FD\u7684\u519B\u5E08\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u4E1C\u89E3\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bhszwwsdgyscsnlr",
		"question":"\u88AB\u540E\u4E16\u5C0A\u4E3A\u6B66\u795E\u7684\u5173\u7FBD\u662F\u51FA\u751F\u54EA\u91CC\u4EBA?",
		"id":17323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"sldzdxsss",
		"question":"\u6740\u4E86\u8463\u5353\u7684\u51F6\u624B\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u96C4",
		"indexes":"qxtfdzzssgyzljddjss",
		"question":"\u7FA4\u96C4\u8BA8\u4F10\u8463\u5353\uFF0C\u5728\u6CD7\u6C34\u5173\u8FCE\u6218\u8054\u519B\u7684\u5927\u5C06\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u89D2",
		"indexes":"qwhjzdldss",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u9EC4\u5DFE\u8D3C\u7684\u8001\u5927\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"dqjjl",
		"question":"\u5927\u4E54\u5AC1\u7ED9\u4E86?",
		"id":17327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u83B7",
		"indexes":"wpdnzdqdplbkmqqqzds",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u5E73\u5B9A\u5357\u4E2D\u5730\u533A\u7684\u53DB\u4E71\uFF0C\u88AB\u5B54\u660E\u300C\u4E03\u64D2\u4E03\u7EB5\u300D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17328
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"nwhjcylbjsgn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u8C6A\u6770\u66FE\u4E0E\u5415\u5E03\u4EA4\u624B\u8FC7\u5462?",
		"id":17329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u989C\u826F",
		"indexes":"gyzcjsxzslnywyjdj",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5728\u66F9\u519B\u65F6\u5148\u65A9\u6740\u4E86\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u8881\u519B\u5927\u5C06?",
		"id":17330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"ctmzzzrss",
		"question":"\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\u6700\u65E9\u4E3B\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u81EA\u91CF\u529B",
		"indexes":"sgxhyggqmsddhms",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\uFF0C\u300C\u5173\u516C\u524D\u9762\u800D\u5927\u5200\u300D\u540E\u9762\u662F?",
		"id":17332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u8853",
		"indexes":"ysdsdss",
		"question":"\u8881\u7ECD\u7684\u4E09\u5F1F\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u7FA4",
		"indexes":"jpgrzsstcld",
		"question":"\u300C\u4E5D\u54C1\u5B98\u4EBA\u5236\u300D\u662F\u8C01\u63D0\u51FA\u6765\u7684?",
		"id":17334
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5175\u6CD5\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u7BC7",
		"indexes":"zgllzscsjwdbfs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E34\u7EC8\u65F6\u4F20\u6388\u59DC\u7EF4\u7684\u5175\u6CD5\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"sgzbzglczzjjyds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u88AB\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u79F0\u8D5E\u300C\u771F\u5C06\u519B\u4E5F\u300D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u523D\u5B50\u624B",
		"indexes":"gyzxhnyzzy",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u6700\u559C\u6B22\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9093\u8302",
		"indexes":"sgyyzdygszzfzbsmzxds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6B7B\u5728\u5F20\u98DE\u4E08\u516B\u86C7\u77DB\u4E4B\u4E0B\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u6538",
		"indexes":"yssxnwmsdtccbxjhswclc",
		"question":"\u8881\u7ECD\u624B\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u8C0B\u58EB\u5012\u6295\u66F9\u64CD\u5E76\u732E\u8BA1\u706B\u70E7\u4E4C\u5DE2\u7CAE\u4ED3?",
		"id":17339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6728\u725B\u6D41\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"zglfmdysgjjz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u53D1\u660E\u7684\u8FD0\u8F93\u5DE5\u5177\u53EB\u4F5C?",
		"id":17340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F",
		"indexes":"sgsqjgzzds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u5EFA\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u5D69",
		"indexes":"ccdfqmzs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u540D\u5B57\u662F?",
		"id":17342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"gydccshrdymgsyt",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5BF9\u66F9\u64CD\u8BF4\u4F55\u4EBA\u7684\u52C7\u731B\u66F4\u80DC\u4E8E\u4ED6?",
		"id":17343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CAE\u6388",
		"indexes":"hrjyysxtzylzhdbjj",
		"question":"\u4F55\u4EBA\u5EFA\u8BAE\u8881\u7ECD\u300C\u631F\u5929\u5B50\u4EE5\u4EE4\u8BF8\u4FAF\u300D\u4F46\u88AB\u62D2\u7EDD?",
		"id":17344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5DDE\u5175",
		"indexes":"ccjyzzsmb",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u636E\u5156\u5DDE\u7EC4\u4EC0\u4E48\u5175?",
		"id":17345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88F4\u5143\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"bydqgydctmdzzdsgyhjgsds",
		"question":"\u672C\u6B32\u593A\u53BB\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\uFF0C\u4F46\u5728\u77E5\u9053\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u540E\u5373\u5F52\u987A\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":17346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E50\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"zglczbgzhs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5E38\u81EA\u6BD4\u7BA1\u4EF2\u548C\u8C01?",
		"id":17347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E7F",
		"indexes":"xdzxcslscccyxddgsslyzdwnzdwssm",
		"question":"\u732E\u5E1D\u5728\u8BB8\u660C\u72E9\u730E\u65F6\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u66FE\u7528\u732E\u5E1D\u7684\u5F13\u5C04\u6740\u4E86\u4E00\u53EA\u52A8\u7269\uFF0C\u90A3\u53EA\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"mtshrfmd",
		"question":"\u9992\u5934\u662F\u4F55\u4EBA\u53D1\u660E\u7684?",
		"id":17349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"cccjmscbjjys",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u66FE\u7ECF\u547D\u8C01\u51FA\u5175\u622A\u51FB\u8881\u672F?",
		"id":17350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"lbssszyxnygr",
		"question":"\u300C\u4E50\u4E0D\u601D\u8700\u300D\u662F\u6307\u4EE5\u4E0B\u90A3\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EBA?",
		"id":17351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5356\u8349\u978B",
		"indexes":"lbcjzgsmzy",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u66FE\u7ECF\u4F5C\u8FC7\u4EC0\u4E48\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"cczjlyxszdyxss",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\u65F6\u6307\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":17353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4E15",
		"indexes":"ccshyhrjc",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6B7B\u540E\u7531\u4F55\u4EBA\u7EE7\u627F?",
		"id":17354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"qwdjdgrsjhssdsj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u201C\u5BF9\u9152\u5F53\u6B4C\uFF0C\u4EBA\u751F\u51E0\u4F55\uFF1F\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":17355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706B\u70E7\u8FDE\u8425",
		"indexes":"qwxmsjzycbzzwgdsjy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u9762\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E2D\u4E0E\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u65E0\u5173\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6\u6709\uFF1F",
		"id":17356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u5E1D\u57CE",
		"indexes":"qwlbtgddds",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5218\u5907\u6258\u5B64\u7684\u5730\u70B9\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9C\u9675\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qwswlfzzzjsdzys",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u8700\u5434\u4E24\u65B9\u4F5C\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u51B3\u80DC\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u57CE",
		"indexes":"qwgybzddfj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5173\u7FBD\u8D25\u8D70\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u53EB\uFF1F",
		"id":17359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u955C\u5148\u751F",
		"indexes":"zgldlss",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u8001\u5E08\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"djszydsjzjss",
		"question":"\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u6218\u5F79\u7684\u8700\u519B\u4E3B\u5C06\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u891A",
		"indexes":"cycbszsznwjldsj",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u8D64\u818A\u4E0A\u9635\u201D\u662F\u6307\u90A3\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886\u7684\u4E8B\u8FF9\uFF1F",
		"id":17362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u708E",
		"indexes":"zhtysgdrss",
		"question":"\u6700\u540E\u7EDF\u4E00\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17363
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"gdzzzbysjwkdjls",
		"question":"\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u88AB\u8881\u7ECD\u519B\u56F4\u56F0\u7684\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzygQQhxmsyjsdcksgydm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u4E00\u4E2AQQ\u53F7\u4E0B\u9762\u6240\u6709\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u662F\u5171\u7528\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":17365
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzjjkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u51E0\u7EA7\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":17366
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzydsgfzy",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"zxscdngNPCkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u7684\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1\uFF1F",
		"id":17368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u80FD\u505A\u84DD\u836F\u4E5F\u80FD\u505A\u7EA2\u836F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzfzypddzyssm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u5E96\u4E01\u7684\u4F5C\u7528\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DE\u4F53\u529B\u7684\u84DD\u836F",
		"indexes":"nehss",
		"question":"\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u662F\u5565?",
		"id":17370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u56DE\u590D\u751F\u547D\u7684",
		"indexes":"clhhrysy",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u7EA2\u7EA2\u8089\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":17371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D500\u751F\u547D",
		"indexes":"cljzhhfssmsq",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u997A\u5B50\u540E\u4F1A\u53D1\u751F\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E8B\u60C5?",
		"id":17372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D200\u4F53\u529B",
		"indexes":"hlmrwjhfssmsq",
		"question":"\u559D\u4E86\u7F8E\u9AEF\u6E29\u9152\u4F1A\u53D1\u751F\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E8B\u60C5?",
		"id":17373
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u8FD0\u5408\u6210\u6216\u8005\u4F7F\u7528\u521D\u7EA7\u9505",
		"indexes":"y5gjdkyscc10gzjdm",
		"question":"\u75285\u4E2A\u9E21\u86CB\u53EF\u4EE5\u751F\u4EA7\u51FA10\u4E2A\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D300\u751F\u547D",
		"indexes":"clzjddhgs",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u7684\u540E\u679C\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7259\u7B7E\u6ED1\u9C7C\u548C\u95EA\u907F\u4E4B\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhhzjhb",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u4F1A\u589E\u52A0\u56DE\u907F?",
		"id":17376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjntgtldhfsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F53\u529B\u7684\u6062\u590D\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":17377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjntgsmdhfsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u63D0\u9AD8\u751F\u547D\u7684\u6062\u590D\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":17378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4E50\u9E21\u7FC5\u548C\u4E00\u98DE\u51B2\u5929",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjnzjyddsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u589E\u52A0\u79FB\u52A8\u7684\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":17379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u521B\u836F\u548C\u53CC\u9EC4\u86CB\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"yxffnzkykshfsm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u54EA\u79CD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u56DE\u590D\u751F\u547D\uFF1F",
		"id":17380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u5FC3\u9732\u548C\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"yxffnzkykshftl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u54EA\u79CD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u56DE\u590D\u4F53\u529B\uFF1F",
		"id":17381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ED920\u7EA7\u4EE5\u524D\u7684\u88C5\u5907\u6253\u5B54\u7684",
		"indexes":"ejqqzs",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u7EA7\u5D4C\u5668\u4E4B\u77F3",
		"id":17382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u6700\u5927\u751F\u547D\u7684",
		"indexes":"zjxqzyysy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u7EA7\u8840\u6C14\u4E4B\u7389\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":17383
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F31\u6548\u5316\u4F24\u4E3A\u4F53\u7389",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkyjsddshzhwtl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u5C06\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\u8F6C\u5316\u4E3A\u4F53\u529B\uFF1F",
		"id":17384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8346\u68D8\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkyjsddshfdjgjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u5C06\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\u53CD\u5F39\u7ED9\u653B\u51FB\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":17385
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F85\u52A9\u6279\u91CF\u751F\u4EA7\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u7684",
		"indexes":"cjjhysy",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9152\u58F6\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":17386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkytghbl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u4F9B\u56DE\u907F\u7387\uFF1F",
		"id":17387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9576\u5DE5",
		"indexes":"cjjhsngfzyscd",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9152\u58F6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7684?",
		"id":17388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B21\u7EA7\u8840\u6C14\u4E4B\u7389",
		"indexes":"yxsmwpkyyjtgndsmzdz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u6C38\u4E45\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F60\u7684\u751F\u547D\u6700\u5927\u503C\uFF1F",
		"id":17389
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u529B\u6C34\u6676",
		"indexes":"yxsmwpkyyjtgndtlzdz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u6C38\u4E45\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F60\u7684\u4F53\u529B\u6700\u5927\u503C\uFF1F",
		"id":17390
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FEE\u590D\u6C34\u6676\u548C\u4FEE\u590D\u77F3\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"rhxlshddj",
		"question":"\u5982\u4F55\u4FEE\u7406\u635F\u574F\u7684\u9053\u5177\uFF1F",
		"id":17391
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C060~3\u7EA7\u522B\u88C5\u5907\u5F3A\u5316",
		"indexes":"xpqhsysy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u54C1\u5F3A\u5316\u77F3\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":17392
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F85\u52A9\u6279\u91CF\u751F\u4EA7\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u7684",
		"indexes":"cjgysy",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9505\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":17393
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u884C\u77F3",
		"indexes":"myyzQQsgzrgxzxqsyxngstydsdhkyx",
		"question":"\u6CA1\u6709\u7528\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u5982\u679C\u978B\u5B50\u9576\u5D4C\u4E0A\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u77F3\u5934,\u79FB\u52A8\u901F\u5EA6\u4F1A\u5FEB\u4E00\u4E9B?",
		"id":17394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkytgydsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u9AD8\u79FB\u52A8\u901F\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":17395
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"cjxlbssngfzyscd",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u4FEE\u7406\u5B9D\u77F3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7684?",
		"id":17396
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zbqhysmxg",
		"question":"\u88C5\u5907\u5F3A\u5316\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u6548\u679C\uFF1F",
		"id":17397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"cjgsngfzyscd",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9505\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7684?",
		"id":17398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"hjfbtgngNPCkyj",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u901A\u8FC7\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u8FDB?",
		"id":17399
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u66FC",
		"indexes":"hjfbdygdBOSSjsmz",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u7B2C\u4E00\u5173\u7684BOSS\u53EB\u5565\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":17400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"nqhjfbswls",
		"question":"\u4F60\u53BB\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u5565?",
		"id":17401
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"hjfbdsjyskyj",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u4EE5\u4E0A\u53EF\u4EE5\u8FDB\uFF1F",
		"id":17402
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"dsjbyskystd",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u4EE5\u4E0A\u53EF\u4EE5\u6536\u5F92\u5F1F?",
		"id":17403
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"dsjbyxcnbs",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u624D\u80FD\u62DC\u5E08?",
		"id":17404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"styqzdljyshc",
		"question":"\u5E08\u5F92\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7,\u6709\u5565\u597D\u5904?",
		"id":17405
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"tddsjbcs",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u51FA\u5E08?",
		"id":17406
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"tdcshhsfyqzdljyhcm",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u51FA\u5E08\u540E\uFF0C\u548C\u5E08\u5085\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7\u6709\u597D\u5904\u5417?",
		"id":17407
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"tdmcshsfyqzdljyxnxsdd",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u6CA1\u51FA\u5E08\uFF0C\u548C\u5E08\u5085\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7\uFF0C\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u5BF9\u7684?",
		"id":17408
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6740\u795E\u548C\u5982\u610F\u90FD\u80FD\u6362\u5230",
		"indexes":"xszdzysmy",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":17409
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E08\u7F18\u9690\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xszdzszxscnldhwp",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u4E66\u5728\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u54EA\u91CC\u5151\u6362\u7269\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":17410
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"ygdwlzdkyydsr",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u961F\u4F0D\u91CC\u6700\u591A\u53EF\u4EE5\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA?",
		"id":17411
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zdhdzkygbm",
		"question":"\u7EC4\u961F\u540E\u961F\u957F\u53EF\u4EE5\u6539\u53D8\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F8\u540C\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u83B7\u5F97\u66F4\u591A\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u503C",
		"indexes":"rgdjdbtljbcbddrzdyqljysmhc",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u5927\u5BB6\u90FD\u4E0D\u5077\u61D2\uFF0C\u7EA7\u522B\u5DEE\u4E0D\u591A\u7684\u4EBA\u7EC4\u961F\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC3\u7EA7\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u597D\u5904\uFF1F",
		"id":17413
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"zddrsfztyzdtcnfxjy",
		"question":"\u7EC4\u961F\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u5426\u5728\u540C\u4E00\u5F20\u5730\u56FE\u624D\u80FD\u5206\u4EAB\u7ECF\u9A8C\uFF1F",
		"id":17414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"kytsjdgrwm",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u540C\u65F6\u63A5\u591A\u4E2A\u4EFB\u52A1\u5417?",
		"id":17415
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"gjrwkydczfzm",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u53EF\u4EE5\u591A\u6B21\u91CD\u590D\u505A\u5417?",
		"id":17416
	},
	{
		"answer":"BOSS\u6765\u7684\uFF0C\u5237\u65B0\u65F6\u95F4\u6709\u70B9\u957F",
		"indexes":"sgxscpbdgwxmzwsmjczbd",
		"question":"\u8700\u56FD\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u602A\u7269\u5C0F\u86EE\u732A\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u7ECF\u5E38\u627E\u4E0D\u5230?",
		"id":17417
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u94B1\u548C\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u6750\u6599",
		"indexes":"zgjrwknhddsmjl",
		"question":"\u505A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u53EF\u80FD\u4F1A\u5F97\u5230\u4EC0\u4E48\u5956\u52B1?",
		"id":17418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u4E66\u4E1E",
		"indexes":"dnljgjrw",
		"question":"\u5230\u54EA\u91CC\u63A5\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\uFF1F",
		"id":17419
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"gjrwybydsb",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u4E00\u822C\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6B65\uFF1F",
		"id":17420
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u5206\u949F",
		"indexes":"xscpbdxBOSSdzsjsxyc",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u5C0FBOSS\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\u5237\u65B0\u4E00\u6B21\uFF1F",
		"id":17421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zdgjdgwhbdgjdgwysbt",
		"question":"\u4E3B\u52A8\u653B\u51FB\u7684\u602A\u7269\u548C\u88AB\u52A8\u653B\u51FB\u7684\u602A\u7269\u6709\u5565\u4E0D\u540C\uFF1F",
		"id":17422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u4EBA\u7684",
		"indexes":"bmxdjmjxjsrddbchbnmjqtNPCdhddm",
		"question":"\u628A\u67D0\u4E9B\u9053\u5177\u5356\u7ED9\u884C\u811A\u5546\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5F97\u5230\u62A5\u916C\u4F1A\u6BD4\u4F60\u5356\u7ED9\u5176\u5B83NPC\u591A\u5F88\u591A\uFF0C\u5BF9\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u6BD4\u5B83\u9AD8",
		"indexes":"rggwdmzslsdsmnhtddj",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u602A\u7269\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\u7EFF\u8272\u7684\uFF0C\u8BF4\u660E\u4F60\u548C\u4ED6\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7",
		"id":17424
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934\u4E0A\u6709\u9EC4\u8272\u7684\u611F\u53F9\u53F7\u5728\u95EA\u70C1\u7684",
		"indexes":"znxNPCkyjxrw",
		"question":"\u627E\u54EA\u4E9BNPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u65B0\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":17425
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u6709\u4EFB\u52A1\u6CA1\u505A\u5B8C\uFF0C\u9700\u8981\u548C\u4ED6\u5BF9\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"NPCdtsdzygwhssysy",
		"question":"NPC\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A\u95EE\u53F7\u662F\u5565\u610F\u601D\u5440?",
		"id":17426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u518D\u5347\u7EA7\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u65B0\u4EFB\u52A1\u4E86",
		"indexes":"NPCdtsdzyghsdgthssysy",
		"question":"NPC\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A\u7070\u8272\u7684\u611F\u53F9\u53F7\u662F\u5565\u610F\u601D\u5440?",
		"id":17427
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"dsjbkycjjt",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u53EF\u4EE5\u521B\u5EFA\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":17428
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"dsjbkyjrjt",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u53EF\u4EE5\u52A0\u5165\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":17429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519B\u56E2\u7BA1\u7406\u4E13\u5458",
		"indexes":"zngNPCkycjjt",
		"question":"\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u521B\u5EFA\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":17430
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"rgnjrlygjtjyy",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u52A0\u5165\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u519B\u56E2\uFF0C\u5C06\u62E5\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":17432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u5E38\u5728\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u8BF4\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzyggsxfdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u704C\u6C34\u5148\u950B'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":17433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u7ECF\u5E38\u751F\u4EA7\u8865\u84DD\/\u7EA2\u7684\u836F",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzhssdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u4E2D\u534E\u98DF\u795E'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":17434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320\u505A\u591A\u4E86",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzzdsdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u94F8\u9020\u5927\u5E08'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":17435
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9576\u5D4C\u505A\u591A\u4E86",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzqdsdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u5236\u5668\u5927\u5E08'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":17436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zyhNPCdh",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u548CNPC\u5BF9\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":17437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u6750\u6599\u548C\u9AD8\u7EA7\u5408\u6210\u4E66",
		"indexes":"xtbdshhdsmwp",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u5077\u88AB\u6253\u6B7B\u540E,\u4F1A\u6389\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1?",
		"id":17438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u9675\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u5C0F\u5077",
		"indexes":"zykndzjgjsdgws",
		"question":"\u6700\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u6389\u4E2D\u7EA7\u5DE5\u5320\u4E66\u7684\u602A\u7269\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u9675\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u5C0F\u5077",
		"indexes":"zykndzjxgsdgws",
		"question":"\u6700\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u6389\u4E2D\u7EA7\u9576\u5DE5\u4E66\u7684\u602A\u7269\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17440
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"wsmyxfzydszgssrnlmbd",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u4E9B\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u4E66\u5728\u53E4\u4E66\u5546\u4EBA\u90A3\u91CC\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230?",
		"id":17441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79C1\u804A",
		"indexes":"yxnzfskysxnhlygwjydydlt",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5B9E\u73B0\u4F60\u548C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u73A9\u5BB6\u4E00\u5BF9\u4E00\u5730\u804A\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":17442
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"dsjkysyzypdsh",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u53EF\u4EE5\u4F7F\u7528\u804C\u4E1A\u9891\u9053\u8BF4\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":17443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zwgsygjpdshwgkykjm",
		"question":"\u5728\u9B4F\u56FD\u4F7F\u7528\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u8BF4\u8BDD\uFF0C\u5434\u56FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u89C1\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u5587\u53ED",
		"indexes":"nsdhrgxyqfwqdsggjdntdygsy",
		"question":"\u4F60\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD\u5982\u679C\u60F3\u8981\u5168\u670D\u52A1\u5668\u7684\u4E09\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u90FD\u80FD\u542C\u5230\uFF0C\u5E94\u8BE5\u4F7F\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":17445
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zmhlygwjsl",
		"question":"\u600E\u4E48\u548C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u73A9\u5BB6\u79C1\u804A\uFF1F",
		"id":17446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"cwhyhysmhc",
		"question":"\u6210\u4E3A\u597D\u53CB\u540E\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u597D\u5904\uFF1F",
		"id":17447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66",
		"indexes":"rgycygcsdlygcszkdffs",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u8981\u4ECE\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5230\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\uFF0C\u6700\u5FEB\u7684\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u627E\u57CE\u5E02\u91CC\u7684\u9A7F\u7AD9\u9A6C\u592B\u548C\u4ED6\u5BF9\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"zmzmcy",
		"question":"\u600E\u4E48\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66\u5440\uFF1F",
		"id":17449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"hmdrkyzmcm",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u540D\u7684\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17450
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zxhdzjdygcsyxffkx",
		"question":"\u5728\u60F3\u56DE\u5230\u6700\u8FD1\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\uFF0C\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":17451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51CF\u5C11QQ\u53F7\u88AB\u76D7\u540E\u4F60\u7684\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u635F\u5931",
		"indexes":"cjjsdshszmmsgmyd",
		"question":"\u521B\u5EFA\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u65F6\u5019\u8BBE\u7F6E\u5BC6\u7801\u662F\u5E72\u561B\u7528\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zyjzjdydwpdjmcqzq",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u5C06\u81EA\u5DF1\u591A\u4F59\u7684\u7269\u54C1\u9053\u5177\u5356\u51FA\u53BB\u8D5A\u94B1\uFF1F",
		"id":17453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u53BB\u6253\u602A",
		"indexes":"btdrky",
		"question":"\u6446\u644A\u7684\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5\uFF1A",
		"id":17454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"btdtwydsg",
		"question":"\u6446\u644A\u7684\u644A\u4F4D\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u683C\uFF1F",
		"id":17455
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"rgnzydzkssjsbdzjhcxsmxx",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u5728\u79FB\u52A8\u4E2D\u5FEB\u901F\u53CC\u51FB\u9F20\u6807\u7684\u5DE6\u952E\uFF0C\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u4EC0\u4E48\u73B0\u8C61\uFF1F",
		"id":17456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u73B0\u547D\u4EE4\u9009\u5355",
		"indexes":"rgzwjtxsdjsbyjhcxsmxx",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u5728\u73A9\u5BB6\u5934\u50CF\u4E0A\u70B9\u51FB\u9F20\u6807\u53F3\u952E\uFF0C\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u4EC0\u4E48\u73B0\u8C61\uFF1F",
		"id":17457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BF9",
		"indexes":"zycwndhyncnfxjjtdm",
		"question":"\u53EA\u6709\u6210\u4E3A\u4F60\u7684\u597D\u53CB\uFF0C\u4F60\u624D\u80FD\u53D1\u4FE1\u4EF6\u7ED9\u4ED6\uFF0C\u5BF9\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17458
	},
	{
		"answer":"50",
		"indexes":"ygjsdyxzdnrndsfyj",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u90AE\u7BB1\u6700\u591A\u80FD\u5BB9\u7EB3\u591A\u5C11\u5C01\u90AE\u4EF6\uFF1F",
		"id":17459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u4F7F\u7528\u4E86\u79C1\u4EBA\u4ED3\u5E93\u9053\u5177",
		"indexes":"wsmyxrdckbwdrld",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u6BD4\u6211\u7684\u5BB9\u91CF\u5927\uFF1F",
		"id":17460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"btcyxkyhdtyqdlytxm",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u9000\u51FA\u6E38\u620F\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u6362\u5230\u540C\u4E00\u533A\u7684\u53E6\u4E00\u6761\u7EBF\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"rgwyjAjszwqtdjngjkym",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u6211\u8981\u5C06A\u952E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u4E3A\u5176\u5B83\u7684\u6280\u80FD\u653B\u51FB\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u5728\u7CFB\u7EDF\u8BBE\u7F6E\u4E86\u81EA\u52A8\u653B\u51FB",
		"indexes":"wsmyshwdgdyxhwbajpwdkyjxdzgg",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u65F6\u5019\u6211\u6253\u602A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E0B\u540E\u6211\u4E0D\u6309\u952E\u76D8\u6211\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u7EE7\u7EED\u6253\u8FD9\u4E2A\u602A\uFF1F",
		"id":17463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6309F11",
		"indexes":"pbrtdlwxpbtmzmb",
		"question":"\u65C1\u8FB9\u4EBA\u592A\u591A\u4E86\uFF0C\u6211\u60F3\u5C4F\u853D\u4ED6\u4EEC\uFF0C\u600E\u4E48\u529E\uFF1F",
		"id":17464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"bbldwpwky",
		"question":"\u80CC\u5305\u91CC\u7684\u7269\u54C1\uFF0C\u6211\u53EF\u4EE5\uFF1A",
		"id":17465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6309M\u952E\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zyxlkykdsjdtm",
		"question":"\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u91CC\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u5230\u4E16\u754C\u5730\u56FE\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxlddjyjz",
		"question":"\u6E38\u620F\u91CC\u7684\u9053\u5177\u6709\u51E0\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":17467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxzddjlyy",
		"question":"\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7684\u9053\u5177\u6765\u6E90\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":17468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"gymcdmsnxszqd",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u9A6C\u8349\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17469
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"QQsgsyksmtcdyx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u662F\u4E00\u6B3E\u4EC0\u4E48\u9898\u6750\u7684\u6E38\u620F?",
		"id":17470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zglsnggjd",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684?",
		"id":17471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":17472
	},
	{
		"answer":"QQ\u53F7\u7801",
		"indexes":"ysmzhjkyzjdlQQsg",
		"question":"\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E10\u53F7\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u76F4\u63A5\u767B\u9646QQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":17473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72B6\u6001\u754C\u9762",
		"indexes":"F1ssmjmdkjj",
		"question":"'F1'\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u754C\u9762\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E?",
		"id":17474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u57CE",
		"indexes":"F9ssmjmdkjj",
		"question":"'F9'\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u754C\u9762\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E?",
		"id":17475
	},
	{
		"answer":"F9",
		"indexes":"scdkjjssm",
		"question":"'\u5546\u57CE'\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17476
	},
	{
		"answer":"G",
		"indexes":"yzjdNPCdhdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u4E0E\u6700\u8FD1\u7684NPC\u5BF9\u8BDD\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17477
	},
	{
		"answer":"C",
		"indexes":"sqlzdsddjdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u62FE\u53D6\u843D\u5728\u5730\u4E0A\u7684\u9053\u5177\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17478
	},
	{
		"answer":"~",
		"indexes":"ksdxsbwjjsdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5FEB\u901F\u70B9\u9009\u8EAB\u8FB9\u73A9\u5BB6\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17479
	},
	{
		"answer":"Tab",
		"indexes":"ksdxsbgwdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5FEB\u901F\u70B9\u9009\u8EAB\u8FB9\u602A\u7269\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17480
	},
	{
		"answer":"M",
		"indexes":"dkdtdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u6253\u5F00\u5730\u56FE\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC4\u7BA1\u5C0F\u5996",
		"indexes":"ssdwpyjzmlygzngNPC",
		"question":"\u8EAB\u4E0A\u7684\u7269\u54C1\u5DF2\u7ECF\u88C5\u6EE1\u4E86,\u5E94\u8BE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC?",
		"id":17482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8F66\u592B",
		"indexes":"xksddlwdccygzngNPC",
		"question":"\u60F3\u5FEB\u901F\u5230\u8FBE\u53E6\u5916\u7684\u57CE\u6C60,\u5E94\u8BE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC?",
		"id":17483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u594B\u5A01\u4E2D\u90CE\u5C06",
		"indexes":"xxlzjygzngNPC",
		"question":"\u60F3\u4FEE\u70BC\u81EA\u5DF1,\u5E94\u8BE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC?",
		"id":17484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7269\u54C1\u754C\u9762",
		"indexes":"xzyxzbgtwygtgngjmcz",
		"question":"\u60F3\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u6446\u4E2A\u644A\u4F4D,\u5E94\u8BE5\u901A\u8FC7\u54EA\u4E2A\u754C\u9762\u64CD\u4F5C?",
		"id":17485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A91\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzysbsyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"QQsgdrwzgyjljbsx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u603B\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u7C7B\u57FA\u672C\u5C5E\u6027?",
		"id":17491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u5747\u578B",
		"indexes":"jsssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u5251\u4F8D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u9632\u578B",
		"indexes":"hjssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u8C6A\u6770\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u653B\u578B",
		"indexes":"yysssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6062\u590D\u578B",
		"indexes":"xssssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17495
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"jszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u5251\u4F8D\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":17496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65A7\u5934",
		"indexes":"hjzbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u8C6A\u6770\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":17497
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6756",
		"indexes":"yyszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":17498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6247\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xsszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":17499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"mgzytsjyyjlxf",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u5929\u751F\u5C31\u62E5\u6709\u51E0\u7C7B\u5FC3\u6CD5?",
		"id":17500
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"1QbngdhdsQd",
		"question":"1Q\u5E01\u80FD\u591F\u5151\u6362\u591A\u5C11Q\u70B9?",
		"id":17501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"hjjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6A2A\u5251\u51FB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17502
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxjwsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u996E\u8840\u5251\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"hfflsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u56DE\u98CE\u62C2\u67F3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jrsxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u5203\u566C\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"fgzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5206\u5149\u65A9\u5F71\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"klqxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u96F7\u4E03\u661F\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"shyssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6151\u9B42\u4E00\u5F0F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jdbhsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u8361\u516B\u8352\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"cysxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6B8B\u5F71\u8680\u5FC3\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"adcqsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u50B2\u65AD\u82CD\u7A79\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jhhjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u9E3F\u5E7B\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"cyhxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u51FA\u4E91\u5E7B\u661F\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jqcjxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u6C14\u51B2\u4E5D\u9704\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bwfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u9738\u738B\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"qxfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6CE3\u8840\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17516
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jxlhfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u796D\u8840\u8FDE\u73AF\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17517
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"nhktsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6012\u6D77\u72C2\u6D9B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"sggfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u5DE5\u9B3C\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"lzqjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u529B\u65A9\u5343\u94A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jlldsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u96F7\u88C2\u5730\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"slthsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u9F99\u63A2\u6D77\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jzfldsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E5D\u5DDE\u98CE\u96F7\u52A8\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"kfcxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u65A7\u51B2\u9704\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"ksbzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u6C99\u767E\u6218\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"sxptsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u55DC\u8840\u7834\u5929\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"tnrysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5929\u6012\u4EBA\u6028\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u706B\u708E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cyxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70BD\u708E\u88AD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"kyysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u708E\u6D8C\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cyzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6B8B\u9633\u7099\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xhzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u661F\u706B\u5760\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yhfxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E1A\u706B\u711A\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hjlhsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5E7B\u5251\u79BB\u706B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jskwsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u91D1\u86C7\u72C2\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xjmysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5378\u7532\u51A5\u7130\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yhlysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u91CE\u706B\u71CE\u539F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"aydcxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6697\u708E\u51CB\u6B8B\u661F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"lyymzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70BC\u72F1\u9634\u9B54\u5492\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xllhzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70AB\u7075\u6D41\u706B\u5492\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jsfhxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6C5F\u5C71\u70FD\u706B\u5578\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"spsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6C34\u7011\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hcssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u56DE\u6625\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xbhdsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7384\u51B0\u62A4\u76FE\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zyrtsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u771F\u5143\u5165\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u71D5\u884C\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hbcsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5BD2\u51B0\u523A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"nsjxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u51DD\u795E\u9759\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xmjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7EED\u547D\u8BC0\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"tjqlssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u592A\u6781\u6E05\u7075\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"ylgxssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5143\u7075\u5F52\u5FC3\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17551
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"chncsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6CA7\u6D77\u6012\u6F6E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cfftsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6625\u98CE\u62C2\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jfssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u75BE\u98CE\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"bhcssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u78A7\u6D77\u6F6E\u751F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"lhcsssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u83B2\u534E\u51FA\u6C34\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jtcyssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u6D9B\u7A7F\u4E91\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17557
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"qlssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u8F7B\u7075\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jjjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6FC0\u5C06\u8BA1\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"ysjfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7389\u77F3\u4FF1\u711A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bmjssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u706D\u91D1\u8EAB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bbzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u78C5\u7934\u6218\u610F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"txsfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6311\u8845\u56DB\u65B9\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"ksfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5F00\u5C71\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zqhtsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u771F\u6C14\u62A4\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hfftsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u706B\u51E4\u9644\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"wstxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5A01\u6151\u5929\u4E0B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zmssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u667A\u8C0B\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"njzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5B81\u9759\u81F4\u8FDC\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hbzjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7F13\u5175\u4E4B\u8BA1\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":17570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u594B\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"xtgzjdwlgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":17571
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5996\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"xtgzjdmfgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u9B54\u6CD5\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":17572
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7981\u536B",
		"indexes":"xjszjsddwlgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u51CF\u5C11\u81EA\u5DF1\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":17573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"xjszjsddmfgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u51CF\u5C11\u81EA\u5DF1\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u9B54\u6CD5\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":17574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u9A8C",
		"indexes":"yxnyxnzxlzswfgbd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u9879,\u4F60\u5728'\u4FEE\u70BC'\u4E2D\u662F\u65E0\u6CD5\u6539\u53D8\u7684?",
		"id":17575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672C\u56FD\u4E66\u4E1E",
		"indexes":"xyyzhdjqrwkyzngNPCjsrw",
		"question":"\u60F3\u8981\u4E00\u76F4\u83B7\u5F97\u91D1\u94B1\u4EFB\u52A1,\u53EF\u4EE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u63A5\u53D7\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":17576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"QQsgyjzfzy",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u6709\u51E0\u79CD\u526F\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":17577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"yxnlfzsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u7C7B\u526F\u804C\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":17578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E96\u4E01",
		"indexes":"kyschftlhsmdfzs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u751F\u4EA7\u56DE\u590D\u4F53\u529B\u548C\u751F\u547D\u7684\u526F\u804C\u662F?",
		"id":17579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"zzzssngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"'\u91CD\u94F8\u4E4B\u4E66'\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":17580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E96\u4E01",
		"indexes":"jrwjsngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"'\u9152\u8089\u65E0\u5FCC'\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":17581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9576\u5DE5",
		"indexes":"wszzfsngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"'\u6B66\u795E\u4E4B\u795D\u798F'\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":17582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"hcdzngNPCckygmd",
		"question":"'\u56DE\u6625\u4E39'\u5728\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u5904\u53EF\u4EE5\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230?",
		"id":17583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"yxngdjzqhscsgmbdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u5728\u5343\u8D27\u5546\u5904\u662F\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":17584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"yxngdjskyzscngmdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u662F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u5546\u57CE\u5185\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":17585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"fzsxydclybdkyznlgmd",
		"question":"\u526F\u804C\u6240\u9700\u8981\u7684\u6750\u6599,\u4E00\u822C\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230?",
		"id":17586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795E\u884C\u4E4B\u5377",
		"indexes":"kysjtgzjdydhtyddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u77AC\u95F4\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u79FB\u52A8\u548C\u8DF3\u8DC3\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":17587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u5F3A\u4E38",
		"indexes":"kymcswcfddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u9664\u6B7B\u4EA1\u60E9\u7F5A\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":17588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"kysjtgzjydhlddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u77AC\u95F4\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u4E00\u5B9A\u6D3B\u529B\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":17589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4E38",
		"indexes":"kyszjhdsbjyddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u4F7F\u81EA\u5DF1\u83B7\u5F97\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":17590
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E92\u9E9F\u533A",
		"indexes":"xlngqybsdjzzxyzddqy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u533A\u57DF\u4E0D\u662F\u593A\u8346\u5DDE\u4E2D\u9700\u8981\u4E89\u593A\u7684\u533A\u57DF",
		"id":17591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9",
		"indexes":"zbyxngdjjkyzdjzjjx",
		"question":"\u88C5\u5907\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u81EA\u52A8\u7ED9\u81EA\u5DF1\u52A0\u8840?",
		"id":17592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88C5\u5907'\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9'\u540E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u9ED8\u8BA4\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u836F\u7269",
		"indexes":"gmlzdbjrhcnzdjzjdjsbj",
		"question":"\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E86'\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9'\u5982\u4F55\u624D\u80FD\u81EA\u52A8\u7ED9\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u89D2\u8272\u8865\u7ED9?",
		"id":17593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u5587\u53ED",
		"indexes":"syyxngdjkyrsydrdkjnsdh",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u53EF\u4EE5\u8BA9\u6240\u6709\u7684\u4EBA\u90FD\u770B\u89C1\u4F60\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD?",
		"id":17594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968F\u7740\u7B49\u7EA7\u53D8\u5316",
		"indexes":"sygjpdfyxydssgb",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u53D1\u8A00,\u9700\u8981\u591A\u5C11\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01?",
		"id":17595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u9505\u5934",
		"indexes":"yxngdjsQQsgnd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177\u662FQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u5185\u7684?",
		"id":17596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D29\u5356\u5546\u57CE\u9053\u5177",
		"indexes":"yxnzfsbnhdsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u4E0D\u80FD\u83B7\u5F97\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\uFF1F",
		"id":17597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7269\u653B",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxdbwqdwlgjl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4EE3\u8868\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u529B?",
		"id":17598
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7075\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxyxjsdhbnl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u5F71\u54CD\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u56DE\u907F\u80FD\u529B?",
		"id":17599
	},
	{
		"answer":"F1",
		"indexes":"xszzjdgxqmygsyngkjjhjztjm",
		"question":"\u60F3\u8BBE\u7F6E\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u4E2A\u6027\u7B7E\u540D,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4F7F\u7528\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u547C\u53EB\u72B6\u6001\u754C\u9762?",
		"id":17600
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"yzjbznsydsgsbjyw",
		"question":"\u4E00\u5468\u57FA\u672C\u53EA\u80FD\u4F7F\u7528\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A& #39;\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4E38& #39;?",
		"id":17601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7070\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjrhddgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u5F31\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":17602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7EFF\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjsrdgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u7A0D\u5F31\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":17603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u9EC4\u8272",
		"indexes":"hwjcbddgw",
		"question":"\u548C\u73A9\u5BB6\u5DEE\u4E0D\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":17604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u6A59\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjsqdgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u7A0D\u5F3A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":17605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7EA2\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjqhddgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u5F3A\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":17606
	},
	{
		"answer":"sg.qq.com",
		"indexes":"QQsggfwzdwzs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u5B98\u65B9\u7F51\u7AD9\u7684\u7F51\u5740\u662F:",
		"id":17607
	},
	{
		"answer":",",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyqfzdykjjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u524D\u7FFB'\u81EA\u5B9A\u4E49\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u7EC4'?",
		"id":17608
	},
	{
		"answer":".",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyhfzdykjjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u540E\u7FFB'\u81EA\u5B9A\u4E49\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u7EC4'?",
		"id":17609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6570\u5B57\u952E1\u81F35",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyksxzzjddy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u9009\u62E9\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u961F\u53CB?",
		"id":17610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90AE\u4EF6",
		"indexes":"rgndhybzxnkytgsmfsjtly",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u7684\u597D\u53CB\u4E0D\u5728\u7EBF,\u4F60\u53EF\u4EE5\u901A\u8FC7\u4EC0\u4E48\u65B9\u5F0F\u7ED9\u4ED6\u7559\u8A00?",
		"id":17611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79C1\u804A",
		"indexes":"yyxnzfskyydddckhbrjl",
		"question":"\u7528\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u53EF\u4EE5\u7528\u5355\u72EC\u7684\u7A97\u53E3\u548C\u522B\u4EBA\u4EA4\u6D41?",
		"id":17612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053",
		"indexes":"yxcwdhwnxyznldlfy",
		"question":"\u8981\u60F3\u6210\u4E3A\u5927\u8BDD\u738B,\u4F60\u9700\u8981\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u5927\u91CF\u53D1\u8A00?",
		"id":17613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u65B9\u5DE1\u67E5\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"cxgzyzdjpxbnxyznwNPC",
		"question":"\u67E5\u8BE2\u5404\u804C\u4E1A\u4E3B\u7B49\u7EA7\u6392\u884C\u699C,\u4F60\u9700\u8981\u627E\u54EA\u4F4DNPC?",
		"id":17614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7CA4\u83DC",
		"indexes":"krzsngcxddbc",
		"question":"\u70E4\u4E73\u732A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u83DC\u7CFB\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u83DC",
		"id":17615
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C0B\u751F",
		"indexes":"xmnbdybszblzbzdzyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u7535\u5F71\u4E0D\u662F\u5353\u522B\u6797\u81EA\u7F16\u81EA\u5BFC\u81EA\u6F14\u7684",
		"id":17616
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E03\u4E03\u4E8B\u4EF6",
		"indexes":"qgxkrzzbfdbzs",
		"question":"\u5168\u56FD\u6027\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u7206\u53D1\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17617
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B",
		"indexes":"wgzmdzzqjyngcd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u7684\u8D75\u5DDE\u6865\u5EFA\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":17618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B",
		"indexes":"lzsqzsmchgghzwzyd",
		"question":"\u8001\u5B50\u662F\u9A91\u7740\u4EC0\u4E48\u51FA\u51FD\u8C37\u5173\u540E\u518D\u65E0\u8E2A\u5F71\u7684",
		"id":17619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u67F3\u6811\u76AE",
		"indexes":"asplzctqy",
		"question":"\u963F\u53F8\u5339\u6797\u6700\u521D\u63D0\u53D6\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":17620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8303\u8821",
		"indexes":"bhrcwtzgdss",
		"question":"\u88AB\u540E\u4EBA\u79F0\u4E3A\u9676\u6731\u516C\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":17621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u829D\u9EBB\u5F00\u95E8",
		"indexes":"albbhssdddgszdksmdzys",
		"question":"\u963F\u91CC\u5DF4\u5DF4\u548C\u56DB\u5341\u5927\u76D7\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u4E2D\u6253\u5F00\u77F3\u95E8\u7684\u5492\u8BED\u662F",
		"id":17622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjszzdzbcsznl",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u7EB8\u5E01\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u91CC",
		"id":17623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AF9\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlsmzwszsdzk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4EC0\u4E48\u690D\u7269\u751F\u957F\u901F\u5EA6\u6700\u5FEB?",
		"id":17624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u8272",
		"indexes":"mygssmzdyzjxadysszzdcydmgzxa",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u90FD\u6709\u81EA\u5DF1\u559C\u7231\u7684\u989C\u8272\uFF0C\u751F\u957F\u5728\u5927\u8349\u539F\u7684\u8499\u53E4\u65CF\u559C\u7231:",
		"id":17625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8718\u86DB",
		"indexes":"qzcxlznyzbskc",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u662F\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":17626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zynsxsnggjsjmgdlw",
		"question":"\uFF02\u81EA\u7531\u5973\u795E\u50CF\uFF02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u9001\u7ED9\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u793C\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":17627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B3C\u8C37\u5B50",
		"indexes":"sbdlsjsm",
		"question":"\u5B59\u8191\u7684\u8001\u5E08\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u661F",
		"indexes":"tyxznkxxdbmwdzg",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u7CFB\u4E2D\u54EA\u9897\u884C\u661F\u7684\u8868\u9762\u6E29\u5EA6\u6700\u9AD8?",
		"id":17629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u989D\u5C14\u9F50\u65AF\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"fyywgwyzrbbydhls",
		"question":"\u53D1\u6E90\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u552F\u4E00\u6CE8\u5165\u5317\u51B0\u6D0B\u7684\u6CB3\u6D41\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9CB8",
		"indexes":"nzhydwhxneyycg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u6D77\u6D0B\u52A8\u7269\u4F1A\u50CF\u9E1F\u513F\u4E00\u6837\u5531\u6B4C?",
		"id":17631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u5BAA\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"sjsdybcwxfs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u6210\u6587\u5BAA\u6CD5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u950C",
		"indexes":"slbcxlnzyskfzfc",
		"question":"\u9002\u91CF\u8865\u5145\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u5143\u7D20\u53EF\u9632\u6B62\u7C89\u523A\uFF1F",
		"id":17633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u683C\u62C9\u5E95",
		"indexes":"xlnwsxjbpsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u88AB\u5224\u6B7B\u5211",
		"id":17634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7334\u7968",
		"indexes":"xfxdsxypznzjzzg",
		"question":"\u73B0\u53D1\u884C\u7684\u5C5E\u76F8\u90AE\u7968\u4E2D\u54EA\u79CD\u4EF7\u503C\u6700\u9AD8",
		"id":17635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"mlyydlszddsczynl",
		"question":"\u6BCD\u72FC\u4E0E\u4E00\u5BF9\u5B6A\u751F\u5B50\u7684\u96D5\u5851\u5B58\u5728\u4E8E\u54EA\u91CC",
		"id":17636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u52C3",
		"indexes":"ctsjzy",
		"question":"\u201C\u521D\u5510\u56DB\u6770\u201D\u4E2D\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":17637
	},
	{
		"answer":"26\u5757",
		"indexes":"mfsyjgxfkzcd",
		"question":"\u9B54\u65B9\u662F\u7531\u51E0\u4E2A\u5C0F\u65B9\u5757\u7EC4\u6210\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6559\u5802\u91CC",
		"indexes":"zgldyyssz",
		"question":"\u6700\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u533B\u9662\u662F\u8BBE\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":17639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5CB8",
		"indexes":"jztjznlhd",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5B57\u5854\u5EFA\u5728\u5C3C\u7F57\u6CB3\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C98\u571F",
		"indexes":"ktfmdxztydqbsysmhsmhhzcd",
		"question":"\u5B54\u6CF0\u53D1\u660E\u7684\u73B0\u5728\u901A\u7528\u7684\u94C5\u7B14\u662F\u7531\u77F3\u58A8\u548C\u4EC0\u4E48\u6DF7\u5408\u5236\u6210\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u607A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"lsftssdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u6D1B\u795E\u8D4B\u56FE\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":17642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"lysllcmngzdsdmssfmd",
		"question":"\u5229\u7528\u6C34\u529B\u6765\u8202\u7C73\u78BE\u8C37\u5B50\u7684\u6C34\u7893\u78E8\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u660E\u7684",
		"id":17643
	},
	{
		"answer":"1967",
		"indexes":"rlslxzyzsssnnsxd",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u9996\u4F8B\u5FC3\u810F\u79FB\u690D\u624B\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u5E74\u65BD\u884C\u7684",
		"id":17644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u4E95",
		"indexes":"ncwcdchzzsjgrhgsylcfzznl",
		"question":"\u5357\u9648\u738B\u671D\u7684\u9648\u540E\u4E3B\u5728\u968B\u519B\u653B\u5165\u7687\u5BAB\u65F6\u4E0E\u4E24\u5BA0\u5983\u85CF\u5728\u54EA\u91CC",
		"id":17645
	},
	{
		"answer":"3-6\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"qzjdbfgdqzjdqxwdzsj",
		"question":"\u300A\u5F3A\u5236\u6212\u6BD2\u529E\u6CD5\u300B\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u5F3A\u5236\u6212\u6BD2\u671F\u9650\u4E3A\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":17646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EDA\u8F6E",
		"indexes":"yxngbsgqdnbjg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5149\u9A71\u7684\u5185\u90E8\u7ED3\u6784?",
		"id":17647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73\u5BFF",
		"indexes":"88sygscqwssm",
		"question":"88\u5C81\u6709\u4E2A\u4FD7\u79F0\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63A5\u5929\u83B2\u53F6\u65E0\u7A77\u78A7\uFF0C\u6620\u65E5\u8377\u82B1\u522B\u6837\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsyxhcljjjzyqtlstcztyzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0E\u201C\u5C0F\u8377\u624D\u9732\u5C16\u5C16\u89D2\uFF0C\u65E9\u6709\u873B\u8713\u7ACB\u4E0A\u5934\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u540C\u4E00\u4F5C\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":17649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u706B\u661F\u516C\u4E3B\u300B",
		"indexes":"qwxlxszngbsfendzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u51E1\u5C14\u7EB3\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1",
		"id":17650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690",
		"indexes":"ltrnysyzjsdyzzss",
		"question":"\u201C\u84DD\u7530\u65E5\u6696\u7389\u751F\u70DF\u201D\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BD7\u7684\u539F\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":17651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A00\u60C5",
		"indexes":"ycyqtmsdyykzycbpszdqtmssysmlxdzj",
		"question":"\u7531\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u5899\u5934\u9A6C\u4E0A\u201D\u7684\u539F\u610F\u53EF\u77E5\uFF0C\u5143\u671D\u767D\u6734\u6240\u8457\u7684\u300A\u5899\u5934\u9A6C\u4E0A\u300B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6742\u5267\uFF1F",
		"id":17652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u897F",
		"indexes":"glwywgdngs",
		"question":"\u6842\u6797\u4F4D\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":17653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u949F\u6446",
		"indexes":"czjslyyxlngwpdqs",
		"question":"\u4F20\u771F\u6280\u672F\u6765\u6E90\u4E8E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u7269\u54C1\u7684\u542F\u793A\uFF1F",
		"id":17654
	},
	{
		"answer":"36\u90E1",
		"indexes":"qckstxjxzdzqgs",
		"question":"\u79E6\u671D\u5F00\u59CB\u63A8\u884C\u90E1\u53BF\u5236\u5EA6\u5728\u5168\u56FD\u8BBE",
		"id":17655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u5B50\u6602",
		"indexes":"qbjgrhbjlzntdzyydcretxczhrzs",
		"question":"\u524D\u4E0D\u89C1\u53E4\u4EBA\uFF0C\u540E\u4E0D\u89C1\u6765\u8005\u3002\u5FF5\u5929\u5730\u4E4B\u60A0\u60A0\uFF0C\u72EC\u6006\u7136\u800C\u6D95\u4E0B\u3002\u51FA\u81EA\u4F55\u4EBA\u4E4B\u624B\uFF1F",
		"id":17656
	},
	{
		"answer":"CPU",
		"indexes":"jddnyxszpldsyxngbj",
		"question":"\u51B3\u5B9A\u7535\u8111\u8FD0\u884C\u65F6\u949F\u9891\u7387\u7684\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u90E8\u4EF6\uFF1F",
		"id":17657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72E9\u730E",
		"indexes":"wkymdwzzgdglmybszsm",
		"question":"\u201C\u7F51\u5F00\u4E00\u9762\u201D\u7684\u201C\u7F51\u201D\u5728\u8FD9\u4E2A\u5178\u6545\u91CC\u9762\u539F\u672C\u662F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E0C\u814A",
		"indexes":"zzdggzyssnggjdgg",
		"question":"\u6700\u957F\u7684\u56FD\u6B4C\u201C\u81EA\u7531\u9882\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u56FD\u6B4C\uFF1F",
		"id":17659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78B3\u68D2",
		"indexes":"tcqkxxmnygsdt",
		"question":"\u901A\u5E38\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0B\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u6839\u662F\u5BFC\u4F53\uFF1F",
		"id":17660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u514B\u6717",
		"indexes":"nwhbs",
		"question":"\u632A\u5A01\u8D27\u5E01\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u62C9\u7B2C",
		"indexes":"fxdcgyxxdwlxjs",
		"question":"\u53D1\u73B0\u7535\u78C1\u611F\u5E94\u73B0\u8C61\u7684\u7269\u7406\u5B66\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5144\u5F1F",
		"indexes":"xlshzbsdszsd",
		"question":"\u5E0C\u814A\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u6CE2\u8D5B\u987F\u662F\u5B99\u65AF\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EB8",
		"indexes":"pydyxsysmcl",
		"question":"\u76AE\u5F71\u7684\u539F\u578B\u662F\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u6750\u6599\uFF1A",
		"id":17664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F8\u94DC\u9540\u91D1",
		"indexes":"zgdyjjjjpsgd35gfdyzzxymdjxdxzzdxs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7535\u5F71\u91D1\u9E21\u5956\u5956\u54C1\u662F\u9AD8\u8FBE35\u516C\u5206\u7684\u4E00\u5EA7\u9020\u578B\u4F18\u7F8E\u7684\u9E21\u5F62\u96D5\u50CF\uFF0C\u8FD9\u5EA7\u96D5\u50CF\u662F",
		"id":17665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671D\u9633",
		"indexes":"yxngcssyhqmd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\u7528\u82B1\u53D6\u540D\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u8428\u514B\u65CF",
		"indexes":"gnzsngmzdyx",
		"question":"\u201C\u59D1\u5A18\u8FFD\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u6E38\u620F\uFF1F",
		"id":17667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DDD\u83DC",
		"indexes":"ymlxxdlewmdcxs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u9EBB\u8FA3\u8F9B\u9999\u8C03\u6599\u800C\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u83DC\u7CFB\u662F",
		"id":17668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u5B9D\u7CA5",
		"indexes":"yxngslycbdctsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u814A\u6708\u521D\u516B\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u98DF\u7269?",
		"id":17669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u5170",
		"indexes":"dojbcnggjzxbf",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6B27\u5267\u53D8\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6700\u5148\u7206\u53D1\uFF1F",
		"id":17670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u798F\u5EFA\u83DC\u7CFB",
		"indexes":"ftqsngcxddbc",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u8DF3\u5899\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u83DC\u7CFB\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u83DC",
		"id":17671
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5E9C\u83DC",
		"indexes":"bxghnlhsngcxdzmcy",
		"question":"\u516B\u4ED9\u8FC7\u6D77\u95F9\u7F57\u6C49\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u83DC\u7CFB\u7684\u8457\u540D\u83DC\u80B4?",
		"id":17672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"ddmsnldtssp",
		"question":"\u62C5\u62C5\u9762\u662F\u54EA\u91CC\u7684\u7279\u8272\u98DF\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":17673
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F15",
		"indexes":"nbccmtssm",
		"question":"\u5357\u5317\u671D\u79F0\u9762\u6761\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5143\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"tdssdzwjcqssysmsq",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u8BBE\u5341\u9053\u4F5C\u4E3A\u76D1\u5BDF\u533A\u662F\u59CB\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":17675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u751C\u9178\u54B8\u82E6",
		"indexes":"rdwlnbbdwdy",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7684\u5473\u857E\u80FD\u8FA8\u522B\u7684\u5473\u9053\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":17676
	},
	{
		"answer":"2003\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gjbdmmwyhzsmmlgzbdksznyn",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u75C5\u6BD2\u547D\u540D\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u6B63\u5F0F\u547D\u540D\u4E86\u51A0\u72B6\u75C5\u6BD2\u79D1\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":17677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u536B\u7684\u8868\u73B0",
		"indexes":"wybygnmyszdldwyzcydzgnmsbqztdyjzsyw",
		"question":"\u4E4C\u9E26\u88AB\u4E00\u4E2A\u519C\u6C11\u7528\u77F3\u5B50\u6253\u4E86\uFF0C\u5F53\u4E4C\u9E26\u518D\u6B21\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u4E2A\u519C\u6C11\u65F6\uFF0C\u4FBF\u53BB\u5544\u4ED6\u7684\u773C\u775B\uFF0C\u8FD9\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":17678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5154\u5B50\u7684\u8679\u819C\u662F\u65E0\u8272\u7684",
		"indexes":"tzdyjwsmshsd",
		"question":"\u5154\u5B50\u7684\u773C\u775B\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u662F\u7EA2\u8272\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u7720\u52A8\u7269\u51FA\u571F\u6D3B\u52A8",
		"indexes":"zwgdnljqzjzxzzsm",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u519C\u5386\u8282\u6C14\u4E2D\uFF0C\u201C\u60CA\u86F0\u201D\u8C61\u5F81\u7740\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DB3\u7403\u7BEE\u7403\u6392\u7403",
		"indexes":"sjsbcwsdqyddsnszyd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4E09\u5927\u7403\u201D\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E09\u79CD\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":17681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C11\u65CF\u4F20\u8BF4",
		"indexes":"dzgpsjsyw",
		"question":"\u50A3\u65CF\u8FC7\u6CFC\u6C34\u8282\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":17682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6D77",
		"indexes":"jdwxzjlxzzgngcsss",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u5BB6\u9C81\u8FC5\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u901D\u4E16?",
		"id":17683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u9C7C\u5B50",
		"indexes":"yyadzyljsm",
		"question":"\u7528\u76D0\u814C\u7684\u9CDF\u9C7C\u5375\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E90\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxnycmsblrsjwhjgyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u5904\u540D\u80DC\u88AB\u5217\u5165\u201C\u4E16\u754C\u6587\u5316\u666F\u89C2\u9057\u4EA7\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":17685
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u6E38",
		"indexes":"xjcszddsrs",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4ECA\u5B58\u8BD7\u6700\u591A\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":17686
	},
	{
		"answer":"3000",
		"indexes":"sjjzdlsdyydsn",
		"question":"\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\u8BB0\u8F7D\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u5927\u7EA6\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":17687
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"mdxxkwcxxkyjdyyldsn",
		"question":"\u660E\u4EE3\u5F90\u971E\u5BA2\u5B8C\u6210\u300A\u5F90\u971E\u5BA2\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u5927\u7EA6\u7528\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":17688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"mhqlzdzzsngd",
		"question":"\u6F2B\u753B\u4E03\u9F99\u73E0\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":17689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u661F",
		"indexes":"ltyzjdxxssmx",
		"question":"\u79BB\u592A\u9633\u6700\u8FD1\u7684\u884C\u661F\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u661F?",
		"id":17690
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u7C73",
		"indexes":"hzacddjfstdzyylky",
		"question":"\u6C49\u957F\u5B89\u57CE\u7684\u5927\u8857\u5206\u4E09\u6761\u9053\uFF0C\u4E2D\u592E\u5FA1\u8DEF\u5BBD\u7EA6",
		"id":17691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"qbsdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E03\u6B65\u8BD7\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5B5F\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"tsbrdldlbrrhcz",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u65F6\u4E0D\u5982\u5730\u5229\uFF0C\u5730\u5229\u4E0D\u5982\u4EBA\u548C\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\uFF1A",
		"id":17693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5362\u68AD",
		"indexes":"fgqmydzzfmzqxdzjs",
		"question":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u542F\u8499\u8FD0\u52A8\u4E2D\u6700\u5BCC\u6C11\u4E3B\u503E\u5411\u7684\u4F5C\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":17694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u9152",
		"indexes":"slyjdstyhcqwxlnzjdxxgjbyyfzy",
		"question":"\u5C11\u91CF\u996E\u9152\u5BF9\u8EAB\u4F53\u6709\u597D\u5904\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9152\u5BF9\u5FC3\u8840\u7BA1\u75BE\u75C5\u6709\u9884\u9632\u4F5C\u7528",
		"id":17695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20C",
		"indexes":"yyccxdrybtnqf",
		"question":"\u7259\u9F88\u5E38\u51FA\u8840\u7684\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E00\u822C\u4F53\u5185\u7F3A\u4E4F",
		"id":17696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E24\u6D77",
		"indexes":"xlsywgnhds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u5185\u6D77\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17697
	},
	{
		"answer":"1999\u5E7410\u670812\u65E5",
		"indexes":"sj60yrkrs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C60\u4EBF\u4EBA\u53E3\u65E5\u662F",
		"id":17698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8102\u80AA",
		"indexes":"xlwzztgrlzdds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u7269\u8D28\u4E2D\uFF0C\u63D0\u4F9B\u70ED\u91CF\u6700\u591A\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68D5\u6988\u53F6",
		"indexes":"rmgydbjssysmzwdyzzd",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u60EF\u7528\u7684\u82AD\u8549\u6247\u662F\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u690D\u7269\u7684\u53F6\u5B50\u505A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7435\u7436\u66F2",
		"indexes":"smmfs",
		"question":"\u300A\u5341\u9762\u57CB\u4F0F\u300B\u662F",
		"id":17701
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u6B21",
		"indexes":"nzdhbszsdl",
		"question":"\u7537\u5B50\u540A\u73AF\u6BD4\u8D5B\u81F3\u5C11\u5012\u7ACB\uFF1A",
		"id":17702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5C01",
		"indexes":"ngsscdgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u53E4\u90FD\uFF1A",
		"id":17703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9526\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"lszyzzxjfdcss",
		"question":"\u8FBD\u6C88\u6218\u5F79\u4E2D\u6700\u5148\u89E3\u653E\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F?",
		"id":17704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"dygcfdllmdhds",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u518C\u5C01'\u8FBE\u8D56\u5587\u561B'\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F",
		"id":17705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83CF\u6CFD",
		"indexes":"mdzxssdsd",
		"question":"\u7261\u4E39\u4E4B\u4E61\u662F\u5C71\u4E1C\u7701\u7684",
		"id":17706
	},
	{
		"answer":"18",
		"indexes":"qcbqghfwdsgs",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u628A\u5168\u56FD\u5212\u5206\u4E3A\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":17707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u628A\u5934\u53D1\u6813\u5728\u623F\u7CB1\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"sqysmbffzdssdks",
		"question":"\u82CF\u79E6\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u529E\u6CD5\u9632\u6B62\u8BFB\u4E66\u65F6\u6253\u778C\u7761?",
		"id":17708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u7F8E\u6D32",
		"indexes":"ngzdysslmjzd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D32\u7684\u539F\u59CB\u68EE\u6797\u9762\u79EF\u6700\u5927\uFF1A",
		"id":17709
	},
	{
		"answer":"1919",
		"indexes":"wsydfsznyn",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u56DB\u8FD0\u52A8\u201D\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":17710
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"dsrwtssdlrjxssszdkywtdsr",
		"question":"\u5F53\u4E8B\u4EBA\u59D4\u6258\u8BC9\u8BBC\u4EE3\u7406\u4EBA\u8FDB\u884C\u8BC9\u8BBC\u65F6\uFF0C\u6700\u591A\u53EF\u4EE5\u59D4\u6258\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":17711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F2\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"nxrfzkycqjqhzmccf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E9B\u4EBA\u72AF\u7F6A\u53EF\u4EE5\u4ECE\u8F7B\u3001\u51CF\u8F7B\u6216\u8005\u514D\u9664\u5904\u7F5A\uFF1F",
		"id":17712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8F7C",
		"indexes":"myjsybjwqtssdc",
		"question":"\u660E\u6708\u51E0\u65F6\u6709\uFF0C\u628A\u9152\u95EE\u9752\u5929\u3002\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":17713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u7F06",
		"indexes":"zdmtjsjxtzbnyyccdmtxxdssm",
		"question":"\u5728\u591A\u5A92\u4F53\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u7CFB\u7EDF\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0D\u80FD\u7528\u4EE5\u5B58\u50A8\u591A\u5A92\u4F53\u4FE1\u606F\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5E73\u6D0B",
		"indexes":"sjszddyw",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6D0B\u4E3A",
		"id":17715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E9A\u6D32",
		"indexes":"sjszddzw",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6D32\u4E3A",
		"id":17716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A79\u5929\u4F51",
		"indexes":"jztldzsjsss",
		"question":"\u4EAC\u5F20\u94C1\u8DEF\u7684\u603B\u8BBE\u8BA1\u5E08\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D",
		"indexes":"nycfccxzd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u671D\u5E9F\u9664\u4E1E\u76F8\u5236\u5EA6",
		"id":17718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34",
		"indexes":"zzdwdjlmydsnzry",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6E29\u5EA6\u8BA1\u91CC\u9762\u7528\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u6EB6\u6DB2\uFF1F",
		"id":17719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"mlspglfsngrfmd",
		"question":"\u6469\u7F57\u6C0F\u82F9\u679C\u7597\u6CD5\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u53D1\u660E\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u6C49\u537F",
		"indexes":"sbywzgdssby",
		"question":"\u8C01\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u201C\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":17721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u918B",
		"indexes":"xzccyzlmfxsm",
		"question":"\u978B\u5B50\u9664\u81ED\u5E94\u5728\u91CC\u9762\u653E\u4E9B\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEE\u9634",
		"indexes":"hxdljznl",
		"question":"\u97E9\u4FE1\u7684\u8001\u5BB6\u5728\u54EA\u91CC",
		"id":17723
	},
	{
		"answer":"1978\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zhrmghghkdjtlsnynbbssd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u6237\u53E3\u767B\u8BB0\u6761\u4F8B\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u9881\u5E03\u5B9E\u65BD\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgdngcdcjlhkoylzdddg",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u66FE\u5EFA\u7ACB\u6A2A\u8DE8\u6B27\u4E9A\u4E24\u6D32\u7684\u5927\u5E1D\u56FD\uFF1A",
		"id":17725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6C49",
		"indexes":"zglsshggygzsy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u5BA6\u5B98\u5E72\u9884\u56FD\u653F\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":17726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u975E",
		"indexes":"sjscchjzddgjs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u51FA\u4EA7\u9EC4\u91D1\u6700\u591A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17727
	},
	{
		"answer":"3\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zgldgdbjxanjlykfhzyjgwyhhly",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u516D\u5927\u53E4\u90FD\uFF1A\u5317\u4EAC,\u897F\u5B89,\u5357\u4EAC,\u6D1B\u9633,\u5F00\u5C01,\u676D\u5DDE\u3002\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u4F4D\u4E8E\u9EC4\u6CB3\u6D41\u57DF",
		"id":17728
	},
	{
		"answer":"1956\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgynynwcshzygz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5B8C\u6210\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u6539\u9020\uFF1A",
		"id":17729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706B\u795E",
		"indexes":"zswlcfamdwnsqptjjtszd",
		"question":"\u5B99\u65AF\u4E3A\u4E86\u60E9\u7F5A\u50B2\u6162\u7684\u7EF4\u7EB3\u65AF\uFF0C\u5F3A\u8FEB\u5979\u5AC1\u7ED9\u5929\u795E\u4E2D\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u89C2",
		"indexes":"zmcjlqrsjzsyqzccmmdzzs",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u8BCD\u53E5\u4E24\u60C5\u82E5\u662F\u4E45\u957F\u65F6,\u53C8\u5C82\u5728\u3001\u671D\u671D\u66AE\u66AE\u3002\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5C1D\u541B",
		"indexes":"cyjmgdgxmdngrwyg",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u9E21\u9E23\u72D7\u76D7\u201D\u8DDF\u4E0B\u9762\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u6709\u5173\uFF1A",
		"id":17732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u66B4\u98CE\u96E8\u300B",
		"indexes":"xmdxjzbsssbydsdbjzyds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u7684\u620F\u5267\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0D\u662F\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u7684\u201C\u56DB\u5927\u60B2\u5267\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6743\u7684\u59B9\u59B9",
		"indexes":"plfryzbzdfrzds",
		"question":"\u201C\u8D54\u4E86\u592B\u4EBA\u53C8\u6298\u5175\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u592B\u4EBA\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u679C",
		"indexes":"bcsjsxmngrwddbz",
		"question":"\u300A\u60B2\u60E8\u4E16\u754C\u300B\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1A",
		"id":17735
	},
	{
		"answer":"1911\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xhgmfsznyn",
		"question":"\u8F9B\u4EA5\u9769\u547D\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":17736
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"xzgclhwggbbljbxf",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u6210\u7ACB\u540E\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5171\u9881\u5E03\u4E86\u51E0\u90E8\u5BAA\u6CD5\uFF1A",
		"id":17737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xtqsnggq",
		"question":"\u661F\u6761\u65D7\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u56FD\u65D7\uFF1A",
		"id":17738
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"yzzwmczdsbkmqhddqjs",
		"question":"\u626C\u5DDE\u4F5C\u4E3A\u540D\u57CE\uFF0C\u6700\u591A\u65F6\u5305\u62EC\u76EE\u524D\u534E\u4E1C\u5730\u533A\u51E0\u7701\uFF1A",
		"id":17739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E3B\u5E2D",
		"indexes":"yzxfgdysfbfl",
		"question":"\u4F9D\u7167\u5BAA\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\u7531\u8C01\u53D1\u5E03\u6CD5\u5F8B\uFF1A",
		"id":17740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u723D",
		"indexes":"yxnygbswxsdsczy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6587\u5B66\u4E0A\u7684\u4E09\u66F9\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":17741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9774\u5B50",
		"indexes":"ydlzdtsx",
		"question":"\u610F\u5927\u5229\u5728\u5730\u56FE\u4E0A\u50CF",
		"id":17742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u8033\u66FC\u8BED\u65CF",
		"indexes":"yysynyyz",
		"question":"\u82F1\u8BED\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u8BED\u65CF\uFF1A",
		"id":17743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"yazbhsxtdzsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0E\u51F9\u5B57\u7B14\u753B\u6570\u76F8\u540C\u7684\u5B57\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":17744
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8170\u90E8",
		"indexes":"ymqfqsqbncg",
		"question":"\u7FBD\u6BDB\u7403\u53D1\u7403\u65F6\uFF0C\u7403\u4E0D\u80FD\u8D85\u8FC7\uFF1A",
		"id":17745
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50\u767D\u77F3",
		"indexes":"czjmtshbmjgjdhjs",
		"question":"\u66FE\u5728\u5BB6\u95E8\u5E16\u4E0A\u753B\u4E0D\u4E70\u7ED9\u5B98\u5BB6\u7684\u753B\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u6C34",
		"indexes":"zcydsysmsws",
		"question":"\u716E\u8336\u7528\u7684\u6C34\uFF0C\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u6C34\u4E3A\u4E0A\uFF1F",
		"id":17747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u732B\u57CE\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"zgwxdslscxgybkhxstdmzs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6587\u5B66\u5927\u5E08\u8001\u820D\u66FE\u5199\u8FC7\u4E00\u90E8\u79D1\u5E7B\u5C0F\u8BF4\uFF0C\u5B83\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u745E\u58EB",
		"indexes":"ngrzxzzclnnqkl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u6700\u5148\u5236\u4F5C\u51FA\u4E86\u725B\u5976\u5DE7\u514B\u529B\uFF1F",
		"id":17749
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94B1\u5E01\u540D",
		"indexes":"jcdsgddyz",
		"question":"\u91D1\u9519\u5200\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\uFF1A",
		"id":17750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC",
		"indexes":"djjxqjhcjxqdzzs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E5D\u4EA4\u54CD\u66F2\uFF08\u5373\u5408\u5531\u4EA4\u54CD\u66F2\uFF09\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u5C71\u65CF",
		"indexes":"alsdgnsnzmg",
		"question":"\u963F\u91CC\u5C71\u7684\u59D1\u5A18\u662F\u54EA\u65CF\u6C11\u6B4C\uFF1A",
		"id":17752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u624B",
		"indexes":"ksdyc",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u624B\u9053\u539F\u79F0",
		"id":17753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E94\u5929\u5E9C",
		"indexes":"zywddcsc",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\u65F6\u79F0",
		"id":17754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u5929",
		"indexes":"zywdswdstbzdlljtzhmd",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u7684\u6240\u8C13\u7684\u5C38\u4F53\u88AB\u6731\u68E3\u667E\u4E86\u51E0\u5929\u4E4B\u540E\u57CB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C91\u53C2",
		"indexes":"hryycflqswslhkqwcsdzzss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5FFD\u5982\u4E00\u591C\u6625\u98CE\u6765\uFF0C\u5343\u6811\u4E07\u6811\u68A8\u82B1\u5F00\u3002\u201D\u8BF7\u95EE\u6B64\u8BD7\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17756
	},
	{
		"answer":"75",
		"indexes":"yyjjsdsd",
		"question":"\u533B\u7528\u9152\u7CBE\u662F\u591A\u5C11\u5EA6",
		"id":17757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u9AD8\u4E1C\u4F4E",
		"indexes":"wgddsssmyd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u5730\u52BF\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6837\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"gefqqyy",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u5C14\u592B\u7403\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E",
		"id":17759
	},
	{
		"answer":"7\u65E5",
		"indexes":"rmfysdqszhydzdzsjnlahzzcbysldcd",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u6CD5\u9662\u6536\u5230\u8D77\u8BC9\u72B6\u540E\uFF0C\u5E94\u5F53\u5728\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u7ACB\u6848\u6216\u8005\u4F5C\u51FA\u4E0D\u4E88\u53D7\u7406\u7684\u88C1\u5B9A\uFF1F",
		"id":17760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u4E4B\u72EE",
		"indexes":"adlhbmyzyg",
		"question":"\u5965\u9EDB\u4E3D\u00B7\u8D6B\u672C\u6CA1\u6709\u4E3B\u6F14\u8FC7\uFF1A",
		"id":17761
	},
	{
		"answer":"8-12\u00B0C",
		"indexes":"rxxcjjsxhxymttsxyljsxhszdsywdkxsyzmdsxdszzsydsww",
		"question":"\u82E5\u60F3\u65B0\u6625\u4F73\u8282\u6C34\u4ED9\u82B1\u9999\u6EA2\u6EE1\u5385\u5802\uFF0C\u9996\u5148\uFF0C\u8981\u4E86\u89E3\u6C34\u4ED9\u82B1\u751F\u957F\u7684\u9002\u5B9C\u6E29\u5EA6\u3002\u79D1\u5B66\u8BD5\u9A8C\u8BC1\u660E\u5BF9\u6C34\u4ED9\u7684\u751F\u957F\u6700\u9002\u5B9C\u7684\u5BA4\u6E29\u4E3A?",
		"id":17762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8D75\u6C0F\u5B64\u513F\u300B",
		"indexes":"dybbjsdozqdzggdxqsnb",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u88AB\u4ECB\u7ECD\u5230\u6B27\u6D32\u53BB\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u620F\u66F2\u662F\u54EA\u90E8\uFF1F",
		"id":17763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjmcxtlsngscd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u540D\u8F66\u96EA\u94C1\u9F99\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u751F\u4EA7\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17764
	},
	{
		"answer":"28\u5757",
		"indexes":"z2000nd27jxnalpkydhszgdbdhdldskjp",
		"question":"\u57282000\u5E74\u7B2C27\u5C4A\u6089\u5C3C\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A\u4E0A\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EE3\u8868\u961F\u83B7\u5F97\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5757\u91D1\u724C\uFF1F",
		"id":17765
	},
	{
		"answer":"21",
		"indexes":"shsddhqhsds",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u5E02\u7684\u7535\u8BDD\u533A\u53F7\u662F\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F",
		"id":17766
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5904\u6691",
		"indexes":"zessjqzlqdxygjqssm",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u8282\u6C14\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7ACB\u79CB\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u4E2A\u8282\u6C14\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17767
	},
	{
		"answer":"3800",
		"indexes":"hydpjsdwdsm",
		"question":"\u6D77\u6D0B\u7684\u5E73\u5747\u6DF1\u5EA6\u4E3A\u591A\u5C11\u7C73",
		"id":17768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u7EE7\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"zgtszayhshddymjpdydys",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8DF3\u6C34\u5728\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E0A\u83B7\u5F97\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u91D1\u724C\u7684\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u662F",
		"id":17769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u6CE2\u7F5711\u53F7",
		"indexes":"amstlscngfccgdyd",
		"question":"\u963F\u59C6\u65AF\u7279\u6717\u662F\u4E58\u54EA\u4E2A\u98DE\u8239\u6210\u529F\u767B\u6708\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u7389\u5170",
		"indexes":"shdshssm",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u7684\u5E02\u82B1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":17771
	},
	{
		"answer":"84",
		"indexes":"adqgjtybzzzbdbygydsd",
		"question":"\u6309\u5F53\u524D\u56FD\u9645\u901A\u7528\u6807\u51C6\uFF0C\u7EB8\u5F20\u767D\u5EA6\u4E0D\u5E94\u9AD8\u4E8E\u591A\u5C11\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":17772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5256\u5F00\u7F8A\u809A",
		"indexes":"azmgdfssybxs",
		"question":"\u6309\u7167\u8499\u53E4\u7684\u98CE\u4FD7\uFF0C\u6740\u7F8A\u5FC5\u987B\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5357\u5730\u533A",
		"indexes":"azjrlbfbjsxldqzkkfsnzybzzdds",
		"question":"\u6309\u88C5\u673A\u5BB9\u91CF\u767E\u5206\u6BD4\u8BA1\u7B97\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u5730\u533A\u4E2D\u53EF\u5F00\u53D1\u6C34\u80FD\u8D44\u6E90\u6BD4\u91CD\u6700\u5927\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"d18jsjbznggjjx",
		"question":"\u7B2C18\u5C4A\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E3E\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":17775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5927\u948A",
		"indexes":"zwgzzjsegsygmxcmkszyds",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u4ECB\u7ECD\u4FC4\u56FD\u5341\u6708\u9769\u547D\uFF0C\u5BA3\u4F20\u9A6C\u514B\u601D\u4E3B\u4E49\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357",
		"indexes":"sjtzxsgdrgtsmdzzzx",
		"question":"\u4E16\u7EAA\u575B\u9020\u578B\u662F\u4E2A\u5927\u65E5\u6677\u5B83\u4E0A\u9762\u7684\u6307\u9488\u6307\u5411\uFF1A",
		"id":17777
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u7C73\u5DE6\u53F3",
		"indexes":"lyjssyxwxdjsqcsfwz",
		"question":"\u84DD\u7259\u6280\u672F\u662F\u4E00\u9879\u65E0\u7EBF\u7535\u6280\u672F\u5176\u4F20\u8F93\u8303\u56F4\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":17778
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58A8\u897F\u54E5",
		"indexes":"cjlxlcjbsjbdgjs",
		"question":"\u66FE\u7ECF\u8FDE\u7EED\u4E24\u6B21\u4E3E\u529E\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u5C45\u6613",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrhxsjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u53F7\u9999\u5C71\u5C45\u58EB\uFF1F",
		"id":17780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91",
		"indexes":"xmbsybgds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u5366\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"rwsqyzzdddcznl",
		"question":"\u65E5\u4F2A\u65F6\u671F\u4E9A\u6D32\u6700\u5927\u7684\u7535\u5382\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":17782
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9020\u7EB8\u672F",
		"indexes":"wggddsdfmzzzcxds",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u56DB\u5927\u53D1\u660E\u4E2D\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91C7\u7528\u6A2A\u5237\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"wlycdjkcyzqdsyffsxdzydxlnyzsfscwd",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u7259\u9F7F\u7684\u5065\u5EB7\uFF0C\u91C7\u7528\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u5237\u7259\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F\u76F8\u5F53\u91CD\u8981\u7684\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u8BF4\u6CD5\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u963F\u7518\u6B63\u4F20\u300B",
		"indexes":"wtmhksdecydaskzjnzjjdyps",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u6C64\u59C6\u00B7\u6C49\u514B\u65AF\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u8D62\u5F97\u5965\u65AF\u5361\u6700\u4F73\u7537\u4E3B\u89D2\u5956\u7684\u5F71\u7247\u662F\u2026\u2026",
		"id":17785
	},
	{
		"answer":"GIF",
		"indexes":"jsjtpzksydhxsdtpgssng",
		"question":"\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u56FE\u7247\u4E2D\uFF0C\u53EF\u4F7F\u7528\u52A8\u753B\u5F62\u5F0F\u7684\u56FE\u7247\u683C\u5F0F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":17786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"zgwydjlghdhzdlmz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u552F\u4E00\u7684\u5C06\u4E24\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5408\u846C\u7684\u9675\u5893\u5728",
		"id":17787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u75C5\u6B7B\u5728\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"wjwsymddhjzhdxcs",
		"question":"\u6C6A\u7CBE\u536B\u662F\u6709\u540D\u7684\u5927\u6C49\u5978\uFF0C\u6700\u540E\u7684\u4E0B\u573A\u662F",
		"id":17788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6606\u660E\u6E56",
		"indexes":"wgwzcy",
		"question":"\u738B\u56FD\u7EF4\u81EA\u6C89\u4E8E",
		"id":17789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5B9D\u5609",
		"indexes":"gcxxjdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u5B98\u573A\u73B0\u5F62\u8BB0\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F",
		"id":17790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA",
		"indexes":"wlssjkjbnygfr",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u4F7F\u6C34\u5C3D\u5FEB\u7ED3\u51B0\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\u653E\u5165",
		"id":17791
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u7C73",
		"indexes":"wlyjdjkkdssyzdldsjmys",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u773C\u775B\u7684\u5065\u5EB7\uFF0C\u770B\u7535\u89C6\u65F6\u5E94\u505A\u5230\u79BB\u7535\u89C6\u51E0\u7C73\u4EE5\u4E0A\uFF1F",
		"id":17792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u6D32",
		"indexes":"ymdycdz",
		"question":"\u7389\u7C73\u7684\u539F\u4EA7\u5730\u5728",
		"id":17793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjsdygxqxhclyhg",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u661F\u7403\u534F\u4F1A\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E\u4F55\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":17794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E03\u7565\u300B",
		"indexes":"sjszzdtsflfjzynbs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u56FE\u4E66\u5206\u7C7B\u6CD5\uFF0C\u89C1\u4E4B\u4E8E\u54EA\u672C\u4E66\uFF1F",
		"id":17795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D0\u78B1\u571F",
		"indexes":"zzgbbyhdqdtrglsyglsmtrwz",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u5317\u90E8\u6CBF\u6D77\u5730\u533A\u7684\u571F\u58E4\u6539\u826F\u662F\u4EE5\u6539\u826F\u4EC0\u4E48\u571F\u58E4\u4E3A\u4E3B",
		"id":17796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u594E\u5B81\u4E01",
		"indexes":"wbmfhexymbbcdyps",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u907F\u514D\u98CE\u5316\u800C\u9700\u8981\u5BC6\u95ED\u4FDD\u5B58\u7684\u836F\u54C1\u662F",
		"id":17797
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5408",
		"indexes":"zggdjlrlddwssdsqz1s10d1d10sn1s10",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BA1\u91CF\u5BB9\u91CF\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u5347\u3001\u6597\u3001\u77F3\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D1\u77F3\uFF1D10\u6597\uFF1B1\u6597\uFF1D10\u5347\uFF1B\u90A31\u5347\uFF1D10\uFF1F",
		"id":17798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E29\u5E26\u5927\u9646\u6027\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"sczlyxmjzddqhlxs",
		"question":"\u4E1D\u7EF8\u4E4B\u8DEF\u6CBF\u7EBF\u9762\u79EF\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6C14\u5019\u7C7B\u578B\u662F",
		"id":17799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5FBD\u7701",
		"indexes":"thxwywgngs",
		"question":"\u592A\u6E56\u53BF\u4F4D\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":17800
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u5321\u80E4",
		"indexes":"cqbbssfdd",
		"question":"\u9648\u6865\u5175\u53D8\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u52A8\u7684",
		"id":17801
	},
	{
		"answer":"1919",
		"indexes":"wsydbfynyndwysr",
		"question":"\u4E94\u56DB\u8FD0\u52A8\u7206\u53D1\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7684\u4E94\u6708\u56DB\u65E5",
		"id":17802
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u90A6",
		"indexes":"hgzs",
		"question":"\u6C49\u9AD8\u7956\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17803
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"mczzdgdytsjtd",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u56FD\u90FD\u5E94\u5929\u662F\u4ECA\u5929\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":17804
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8036\u8DEF\u6492\u51B7",
		"indexes":"jdjysljytjdkzscds",
		"question":"\u57FA\u7763\u6559\u3001\u4F0A\u65AF\u5170\u6559\u3001\u72B9\u592A\u6559\u90FD\u770B\u4F5C\u5723\u57CE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u6CB3\u6307\u5E7C\u53D1\u62C9\u5E95\u6CB3\u548C\u5E95\u683C\u91CC\u65AF\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"gylhlydxszqds",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u4E24\u6CB3\u6D41\u57DF\u7684\u53D9\u8FF0\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17806
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DA\u660E",
		"indexes":"dygcwNBAzyxdzgqyss",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6210\u4E3ANBA\u72B6\u5143\u79C0\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17807
	},
	{
		"answer":"199",
		"indexes":"zgzqjAlsksynyn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u7532A\u8054\u8D5B\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":17808
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u679C",
		"indexes":"bcsjssdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u60B2\u60E8\u4E16\u754C\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":17809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152",
		"indexes":"tswcbyycztdsrlbdnyss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u751F\u6211\u6750\u5FC5\u6709\u7528\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u5510\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u54EA\u4E00\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":17810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B97\u6559\u8282\u65E5",
		"indexes":"gebjsyzsmjr",
		"question":"\u201C\u53E4\u5C14\u90A6\u8282\u201D\u662F\u4E00\u79CD\u4EC0\u4E48\u8282\u65E5\uFF1F",
		"id":17811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u9E26",
		"indexes":"zbmydardshzsnzdwczlsjczlrl",
		"question":"\u5728\u5317\u7F8E\u5370\u7B2C\u5B89\u4EBA\u7684\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u521B\u9020\u4E86\u4E16\u754C\uFF0C\u521B\u9020\u4E86\u4EBA\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":17812
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u5B8B",
		"indexes":"ftjssggtdzszddyxzycstzzcxy",
		"question":"\u65B9\u7530\u5747\u7A0E\u662F\u6539\u9769\u571F\u5730\u5F81\u7A0E\u5236\u5EA6\u7684\u4E00\u9879\u91CD\u8981\u63AA\u65BD\uFF0C\u5B83\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E",
		"id":17813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u66E6\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"dckxybsz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E1C\u5E8A\u5FEB\u5A7F\u201D\u539F\u672C\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":17814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA6\u745F\u592B\u00B7\u6D77\u52D2",
		"indexes":"desetjgdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u7B2C\u4E8C\u5341\u4E8C\u6761\u519B\u89C4\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u8C37\u5E73\u539F\u548C\u7EFF\u6D32",
		"indexes":"xyhbftwggnyqzynyqfbz",
		"question":"\u897F\u4E9A\u548C\u5317\u975E\u540C\u4E3A\u704C\u6E89\u519C\u4E1A\uFF0C\u5176\u4E3B\u8981\u519C\u4E1A\u533A\u5206\u5E03\u5728",
		"id":17816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EBD\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"lhgmsczbsz",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u79D8\u4E66\u5904\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728",
		"id":17817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u53E4\u65CF",
		"indexes":"zwwsngmzdwd",
		"question":"\u201C\u76C5\u7897\u821E\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u821E\u8E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE",
		"indexes":"nshfcpdzydbrws",
		"question":"\u5357\u5B8B\u8C6A\u653E\u8BCD\u6D3E\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u4EE3\u8868\u4EBA\u7269\u662F",
		"id":17819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u626C\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"lbszsmhrzglzdglzds",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u8BD7\u4F5C\u300A\u9001\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u4E4B\u5E7F\u9675\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u5E7F\u9675\u6307\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17820
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8D39\u57CE\u6545\u4E8B\u300B",
		"indexes":"tmhkszyg",
		"question":"\u6C64\u59C6-\u6C49\u514B\u65AF\u4E3B\u6F14\u8FC7\uFF1A",
		"id":17821
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E0A\u519C\u300B",
		"indexes":"yxslscqzdyxpznypsjnyzcd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u662F\u300A\u5415\u6C0F\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u4E9B\u7BC7\u7AE0\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u7BC7\u662F\u8BB2\u519C\u4E1A\u653F\u7B56\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17822
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u672B",
		"indexes":"sccxz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u66F9\u201D\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":17823
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687",
		"indexes":"hdzwgjysdzschsy",
		"question":"\u201C\u7687\u5E1D\u201D\u4F5C\u4E3A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5143\u9996\u7684\u6B63\u5F0F\u79F0\u53F7\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":17824
	},
	{
		"answer":"23\u5BF9",
		"indexes":"rtnhydrstsw",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u5185\u542B\u6709\u7684\u67D3\u8272\u4F53\u6570\u4E3A",
		"id":17825
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8033\u987A",
		"indexes":"sselssbhlsssm",
		"question":"\u4E09\u5341\u800C\u7ACB\uFF0C\u56DB\u5341\u4E0D\u60D1\u3002\u516D\u5341\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17826
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50",
		"indexes":"bcdsgcdzngcdtzsjzd",
		"question":"\u5317\u671D\u7684\u56DB\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u7EDF\u6CBB\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u77ED\uFF1F",
		"id":17827
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u6C49",
		"indexes":"zzssngcdfmd",
		"question":"\u9020\u7EB8\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u53D1\u660E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17828
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u5C14\u6EE8",
		"indexes":"wgngcsybdzm",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4EE5\u51B0\u96D5\u8457\u540D\uFF1F",
		"id":17829
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"slyyngyy",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C99\u9F99\u201D\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u56FD\u8BED\u8A00\uFF1F",
		"id":17830
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E95\u90E8",
		"indexes":"tkcdsdckwlygckzn",
		"question":"\u5766\u514B\u9664\u9876\u4E0A\u7684\u51FA\u53E3\u5916\uFF0C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u51FA\u53E3\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":17831
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xdalpkydcsrpaedgbds",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4EE3\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u8FD0\u52A8\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u76AE\u57C3\u5C14\u00B7\u5FB7\u00B7\u987E\u62DC\u65E6\u662F",
		"id":17832
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u71C3",
		"indexes":"mjtcssdghshxzdsmxx",
		"question":"\u6C11\u95F4\u901A\u5E38\u6240\u8BF4\u7684\u9B3C\u706B\u662F\u5316\u5B66\u4E2D\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u73B0\u8C61",
		"id":17833
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u897F\u9AD8\u539F",
		"indexes":"sjzddgysyxnyg",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u5927\u7684\u9AD8\u539F\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":17834
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u864E",
		"indexes":"gdrcddcssm",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u4EBA\u79F0\u7684\u201C\u5927\u866B\u201D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17835
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"wmsxdmqjsyzynggj",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u719F\u6089\u7684\u6BCD\u4EB2\u8282\u662F\u6E90\u81EA\u4E0E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":17836
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8F7C",
		"indexes":"bzbsswyddzgcjdzjs",
		"question":"\u6807\u5FD7\u5317\u5B8B\u8BD7\u6587\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u6210\u5C31\u7684\u4F5C\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":17837
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u7248\u81EA\u7531",
		"indexes":"xlxxznyxbsyxfsgddgmdwhql",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u9009\u9879\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BAA\u6CD5\u6240\u89C4\u5B9A\u7684\u516C\u6C11\u7684\u6587\u5316\u6743\u5229?",
		"id":17838
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D",
		"indexes":"kgjjzzwcjkycgsjgdkjg",
		"question":"\u300A\u8003\u5DE5\u8BB0\u300B\u8BB0\u8F7D\u5468\u738B\u57CE\u8857\u5BBD\u4EE5\u8F66\u8F68\u6570\u8BA1,\u5E72\u9053\u5BBD\u51E0\u8F68\uFF1F",
		"id":17839
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E14\u4ECB\u4EAD\u6742\u6587\u300B",
		"indexes":"lxdzqzwjs",
		"question":"\u9C81\u8FC5\u7684\u65E9\u671F\u6742\u6587\u96C6\u662F",
		"id":17840
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u4E16\u7EAA20\u5E74\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"djxycsynynd",
		"question":"\u72EC\u89D2\u620F\u7EA6\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":17841
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u5170",
		"indexes":"sjyyngrfm",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u8BED\u7531\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u53D1\u660E",
		"id":17842
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7FFC\u300B",
		"indexes":"dyjaskzjypdmcw",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u5965\u65AF\u5361\u6700\u4F73\u5F71\u7247\u7684\u540D\u79F0\u4E3A",
		"id":17843
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u65A42\u4E24",
		"indexes":"zytptcrcdmkdgxymx",
		"question":"\u7EC7\u4E00\u6761\u666E\u901A\u6210\u4EBA\u7A7F\u7684\u6BDB\u88E4\u5927\u6982\u9700\u7528\u6BDB\u7EBF",
		"id":17844
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9EA6\u7684\u5B89\u5F92\u751F",
		"indexes":"hddxzdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u65B0\u88C5\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17845
	},
	{
		"answer":"112",
		"indexes":"yxcyjzdhnygsgzdh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5E38\u7528\u6551\u52A9\u7535\u8BDD\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6545\u969C\u7535\u8BDD\uFF1A",
		"id":17846
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u91D1\u5229\u5C71",
		"indexes":"bmdzgfs",
		"question":"\u5317\u7F8E\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u5CF0\u662F",
		"id":17847
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72FC",
		"indexes":"qdfyzdmhssmdw",
		"question":"\u9752\u5C9B\u65B9\u8A00\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u9A6C\u864E\u201D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":17848
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"wxjjbezksngr",
		"question":"\u6587\u5B66\u5DE8\u5320\u5DF4\u5C14\u624E\u514B\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":17849
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u72C2\u4EBA\u65E5\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"lxfbddypbhxss",
		"question":"\u9C81\u8FC5\u53D1\u8868\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u7BC7\u767D\u8BDD\u5C0F\u8BF4\u662F",
		"id":17850
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5730\u7384\u9EC4",
		"indexes":"qzwddyjs",
		"question":"\u5343\u5B57\u6587\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17851
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E92\u52A9\u539F\u5219\u7684\u8981\u6C42",
		"indexes":"yrynzrxbyfynbfzyzsrjjwz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\u4EBA\u6709\u96BE\uFF0C\u4F17\u4EBA\u76F8\u5E2E\uFF1B\u4E00\u65B9\u6709\u96BE\uFF0C\u516B\u65B9\u652F\u63F4\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u662F\u4EBA\u9645\u4EA4\u5F80\u4E2D",
		"id":17852
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CC\u6D77",
		"indexes":"sjszddnlhssmh",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u5185\u9646\u6E56\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6E56\uFF1F",
		"id":17853
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u7403\u5230\u592A\u9633\u7684\u8DDD\u79BB",
		"indexes":"ygtwdwsz",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u5929\u6587\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":17854
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9676\u6E0A\u660E",
		"indexes":"wgwxssdygdlxtysdsrs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6587\u5B66\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5927\u91CF\u5199\u7530\u56ED\u8BD7\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17855
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\/3\u5904",
		"indexes":"jbqsbqzxjdjlgd",
		"question":"\u964D\u534A\u65D7\u662F\u628A\u65D7\u5B50\u4E0B\u964D\u5230\u8DDD\u79BB\u6746\u9876",
		"id":17856
	},
	{
		"answer":"206",
		"indexes":"rssgydskgt",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u8EAB\u4E0A\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5757\u9AA8\u5934?",
		"id":17857
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4EA4\u54CD\u4E50\u4E4B\u7236\u201D\u7684\u662F\u5DF4\u8D6B",
		"indexes":"dxlyljdpsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6\u7684\u8BC4\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17858
	},
	{
		"answer":"17\u300118\u4E16\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"ozcxblklkkyssz",
		"question":"\u6B27\u6D32\u51FA\u73B0\u5DF4\u7F57\u514B\u3001\u6D1B\u53EF\u53EF\u827A\u672F\u662F\u5728",
		"id":17859
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u9646\u5728\u6D77\u5E95\u7684\u5EF6\u4F38",
		"indexes":"dljssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u9646\u67B6\u201D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17860
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u5F15",
		"indexes":"nbccmtwsm",
		"question":"\u5357\u5317\u671D\u79F0\u9762\u6761\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17861
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u6839\u5EF7",
		"indexes":"1916nmzbgjs",
		"question":"1916\u5E74\u7F8E\u6D32\u676F\u51A0\u519B\u662F",
		"id":17862
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u957F\u6625",
		"indexes":"dsjayhzgdbtg6rcjdydyjyrzgrs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u5341\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EE3\u8868\u56E2\u51716\u4EBA\u53C2\u52A0\uFF0C\u4F46\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u4EC5\u4E00\u4EBA\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E2A\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17863
	},
	{
		"answer":"70\u591A\u5EA7",
		"indexes":"gajgwcxjdddxxdjztgy",
		"question":"\u53E4\u57C3\u53CA\u5404\u738B\u671D\u4FEE\u5EFA\u7684\u5927\u5927\u5C0F\u5C0F\u7684\u91D1\u5B57\u5854\u5171\u6709",
		"id":17864
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B83\u7684\u8F6E\u5ED3\u6709\u70B9\u8C61\u6C49\u5B57\u201C\u91D1\u201D\u5B57",
		"indexes":"wmbgajflfmjzjztdyys",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u628A\u53E4\u57C3\u53CA\u6CD5\u8001\u575F\u5893\u53EB\u505A\u201C\u91D1\u5B57\u5854\u201D\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u662F",
		"id":17865
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F24\u5BB3\u7F6A",
		"indexes":"zggddzmzxdyxdd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u7F6A\u540D\u201C\u8D3C\u201D\u76F8\u5F53\u4E8E\u73B0\u4EE3\u7684",
		"id":17866
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC\u3001\u897F\u5B89\u3001\u5357\u4EAC\u3001\u676D\u5DDE\u3001\u6D1B\u9633\u3001\u5F00\u5C01",
		"indexes":"zgdldgdsng",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u516D\u5927\u53E4\u90FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A",
		"id":17867
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E7F\u7279\u4E39",
		"indexes":"sjzddhgw",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6D77\u6E2F\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":17868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9655\u897F\u5B9D\u9E21",
		"indexes":"mxzdadcczdccszxzd",
		"question":"\u201C\u660E\u4FEE\u6808\u9053\uFF0C\u6697\u6E21\u9648\u4ED3\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u9648\u4ED3\u662F\u6307\u73B0\u5728\u7684",
		"id":17869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u79CD",
		"indexes":"tqdbzccydsz",
		"question":"\u56E2\u65D7\u7684\u6807\u51C6\u5C3A\u5BF8\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u79CD",
		"id":17870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u7CAE\u5317\u8C03\u4F9B\u5E94\u5927\u90FD",
		"indexes":"yckzstdyhdzjmds",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u5F00\u51FF\u758F\u901A\u5927\u8FD0\u6CB3\u7684\u76F4\u63A5\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u9AA8\u6587\u8BB0\u8F7D\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\u6709\u4E9B\u4E0E\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\u76F8\u5370\u8BC1",
		"indexes":"wgywzkkdxsscscksdsyw",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6709\u6587\u5B57\u53EF\u8003\u7684\u4FE1\u53F2\u662F\u4ECE\u5546\u671D\u5F00\u59CB\u7684\uFF0C\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A",
		"id":17872
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u4E86\u51B6\u94C1\u7684\u8D28\u91CF",
		"indexes":"dhsqzscssyspdjbyyzy",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u65F6\u671F\u5728\u751F\u4EA7\u4E0A\u4F7F\u7528\u201C\u6C34\u6392\u201D\u7684\u8FDB\u6B65\u610F\u4E49\u5728\u4E8E",
		"id":17873
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793C\u90E8\u2192\u603B\u7406\u8859\u95E8\u2192\u5916\u4EA4\u90E8",
		"indexes":"qczwwjswdjgycxzqdyzw",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u638C\u63E1\u5916\u4EA4\u4E8B\u52A1\u7684\u673A\u6784\uFF0C\u4F9D\u6B21\u5E8F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u7EC4\u4E3A",
		"id":17874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D\u5185\u5730\u5175\u529B\u7A7A\u865A",
		"indexes":"755nalsplnghkgzlyzadzyyys",
		"question":"755\u5E74,\u5B89\u7984\u5C71\u53DB\u4E71\u80FD\u591F\u5F88\u5FEB\u653B\u5360\u6D1B\u9633\u3001\u957F\u5B89\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u56E0\u662F",
		"id":17875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5357\u6FEE\u9633",
		"indexes":"cyzmdydddczsjtd",
		"question":"\u201C\u6FB6\u6E0A\u4E4B\u76DF\u201D\u7684\u8BAE\u5B9A\u5730\u70B9\u6FB6\u5DDE\u662F\u4ECA\u5929\u7684",
		"id":17876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BAB\u57CE\u3001\u7687\u57CE\u3001\u4EAC\u57CE",
		"indexes":"mcbjcyldwdsxs",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u5317\u4EAC\u57CE\u7531\u91CC\u5230\u5916\u7684\u987A\u5E8F\u662F",
		"id":17877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEE\u6CB3\u4EE5\u5317",
		"indexes":"lzcjlddszqkzdnbdqzydd",
		"question":"\u674E\u81EA\u6210\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684\u5927\u987A\u653F\u6743\u63A7\u5236\u7684\u5357\u90E8\u5730\u533A\u6700\u8FDC\u5230\u8FBE",
		"id":17878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5974\u96B6\u4E3B\u8D35\u65CF",
		"indexes":"cqsqzzdfjdzsnxrzheld",
		"question":"\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5C01\u5EFA\u5730\u4E3B\u662F\u54EA\u4E9B\u4EBA\u8F6C\u5316\u800C\u6765\u7684?",
		"id":17879
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236\u74F7\u4E1A",
		"indexes":"zgsqhmycxdsgxys",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u8FD8\u6CA1\u6709\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\u624B\u5DE5\u884C\u4E1A\u662F",
		"id":17880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u6587\u5E1D\u4E0E\u6B66\u5219\u5929",
		"indexes":"stsqtcfjgjmydtzzs",
		"question":"\u968B\u5510\u65F6\u671F,\u63A8\u5D07\u4F5B\u6559\u5E7F\u5EFA\u5E99\u5B87\u7684\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u662F",
		"id":17881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u632A\u5A01\u519B\u961F",
		"indexes":"xlgjjdzzdecsjdzcqkjdgrqsjzzds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u56FD\u5BB6\u519B\u961F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5728\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u521D\u671F\u6297\u51FB\u5FB7\u56FD\u5165\u4FB5\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u957F\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u5B8B",
		"indexes":"wgmhdzzcgdfjkzdhhlysz",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u68C9\u82B1\u7684\u79CD\u690D\u4ECE\u5E7F\u4E1C\u3001\u798F\u5EFA\u6269\u5C55\u5230\u6DEE\u6CB3\u6D41\u57DF\u662F\u5728",
		"id":17883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u589E\u52A0\u8D22\u653F\u6536\u5165",
		"indexes":"wasbfdzjmds",
		"question":"\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u7684\u76F4\u63A5\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u65B9\u7EA21\u53F7",
		"indexes":"wgdykrzdqwxj",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9897\u4EBA\u9020\u5730\u7403\u536B\u661F\u53EB",
		"id":17885
	},
	{
		"answer":"96\uFF0D99\uFF05",
		"indexes":"syzthqdhlz",
		"question":"\u77F3\u6CB9\u4E2D\u78B3\u548C\u6C22\u7684\u542B\u91CF\u5360\uFF1A",
		"id":17886
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7164\u6CB9",
		"indexes":"mhpqfjsyrlw",
		"question":"\u6C11\u822A\u55B7\u6C14\u98DE\u673A\u4F7F\u7528\u71C3\u6599\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":17887
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A74",
		"indexes":"zmhjhzzszhsmdw",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u9EC4\u80C4\u6700\u64C5\u957F\u753B\u4EC0\u4E48\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":17888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u5143\u57F9",
		"indexes":"zhmgdyrjyzzs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u534E\u6C11\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u6559\u80B2\u603B\u957F\u662F",
		"id":17889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u624E\u7279",
		"indexes":"fjldhlsszq",
		"question":"\u300A\u8D39\u52A0\u7F57\u7684\u5A5A\u793C\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u4F5C\u66F2\uFF1F",
		"id":17890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u671D",
		"indexes":"jdzcyssy",
		"question":"\u666F\u5FB7\u9547\u74F7\u7A91\u59CB\u70E7\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":17891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A1A\u9F84\u671F",
		"indexes":"yxsjet13sdjdcw",
		"question":"\u533B\u5B66\u4E0A\u5C06\u513F\u7AE51\uFF5E3\u5C81\u7684\u9636\u6BB5\u79F0\u4E3A",
		"id":17892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u677E",
		"indexes":"sdmzlylwxztmfbsxyjzdswkhshczd",
		"question":"\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u8457\u91CC\u6709\u4E24\u4F4D\u884C\u8005\uFF0C\u5B83\u4EEC\u5206\u522B\u662F\u300A\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u5B59\u609F\u7A7A\u548C\u300A\u6C34\u6D52\u4F20\u300B\u4E2D\u7684",
		"id":17893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E2D\u5B50",
		"indexes":"yxdwzcjzjdswcsys",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u52A8\u7269\u4E2D\u6625\u5B63\u6700\u4F73\u7684\u6C34\u6E29\u6D4B\u8BD5\u5458\u662F",
		"id":17894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgnxhmksysmsh",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5973\u6027\u753B\u7709\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019",
		"id":17895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u57CE",
		"indexes":"czdjcssm",
		"question":"\u6F6E\u5DDE\u7684\u7B80\u79F0\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5361\u6587\u8FEA\u8BB8",
		"indexes":"szxccylclG",
		"question":"\u8C01\u6700\u5148\u6D4B\u51FA\u5F15\u529B\u5E38\u91CFG",
		"id":17897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B57\u8282",
		"indexes":"zjsjzxxccdzxdwssm",
		"question":"\u5728\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u4E2D\u4FE1\u606F\u5B58\u50A8\u7684\u6700\u5C0F\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u81F3",
		"indexes":"zgmjddjjscnytksd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u95F4\u7684\u201C\u51AC\u4E5D\u4E5D\u201D\u662F\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5929\u5F00\u59CB\u7684",
		"id":17899
	},
	{
		"answer":"5\u30016\u70B9",
		"indexes":"wgdysjdz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u66F4\u201D\u5927\u7EA6\u662F\u51E0\u70B9\u949F\uFF1F",
		"id":17900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57C3\u53CA",
		"indexes":"sjssxwmcxzzddqs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6570\u5B66\u6587\u660E\u51FA\u73B0\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5730\u533A\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17901
	},
	{
		"answer":"1958",
		"indexes":"wgszdjnyzcdytjsjd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u662F\u5728\u7B2C\u51E0\u5E74\u7814\u5236\u51FA\u7B2C\u4E00\u53F0\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17902
	},
	{
		"answer":"RAM\u5B58\u50A8\u5668",
		"indexes":"qddyhjsjsyxxdsdccqssm",
		"question":"\u5207\u65AD\u7535\u6E90\u540E\uFF0C\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u6240\u6709\u4FE1\u606F\u4E22\u5931\u7684\u5B58\u50A8\u5668\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"gdsdedjssm",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u4E1C\u7701\u7B2C\u4E8C\u5927\u6C5F\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":17904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7267\u91CE\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"zxllssjzdzwcgtds",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E0B\u5217\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5BFC\u81F4\u738B\u671D\u66F4\u66FF\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17905
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u5927\u6797\u683C\u52D2\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"decsjdzdzdzzds",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u7684\u91CD\u5927\u8F6C\u6298\u70B9\u662F",
		"id":17906
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u6CD5\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"jdsscxzgbbebjjdzzs",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u53F2\u4E0A\uFF0C\u51FA\u73B0\u201C\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E0D\u8D25\u800C\u8D25\u201D\u7ED3\u5C40\u7684\u6218\u4E89\u662F",
		"id":17907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519C\u6C11\u9769\u547D\u9886\u8896",
		"indexes":"jdsszztczzgfzzbzyfads",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u53F2\u4E0A\uFF0C\u6700\u65E9\u63D0\u51FA\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u53D1\u5C55\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u65B9\u6848\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17908
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u5EF7\u9534\u3001\u848B\u5149\u9F10",
		"indexes":"yebsbzlsjljzshkjrjqlds",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\uFF0E\u4E8C\u516B\u201D\u4E8B\u53D8\u4E2D\u7387\u5341\u4E5D\u8DEF\u519B\u5728\u4E0A\u6D77\u6297\u51FB\u65E5\u519B\u4FB5\u7565\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u578B\u5173\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"qmkzbfhzgjdscqdsldzys",
		"question":"\u5168\u9762\u6297\u6218\u7206\u53D1\u540E\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u519B\u961F\u9996\u6B21\u53D6\u5F97\u80DC\u5229\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F",
		"id":17910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E1D\u56FD\u4E3B\u4E49\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"dycsjdzsyc",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u662F\u4E00\u573A",
		"id":17911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u8F7B\u5973\u5B50",
		"indexes":"jjzhdsz",
		"question":"\u4EAC\u5267\u4E2D\u82B1\u65E6\u662F\u6307",
		"id":17912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u901A\u8FC7\u5723\u5E93\u5236\u5EA6\u5E73\u5747\u5206\u914D\u6240\u6709\u519C\u526F\u4EA7\u54C1",
		"indexes":"tctmzdjyjdpjzyxzywtgd",
		"question":"\u300A\u5929\u671D\u7530\u4EA9\u5236\u5EA6\u300B\u5177\u6709\u7EDD\u5BF9\u5E73\u5747\u4E3B\u4E49\u6027\u8D28\uFF0C\u56E0\u4E3A\u5B83\u89C4\u5B9A",
		"id":17913
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u5149\u8363\u9769\u547D\u201D",
		"indexes":"ygzcjjgmjsdbzs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u7ED3\u675F\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":17914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BFA\u66FC\u5E95\u767B\u9646",
		"indexes":"decsjdzhqsdjxrsjhymmjjjzdjsxds",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540E\u671F\uFF0C\u4F7F\u5FB7\u519B\u9677\u5165\u82CF\u519B\u548C\u82F1\u7F8E\u76DF\u519B\u5939\u51FB\u4E2D\u7684\u519B\u4E8B\u884C\u52A8\u662F",
		"id":17915
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3A\u8FD1\u4EE3\u5316\u626B\u9664\u969C\u788D",
		"indexes":"19sjzydgrzsexdwclfgrcjzxesqdszgsdszs",
		"question":"19\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E2D\u53F6\uFF0C\u5FB7\u56FD\u4EBA\u81EA\u4E0A\u800C\u4E0B\u5730\u5B8C\u6210\u4E86\u6CD5\u56FD\u4EBA\u66FE\u7ECF\u201C\u81EA\u4E0B\u800C\u4E0A\u5343\u7684\u4E8B\u201D\u3002\u8FD9\u4E2A\u201C\u4E8B\u201D\u7684\u5B9E\u8D28\u662F",
		"id":17916
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u9633\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zbjrzhsddrzqshzzjlydysrqs",
		"question":"\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u4EBA\u4E4B\u540E\u3001\u5C71\u9876\u6D1E\u4EBA\u4E4B\u524D\uFF0C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u957F\u6C5F\u6D41\u57DF\u7684\u539F\u59CB\u4EBA\u7FA4\u662F",
		"id":17917
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8\u7B2C",
		"indexes":"wjnbcsqszxszztqdyjs",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u664B\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u58EB\u65CF\u4EAB\u53D7\u653F\u6CBB\u7279\u6743\u7684\u4F9D\u636E\u662F",
		"id":17918
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u9016\u5317\u4F10",
		"indexes":"cyzljjyxlnysjyg",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u4E2D\u6D41\u51FB\u696B\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E8B\u4EF6\u6709\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":17919
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u5348\u4E2D\u65E5\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"dgzygjkszzgdgmtzscsznczzzh",
		"question":"\u5E1D\u56FD\u4E3B\u4E49\u56FD\u5BB6\u5F00\u59CB\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u6295\u8D44\u8BBE\u5382\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u6B21\u6218\u4E89\u4E4B\u540E\uFF1F",
		"id":17920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6536\u517B\u5408\u540C",
		"indexes":"xlhtzbsyhtfds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5408\u540C\u4E2D\u4E0D\u9002\u7528\u5408\u540C\u6CD5\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BBE\u7ACB\u5382\u536B\u7279\u52A1\u673A\u6784",
		"indexes":"mcjqzztzdcszyhlhgzqyzjgxds",
		"question":"\u660E\u521D\u52A0\u5F3A\u4E13\u5236\u7EDF\u6CBB\u7684\u63AA\u65BD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0E\u540E\u6765\u5BA6\u5B98\u4E13\u6743\u6709\u76F4\u63A5\u5173\u7CFB\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17922
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9547\u538B\u5FB7\u56FD\u5171\u4EA7\u515A",
		"indexes":"1933n2ydgfxszzghzhadqts",
		"question":"1933\u5E742\u6708\uFF0C\u5FB7\u56FD\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u5236\u9020\u201C\u56FD\u4F1A\u7EB5\u706B\u6848\u201D\u7684\u4F01\u56FE\u662F",
		"id":17923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u5229\u65F6",
		"indexes":"19sjmqdlgqzhktldljyqds",
		"question":"19\u4E16\u7EAA\u672B\uFF0C\u53D6\u5F97\u5362\u6C9F\u6865\u81F3\u6C49\u53E3\u94C1\u8DEF\u4EE3\u7406\u7ECF\u8425\u6743\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17924
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236\u9020\u9676\u5668",
		"indexes":"bprhhmdrshdgtds",
		"question":"\u534A\u5761\u4EBA\u548C\u6CB3\u59C6\u6E21\u4EBA\u751F\u6D3B\u7684\u5171\u540C\u70B9\u662F",
		"id":17925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8981\u6C42\u9769\u65B0\u56FE\u5F3A",
		"indexes":"qybcwlfdzyyys",
		"question":"\u5C48\u539F\u88AB\u695A\u738B\u6D41\u653E\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u56E0\u662F",
		"id":17926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u5348\u4E2D\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u4EE5\u540E",
		"indexes":"zgmzzydcbfzsz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u65CF\u4E3B\u4E49\u7684\u521D\u6B65\u53D1\u5C55\u662F\u5728",
		"id":17927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u57DF\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C",
		"indexes":"zyzfgxymghygyxtsnbdqzzdxzjsjgs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u592E\u653F\u5E9C\u7BA1\u8F96\u7389\u95E8\u5173\u548C\u9633\u5173\u4EE5\u897F\u3001\u5929\u5C71\u5357\u5317\u5730\u533A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u884C\u653F\u3001\u519B\u4E8B\u673A\u6784\u662F",
		"id":17928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u901A\u60E0\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"yccylxzbdydhds",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u6F15\u8FD0\u8DEF\u7EBF\u6700\u5317\u7684\u4E00\u6BB5\u6CB3\u9053\u662F",
		"id":17929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u664B\u5180\u8C6B\u3001\u664B\u7EE5\u3001\u664B\u5BDF\u5180",
		"indexes":"btdzzzqysjdzykrgjds",
		"question":"\u767E\u56E2\u5927\u6218\u4F5C\u6218\u533A\u57DF\u6D89\u53CA\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u6297\u65E5\u6839\u636E\u5730\u662F",
		"id":17930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF2\u610F\u8BC6\u5230\u4F7F\u56FD\u5BB6\u6446\u8131\u843D\u540E\u8FFD\u8D76\u5148\u8FDB\u7684\u5FC5\u8981\u6027",
		"indexes":"18sjch1861neglcddggdsyshtxdzbmtm",
		"question":"18\u4E16\u7EAA\u521D\u548C1861\u5E74\u4FC4\u56FD\u4E24\u6B21\u5927\u7684\u6539\u9769\u90FD\u662F\u7531\u6C99\u7687\u63A8\u884C\u7684\uFF0C\u8FD9\u8868\u660E\u4ED6\u4EEC",
		"id":17931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u5730",
		"indexes":"ydfblbhzyddldrs",
		"question":"\u5370\u5EA6\u975E\u66B4\u529B\u4E0D\u5408\u4F5C\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":17932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6743\u5206\u7ACB\u5B66\u8BF4",
		"indexes":"zmdzcjjqmsxjmdsjtc",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u542F\u8499\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u5B5F\u5FB7\u65AF\u9E20\u63D0\u5021",
		"id":17933
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5141\u8BB8\u65E5\u672C\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u6295\u8D44\u5EFA\u7B51\u94C1\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"xlbsymgtynrds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u9A6C\u5173\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\u5185\u5BB9\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u5E73\u5171\u5904\u4E94\u9879\u539F\u5219\u7684\u63D0\u51FA",
		"indexes":"xzgwjzccsdbzs",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u5916\u4EA4\u653F\u7B56\u6210\u719F\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":17935
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"ozzbzymyzxcsy",
		"question":"\u6B27\u6D32\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u840C\u82BD\u6700\u5148\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E",
		"id":17936
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u6587\u4E3B\u4E49",
		"indexes":"wyfxsqzydshscs",
		"question":"\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u4E3B\u8981\u7684\u793E\u4F1A\u601D\u6F6E\u662F",
		"id":17937
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u4E16\u7EAA\u65E9\u671F",
		"indexes":"nlmyflzzksy",
		"question":"\u5974\u96B6\u8D38\u6613\u6CDB\u6EE5\u6700\u65E9\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":17938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666E\u5217\u6C49\u8BFA\u592B",
		"indexes":"19sj80ndkszegcbmkszyds",
		"question":"19\u4E16\u7EAA80\u5E74\u4EE3\u5F00\u59CB\u5728\u4FC4\u56FD\u4F20\u64AD\u9A6C\u514B\u601D\u4E3B\u4E49\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u573A\u624B\u5DE5\u4E1A",
		"indexes":"16sjd18sjxbqozgysczzdjbxss",
		"question":"16\u4E16\u7EAA\u523018\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E0B\u534A\u671F\uFF0C\u6B27\u6D32\u5DE5\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7EC4\u7EC7\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u5F62\u5F0F\u662F",
		"id":17940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u5929",
		"indexes":"tyzsmshjwmzj",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8DDD\u6211\u4EEC\u6700\u8FD1\uFF1F",
		"id":17941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE9\u56FA\u548C\u52A0\u5F3A\u521A\u521A\u7EDF\u4E00\u7684\u5FB7\u610F\u5FD7\u5E1D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"dgsxbsmtxfshzyfcfdzymds",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u9996\u76F8\u4FFE\u65AF\u9EA6\u63A8\u884C\u53CD\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u201C\u975E\u5E38\u6CD5\u201D\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u4E16\u6C11",
		"indexes":"qlsemlqqyzzemssjsd",
		"question":"\u5343\u91CC\u9001\u9E45\u6BDB,\u793C\u8F7B\u60C5\u610F\u91CD.\u8FD9\u9E45\u6BDB\u662F\u9001\u7ED9\u8C01\u7684",
		"id":17943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D8A\u91CD\u8D8A\u80FD\u98DE",
		"indexes":"yqxxxdhnyb",
		"question":"\u6709\u8FC1\u5F99\u4E60\u6027\u7684\u5019\u9E1F\u4E00\u822C\uFF1A",
		"id":17944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199",
		"indexes":"qdnbctysznghdsq",
		"question":"\u7B7E\u5B9A\u300A\u5C3C\u5E03\u695A\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1A",
		"id":17945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C9C\u5351\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nbcsqdymmgclgcz",
		"question":"\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4F18\u7F8E\u6C11\u6B4C\u300A\u6555\u52D2\u6B4C\u300B\u51FA\u81EA",
		"id":17946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u6539\u9020\u7684\u5B8C\u6210",
		"indexes":"wgksjrshzycjjddbzs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5F00\u59CB\u8FDB\u5165\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u521D\u7EA7\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":17947
	},
	{
		"answer":"1919\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wsydbfynyndwysr",
		"question":"\u4E94\u56DB\u8FD0\u52A8\u7206\u53D1\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7684\u4E94\u6708\u56DB\u65E5\uFF1A",
		"id":17948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67FF\u5B50",
		"indexes":"sywgtcds",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7279\u4EA7\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u5C0F\u65F6",
		"indexes":"hmccqfzszmg35fzdsmhxyczznqf",
		"question":"\u6CB3\u9A6C\u5E38\u5E38\u6F5C\u4F0F\u5728\u6C34\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6BCF\u96943\u20145\u5206\u949F\u5230\u6C34\u9762\u547C\u5438\u4E00\u6B21\uFF0C\u6700\u957F\u80FD\u6F5C\u4F0F",
		"id":17950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u652F\u6301\u6839",
		"indexes":"ymjjbcsdgsy",
		"question":"\u7389\u7C73\u830E\u57FA\u90E8\u4EA7\u751F\u7684\u6839\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":17951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u6D25",
		"indexes":"gblbzdycdsnl",
		"question":"\u72D7\u4E0D\u7406\u5305\u5B50\u7684\u539F\u4EA7\u5730\u662F\u54EA\u91CC:",
		"id":17952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u540E",
		"indexes":"pkpsdQdbsm",
		"question":"\u6251\u514B\u724C\u4E0A\u7684Q\u4EE3\u8868\u4EC0\u4E48:",
		"id":17953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"wgngcsdyhszym",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u7684\u96E8\u82B1\u77F3\u6700\u6709\u540D",
		"id":17954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u9707",
		"indexes":"hxybsysmyqd",
		"question":"\u6D77\u5578\u4E00\u822C\u662F\u7531\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F15\u8D77\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC",
		"indexes":"wdssdjdsysmczzc",
		"question":"\u6B66\u5F53\u5C71\u4E0A\u7684\u201C\u91D1\u9876\u201D\u662F\u7531\u4EC0\u4E48\u6750\u8D28\u5236\u6210\uFF1F",
		"id":17956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u9F84\u672A\u5A5A\u8005",
		"indexes":"rmxcsmrswlw",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u620F\u79F0\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EBA\u662F\u201C\u738B\u8001\u4E94\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":17957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BA1\u7B97\u65F6\u95F4",
		"indexes":"gddthdlyy",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u94DC\u58F6\u6EF4\u6F0F\u7528\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":17958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C7D\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xmnzylyyddcmzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u79CD\u996E\u6599\u6709\u4E00\u5B9A\u7684\u50AC\u7720\u4F5C\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":17959
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5410\u9C81\u756A",
		"indexes":"wgfnzclyw16yqwqzklywsfzywgdfkz",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u98CE\u80FD\u603B\u50A8\u91CF\u7EA6\u4E3A16\u4EBF\u5343\u74E6\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u53EF\u5229\u7528\u4E3A\u5341\u5206\u4E4B\u4E00\u3002\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u98CE\u5E93\u5728",
		"id":17960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8861\u9633",
		"indexes":"sjzjhnddedcss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E4B\u4EA4\uFF0C\u6E56\u5357\u7684\u7B2C\u4E8C\u5927\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u957F\u57CE",
		"indexes":"kcdssjzzqjsmblswcqfdhdgccscddyhwzwdxds",
		"question":"\u582A\u79F0\u5F53\u65F6\u4E16\u754C\u4E4B\u6700\uFF0C\u5374\u52A0\u901F\u6C11\u4E0D\u804A\u751F\u3001\u738B\u671D\u503E\u8986\u7684\u5B8F\u5927\u5DE5\u7A0B\uFF0C\u9664\u968B\u671D\u7684\u5927\u8FD0\u6CB3\u5916\uFF0C\u6700\u4E3A\u5178\u578B\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"mxbtdzzsks",
		"question":"\u300A\u68A6\u6EAA\u7B14\u8C08\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u6C88\u62EC\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u996D\u540E",
		"indexes":"zxhdywyzsmshfy",
		"question":"\u52A9\u6D88\u5316\u7684\u836F\u7269\u5E94\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u670D\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":17964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D59\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"fszysjfdzcmhwnjbyrzcwklfmqzlfkclzsjnclzqgnzdtzwgdngsm",
		"question":"\u77FE\u5C71\u9547\uFF0C\u6709'\u4E16\u754C\u77FE\u90FD'\u4E4B\u79F0\u3002\u660E\u6D2A\u6B66\u5E74\u95F4\uFF0C\u4FBF\u6709\u4EBA\u5728\u6B64\u6316\u77FF\u70BC\u77FE\u3002\u76EE\u524D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u91CC\u77FE\u77FF\u50A8\u91CF\u5360\u4E16\u754C\uFF16\uFF10\uFF05\uFF0C\u5E74\u4EA7\u91CF\u5360\u5168\u56FD\uFF17\uFF10\uFF05\u3002\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u5B83\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u90A3\u4E2A\u7701\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":17965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57F9\u6839",
		"indexes":"zsjsllssdmy",
		"question":"\u201C\u77E5\u8BC6\u5C31\u662F\u529B\u91CF\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u540D\u8A00\uFF1F",
		"id":17966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8910\u85FB",
		"indexes":"wmpccdhdsy",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u5E73\u5E38\u5403\u7684\u6D77\u5E26\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":17967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u79CD\u8718\u86DB",
		"indexes":"xxlwsbscgjyrxxhgfdshhgfsz",
		"question":"\u65B0\u897F\u5170\u536B\u751F\u90E8\u65F6\u5E38\u544A\u8BEB\u6E38\u4EBA\u5C0F\u5FC3\u201C\u9ED1\u5BE1\u5987\u201D\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\uFF0C\u201C\u9ED1\u5BE1\u5987\u201D\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":17968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4E9A\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"amdxyqjsmdx",
		"question":"\u6FB3\u95E8\u5927\u5B66\u4EE5\u524D\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\u5927\u5B66\uFF1F",
		"id":17969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"jwzzszghnyggjjz",
		"question":"\u7532\u5348\u6218\u4E89\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u548C\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EA4\u6218\uFF1F",
		"id":17970
	},
	{
		"answer":"1996\u5E7410\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zhrmghglnrqybzfyhnhyhrkssx",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u8001\u5E74\u4EBA\u6743\u76CA\u4FDD\u969C\u6CD5\u300B\u4E8E\u4F55\u5E74\u4F55\u6708\u4F55\u65E5\u5F00\u59CB\u65BD\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":17971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"klOKxqyng",
		"question":"'\u5361\u62C9OK'\u5174\u8D77\u4E8E\u54EA\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":17972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u9002\u5E94\u5916\u754C\u6E29\u5EA6\u53D8\u5316",
		"indexes":"hmwsmzzsldzbsaxlnygyybzq",
		"question":"\u6CB3\u9A6C\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u603B\u5728\u6C34\u91CC\u8EB2\u7740\u4E0D\u4E0A\u5CB8\uFF1F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u539F\u56E0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\uFF1A",
		"id":17973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D3A\u9F99",
		"indexes":"dykdhkrgjddkpzs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5757\u654C\u540E\u6297\u65E5\u6839\u636E\u5730\u7684\u5F00\u8F9F\u8005\u662F",
		"id":17974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u65AF\u79D1\u4F1A\u8BAE",
		"indexes":"xzgdycysjwdgddwcxdgjhys",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4EE5\u4E16\u754C\u4E94\u5927\u56FD\u7684\u5730\u4F4D\u51FA\u5E2D\u7684\u56FD\u9645\u4F1A\u8BAE\u662F",
		"id":17975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6570\u636E\u5B58\u50A8\u4E0E\u6570\u636E\u5907\u4EFD",
		"indexes":"xlbsyjsjwlgnds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u7F51\u7EDC\u529F\u80FD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C40\u57DF\u7F51\u548C\u5E7F\u57DF\u7F51",
		"indexes":"wlafgddlfwflzyfw",
		"question":"\u7F51\u7EDC\u6309\u8986\u76D6\u7684\u5730\u7406\u8303\u56F4\u5206\u7C7B\uFF0C\u4E3B\u8981\u5206\u4E3A",
		"id":17977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DD\u5B9D\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnzbcjyddss",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u88AB\u79F0\u4E5D\u6708\u7684\u8BDE\u751F\u77F3\uFF1F",
		"id":17978
	},
	{
		"answer":"2:8:3",
		"indexes":"dzldmtlzzldyqzwqrssxhyqdzlbs",
		"question":"\u7B49\u8D28\u91CF\u7684\u9541\u3001\u78B3\u3001\u786B\u5728\u8DB3\u91CF\u7684\u6C27\u6C14\u4E2D\u5B8C\u5168\u71C3\u70E7\u65F6\uFF0C\u6D88\u8017\u6C27\u6C14\u7684\u8D28\u91CF\u6BD4\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":17979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"ylddsznlbcd",
		"question":"\u6C38\u4E50\u5927\u5178\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u7F16\u6210\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17980
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"rdysydsgry",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7684\u4E00\u751F\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u4E73\u7259\uFF1F",
		"id":17981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"gdzjzzlyjsm",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u9A7B\u519B\u53EA\u4F4F\u4E24\u591C\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":17982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7231\u4F26.\u5761",
		"indexes":"xfztxsdbzss",
		"question":"\u897F\u65B9\u4FA6\u63A2\u5C0F\u8BF4\u7684\u9F3B\u7956\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u8D8A\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bqyms",
		"question":"\u6241\u9E4A\u539F\u540D\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":17984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DD\u9CB8",
		"indexes":"sjszddbrldws",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u54FA\u4E73\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269\u662F:",
		"id":17985
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"gwzpzdsjpmlc",
		"question":"\u53E4\u6587\u4E2D\u9A88\u6307\u7684\u662F\u51E0\u5339\u9A6C\u62C9\u8F66\uFF1F",
		"id":17986
	},
	{
		"answer":"17",
		"indexes":"2003sjsjyjfcsbsgyjz",
		"question":"2003\u8D5B\u5B63\u4E16\u754C\u4E00\u7EA7\u65B9\u7A0B\u5F0F\u6BD4\u8D5B\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u7AD9?",
		"id":17987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u666E",
		"indexes":"jjxzdzbzcdjmxsynywtcd",
		"question":"\u7ECF\u6D4E\u5B66\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u8D44\u672C\u8D44\u4EA7\u5B9A\u4EF7\u6A21\u578B\u201D\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17988
	},
	{
		"answer":"15\u70B9-17\u70B9",
		"indexes":"grysedzbsytdsegscmgsclgxjsszdssmsj",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u7528\u5341\u4E8C\u5730\u652F\u8868\u793A\u4E00\u5929\u7684\u5341\u4E8C\u4E2A\u65F6\u8FB0\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u65F6\u8FB0\u4E24\u4E2A\u5C0F\u8FDB\uFF0C\u7533\u65F6\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":17989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"xycsycydzhyddyzzwqwtsxmnggjdgh",
		"question":"\u85B0\u8863\u8349\u662F\u539F\u4EA7\u4E8E\u5730\u4E2D\u6D77\u4E00\u5E26\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u690D\u7269\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u5B83\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u56FD\u82B1\uFF1F",
		"id":17990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u5723\u53F9",
		"indexes":"zgdygxsppjss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C0F\u8BF4\u6279\u8BC4\u5BB6\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u65AF",
		"indexes":"zgqdwydzjss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u79E6\u4EE3\u552F\u4E00\u7684\u4F5C\u5BB6\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":17992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u89C2",
		"indexes":"zzfhqrmwbsyxrcsnwcrdmj",
		"question":"\u201C\u81EA\u5728\u98DE\u82B1\u8F7B\u82E5\u68A6\uFF0C\u65E0\u8FB9\u4F3C\u96E8\u7EC6\u5982\u6101\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u7684\u540D\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":17993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666E\u9640\u5C71",
		"indexes":"fjsdmszxcwgypssjzcds",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u6559\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u5C71\u4E2D\uFF0C\u76F8\u4F20\u4E3A\u89C2\u97F3\u83E9\u8428\u6240\u5C45\u4E4B\u5904\u7684\u662F",
		"id":17994
	},
	{
		"answer":"70",
		"indexes":"zcqkxrdxtzyfznytdsc",
		"question":"\u6B63\u5E38\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0B\uFF0C\u4EBA\u7684\u5FC3\u8DF3\u5728\u4E00\u5206\u949F\u5185\u7EA6\u8DF3\u591A\u5C11\u6B21\uFF1F",
		"id":17995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7535\u91CF\u76F8\u7B49\u3001\u70ED\u91CF\u4E0D\u7B49",
		"indexes":"bdzzbxtdlddrsclqltdsjxdlgtddlhcsdrldgxs",
		"question":"\u628A\u7535\u963B\u503C\u4E0D\u76F8\u540C\u7684\u4E24\u6BB5\u7535\u70ED\u4E1D\u4E32\u8054\u8D77\u6765\u901A\u7535\u65F6\u95F4\u76F8\u7B49\u6D41\u8FC7\u5B83\u7684\u7535\u91CF\u548C\u4EA7\u751F\u7684\u70ED\u91CF\u7684\u5173\u7CFB\u662F",
		"id":17996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624B\u6307\u5C16",
		"indexes":"rtncdpfdwlcjzmg",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u54EA\u5904\u7684\u76AE\u80A4\u5BF9\u5916\u6765\u523A\u6FC0\u6700\u654F\u611F\uFF1F",
		"id":17997
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5706\u7403\u4F53",
		"indexes":"yqssmxzd",
		"question":"\u773C\u7403\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F62\u72B6\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":17998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6749",
		"indexes":"bcwhhsdzws",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u6D3B\u5316\u77F3\u7684\u690D\u7269\u662F",
		"id":17999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5211\u72F1",
		"indexes":"xyjzwmnndyxsxwmnmxwmzwgdshcszzzszgsmdsd",
		"question":"\u300A\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u4E2D\u738B\u6BCD\u5A18\u5A18\u7684\u539F\u578B\u662F\u897F\u738B\u6BCD\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u897F\u738B\u6BCD\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u795E\u8BDD\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u6700\u65E9\u662F\u638C\u7BA1\u4EC0\u4E48\u7684\u795E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18000
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.7",
		"indexes":"bkjdcjszzgddslgdzdsys",
		"question":"\u62A5\u8003\u673A\u52A8\u8F66\u9A7E\u9A76\u804C\u7167\u89C4\u5B9A\u7684\u89C6\u529B\u89C4\u5B9A\u5728\u591A\u5C11\u4EE5\u4E0A",
		"id":18001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5355\u5B81\u9178",
		"indexes":"czzhysmwzkyjsxsswzdtz",
		"question":"\u8336\u4E4B\u4E2D\u542B\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u8D28\u53EF\u4EE5\u51CF\u5C11\u5438\u6536\u98DF\u7269\u4E2D\u7684\u94C1\u8D28",
		"id":18002
	},
	{
		"answer":"1911",
		"indexes":"qhdxjynyn",
		"question":"\u6E05\u534E\u5927\u5B66\u5EFA\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u7B2C\u5B89\u90A3\u6CE2\u5229\u65AF",
		"indexes":"F1mgzzmgdngcsjx",
		"question":"F1\u7F8E\u56FD\u7AD9\u5728\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E3E\u884C",
		"id":18004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D8\u5C0F",
		"indexes":"qgxtkhysmbh",
		"question":"\u5F3A\u5149\u4E0B\uFF0C\u77B3\u5B54\u4F1A\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u53D8\u5316\uFF1F",
		"id":18005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjyszds",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u827A\u672F\u4E4B\u90FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u6A80",
		"indexes":"hmjjdyls",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u6728\u5BB6\u5177\u7684\u539F\u6599\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"mqwgnqgyzslwjsjdjmqzlhcglyddhjjsjxjsp",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5E74\u5668\u5B98\u79FB\u690D\u6570\u91CF\u4F4D\u5C45\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u51E0\u540D\uFF0C\u5176\u79CD\u7C7B\u548C\u6210\u529F\u7387\u4E5F\u8FBE\u5230\u6216\u63A5\u8FD1\u4E16\u754C\u5148\u8FDB\u6C34\u5E73\uFF1F",
		"id":18008
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u5A5A",
		"indexes":"hl50ns",
		"question":"\u5A5A\u9F8450\u5E74\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7070\u7EFF\u8272",
		"indexes":"fgrjhsmys",
		"question":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u4EBA\u5FCC\u8BB3\u4EC0\u4E48\u989C\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":18010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u9F99\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"wgzzyjxndsfs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u8FCE\u63A5\u65B0\u5E74\u7684\u7701\u4EFD\u662F",
		"id":18011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u516B\u8857\u9EBB\u82B1\u3001\u72D7\u4E0D\u7406\u5305\u5B50\u3001\u8033\u6735\u773C\u70B8\u7CD5",
		"indexes":"tjsjzdssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u6D25\u4E09\u7EDD\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27.\u4EAB\u5229",
		"indexes":"bcwmhdggsrdss",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u66FC\u54C8\u987F\u6842\u51A0\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18013
	},
	{
		"answer":"12\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"bbqtyzsdqjlzydyts",
		"question":"\u5317\u534A\u7403\u592A\u9633\u76F4\u5C04\u5730\u7403\u8DDD\u79BB\u6700\u8FDC\u7684\u4E00\u5929\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5180\u5156\u9752\u5F90\u8346\u9633\u8C6B\u6881\u96CD",
		"indexes":"zggcjzjzznjz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u79F0\u201C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\uFF0C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u6307\u54EA\u4E5D\u5DDE\uFF1F",
		"id":18015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u4E1C\u5730\u533A",
		"indexes":"ylkwysmdq",
		"question":"\u4F0A\u62C9\u514B\u4F4D\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u533A",
		"id":18016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DDF\u8303\u8821\u8FDC\u8D70\u9AD8\u98DE",
		"indexes":"cszxszwgbbhdmyrh",
		"question":"\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u201C\u897F\u65BD\u201D\u5728\u5434\u56FD\u5175\u8D25\u540E\u7684\u547D\u8FD0\u5982\u4F55\uFF1F",
		"id":18017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5364\u4EE3\u70F7",
		"indexes":"xlnyzmhsbdhjysh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u706D\u706B\u8BBE\u5907\u5BF9\u73AF\u5883\u6709\u635F\u5BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":18018
	},
	{
		"answer":"3000",
		"indexes":"qnscqldtkltsnkdxxdygs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u4F60\u8BF4\u51FA\u6674\u6717\u7684\u5929\u7A7A\u91CC\uFF0C\u5929\u4E0A\u80FD\u770B\u5230\u661F\u661F\u5927\u7EA6\u4E2A\u6570",
		"id":18019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u987F",
		"indexes":"nwzmyljbcwjxlzf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A'\u4EA4\u54CD\u4E50\u4E4B\u7236'\uFF1F",
		"id":18020
	},
	{
		"answer":"1681",
		"indexes":"sjsdyzgygsnynfmd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u53EA\u9AD8\u538B\u9505\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53D1\u660E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18021
	},
	{
		"answer":"3000",
		"indexes":"wgcqdfmdyydsndlsl",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u74F7\u5668\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u5927\u7EA6\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":18022
	},
	{
		"answer":"3000",
		"indexes":"cxswgzmdctgyzyyydsndlsl",
		"question":"\u523A\u7EE3\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u5DE5\u827A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u7EA6\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":18023
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"wlzcznygsqksxjd",
		"question":"\u4E07\u91CC\u957F\u57CE\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u65F6\u671F\u5F00\u59CB\u5174\u5EFA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18024
	},
	{
		"answer":"1794",
		"indexes":"wgdjhdyhqzds",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u4EAC\u676D\u5927\u8FD0\u6CB3\u5168\u957F\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F",
		"id":18025
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E50\u6BB5",
		"indexes":"ylzndlcznbdwzysdzxdwssm",
		"question":"\u97F3\u4E50\u4E2D\u80FD\u72EC\u7ACB\u5B58\u5728\uFF0C\u80FD\u8868\u8FBE\u5B8C\u6574\u610F\u601D\u7684\u6700\u5C0F\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA4\u54CD\u4E50",
		"indexes":"nzlqxssfyxjxddxgxltq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u4E50\u66F2\u5F62\u5F0F\u662F\u5BCC\u4E8E\u620F\u5267\u6027\u7684\u5927\u578B\u7BA1\u5F26\u4E50\u5957\u66F2\uFF1F",
		"id":18027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73\u5F00\u6717\u5947\u7F57",
		"indexes":"xstjtwddbhsynwdhjshd",
		"question":"\u897F\u65AF\u5EF7\u6559\u5802\u5C4B\u9876\u7684\u58C1\u753B\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4F4D\u5927\u753B\u5BB6\u6240\u753B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18028
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u683C\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"tcdlpysdrss",
		"question":"\u63D0\u51FA\u5927\u9646\u6F02\u79FB\u8BF4\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18029
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AFA\u53EF\u6862",
		"indexes":"bywzdbmdsnywkxj",
		"question":"\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A'\u6D59\u5927\u4FDD\u59C6'\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5C01",
		"indexes":"mhqmshtmxngcsdssshyjrjx",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u4E0A\u6CB3\u56FE\u300B\u63CF\u5199\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u7684\u4E16\u4FD7\u751F\u6D3B\u4E0E\u8282\u65E5\u666F\u8C61\uFF1F",
		"id":18031
	},
	{
		"answer":"1900",
		"indexes":"zqydznynblwayhbsxm",
		"question":"\u8DB3\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u88AB\u5217\u4E3A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":18032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u752B\u6D1B\u592B",
		"indexes":"tjfsxsdclzss",
		"question":"\u6761\u4EF6\u53CD\u5C04\u5B66\u8BF4\u7684\u521B\u7ACB\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D59\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"dywpyycmywzfdlhmdkxjzxsngsdr",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u57F9\u517B\u80B2\u51FA\u6CA1\u6709\u5916\u7956\u7236\u7684\u765E\u86E4\u87C6\u7684\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u6731\u6D17\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"wqydqyynggj",
		"question":"\u7F51\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199",
		"indexes":"yzbgsnysqzjsyzhddypzyhj",
		"question":"\u201C\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u65F6\u671F\u5728\u6C5F\u82CF\u626C\u5DDE\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u4E00\u6279\u804C\u4E1A\u753B\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6977\u4E66",
		"indexes":"xlnzstztdsfzdds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u4E66\u4F53\u5728\u5510\u4EE3\u65F6\u53D1\u5C55\u5230\u9F0E\u76DB\uFF1F",
		"id":18037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u770B\u6797\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zxcdfmzdlsybscssmgzd",
		"question":"\u81EA\u884C\u8F66\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u8005\u5FB7\u83B1\u65AF\u539F\u672C\u662F\u4ECE\u4E8B\u4EC0\u4E48\u5DE5\u4F5C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6",
		"indexes":"nzjsnsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u91D1\u5C5E\u80FD\u6740\u83CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18039
	},
	{
		"answer":"500",
		"indexes":"phmydzyddphmydszlm",
		"question":"'\u5E73\u8861\u6728'\u8FD0\u52A8\u4E2D\u7528\u5230\u7684\u5E73\u8861\u6728\uFF0C\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u957F\uFF1F\uFF08\u5398\u7C73\uFF09",
		"id":18040
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5409\u666E\u8D5B\u5973\u90CE",
		"indexes":"xlnfzpbrwshxzcsdyf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u5E45\u4F5C\u54C1\u88AB\u8BA4\u4E3A\u662F\u201C\u753B\u7B11\u6700\u51FA\u8272\u7684\u4E00\u5E45\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u5C14\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"dsdfmzss",
		"question":"\u7535\u89C6\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F26\u52C3\u6717",
		"indexes":"mhyxssdzp",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u300A\u591C\u5DE1\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18043
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"zgxqdqpzsfhxfhyjcxddfjsm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8C61\u68CB\u7684\u68CB\u76D8\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0A\u65B9\u548C\u4E0B\u65B9\u5212\u6709\u4EA4\u53C9\u7EBF\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18044
	},
	{
		"answer":"2000\u4F59",
		"indexes":"mgkxcdcsxydsz",
		"question":"\u83AB\u9AD8\u7A9F\u73B0\u5B58\u7684\u5F69\u5851\u50CF\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5C0A\uFF1F",
		"id":18045
	},
	{
		"answer":"1958",
		"indexes":"tamgczxdrmyxjnbjcyhs",
		"question":"\u5929\u5B89\u95E8\u5E7F\u573A\u4E2D\u5FC3\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u82F1\u96C4\u7EAA\u5FF5\u7891\u5EFA\u6210\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":18046
	},
	{
		"answer":"1978",
		"indexes":"kczgzqbjdkhzksyhs",
		"question":"\u582A\u79F0\u4E2D\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u60B2\u5267\u7684\u201C\u6050\u97E9\u75C7\u201D\uFF0C\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":18047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u7F57\u9A6C\u96D5\u50CF",
		"indexes":"dxzpklklshzdx",
		"question":"\u96D5\u50CF\u4F5C\u54C1\u300A\u5361\u62C9\u5361\u62C9\u300B\u662F\u4F55\u79CD\u96D5\u50CF\uFF1F",
		"id":18048
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u82B1\u6C34\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xlnfzpsydhjbdsrsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u5E45\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F\u7531\u5927\u753B\u5BB6--'\u516B\u5927\u5C71\u4EBA'\u6240\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"sjsdyggpjysdsznggj",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u80A1\u7968\u4EA4\u6613\u6240\u8BDE\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18050
	},
	{
		"answer":"1987\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgddybmnyddhktynyn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u6A21\u62DF\u79FB\u52A8\u7535\u8BDD\u5F00\u901A\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u8272\u661F\u671F\u5929",
		"indexes":"bcwswyldlqmzjsm",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u6B7B\u4EA1\u97F3\u4E50\u201D\u7684\u4E50\u66F2\u540D\u5B57\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18052
	},
	{
		"answer":"1988",
		"indexes":"nyntamcldwkf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5929\u5B89\u95E8\u57CE\u697C\u5BF9\u5916\u5F00\u653E",
		"id":18053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"mhjdysngcddrw",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u8463\u6E90\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8305\u4EE5\u5347",
		"indexes":"qtjtlgllyqsssjd",
		"question":"\u94B1\u5858\u6C5F\u94C1\u8DEF\u516C\u8DEF\u4E24\u7528\u6865\u662F\u8C01\u8BBE\u8BA1\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA\u666F\u56FE",
		"indexes":"xlnfzpsyhjmysz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u5E45\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F\u7531\u753B\u5BB6\u9A6C\u8FDC\u6240\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20B2",
		"indexes":"nzwsskcjgdxs",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20\u53EF\u4FC3\u8FDB\u9499\u7684\u5438\u6536\uFF1F",
		"id":18057
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"zggdhhjzhcjxxy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u822A\u6D77\u5BB6\u90D1\u548C\u66FE\u51E0\u4E0B\u897F\u6D0B\uFF1F",
		"id":18058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zmxsjjzjlmllsngr",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u3001\u5267\u4F5C\u5BB6\u7F57\u66FC.\u7F57\u5170\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18059
	},
	{
		"answer":"17",
		"indexes":"zngsjozsxhgqldhhysfg",
		"question":"\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E16\u7EAA\u6B27\u6D32\u76DB\u884C\u534E\u8D35\u7EEE\u4E3D\u7684\u7ED8\u753B\u827A\u672F\u98CE\u683C\uFF1F",
		"id":18060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"lhgjkwzxzzbsznl",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u6559\u79D1\u6587\u7EC4\u5B66\u7EC7\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18061
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E93\u5C14\u8D1D",
		"indexes":"yxnwhjfblxszyxy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u753B\u5BB6\u53D1\u8868\u4E86\u201C\u73B0\u5B9E\u4E3B\u4E49\u5BA3\u8A00\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5217\u5BBE",
		"indexes":"mhfejhsdxfdzzss",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u300A\u4F0F\u5C14\u52A0\u6CB3\u4E0A\u7684\u7EA4\u592B\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18063
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u664B",
		"indexes":"zgchsqkskdzxskdx",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4ECE\u4F55\u65F6\u8D77\u5F00\u59CB\u5F00\u6D1E\u9020\u50CF\uFF08\u77F3\u7A9F\u96D5\u50CF\uFF09\uFF1F",
		"id":18064
	},
	{
		"answer":"1955",
		"indexes":"zgzqxhclynyn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u534F\u4F1A\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"mhzyydrmbxlngrmdffjdzqj",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u300A\u81EA\u7531\u5F15\u5BFC\u4EBA\u6C11\u300B\u8868\u73B0\u4E86\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u7684\u53CD\u5C01\u5EFA\u6597\u4E89\u60C5\u666F\uFF1F",
		"id":18066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809D",
		"indexes":"zdgydqgssm",
		"question":"\u6700\u591A\u529F\u7528\u7684\u5668\u5B98\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519C\u5386\u521D\u4E00",
		"indexes":"rsydfsznyt",
		"question":"\u65E5\u98DF\u4E00\u5B9A\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5929",
		"id":18068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"1868nmzwxhmzthcjdqdjhjhxzsngcs",
		"question":"1868\u5E74\u660E\u6CBB\u7EF4\u65B0\u540E\uFF0C\u660E\u6CBB\u5929\u7687\u4ECE\u4EAC\u90FD\u8FC1\u90FD\u6C5F\u6237\uFF0C\u6C5F\u6237\u73B0\u5728\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\uFF1F",
		"id":18069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u6CFD\u5C14\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"xlnthlbczdyzzm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u6761\u6CB3\u6D41\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C\u201C\u5FB7\u610F\u5FD7\u4E4B\u6BCD\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F9D\u9760\u706B\u7BAD\u5F39\u5C04\u51FA\u5EA7\u8231",
		"indexes":"zdjfxyzjjqkxrhxstlfj",
		"question":"\u6218\u6597\u673A\u98DE\u884C\u5458\u5728\u7D27\u6025\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0B\u5982\u4F55\u8FC5\u901F\u8131\u79BB\u98DE\u673A\uFF1F",
		"id":18071
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"dltydsggjzc",
		"question":"\u72EC\u8054\u4F53\u7531\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7EC4\u6210\uFF1F",
		"id":18072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u98DF\u8681\u517D",
		"indexes":"ngbsadlytyddw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6FB3\u5927\u5229\u4E9A\u7279\u6709\u7684\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"xlngbsctsjzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u521D\u5510\u56DB\u6770\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":18074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CF0\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nzdslsnggjdghm",
		"question":"\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u201C\u7761\u83B2\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u56FD\u82B1\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"wggdsxjzczdzssm",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B\u7684\u5B57\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u6709\u5F15\u529B",
		"indexes":"xmntbsyndsdl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u6761\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u725B\u987F\u4E09\u5B9A\u5F8B\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E03\u9C81\u8BFA",
		"indexes":"xlnwzmkxjwzlxsbsszxhgcd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u4E3A\u771F\u7406\u732E\u8EAB\uFF0C\u88AB\u70E7\u6B7B\u5728\u9C9C\u82B1\u5E7F\u573A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u57C3\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlqyznwzhplzg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u7403\u5458\u4E2D\u54EA\u4F4D\u8F6C\u4F1A\u9891\u7387\u6700\u9AD8?",
		"id":18079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u5C71\u4E0B\u7684\u82B1\u73AF",
		"indexes":"lsxzyysxxsnybdyzdrw",
		"question":"\u201C\u6881\u4E09\u559C\u201D\u8FD9\u4E00\u827A\u672F\u5F62\u8C61\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u7535\u5F71\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BCC\u5170\u514B\u6797",
		"indexes":"mgdywbxygjmydkxjss",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u88AB\u4EAB\u6709\u56FD\u9645\u540D\u8A89\u7684\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C5\u5178",
		"indexes":"dyjxdayhzhdjxd",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u73B0\u4EE3\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u5728\u4F55\u5730\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18082
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u9053\u5B50",
		"indexes":"sztwtswgnwzmhjdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u9001\u5B50\u5929\u738B\u56FE\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"1990ndsyjyyhzhdjx",
		"question":"1990\u5E74\u7B2C\u5341\u4E00\u5C4A\u4E9A\u8FD0\u4F1A\u5728\u4F55\u5730\u4E3E\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":18084
	},
	{
		"answer":"8%",
		"indexes":"2002nwggnsczzsctp10wyyjjzzld",
		"question":"2002\u5E74\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u56FD\u5185\u751F\u4EA7\u603B\u503C\u9996\u6B21\u7A81\u783410\u4E07\u4EBF\u5143\uFF0C\u7ECF\u6D4E\u589E\u957F\u7387\u8FBE",
		"id":18085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u57F9",
		"indexes":"dlddwdsm",
		"question":"\u7535\u6D41\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18086
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u53E4\u65CF",
		"indexes":"zgngmzdwdbxjmbcdxxtbd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u821E\u8E48\u8868\u73B0\u9A8F\u9A6C\u5954\u9A70\u7684\u5F62\u8C61\u7279\u522B\u591A\uFF1F",
		"id":18087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u664B",
		"indexes":"wgzmhjgkzsngcddrw",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u987E\u607A\u4E4B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8042\u8033",
		"indexes":"yyjjxqsyspdq",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E49\u52C7\u519B\u8FDB\u884C\u66F2\u300B\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u8C31\u7684\u66F2\uFF1F",
		"id":18089
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7435\u7436\u66F2",
		"indexes":"smmfsybsmqm",
		"question":"\u300A\u5341\u9762\u57CB\u4F0F\u300B\u662F\u4E00\u90E8\u4EC0\u4E48\u66F2\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":18090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"kqzylqdsynggj",
		"question":"\u53E3\u7434\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E50\u5668\u8BDE\u751F\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6",
		"id":18091
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F3D\u5229\u7565",
		"indexes":"sz1608nzzlsjsdygwyj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u57281608\u5E74\u5236\u9020\u4E86\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u671B\u8FDC\u955C\uFF1F",
		"id":18092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u827A\u8C0B",
		"indexes":"yphglsyszdd",
		"question":"\u5F71\u7247\u300A\u7EA2\u9AD8\u7CB1\u300B\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u6267\u5BFC\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82AD\u857E",
		"indexes":"nzwdbcwtyhxzdys",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u821E\u8E48\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u8DF3\u8DC3\u548C\u65CB\u8F6C\u7684\u827A\u672F\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyxssyszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E'\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E09\u8981\u7D20'\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":18095
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u955C\u5934",
		"indexes":"dyzjbddwssm",
		"question":"\u7535\u5F71\u6700\u57FA\u672C\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18096
	},
	{
		"answer":"1905",
		"indexes":"zgrdycpsypszsmsh",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u62CD\u6444\u5F71\u7247\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":18097
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"ywggxsbtsyggdhhxfybjxtsjshhxfzddgjsdgnzdqnxfldddsymym",
		"question":"\u56E0\u4E3A\u5404\u56FD\u4E60\u4FD7\u4E0D\u540C\uFF0C\u6240\u4EE5\u5404\u56FD\u7684\u82B1\u5349\u6D88\u8D39\u4E5F\u4E0D\u5C3D\u76F8\u540C\uFF0C\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u82B1\u5349\u6D88\u8D39\u6700\u591A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u5FB7\u56FD\uFF0C\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u5176\u5E74\u6D88\u8D39\u91CF\u8FBE\u5230\u591A\u5C11\u4EBF\u7F8E\u5143\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18098
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"txfsngdmd",
		"question":"\u901A\u5FC3\u7C89\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7684\u540D\u70B9",
		"id":18099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7533\u519C",
		"indexes":"xxlddjrss",
		"question":"\u4FE1\u606F\u8BBA\u7684\u5960\u57FA\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":18100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u68D5\u718A",
		"indexes":"xsldjszjddsrdwssm",
		"question":"\u73B0\u65F6\u9646\u5730\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5DE8\u5927\u7684\u98DF\u8089\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":18101
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u9888\u9E7F",
		"indexes":"ldszgdbrdwssm",
		"question":"\u9646\u5730\u4E0A\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":18102
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u8C61",
		"indexes":"ldszzdbrldwssm",
		"question":"\u9646\u5730\u4E0A\u6700\u91CD\u7684\u54FA\u4E73\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":18103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7F\u5C71\u7532",
		"indexes":"yxnzsyldbrldw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u6709\u9CDE\u7684\u54FA\u4E73\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":18104
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u6559",
		"indexes":"cslsyngzjdls",
		"question":"\u300A\u6210\u5B9E\u8BBA\u300B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B97\u6559\u7684\u8BBA\u4E66\uFF1F",
		"id":18105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u8DB3",
		"indexes":"wgymsm",
		"question":"\u8708\u86A3\u53C8\u540D\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":18106
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982",
		"indexes":"lbzsazpzsszjzrxrdkymzsyyqzslgybscwzjdtx",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u5728\u300A\u4E0A\u5B89\u5DDE\u88F4\u957F\u53F2\u4E66\u300B\u4E2D\u201C\u89C1\u5F20\u4EBA\u76F8\u5982\u5927\u5938\u4E91\u68A6\u4E4B\u4E8B\uFF0C\u4E91\u6709\u4E03\u6CFD\uFF0C\u9042\u6765\u89C2\u7109\u3002\u201D\u628A\u8C01\u79F0\u4E3A\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u540C\u4E61\uFF1F",
		"id":18107
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u59D3",
		"indexes":"qflxctqmdlyhdzzzllyjzsm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6E05\u98CE\u4E24\u8896\u671D\u5929\u53BB\uFF0C\u514D\u5F97\u95FE\u960E\u8BDD\u77ED\u957F\u3002\u201D\u5728\u8FD9\u91CC\uFF0C\u201C\u95FE\u960E\u201D\u501F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18108
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u8702",
		"indexes":"zgyfsnyzmfdzr",
		"question":"\u7167\u987E\u5E7C\u8702\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u871C\u8702\u7684\u8D23\u4EFB\uFF1F",
		"id":18109
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u6781",
		"indexes":"bxszzsmdf",
		"question":"\u767D\u718A\u751F\u957F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":18110
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u82CF",
		"indexes":"kqqyy",
		"question":"\u6606\u66F2\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E",
		"id":18111
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CC3",
		"indexes":"jdbfdysysmqghxd",
		"question":"\u7EDD\u5927\u90E8\u5206\u7684\u9C7C\u662F\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u5668\u5B98\u547C\u5438\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CD\u5B50",
		"indexes":"mszwzdnybf",
		"question":"\u7C73\u662F\u690D\u7269\u4E2D\u7684\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u5206\uFF1F",
		"id":18113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5317",
		"indexes":"zjkwy",
		"question":"\u5F20\u5BB6\u53E3\u4F4D\u4E8E",
		"id":18114
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6447\u7BEE\u66F2",
		"indexes":"xlngsblmsdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4F2F\u62C9\u59C6\u65AF\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1",
		"id":18115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"wqydkyzsd13sjdnggj",
		"question":"\u7F51\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u53EF\u4EE5\u8FFD\u6EAF\u523013\u4E16\u7EAA\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E2D\u5A1F",
		"indexes":"djzmsnwyqxsjdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u5F53\u5BB6\u4E3B\u6BCD\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u8A00\u60C5\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18117
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u820D",
		"indexes":"bsyrmysjryjzds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u6388\u4E88\u4EBA\u6C11\u827A\u672F\u5BB6\u8363\u8A89\u5956\u72B6\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18118
	},
	{
		"answer":"ARDS",
		"indexes":"crhxjpzhzdywjcw",
		"question":"\u6210\u4EBA\u547C\u5438\u7A98\u8FEB\u7EFC\u5408\u5F81\u7684\u82F1\u6587\u7B80\u79F0\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"nzdsgsqwgdsdjysxznygcsm",
		"question":"\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u5434\u56FD\u7684\u9996\u90FD\u5EFA\u4E1A\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u661F",
		"indexes":"tyxzzzzmdxxs",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u7CFB\u4E2D\u81EA\u8F6C\u6700\u6162\u7684\u884C\u661F\u662F",
		"id":18121
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u75C5\u4EBA\u7684\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"gdmyssmczlytqxdzjftbzgxjzasxzgmzyy",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u540D\u533B\u5B59\u601D\u9088\u521B\u9020\u4E86\u201C\u4EE5\u75DB\u53D6\u7A74\u201D\u7684\u9488\u7078\u6CD5\uFF0C\u4ED6\u628A\u8FD9\u4E2A\u7A74\u53EB\u505A\u201C\u963F\u662F\u7A74\u201D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E2A\u540D\u5B57\u6E90\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u65AF\u6E7E",
		"indexes":"blzdbqdngdq",
		"question":"\u5DF4\u6797\u5728\u4E1C\u534A\u7403\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u533A\uFF1F",
		"id":18123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"blqyynggj",
		"question":"\u82AD\u857E\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18124
	},
	{
		"answer":"79\u516C\u91CC\u6BCF\u79D2",
		"indexes":"dyyzsdw",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5B87\u5B99\u901F\u5EA6\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FAE\u578B\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A",
		"indexes":"grjsjPCsylx",
		"question":"\u4E2A\u4EBA\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A(PC)\u5C5E\u4E8E()\u7C7B\u578B",
		"id":18126
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"bdsryjgr",
		"question":"\u516B\u5927\u5C71\u4EBA\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8272\u7403\u5C42",
		"indexes":"tyybwytydqd",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u8000\u6591\u4F4D\u4E8E\u592A\u9633\u5927\u6C14\u7684",
		"id":18128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u661F",
		"indexes":"tyxxxzzdqskqlzmlds",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u7CFB\u884C\u661F\u4E2D\u5728\u5730\u7403\u4E0A\u770B\u8D77\u6765\u6700\u660E\u4EAE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18129
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u542C\u89C9\uFF08\u58F0\u7EB3\uFF09",
		"indexes":"bjtzszksmtchsbwt",
		"question":"\u767D\u66A8\u8C5A\u5728\u6C34\u4E2D\u9760\u4EC0\u4E48\u63A2\u6D4B\u548C\u8BC6\u522B\u7269\u4F53\uFF1F",
		"id":18130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u661F",
		"indexes":"zgszggddnykxxdch",
		"question":"\u957F\u5E9A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5BF9\u54EA\u4E00\u9897\u884C\u661F\u7684\u79F0\u547C?",
		"id":18131
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u7528",
		"indexes":"shzhczdxds",
		"question":"\u6C34\u6D52\u4E2D\u53F7\u79F0\u667A\u591A\u661F\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18132
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B59\u9F99",
		"indexes":"bmfmczsk",
		"question":"\u767D\u9A6C\u975E\u9A6C\u51FA\u81EA\u8C01\u53E3?",
		"id":18133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"bqtsngtydyzjwhjdzgdw",
		"question":"\u767D\u9CCD\u8C5A\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7279\u6709\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u6781\u4E3A\u7F55\u89C1\u7684\u73CD\u8D35\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18134
	},
	{
		"answer":"1860\u5E74",
		"indexes":"ymydsfyzsznynbyjfhd",
		"question":"\u5706\u660E\u56ED\u5927\u6C34\u6CD5\u9057\u5740\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u88AB\u82F1\u519B\u711A\u6BC1\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18135
	},
	{
		"answer":"80\u5206",
		"indexes":"awgxxdyzbzjyfwbpxdyzs",
		"question":"\u6309\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u884C\u7684\u90AE\u8D44\u6807\u51C6\uFF0C\u5BC4\u4E00\u5C01\u5916\u57E0\u5E73\u4FE1\u7684\u90AE\u8D44\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18136
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u571F\u9C81\u756A\u76C6\u5730",
		"indexes":"wghbzdddfs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6D77\u62D4\u6700\u4F4E\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18137
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u661F",
		"indexes":"bdsdecsjdzzmjzyzwdgjjlzytzezzqdljrdzjqwbdqddzgdjxsjx",
		"question":"\u5DF4\u987F\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7F8E\u519B\u6700\u6709\u4F5C\u4E3A\u7684\u9AD8\u7EA7\u5C06\u9886\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u4ED6\u5728\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\u53D6\u5F97\u4E86\u60CA\u4EBA\u7684\u6218\u7EE9\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u5DF4\u987F\u53D6\u5F97\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u519B\u8854\u662F\u51E0\u661F\uFF1F",
		"id":18138
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u670810\u65E5",
		"indexes":"wgdjsjs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6559\u5E08\u8282\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18139
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u4F57",
		"indexes":"sjszzsydnfdmyss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u4F7F\u7528\u5BFC\u5C3F\u6CD5\u7684\u540D\u533B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u6D77",
		"indexes":"hhdytznygs",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u6CB3\u7684\u6E90\u5934\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":18141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u673A\u5668\u8BED\u8A00\u7A0B\u5E8F",
		"indexes":"jsjnzjzxdcxs",
		"question":"\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u80FD\u76F4\u63A5\u6267\u884C\u7684\u7A0B\u5E8F\u662F",
		"id":18142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B21\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zywstdd",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u662F\u4ED6\u7239\u7684",
		"id":18143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u4E91\u53F7",
		"indexes":"fgrbhjz813kzstbzshdjdqjs",
		"question":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u65E5\u672C\u6D77\u519B\u57288\u00B713\u6297\u6218\u65F6\u505C\u6CCA\u5728\u4E0A\u6D77\u7684\u8230\u961F\u65D7\u8230\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666E\u7F57\u7C73\u4FEE\u65AF",
		"indexes":"ayhjdqyhsyg",
		"question":"\u5965\u8FD0\u706B\u70AC\u7684\u8D77\u6E90\u548C\u8C01\u6709\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":18145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9C\u5BBE",
		"indexes":"nzdgxctgsxzd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u5412\u7684\u6545\u4E61\u9648\u5858\u5173\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bdfsngr",
		"question":"\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"befxysnggjfbd",
		"question":"\u8D1D\u5C14\u798F\u5BA3\u8A00\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53D1\u8868\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E94\u4EA4\u54CD\u66F2",
		"indexes":"bcwmyjxqdsbdfd",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u547D\u8FD0\u4EA4\u54CD\u66F2\u7684\u662F\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC\u7684",
		"id":18149
	},
	{
		"answer":"4\u540D",
		"indexes":"zsdjlsmdyjmydy",
		"question":"\u6B63\u5F0F\u7684\u63A5\u529B\u8D5B\uFF0C\u6BCF\u961F\u6709\u51E0\u540D\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":18150
	},
	{
		"answer":"40\u5E74",
		"indexes":"mqwgsylyylyddtdsyqcrdzgnxs",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6211\u56FD\u5546\u4E1A\u3001\u65C5\u6E38\u3001\u5A31\u4E50\u7528\u5730\u7684\u571F\u5730\u4F7F\u7528\u6743\u51FA\u8BA9\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u5E74\u9650\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18151
	},
	{
		"answer":"1950\u5E744\u6708",
		"indexes":"gqtzyynynjd5y4rwgqtcljnr",
		"question":"\u5171\u9752\u56E2\u4E2D\u592E\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u51B3\u5B9A5\u67084\u65E5\u4E3A\u5171\u9752\u56E2\u6210\u7ACB\u7EAA\u5FF5\u65E5",
		"id":18152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD0\u8F7D\u706B\u7BAD",
		"indexes":"1970424wgddykrzwxdfhyhysmfssstd",
		"question":"1970.4.24\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u9897\u4EBA\u9020\u536B\u661F\u4E1C\u65B9\u7EA2\u4E00\u53F7\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u65B9\u5F0F\u9001\u4E0A\u5929\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"1234567qgcmdfmzlz",
		"question":"1\u30012\u30013\u30014\u30015\u30016\u30017\u4E03\u4E2A\u5531\u540D\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u8005\u6765\u81EA\uFF1A",
		"id":18154
	},
	{
		"answer":"14\u5C81",
		"indexes":"zwgxfgdxwrfxszrdzxnls",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\uFF0C\u5211\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\u884C\u4E3A\u4EBA\u8D1F\u5211\u4E8B\u8D23\u4EFB\u7684\u6700\u5C0F\u5E74\u9F84\u662F",
		"id":18155
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"z1994nd2003nsndjAlslszdlsddghdjclsgj",
		"question":"\u57281994\u5E74\u52302003\u5E74\u5341\u5E74\u7684\u7532A\u8054\u8D5B\u5386\u53F2\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5927\u8FDE\u5B9E\u5FB7\u961F\u5171\u83B7\u5F97\u51E0\u6B21\u8054\u8D5B\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":18156
	},
	{
		"answer":"1946",
		"indexes":"dytjsjszsmshyzcxd",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u53F0\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u7814\u5236\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u53EC\u5F00\u201C\u56FD\u6C11\u5927\u4F1A\u201D\u662F\u975E\u6CD5\u7684",
		"indexes":"1946nzddzhmgxfswxfyw",
		"question":"1946\u5E74\u5236\u5B9A\u7684\u300A\u4E2D\u534E\u6C11\u56FD\u5BAA\u6CD5\u300B\u662F\u4F2A\u5BAA\u6CD5\uFF0C\u56E0\u4E3A",
		"id":18158
	},
	{
		"answer":"1640\u5E74\u65B0\u8BAE\u4F1A\u7684\u53EC\u5F00",
		"indexes":"ygzcjjgmksdbzs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u5F00\u59CB\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18159
	},
	{
		"answer":"1914\u5E74\uFF0C\u6700\u65E9\u88C5\u5907\u6CD5\u519B",
		"indexes":"tkcsy",
		"question":"\u5934\u76D4\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E",
		"id":18160
	},
	{
		"answer":"4\u5E74",
		"indexes":"dfqyljnsjwclmnlszfh",
		"question":"\u8FBE\u00B7\u82AC\u5947\u7528\u4E86\u51E0\u5E74\u65F6\u95F4\u5B8C\u6210\u4E86\u300A\u8499\u5A1C\u4E3D\u838E\u300B\u8FD9\u5E45\u753B?",
		"id":18161
	},
	{
		"answer":"2864\u4EBF\u7F8E\u5143",
		"indexes":"2002nwggjwhcbyddsymy",
		"question":"2002\u5E74\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u56FD\u5BB6\u5916\u6C47\u50A8\u5907\u5DF2\u8FBE\u591A\u5C11\u4EBF\u7F8E\u5143",
		"id":18162
	},
	{
		"answer":"528.7*24.8",
		"indexes":"mhqmshtdggsdsdwlm",
		"question":"\u540D\u753B\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u4E0A\u6CB3\u56FE\u300B\u7684\u89C4\u683C\u662F\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F\uFF08\u5355\u4F4D\u5398\u7C73\uFF09",
		"id":18163
	},
	{
		"answer":"1894\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gjawhcly",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E",
		"id":18164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u7B1B",
		"indexes":"xllqzbsymzlqds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E50\u5668\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C11\u65CF\u4E50\u5668\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DEF\u6613\u5341\u56DB",
		"indexes":"bcwtywdgwss",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u592A\u9633\u738B\u7684\u56FD\u738B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7ACB\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bdsdgjyljzywdfdlmedkrmjs",
		"question":"\u88AB\u5F53\u65F6\u7684\u56FD\u9645\u8206\u8BBA\u754C\u8D5E\u8A89\u4E3A\u4E1C\u65B9\u7684\u9686\u7F8E\u5C14\u7684\u6297\u65E5\u540D\u5C06\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"qcdxsxbzhcyfdjwzjhcjzchqtzcfhdxtj",
		"question":"\u6C7D\u8F66\u5927\u4FEE\u9001\u4FEE\u6807\u51C6\uFF1A\u8D27\u8F66\u4EE5\u53D1\u52A8\u673A\u4E3A\u4E3B\uFF0C\u7ED3\u5408\u8F66\u67B6\u603B\u6210\u6216\u5176\u5B83\uFF08\uFF09\u603B\u6210\u7B26\u5408\u5927\u4FEE\u6761\u4EF6\u3002",
		"id":18168
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.7",
		"indexes":"bkjdcjsyyqmzyjdslbdy",
		"question":"\u62A5\u8003\u673A\u52A8\u8F66\u9A7E\u9A76\u5458\u8981\u6C42\u6BCF\u53EA\u773C\u775B\u7684\u89C6\u529B\u4E0D\u4F4E\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18169
	},
	{
		"answer":"CIA",
		"indexes":"mgzyqbjdywjxs",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u4E2D\u592E\u60C5\u62A5\u5C40\u7684\u82F1\u6587\u7B80\u5199\u662F",
		"id":18170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u548C\u9756",
		"indexes":"bsnwsrcyjzgsymwqyhwz",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u66FE\u9690\u5C45\u5728\u5B64\u5C71\uFF0C\u4EE5\u6885\u4E3A\u59BB\uFF0C\u4EE5\u9E64\u4E3A\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":18171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u5179\u522B\u514B\u65AF\u5766",
		"indexes":"bywbjzgds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u201C\u767D\u91D1\u4E4B\u56FD\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6155\u5C3C\u9ED1",
		"indexes":"dgdyhfjzzwdzzxzn",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u7684\u5B87\u822A\uFF0C\u98DE\u673A\u5236\u9020\uFF0C\u5FAE\u7535\u5B50\u4E2D\u5FC3\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":18173
	},
	{
		"answer":"6300",
		"indexes":"zjqzdsgl",
		"question":"\u957F\u6C5F\u5168\u957F\u591A\u5C11\u516C\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u6D77",
		"indexes":"dnhzrngh",
		"question":"\u591A\u7459\u6CB3\u6CE8\u5165\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D77\uFF1F",
		"id":18175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DD\u9511\u5408\u91D1",
		"indexes":"bxsccysmcl",
		"question":"\u4FDD\u9669\u4E1D\u5E38\u91C7\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u6750\u6599\uFF1F",
		"id":18176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5308\u7259\u5229",
		"indexes":"hd2002nnbewxjdymlketzsngr",
		"question":"\u83B7\u5F972002\u5E74\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u6587\u5B66\u5956\u7684\u4F0A\u59C6\u96F7.\u51EF\u5C14\u6CF0\u5179\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"id":18177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FE6\u4F2F\u8D5E",
		"indexes":"tzjssxd",
		"question":"\u300A\u9898\u662D\u541B\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u5199\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18178
	},
	{
		"answer":"206\u5757",
		"indexes":"ryjkgt",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6709\u51E0\u5757\u9AA8\u5934\uFF1F",
		"id":18179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u683C\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"dlpyjsssfxd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u9646\u6F02\u79FB\u5047\u8BF4\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u73B0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18180
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5374\u4E0B\u6C34\u7CBE\u5E18\uFF0C\u73B2\u73D1\u671B\u79CB\u6708\u3002",
		"indexes":"yjsblyjqlwzzlbyjydhljs",
		"question":"\u7389\u9636\u751F\u767D\u9732\uFF0C\u591C\u4E45\u4FB5\u7F57\u889C\uFF08\u4F5C\u8005\u674E\u767D\u7389\u9636\u6028\uFF09\u7684\u540E\u4E24\u53E5\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u592E\u5904\u7406\u5668",
		"indexes":"qwdnpjzCPUssm",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u7535\u8111\u914D\u4EF6\u4E2DCPU\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u53E4",
		"indexes":"zyzdygjlshzygjds",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E9A\u6D32\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5EFA\u7ACB\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18183
	},
	{
		"answer":"1924",
		"indexes":"dyjdahynnjxjxmndah",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u51AC\u5965\u4F1A\u4E8E\u54EA\u5E74\u4E3E\u884C\u5373\u590F\u8499\u5C3C\u51AC\u5965\u4F1A",
		"id":18184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5409\u5E73",
		"indexes":"yaswsbccdjzgsfztesdss",
		"question":"\u56E0\u6697\u6740\u672A\u9042\uFF0C\u88AB\u66F9\u64CD\u65AD\u4E5D\u6307\uFF0C\u5272\u820C\uFF0C\u5206\u80A2\u4F53\u800C\u6B7B\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6C14\u5BC6\u5EA6\u6539\u53D8",
		"indexes":"xxysysdyygxlngyyyg",
		"question":"\u661F\u661F\u4E00\u95EA\u4E00\u95EA\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u8DDF\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u539F\u56E0\u6709\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":18186
	},
	{
		"answer":"635\u5343\u514B",
		"indexes":"sjszzdmmxjydz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u91CD\u7684\u201C\u731B\u72B8\u201D\u76F8\u673A\u6709\u591A\u91CD\uFF1F",
		"id":18187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u540D",
		"indexes":"mlsszdsssyg",
		"question":"'\u540D\u843D\u5B59\u5C71'\u4E2D\u7684'\u5B59\u5C71'\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A",
		"id":18188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"wgzzdybybbcxysmsh",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u94F6\u5E01\uFF08\u94F6\u5E03\u5E01\uFF09\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":18189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90D1\u6587",
		"indexes":"zgldlcfwsscdyzzj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7B2C\u516D\u6B21\u4F10\u9B4F\u65F6\u8C01\u66FE\u5230\u8425\u4E2D\u8BC8\u964D\uFF1F",
		"id":18190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u6625",
		"indexes":"xjgwdydjhlgzsngcsdtd",
		"question":"\u201C\u590F\u5B63\u9AD8\u6E29\u591A\u96E8\uFF0C\u51AC\u5B63\u5BD2\u51B7\u5E72\u71E5\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u7684\u7279\u70B9",
		"id":18191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u62C9\u591A\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"rmcsddgsnywwddqx",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u5E38\u8BF4\u7684\u8FED\u6208\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4F1F\u5927\u7684\u7403\u661F\uFF1F",
		"id":18192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9020\u7EB8",
		"indexes":"xlwggdsdfmzysjdqmqggyscjyzcwrds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u56DB\u5927\u53D1\u660E\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7528\u6C34\u8F83\u591A\u4E14\u76EE\u524D\u8BE5\u5DE5\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u6781\u6613\u9020\u6210\u6C61\u67D3\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnggjybzrwz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EE5\u767D\u79CD\u4EBA\u4E3A\u4E3B\uFF1F",
		"id":18194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5DDE\u3001\u60E0\u5DDE\u3001\u510B\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"sssbzds",
		"question":"\u82CF\u8F7C\u201C\u4E09\u8D2C\u201D\u4E4B\u5730\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50\u3001\u695A\u3001\u79E6",
		"indexes":"zgqxzzcqsqcgbds",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5728\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u79F0\u8FC7\u9738\u7684\u662F\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18196
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"zhgjcxxy",
		"question":"\u90D1\u548C\u5171\u51E0\u6B21\u4E0B\u897F\u6D0B\uFF1F",
		"id":18197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C5",
		"indexes":"qsxdcdzyycls",
		"question":"\u94C5\u9178\u84C4\u7535\u6C60\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u6750\u6599\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5C1D\u541B",
		"indexes":"jmgdscznwzggzmx",
		"question":"\u9E21\u9E23\u72D7\u76D7\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4F4D\u6218\u56FD\u516C\u5B50\u95E8\u4E0B",
		"id":18199
	},
	{
		"answer":"2.0V",
		"indexes":"qsxdcdtdeddys",
		"question":"\u94C5\u9178\u84C4\u7535\u6C60\u5355\u4F53\u7684\u989D\u5B9A\u7535\u538B\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u683C\u5170",
		"indexes":"mldnszdnzqdysdzsdjyqd",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u62C9\u591A\u7EB3\u662F\u5728\u5BF9\u54EA\u652F\u7403\u961F\u7528\u4E0A\u5E1D\u4E4B\u624B\u6253\u8FDB\u4E00\u7403\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u52A0\u5761",
		"indexes":"scsnl",
		"question":"\u201C\u72EE\u57CE\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC",
		"indexes":"rlzxsydzzqjdjss",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u6700\u5148\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5236\u9020\u5668\u5177\u7684\u91D1\u5C5E\u662F",
		"id":18203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u7F57\u7684\u6D77",
		"indexes":"sjsydzddhsxlnyg",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u76D0\u5EA6\u6700\u4F4E\u7684\u6D77\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u653B\u51FB\u673A",
		"indexes":"Asmjnzfjddh",
		"question":"\u201CA\u201D\u662F\u7F8E\u519B\u54EA\u79CD\u98DE\u673A\u7684\u4EE3\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":18205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8015\u4F5C",
		"indexes":"yyzwhycyysz",
		"question":"\u82F1\u8BED\u4E2D\u201C\u6587\u5316\u201D\u4E00\u8BCD\u539F\u610F\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":18206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u521A\u679C\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"sjsd2dhsxlnyt",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C2\u5927\u6CB3\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u6761\uFF1F",
		"id":18207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u539F\u7269\u7684\u4E00\u4EFD\u62F7\u8D1D",
		"indexes":"swshfxhdwzdyzjdjxwzzzljxszsmys",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u7F51\u65F6\u4F1A\u53D1\u73B0\u5F88\u591A\u7F51\u7AD9\u90FD\u6709\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u201C\u955C\u50CF\u7F51\u7AD9\u201D\uFF0C\u5728\u8FD9\u91CC\u201C\u955C\u50CF\u201D\u662F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\u610F\u601D",
		"id":18208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"lybbk",
		"question":"\u201C\u516D\u827A\u201D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC",
		"id":18209
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wqtxdjskyqxw",
		"question":"\u65E0\u671F\u5F92\u5211\u7684\u5047\u91CA\u8003\u9A8C\u671F\u9650\u4E3A\uFF1F",
		"id":18210
	},
	{
		"answer":"1965\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgdjtgjsjsnynyzcgd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6676\u4F53\u7BA1\u8BA1\u7B97\u673A\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7814\u5236\u6210\u529F\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"bystgfmzfsblsngr",
		"question":"\u80CC\u8DC3\u5F0F\u8DF3\u9AD8\u53D1\u660E\u8005\u798F\u65AF\u4F2F\u5229\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"id":18212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u660C\u8D6B",
		"indexes":"sjwqssdywhddmgdqss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u56F4\u68CB\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u83B7\u5F97\u5927\u6EE1\u8D2F\u7684\u68CB\u624B\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18213
	},
	{
		"answer":"KFC",
		"indexes":"kdjdywsxssm",
		"question":"\u80AF\u5FB7\u57FA\u7684\u82F1\u6587\u7F29\u5199\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u8272",
		"indexes":"xlhzbsysys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4F55\u8005\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E09\u539F\u8272",
		"id":18215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u5B97\u5143",
		"indexes":"qljqzyyygsdzzss",
		"question":"\u201C\u9ED4\u9A74\u6280\u7A77\u201D\u8FD9\u4E00\u5BD3\u8A00\u6545\u4E8B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C48\u539F",
		"indexes":"jgssdzp",
		"question":"\u4E5D\u6B4C\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1",
		"id":18217
	},
	{
		"answer":"50\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"mgxydsgz",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u73B0\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u5DDE\uFF1F",
		"id":18218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u6866",
		"indexes":"mrsdxms",
		"question":"'\u7F8E\u4EBA\u6811'\u7684\u5B66\u540D\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58A8\u7EFF\u8272",
		"indexes":"yxdyzclyhldyszwhysms",
		"question":"\u94F6\u674F\u7684\u53F6\u5B50\u9664\u4E86\u6709\u9EC4\u7EFF\u7684\u989C\u8272\u4E4B\u5916\uFF0C\u8FD8\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":18220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u57CE",
		"indexes":"wgmckmbrmcsm",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u540D\u57CE\u6606\u660E\u88AB\u4EBA\u4EEC\u79F0\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u715C",
		"indexes":"dyyjcsxdldpmzzwggdsdcz",
		"question":"\u7535\u5F71\u201C\u4E00\u6C5F\u6625\u6C34\u5411\u4E1C\u6D41\u201D\u7684\u7247\u540D\uFF0C\u6458\u81EA\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8C01\u7684\u8BCD\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81E3",
		"indexes":"yxbsyjcdssm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u656C\u79F0\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5938\u7236",
		"indexes":"zygshzzztyds",
		"question":"\u5728\u8FDC\u53E4\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u8FFD\u9010\u592A\u9633\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DF\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"mcjzsdmxdrccw",
		"question":"\u5B5F\u5C1D\u541B\u62DB\u6536\u5230\u95E8\u4E0B\u7684\u4EBA\u624D\u79F0\u4E3A",
		"id":18225
	},
	{
		"answer":"2.26",
		"indexes":"ymdsgs",
		"question":"\u59DA\u660E\u7684\u8EAB\u9AD8\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u519C",
		"indexes":"cpsmzqllsyxngjjxztcd",
		"question":"\u4EA7\u54C1\u751F\u547D\u5468\u671F\u7406\u8BBA\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u7ECF\u6D4E\u5B66\u8005\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C5\u5178\u5A1C",
		"indexes":"xlshzzhnss",
		"question":"\u5E0C\u814A\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u667A\u6167\u5973\u795E\u662F",
		"id":18228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u9F20\u72FC",
		"indexes":"ngdwnqszfcw",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u80FD\u8F7B\u677E\u5236\u670D\u523A\u732C\uFF1F",
		"id":18229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u6D32",
		"indexes":"yhgzddzs",
		"question":"\u6CBF\u6D77\u56FD\u6700\u591A\u7684\u6D32\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18230
	},
	{
		"answer":"500\u4E07\u5E74\u524D",
		"indexes":"rldsydsnq",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u8BDE\u751F\u4E8E\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\u524D\uFF1F",
		"id":18231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54F2\u5B66\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"xlnycwyyddslbxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79F0\u8C13\u4E0E\u96C5\u5178\u7684\u68AD\u4F26\u4E0D\u76F8\u7B26",
		"id":18232
	},
	{
		"answer":"1850",
		"indexes":"xndxsjy",
		"question":"\u6089\u5C3C\u5927\u5B66\u59CB\u5EFA\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18233
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"8gtjxtdxqqzygbqtqgszytpzsccjkzcszdxq",
		"question":"8\u4E2A\u4F53\u79EF\u76F8\u540C\u7684\u5C0F\u7403\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u4E00\u4E2A\u6BD4\u5176\u5B83\u4E03\u4E2A\u7A0D\u91CD\uFF0C\u7528\u5929\u5E73\u6700\u5C11\u79F0\uFF08\uFF09\u6B21\u5C31\u53EF\u627E\u51FA\u7A0D\u91CD\u7684\u5C0F\u7403",
		"id":18234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u9053\u5C14\u592B\u00B7\u8428\u514B\u65AF",
		"indexes":"sksdfmzsfgr",
		"question":"\u8428\u514B\u65AF\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u8005\u662F\u6CD5\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1A",
		"id":18235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u5854\u592B\u91CC\u963F\u8BFA\u65AF",
		"indexes":"qqtssddnwzmlsxjdzz",
		"question":"\u300A\u5168\u7403\u901A\u53F2\u300B\u662F\u5F53\u4EE3\u54EA\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u5386\u53F2\u5B66\u5BB6\u7684\u8457\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"gyswczgzwzhznszsmz",
		"question":"\u53E4\u8A00\u6240\u8C13:\u5403\u5728\u5E7F\u5DDE,\u73A9\u5728\u676D\u5DDE....\u54EA\u6B7B\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5DDE?",
		"id":18237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u540E\u9762",
		"indexes":"zydyjzzstdngbw",
		"question":"\u7AE0\u9C7C\u7684\u773C\u775B\u957F\u5728\u8EAB\u4F53\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u90E8\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":18238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u76DB\u987F",
		"indexes":"mgddyrztss",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u603B\u7EDF\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u8272",
		"indexes":"hsddbssbslsddbsshsnhsddbsssm",
		"question":"\u9ED1\u8272\u7684\u5BF9\u6BD4\u8272\u662F\u767D\u8272,\u7EFF\u8272\u7684\u5BF9\u6BD4\u8272\u662F\u7EA2\u8272,\u90A3\u9EC4\u8272\u7684\u5BF9\u6BD4\u8272\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":18240
	},
	{
		"answer":"3:7",
		"indexes":"rtdrtgyfytysgcqbls",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u7684\u8089\u4F53\u9AA8\u517B\u4EFD\u7531\u70AD\u4E0E\u6C34\u6784\u6210,\u5176\u6BD4\u4F8B\u662F:",
		"id":18241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u585E\u6D66\u8DEF\u65AF",
		"indexes":"sjsnggjgqsybgdt",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u56FD\u65D7\u4E0A\u6709\u672C\u56FD\u5730\u56FE\uFF1F",
		"id":18242
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"zelszgjxgjccczz",
		"question":"\u5728\u4FC4\u7F57\u65AF\u603B\u5171\u8FDB\u884C\u8FC7\u51E0\u6B21\u8F66\u81E3\u6218\u4E89\uFF1A",
		"id":18243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8054",
		"indexes":"dygjrtkdsngr",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u8FDB\u5165\u592A\u7A7A\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u65B0",
		"indexes":"krgqddjxqsnwzqjdzp",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6B4C\u66F2\u201C\u5927\u5200\u8FDB\u884C\u66F2\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u4F5C\u66F2\u5BB6\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6B63\u6559",
		"indexes":"smzjzelsszydzj",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u5B97\u6559\u5728\u4FC4\u7F57\u65AF\u662F\u4E3B\u8981\u7684\u5B97\u6559\uFF1A",
		"id":18246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u5B50",
		"indexes":"wqzygjbzghzxlz",
		"question":"\u56F4\u68CB\u4E2D\u4F9D\u56FD\u9645\u6807\u51C6\u89C4\u4F55\u8005\u5148\u843D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":18247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u8FC1",
		"indexes":"smgsmqsmzsmynwsmxscszz",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u5149\uFF0C\u53F8\u9A6C\u8FC1\uFF0C\u53F8\u9A6C\u662D\uFF0C\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF\uFF0C\u54EA\u4F4D\u53F8\u9A6C\u5148\u751F\u51FA\u751F\u6700\u65E9",
		"id":18248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7A0E",
		"indexes":"zWTOznyzfsswyhfdbhfs",
		"question":"\u5728WTO\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u662F\u552F\u4E00\u5408\u6CD5\u7684\u4FDD\u62A4\u65B9\u5F0F\uFF1F",
		"id":18249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3C\u53E4\u62C9\u4E8C\u4E16",
		"indexes":"elszhywshss",
		"question":"\u4FC4\u7F57\u65AF\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4F4D\u6C99\u7687\u662F\u8C01\uFF1A",
		"id":18250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"60ndnggjdyhyscdsyq",
		"question":"60\u5E74\u4EE3\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u5B87\u822A\u5458\u9996\u6B21\u767B\u4E0A\u6708\u7403\uFF1F",
		"id":18251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"zzqzzgltdxfzmzs",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u4FB5\u5360\u4E2D\u56FD\u9886\u571F\u7684\u897F\u65B9\u6B96\u6C11\u8005\u662F\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9521\u4F2F\u65CF",
		"indexes":"xqjswgngmzdjr",
		"question":"\u897F\u8FC1\u8282\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u8282\u65E5\uFF1F",
		"id":18253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u3001\u5C3C\u8FC7\u5883",
		"indexes":"zmlmfwy",
		"question":"\u73E0\u7A46\u6717\u9A6C\u5CF0\u4F4D\u4E8E\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u51E0\u5185\u4E9A\u5C9B",
		"indexes":"sjszgddy",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u5C9B\u5C7F",
		"id":18255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u695A\u6C49\u4E89\u9738\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"zzdfzyyzzszngcd",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u98CE\u7B5D\u7528\u4E8E\u6218\u4E89\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18256
	},
	{
		"answer":"7\u7C73",
		"indexes":"lsdfedz",
		"question":"\u4E50\u5C71\u5927\u4F5B\u8033\u6735\u957F",
		"id":18257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167",
		"indexes":"hyajsds",
		"question":"\u53F7\u201C\u6613\u5B89\u5C45\u58EB\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18258
	},
	{
		"answer":"2002\u5E745\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"cnynqwgksssxdgjqzxcprzzd",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8D77\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5F00\u59CB\u5B9E\u65BD\u65B0\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u5F3A\u5236\u6027\u4EA7\u54C1\u8BA4\u8BC1\u5236\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":18259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7518\u6CFD\u8C23\u300B",
		"indexes":"ddzjwxbdxswssnrqcyyxnbzp",
		"question":"\u5F53\u4EE3\u4F5C\u5BB6\u738B\u5C0F\u6CE2\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u4E07\u5BFF\u5BFA\u300B\u5185\u5BB9\u53D6\u6750\u4E8E\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u4F53\u6E29\u4FDD\u6301\u6B63\u5E38",
		"indexes":"rzydsylhdyys",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u5728\u8FD0\u52A8\u65F6\u8981\u6D41\u6C57\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u662F\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u9633\u8282",
		"indexes":"sjmfjjbsqzdjjyy",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u53E5\u201C\u6BCF\u9022\u4F73\u8282\u500D\u601D\u4EB2\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4F73\u8282\u201D\u539F\u610F",
		"id":18262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B1B\u798F",
		"indexes":"zpxslbxpljdzzs",
		"question":"\u957F\u7BC7\u5C0F\u8BF4\u3008\u9C81\u6EE8\u900A\u6F02\u6D41\u8BB0\u3009\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18263
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u9897",
		"indexes":"rdryydsk",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7684\u4E73\u7259\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u9897",
		"id":18264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u542C\u89C9",
		"indexes":"gdgjzzcds",
		"question":"\u9F9F\u7684\u611F\u89C9\u4E2D\u6700\u5DEE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u673A\u5931\u4E8B\u8BB0\u5F55\u8D44\u6599\u8C03\u67E5\u539F\u56E0",
		"indexes":"zmhfjdyazhxzdyys",
		"question":"\u5728\u6C11\u822A\u98DE\u673A\u90FD\u8981\u5B89\u88C5\u201C\u9ED1\u5323\u5B50\u201D\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u662F\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zyjsyyxlnglsrw",
		"question":"\u91CD\u9633\u8282\u662F\u7F18\u4E8E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269",
		"id":18267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"xcrfbzdfssy",
		"question":"\u65B0\u6625\u71C3\u653E\u7206\u7AF9\u7684\u98CE\u4FD7\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EA\u6709\u4E0B\u9650\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0A\u9650",
		"indexes":"wdysxxm",
		"question":"\u6E29\u5EA6\u6709\u4E0A\u4E0B\u9650\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6C5F\u5065\u4E09\u90CE",
		"indexes":"cddqnsyxnwzjdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u8FDF\u5230\u7684\u9752\u5E74\u300B\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4F5C\u5BB6\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A0\u5229\u5F17\u5C3C\u4E9A\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"sjzzydITgkjcyjdggwymgdngz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u7684IT\u9AD8\u79D1\u6280\u4EA7\u4E1A\u57FA\u5730\u7845\u8C37\u4F4D\u4E8E\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u90A3\u4E2A\u5DDE",
		"id":18271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58EE\u65CF",
		"indexes":"dylsjsfysmmzdgs",
		"question":"\u7535\u5F71\uFF08\u5218\u4E09\u59D0\uFF09\u662F\u53CD\u6620\u4EC0\u4E48\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":18272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62D2\u7EDD\u6536\u793C",
		"indexes":"tzszwzzzzzshdryzsdtszjhdmds",
		"question":"\u5929\u77E5\u3001\u795E\u77E5\u3001\u6211\u77E5\u3001\u5B50\u77E5\uFF0C\u6700\u65E9\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u4EBA\u6768\u9707\u8BF4\u7684\uFF0C\u4ED6\u8BF4\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BDD\u7684\u76EE\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BBA\u8BED",
		"indexes":"wjswzrjjxdjdhcxlnyzbzqz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u7ECF\u201D\u662F\u4E94\u79CD\u5112\u5BB6\u7ECF\u5B66\u5178\u7C4D\u7684\u5408\u79F0\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u5728\u5176\u4E2D\uFF1F",
		"id":18274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934\u671D\u4E0B",
		"indexes":"qyztrzcss",
		"question":"\u86AF\u8693\u5728\u571F\u58E4\u4E2D\u5403\u98DF\u65F6",
		"id":18275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7535\u5B50\u90AE\u4EF6",
		"indexes":"mqlxdEmaildzwhys",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6D41\u884C\u7684E-mail\u7684\u4E2D\u6587\u542B\u4E49\u662F",
		"id":18276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"zglssdyjzqjysclz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u5BB6\u8BC1\u5238\u4EA4\u6613\u6240\u6210\u7ACB\u5728",
		"id":18277
	},
	{
		"answer":"1997\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgynynshxgzq",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6536\u56DE\u9999\u6E2F\u4E3B\u6743\uFF1F",
		"id":18278
	},
	{
		"answer":"7\u670811\u65E5",
		"indexes":"sjrkrsnyt",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4EBA\u53E3\u65E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":18279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3C\u6CCA\u5C14",
		"indexes":"sjsnggjgqwsjx",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u56FD\u65D7\u4E3A\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\uFF1F",
		"id":18280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73BB\u7483\u7EA4\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"cgtgsygdzds",
		"question":"\u6491\u7AFF\u8DF3\u9AD8\u6240\u7528\u201C\u7AFF\u201D\u7684\u8D28\u5730\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58EE\u65CF",
		"indexes":"wgssmzzrkzdds",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u4E2D\u4EBA\u53E3\u6700\u591A\u7684\u662F\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80AF\u5C3C\u8FEA",
		"indexes":"fwzddmgzts",
		"question":"\u7EEF\u95FB\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7F8E\u56FD\u603B\u7EDF\u662F",
		"id":18283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u5219\u5F90",
		"indexes":"zgjdsszyksjddyrs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u4EE3\u53F2\u4E0A\u7741\u773C\u770B\u4E16\u754C\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u4EF2",
		"indexes":"ssclzzzzwhzsm",
		"question":"\u82CF\u8F7C\u9664\u4E86\u5B57\u5B50\u77BB\u4E4B\u5916\uFF0C\u8FD8\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"ozzsjsmydrbnpdzs",
		"question":"\u6B27\u6D32\u4E2D\u4E16\u7EAA\u4EC0\u4E48\u6837\u7684\u4EBA\u4E0D\u80FD\u4F69\u5E26\u94BB\u77F3",
		"id":18286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6743",
		"indexes":"sgyyzplfryzbdss",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8D54\u4E86\u592B\u4EBA\u53C8\u6298\u5175\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":18287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5904\u6691",
		"indexes":"xlnyjqyqtsgbztyjd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u8282\u6C14\u4E0E\u5176\u5B83\u4E09\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5728\u540C\u4E00\u5B63\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":18288
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgsbqdbhqw",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5546\u6807\u6743\u7684\u4FDD\u62A4\u671F\u4E3A",
		"id":18289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A3D\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"glsssdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u5E7F\u9675\u6563\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1A",
		"id":18290
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"hjlpmxgjmz",
		"question":"\u6D77\u519B\u793C\u70AE\u6BCF\u54CD\u9694\u51E0\u79D2\u949F\uFF1F",
		"id":18291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u656C\u6893",
		"indexes":"rlwsdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u5112\u6797\u5916\u53F2\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u754C\u94F6\u884C\u96C6\u56E2",
		"indexes":"gjkfxhhgjjrgssyyxnygjjrjg",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5F00\u53D1\u534F\u4F1A\u548C\u56FD\u9645\u91D1\u878D\u516C\u53F8\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u56FD\u9645\u91D1\u878D\u673A\u6784\uFF1F",
		"id":18293
	},
	{
		"answer":"13",
		"indexes":"mggqsytw",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u56FD\u65D7\u4E0A\u6709\uFF08\uFF09\u6761\u7EB9\uFF1F",
		"id":18294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5468\u5230\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"sjzpsjlnylssqdsg",
		"question":"\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u4F5C\u54C1\u6536\u96C6\u4E86\u54EA\u4E00\u5386\u53F2\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8BD7\u6B4C",
		"id":18295
	},
	{
		"answer":"37",
		"indexes":"rmyxjnbgdsm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u82F1\u96C4\u7EAA\u5FF5\u7891\u9AD8\u591A\u5C11\u7C73",
		"id":18296
	},
	{
		"answer":"1997",
		"indexes":"ygwfdansznynqs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u738B\u5983\u6234\u5B89\u5A1C\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53BB\u4E16",
		"id":18297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C11\u4E3B\u4E3B\u4E49\u8303\u7574",
		"indexes":"xmzzyshsyyxnyshfc",
		"question":"\u65B0\u6C11\u4E3B\u4E3B\u4E49\u793E\u4F1A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u793E\u4F1A\u8303\u7574\uFF1F",
		"id":18298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u6C49\u957F\u6C5F\u5927\u6865",
		"indexes":"wgjcddyzzjdqs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5EFA\u6210\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u5EA7\u957F\u6C5F\u5927\u6865\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82D7",
		"indexes":"lswsnyssmzdwd",
		"question":"\u82A6\u7B19\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u821E\u8E48",
		"id":18300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E9A\u6D32",
		"indexes":"ylkzggjzngz",
		"question":"\u4F0A\u62C9\u514B\u8FD9\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D32\uFF1F",
		"id":18301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u6851\u6BD4\u514B\u6D77\u5CE1",
		"indexes":"zzdhx",
		"question":"\u6700\u957F\u7684\u6D77\u5CE1",
		"id":18302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u8FB9",
		"indexes":"pdjlsdrxnyb",
		"question":"\u6487\u5200\u656C\u793C\u65F6\uFF0C\u5200\u5203\u50CF\u54EA\u4E00\u8FB9",
		"id":18303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5BB6\u5171\u540C\u5BA3\u8A00\u300B",
		"indexes":"decsjdzzgjffxstyzxxcdbzs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u56FD\u9645\u53CD\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u7EDF\u4E00\u6218\u7EBF\u5F62\u6210\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18304
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"grckzczqzdxdwjgy",
		"question":"\u4E2A\u4EBA\u5B58\u6B3E\u6574\u5B58\u6574\u53D6\u6700\u4F4E\u9650\u5EA6\u4E3A\u51E0\u4E2A\u6708\uFF1F",
		"id":18305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u84DD\u8272\u591A\u7459\u6CB3\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnsgsadlddegg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u6B4C\u662F\u5965\u5730\u5229\u7684\u7B2C\u4E8C\u56FD\u6B4C\uFF1F",
		"id":18306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u718A\u732B",
		"indexes":"sjysswjjhdhhs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u91CE\u751F\u751F\u7269\u57FA\u91D1\u4F1A\u7684\u4F1A\u5FBD\u662F",
		"id":18307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B49\u8FB9\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62",
		"indexes":"zzyddsjxzzydsjxmjzd",
		"question":"\u5468\u957F\u4E00\u5B9A\u7684\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\u4E2D\uFF0C\u600E\u6837\u7684\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\u9762\u79EF\u6700\u5927\uFF1F",
		"id":18308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5B87\u5B99\u98CE\u300B",
		"indexes":"lsdltxzlzyxlnykw",
		"question":"\u8001\u820D\u7684\u300A\u9A86\u9A7C\u7965\u5B50\u300B\u8FDE\u8F7D\u4E8E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u520A\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"zzdxyjsyyclnzdwd",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u8840\u538B\u8BA1\u662F\u7528\u4E8E\u6D4B\u91CF\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u7684",
		"id":18310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"jpmczngcd",
		"question":"\u91D1\u74F6\u6885\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E90\u5C71",
		"indexes":"sjwhjgzzgd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6587\u5316\u666F\u89C2\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684",
		"id":18312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u4FAF\u738B",
		"indexes":"sjzdsjsjsmrzdc",
		"question":"\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E16\u5BB6\u201D\u662F\u7ED9\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EBA\u4F5C\u7684\u4F20",
		"id":18313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963FQ",
		"indexes":"sjwxhlzwydgwxxxs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6587\u5B66\u753B\u5ECA\u4E2D\u552F\u4E00\u7684\u56FD\u6587\u5B66\u5F62\u8C61\u662F?",
		"id":18314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8299\u84C9\u82B1",
		"indexes":"cddsh",
		"question":"\u6210\u90FD\u7684\u5E02\u82B1?",
		"id":18315
	},
	{
		"answer":"1961",
		"indexes":"dycfxywwxsnn",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53D1\u73B0\u6708\u5916\u536B\u661F\u662F\u54EA\u5E74",
		"id":18316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690",
		"indexes":"hdgjxczqhbsyysyz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4F55\u5F53\u5171\u526A\u897F\u7A97\u70DB\uFF0C\u5374\u8BDD\u5DF4\u5C71\u591C\u96E8\u65F6\u3002\u201D\u8BED\u81EA\uFF1A",
		"id":18317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8239\u653F\u5B66\u5802",
		"indexes":"zgqmzzdhjxts",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6E05\u672B\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6D77\u519B\u5B66\u5802\u662F",
		"id":18318
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u4EBF\u7ACB\u65B9\u7C73",
		"indexes":"qgmnpmdlddss",
		"question":"\u5168\u56FD\u6BCF\u5E74\u8DD1\u3001\u5192\u3001\u6EF4\u3001\u6F0F\u7684\u6DE1\u6C34\u662F",
		"id":18319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u54F2\u4F26",
		"indexes":"mmhwjdrs",
		"question":"\u547D\u540D\u201C\u597D\u671B\u89D2\u201D\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u8C0B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xzzddwgjndjzgrly",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5728\u77E5\u9053\u7684\u6211\u56FD\u5883\u5185\u7684\u8F83\u65E9\u53E4\u4EBA\u7C7B\u6709",
		"id":18321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u660C\u65CF",
		"indexes":"zmdhsdsngssmzdtssgzp",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u6237\u6492\u5200\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u7279\u8272\u624B\u5DE5\u5236\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5B97\u5802",
		"indexes":"wgzzcbhjxxdrs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u521B\u529E\u6D77\u519B\u5B66\u6821\u7684\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":18323
	},
	{
		"answer":"1913",
		"indexes":"tgehnndnbewxj",
		"question":"\u6CF0\u6208\u5C14\u83B7\u54EA\u5E74\u7684\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u6587\u5B66\u5956",
		"id":18324
	},
	{
		"answer":"1999\u5E741\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"oyyhszsds",
		"question":"\u6B27\u5143\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\u6B63\u5F0F\u8BDE\u751F",
		"id":18325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u6069\u6765",
		"indexes":"tamqrmyxjnbbmdbwsstxd",
		"question":"\u5929\u5B89\u95E8\u524D\u4EBA\u6C11\u82F1\u96C4\u7EAA\u5FF5\u7891\u80CC\u9762\u7684\u7891\u6587\u662F\u8C01\u9898\u5199\u7684",
		"id":18326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u4F4D\u62A4\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"tlbbszfjzdsm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u9F99\u516B\u90E8\u201D\u662F\u6307\u4F5B\u6559\u4E2D\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":18327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70ED\u6708\u653F\u53D8",
		"indexes":"bz18sjmfgzcjjgmjsdsjs",
		"question":"\u6807\u5FD718\u4E16\u7EAA\u672B\u6CD5\u56FD\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u7ED3\u675F\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6\u662F",
		"id":18328
	},
	{
		"answer":"360",
		"indexes":"yssmmdsm",
		"question":"\u97F3\u901F\u662F\u6BCF\u79D2\u591A\u5C11\u7C73\uFF1F",
		"id":18329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EAA\u5FF5\u91CA\u8FE6\u725F\u5C3C",
		"indexes":"zgmjwsmyclbz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u95F4\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u8981\u5403\u814A\u516B\u7CA5",
		"id":18330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u705E\u6865",
		"indexes":"wccyyqcfszxzsxdsmdf",
		"question":"\u201C\u6E2D\u57CE\u671D\u96E8\u9091\u6E05\u6668\u201D\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u73B0\u5728\u9655\u897F\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":18331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxnzsbsywy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u5EA7\u5C71\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u4E94\u5CB3\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u82CF",
		"indexes":"ygdmjxdywgdngs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u7684\u9762\u79EF\u76F8\u5F53\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701?",
		"id":18333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u60E0\u5802",
		"indexes":"dywrgjzlfzxdhrs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u4EFB\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u526F\u4E3B\u5E2D\u7684\u534E\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":18334
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u8499",
		"indexes":"xlkxjtsddgtljhnbejds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u540C\u65F6\u5F97\u5230\u8FC7\u56FE\u7075\u5956\u548C\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbslhgcrlsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":18336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjszddyskwy",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u9668\u77F3\u5751\u4F4D\u4E8E?",
		"id":18337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E90\u5C71",
		"indexes":"lbdsjysyhljtmhdszgnzmsdpb",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u201C\u7591\u662F\u94F6\u6CB3\u843D\u4E5D\u5929\u201D\u63CF\u7ED8\u7684\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u5EA7\u540D\u5C71\u7684\u7011\u5E03\u3002",
		"id":18338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"cyxsyngcd",
		"question":"\u5403\u5143\u5BB5\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3",
		"id":18339
	},
	{
		"answer":"1217\u5E74\u81F31223\u5E74",
		"indexes":"mgdycxzs",
		"question":"\u8499\u53E4\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u897F\u5F81\u662F",
		"id":18340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5410\u9C81\u756A\u76C6\u5730",
		"indexes":"zgzrddfzn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u70ED\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u5728\u54EA?",
		"id":18341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u9648\u4EE3\u8C22",
		"indexes":"swjxyqsmhddjcs",
		"question":"\u751F\u7269\u8FDB\u884C\u4E00\u5207\u751F\u547D\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u57FA\u7840\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6C14\u538B",
		"indexes":"szdsdftgjqjynzys",
		"question":"\u6C34\u5728\u591A\u5C11\u5EA6\u6CB8\u817E\u5173\u952E\u53D6\u51B3\u4E8E\u54EA\u79CD\u56E0\u7D20\uFF1F",
		"id":18343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0F\u5C14\u52A0\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"xlnthwnlhzblrhydh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u6761\u6CB3\u4E3A\u5185\u6D41\u6CB3\uFF08\u6307\u4E0D\u6D41\u5165\u6D77\u6D0B\u7684\u6CB3\uFF09\uFF1F",
		"id":18344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7231\u56E0\u65AF\u5766",
		"indexes":"xdlsstcd",
		"question":"\u76F8\u5BF9\u8BBA\u662F\u8C01\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82A5\u5B50\u6C14\u70AE\u5F39",
		"indexes":"xlnyzwqsgjfmqgdjzzzzzsyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6B66\u5668\u662F\u56FD\u9645\u6CD5\u660E\u786E\u89C4\u5B9A\u7981\u6B62\u5728\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49",
		"indexes":"tysjysnbmzldgs",
		"question":"\u2018\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u2019\u662F\u54EA\u90E8\u540D\u8457\u91CC\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\uFF1F",
		"id":18347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u94A2\u77F3",
		"indexes":"zrjzyzdzydwzs",
		"question":"\u81EA\u7136\u754C\u4E2D\u5DF2\u77E5\u7684\u6700\u786C\u7684\u7269\u8D28\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"fjsccrwgd",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u6559\u662F\u4ECE\uFF08\uFF09\u4F20\u5165\u6211\u56FD\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C64\u663E\u7956",
		"indexes":"cqjbmdtdzzs",
		"question":"\u4F20\u5947\u5267\u672C\u300A\u7261\u4E39\u4EAD\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C1\u8361\u5C71",
		"indexes":"bcwtxqxdsfs",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5929\u4E0B\u9F50\u79C0\u201D\u7684\u5C71\u5CF0\u662F\uFF08\uFF09\u3002",
		"id":18351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"zgdscqmxzdadccdjcpdsq",
		"question":"\u5728\u53E4\u4EE3\uFF0C\u8C01\u91C7\u53D6\u201C\u660E\u4FEE\u6808\u9053\uFF0C\u6697\u6E21\u9648\u4ED3\u201D\u7684\u8BA1\u7B56\uFF0C\u5E73\u5B9A\u4E09\u79E6\uFF1F",
		"id":18352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u8C79",
		"indexes":"xmnzdwnjhbjdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5357\u6781\u548C\u5317\u6781\u90FD\u6709\uFF1F",
		"id":18353
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"nbejgfsdsx",
		"question":"\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u5171\u5206\u8BBE\u591A\u5C11\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":18354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"jyswgnghdsydnh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5EFA\u5143\u201D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u90A3\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5E74\u53F7",
		"id":18355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6838\u9EC4\u7D20",
		"indexes":"wssB2yjsm",
		"question":"\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20B2\u53C8\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18356
	},
	{
		"answer":"60\u591A\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"ezzydsggjcz",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53C2\u6218\uFF1F",
		"id":18357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9A6C\u5578\u897F\u98CE",
		"indexes":"jyxszbywwxswsds",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5EB8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\uFF0C\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u6B66\u4FA0\u6563\u6587\u8BD7\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E9A\u70ED\u5E26",
		"indexes":"gdscynyzqhqy",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u4E1C\u662F\u5904\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6C14\u5019\u533A\u57DF\uFF1F",
		"id":18359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6838\u6843",
		"indexes":"yxnzggzdzfhlzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u5E72\u679C\u4E2D\u7684\u8102\u80AA\u542B\u91CF\u6700\u9AD8",
		"id":18360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA\u83B1",
		"indexes":"dtdlcthhymyc",
		"question":"\u201C\u51AC\u5929\u5230\u4E86\uFF0C\u6625\u5929\u8FD8\u4F1A\u8FDC\u5417\u201D\u8BED\u51FA",
		"id":18361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F6F\u9A71",
		"indexes":"xlsydndsrscsbds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7535\u8111\u7684\u8F93\u5165\u8F93\u51FA\u8BBE\u5907\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nplsnggjdr",
		"question":"\u62FF\u7834\u4ED1\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18363
	},
	{
		"answer":"1867",
		"indexes":"nbenynfmlg",
		"question":"\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53D1\u660E\u96F7\u7BA1\uFF1F",
		"id":18364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u830E",
		"indexes":"ycsnygbf",
		"question":"\u6D0B\u8471\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u90E8\u5206\uFF1F",
		"id":18365
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C88\u9633",
		"indexes":"wgsdzsgzydwsgzly",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u56DB\u5927\u85CF\u4E66\u9601\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u6587\u6714\u9601\u5750\u843D\u4E8E",
		"id":18366
	},
	{
		"answer":"1978",
		"indexes":"dyjsnzqbssznynjxd",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u5BA4\u5185\u8DB3\u7403\u6BD4\u8D5B\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78F7",
		"indexes":"mjssdghqssnzhxysdzy",
		"question":"\u6C11\u95F4\u6240\u8BF4\u7684\u9B3C\u706B\u5176\u5B9E\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u5316\u5B66\u5143\u7D20\u7684\u4F5C\u7528",
		"id":18368
	},
	{
		"answer":"1953",
		"indexes":"wgdygwnjhcnynks",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E94\u5E74\u8BA1\u5212\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5F00\u59CB\uFF1F",
		"id":18369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"sjszddhdz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u706B\u7535\u7AD9",
		"id":18370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D2A\u8FC8",
		"indexes":"rzsbssdzz",
		"question":"\u300A\u5BB9\u658B\u968F\u7B14\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8457\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u96E8",
		"indexes":"ldhzgysxxcznbzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u9C81\u5927\u6D77\u201D\u8FD9\u4E2A\u827A\u672F\u5F62\u8C61\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A0\u62FF\u5927",
		"indexes":"sjzddhzzhwynggj",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6E56\u4E2D\u4E4B\u6E56\u4F4D\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6",
		"id":18373
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u79CD",
		"indexes":"gjwhscsdhlyjzbsfsff",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5916\u6C47\u5E02\u573A\u4E0A\u7684\u6C47\u7387\u6709\u51E0\u79CD\u8868\u793A\u65B9\u5F0F\u65B9\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":18374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u8083\u971C",
		"indexes":"xmdnyyznwsjjyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u7684\u5973\u6F14\u5458\u4E2D\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4EAC\u5267\u6F14\u5458",
		"id":18375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u7136\u6761\u4EF6",
		"indexes":"gjfgcshfzdjcs",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5206\u5DE5\u4EA7\u751F\u548C\u53D1\u5C55\u7684\u57FA\u7840\u662F",
		"id":18376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6D77",
		"indexes":"tygsdlzbszn",
		"question":"\u7EDF\u4E00\u516C\u53F8\u5927\u9646\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":18377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"cwwgssj30ndwhgmdzjds",
		"question":"\u6210\u4E3A\u6211\u56FD\u4E0A\u4E16\u7EAA30\u5E74\u4EE3\u6587\u5316\u9769\u547D\u7684\u4E3B\u5C06\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u96B6",
		"indexes":"xlnghdqdbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u8FC1\u90FD\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":18379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8304\u679C\u7C7B",
		"indexes":"wmccdljsysmlsc",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u5E38\u5403\u7684\u8FA3\u6912\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u852C\u83DC",
		"id":18380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6FC0\u5149",
		"indexes":"lszds",
		"question":"\u201C\u956D\u5C04\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u7701",
		"indexes":"sdkzhbby",
		"question":"\u77F3\u8FBE\u5F00\u6700\u540E\u5175\u8D25\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u9633",
		"indexes":"xmnygshx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6052\u661F\uFF1A",
		"id":18383
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64\u96C0\u697C",
		"indexes":"xlngbswgsdml",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u697C\uFF1F",
		"id":18384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u632A\u5A01\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"dygddnjdrsngr",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5230\u8FBE\u5357\u6781\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18385
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u964D\u4F4E\u4F53\u6E29",
		"indexes":"xtdxbtdydedzyswl",
		"question":"\u590F\u5929\u5927\u8C61\u4E0D\u505C\u5730\u6447\u52A8\u8033\u6735\u4E3B\u8981\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86",
		"id":18386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E24\u6D77",
		"indexes":"swd33211hjgczdyhszsmh",
		"question":"\u6240\u8C13\u7684'33211'\u73AF\u5883\u5DE5\u7A0B\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u6D77\u662F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\u6D77",
		"id":18387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"xlbsytsbdjzyds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u65AF\u7279",
		"indexes":"zbhmyllzbhyzgylldtczs",
		"question":"\u5728\u4FDD\u62A4\u8D38\u6613\u7406\u8BBA\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4FDD\u62A4\u5E7C\u7A1A\u5DE5\u4E1A\u7406\u8BBA\u7684\u63D0\u51FA\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18389
	},
	{
		"answer":"30\u6BEB\u5B89",
		"indexes":"gjgdrtyxtgdgpdlwdsha",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u89C4\u5B9A\u4EBA\u4F53\u5141\u8BB8\u901A\u8FC7\u7684\u5DE5\u9891\u7535\u6D41\u4E3A\u591A\u5C11\u6BEB\u5B89\uFF1F",
		"id":18390
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.93%",
		"indexes":"qjdkqzhydsy",
		"question":"\u6E05\u6D01\u7684\u7A7A\u6C14\u4E2D\u542B\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6C29?",
		"id":18391
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u76C6\u5730",
		"indexes":"wgdtfzgzdsnl",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u201C\u5929\u5E9C\u4E4B\u56FD\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18392
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjsdymypdsz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u90AE\u7968\u8BDE\u751F\u5728",
		"id":18393
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u5FB7\u683C\u5C14",
		"indexes":"czysjssdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u5B58\u5728\u4E0E\u65F6\u95F4\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u81F3\u65E5",
		"indexes":"tyzsbhgxsysbbqd",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u76F4\u5C04\u5317\u56DE\u5F52\u7EBF\u65F6\uFF0C\u5E94\u662F\u5317\u534A\u7403\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18395
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u9633",
		"indexes":"bcwzggddygjydylcwyxzd",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u76D1\u72F1\u7684\u7F91\u91CC\u57CE\u4F4D\u4E8E\u73B0\u5728\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18396
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u817F\u90E8",
		"indexes":"xsjzededzznl",
		"question":"\u87CB\u87C0\uFF0C\u91D1\u949F\u513F\u7684\u201C\u8033\u6735\u201D\u957F\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u6D77",
		"indexes":"wgclhbsysmhdpjhbpmzwld",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6D4B\u91CF\u6D77\u62D4\u662F\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u6D77\u7684\u5E73\u5747\u6D77\u62D4\u5E73\u9762\u4F5C\u4E3A\u96F6\u70B9",
		"id":18398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u6210\u516C\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"bdlgzcswsjzd",
		"question":"\u5E03\u8FBE\u62C9\u5BAB\u6700\u521D\u662F\u4E3A\u8C01\u5EFA\u9020\u7684?",
		"id":18399
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u6743\u5229\u673A\u5173",
		"indexes":"rmdbdhswgd",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u4EE3\u8868\u5927\u4F1A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510",
		"indexes":"gy618907nswggdngcd",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143618\uFF0D907\u5E74\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3",
		"id":18401
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B",
		"indexes":"dspwjxbryszssdsj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8BFB\u4E66\u7834\u4E07\u5377\uFF0C\u4E0B\u7B14\u5982\u6709\u795E\u201D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":18402
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u4F4D",
		"indexes":"ylkghgdsycljsjdjw",
		"question":"\u4F0A\u62C9\u514B\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u7684\u77F3\u6CB9\u50A8\u91CF\u5C45\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u51E0\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":18403
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F5D\u65CF",
		"indexes":"asmsngmzdgs",
		"question":"\u963F\u8BD7\u739B\u662F\u90A3\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\uFF1F",
		"id":18404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u6C5F\u5973\u795E",
		"indexes":"bqtysmmy",
		"question":"\u767D\u9CCD\u8C5A\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u7F8E\u8A89\uFF1F",
		"id":18405
	},
	{
		"answer":"CPU",
		"indexes":"dnyshkzdhxssm",
		"question":"\u7535\u8111\u8FD0\u7B97\u548C\u63A7\u5236\u7684\u6838\u5FC3\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18406
	},
	{
		"answer":"6\u500D",
		"indexes":"dqdzlwyqsd",
		"question":"\u5730\u7403\u7684\u91CD\u529B\u4E3A\u6708\u7403\u4E0A\u7684",
		"id":18407
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u5316\u6DF3",
		"indexes":"mcdsqrhdzyjzw18nsjdq17ndhgsnyg",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u7B2C\u5341\u4E03\u4EFB\u7687\u5E1D\u6731\u7531\u68C0\u5728\u4F4D18\u5E74\uFF0C\u5B9E\u9645\u5F53\u674317\u5E74\u7684\u5BA6\u5B98\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18408
	},
	{
		"answer":"1990\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgdwgpqwhryscnynq",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5BF9\u5916\u56FD\u6D3E\u9063\u7EF4\u548C\u4EBA\u5458\u662F\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8D77\uFF1F",
		"id":18409
	},
	{
		"answer":"1896",
		"indexes":"dyjxdayhynnjx",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u73B0\u4EE3\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E8E\u54EA\u5E74\u4E3E\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":18410
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EE\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xjpddmyydwygzgdws",
		"question":"\u65B0\u52A0\u5761\u7684\u5F97\u540D\u4E0E\u4E00\u52A8\u7269\u6709\u5173\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F",
		"id":18411
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"xhcljjjzyqtlstdzzscdcds",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u8377\u624D\u9732\u5C16\u5C16\u89D2\uFF0C\u65E9\u6709\u873B\u8713\u7ACB\u4E0A\u5934\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u6240\u5904\u7684\u671D\u4EE3\u662F",
		"id":18412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5185\u6E56\u7B2C\u4E00\u6865",
		"indexes":"thdqjswxsysmch",
		"question":"\u592A\u6E56\u5927\u6865\uFF08\u6C5F\u82CF\u5434\u53BF\u5E02\uFF09\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":18413
	},
	{
		"answer":"1980.8",
		"indexes":"wgxbjjtqwclfcxszsmsj",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5174\u529E\u7ECF\u6D4E\u7279\u533A\u5B8C\u6210\u7ACB\u6CD5\u7A0B\u5E8F\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":18414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7236\u5B50",
		"indexes":"jydxssdyxczoyfhoykssmgx",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5EB8\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u5C04\u96D5\u82F1\u96C4\u4F20\u300B\u4E2D\u6B27\u9633\u950B\u548C\u6B27\u9633\u514B\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB\uFF1F",
		"id":18415
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u5C81",
		"indexes":"rgzds",
		"question":"\u5F31\u51A0\u6307\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18416
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u745E\u58EB\u7684\u65E5\u5185\u74E6",
		"indexes":"sjszzyxhbsdcss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7528\u9C9C\u82B1\u62A5\u65F6\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18417
	},
	{
		"answer":"3-5\u70B9",
		"indexes":"wggddyszxddsmsj",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u201C\u5BC5\u201D\u65F6\u6307\u73B0\u4EE3\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":18418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"zgjdlszzdcss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5EFA\u90FD\u5386\u53F2\u6700\u957F\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F",
		"id":18419
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D\u672B\u671F",
		"indexes":"xslcyjfydssmsqdshxs",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u8001\u6B8B\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u53CD\u6620\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u793E\u4F1A\u73B0\u5B9E",
		"id":18420
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u52D2\u65AF\u5766",
		"indexes":"sjszzcsjddgjs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u4EA7\u751F\u57FA\u7763\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjshhxfzddgjs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u82B1\u5349\u6D88\u8D39\u6700\u591A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u96EA\u82B9",
		"indexes":"qwsdgdmzzdhlmssdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u56DB\u5927\u53E4\u5178\u540D\u8457\u4E2D\u7684\u300A\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":18423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u6C14\u6674\u6717\uFF0C\u4E07\u7269\u6ECB\u751F",
		"indexes":"nlzqmdyss",
		"question":"\u519C\u5386\u4E2D\u201C\u6E05\u660E\u201D\u7684\u610F\u601D\u662F",
		"id":18424
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E9A\u7279\u4E9A\u5927\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"zgppqdznycayhssxldycdmg",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E52\u4E53\u7403\u961F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u6B21\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E0A\u5B9E\u73B0\u4E86\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u201C\u5927\u6EE1\u8D2F\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18425
	},
	{
		"answer":"1992\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgdycpqgbbdcjwhxdscnynq",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u6D3E\u9063\u5DE5\u5175\u90E8\u961F\u53C2\u52A0\u7EF4\u548C\u884C\u52A8\u662F\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8D77\uFF1F",
		"id":18426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0F\u5C14\u52A0\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"ozzzdhls",
		"question":"\u6B27\u6D32\u6700\u957F\u7684\u6CB3\u6D41\u662F",
		"id":18427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u53F7",
		"indexes":"lqzdyhyc",
		"question":"\u4E50\u5668\u4E2D\u7684\u5706\u53F7\u53C8\u79F0\uFF1A",
		"id":18428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20B2",
		"indexes":"kqyknywqfsmyq",
		"question":"\u53E3\u8154\u708E\u53EF\u80FD\u56E0\u4E3A\u7F3A\u4E4F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F15\u8D77\uFF1F",
		"id":18429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u7701",
		"indexes":"lsdfz",
		"question":"\u4E50\u5C71\u5927\u4F5B\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":18430
	},
	{
		"answer":"25-50\u4E07\u5B89\u57F9",
		"indexes":"ldxcdsjdlkd",
		"question":"\u96F7\u7535\u5F62\u6210\u7684\u77AC\u95F4\u7535\u6D41\u53EF\u8FBE\uFF1A",
		"id":18431
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"csghshhdsnggjdr",
		"question":"\u57CE\u5E02\u89C4\u5212\u5E08\u970D\u534E\u5FB7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F1",
		"indexes":"gjmyqsybhxmnyzjsdhjzc",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u7C73\u539F\u5668\u662F\u7531\u94C2\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u91D1\u5C5E\u7684\u5408\u91D1\u5236\u6210\uFF1F",
		"id":18433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u604B\u66F21990",
		"indexes":"ldydzpy",
		"question":"\u7F57\u5927\u4F51\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":18434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B0\u5C9B",
		"indexes":"lkywksnggjsd",
		"question":"\u96F7\u514B\u4E9A\u672A\u514B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u9996\u90FD\uFF1F",
		"id":18435
	},
	{
		"answer":"5\uFF5E6",
		"indexes":"lnrmrdzcsmsjysdsxs",
		"question":"\u8001\u5E74\u4EBA\u6BCF\u65E5\u7684\u6B63\u5E38\u7761\u7720\u65F6\u95F4\u5E94\u662F\u591A\u5C11\u5C0F\u65F6\uFF1A",
		"id":18436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u77EE\u661F",
		"indexes":"tysmdzdssm",
		"question":"\u592A\u9633\u751F\u547D\u7684\u7EC8\u70B9\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lxsydqgjds",
		"question":"\u7387\u5148\u4F7F\u7528\u6BD2\u6C14\u653B\u51FB\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"kzzjldpm",
		"question":"\u5B54\u5B50\u5728\u5BB6\u91CC\u7684\u6392\u540D\uFF1A",
		"id":18439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u918B",
		"indexes":"lnrccydjx",
		"question":"\u8001\u5E74\u4EBA\u5403\u83DC\u5E94\u591A\u52A0\u4E9B\uFF1A",
		"id":18440
	},
	{
		"answer":"5000\u5143",
		"indexes":"mqwgcbqxdqcxdqcjew",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6211\u56FD\u5B58\u672C\u53D6\u606F\u5B9A\u671F\u50A8\u84C4\u7684\u8D77\u5B58\u91D1\u989D\u4E3A",
		"id":18441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u5EA7\u5C0F\u5C71\u5CF0",
		"indexes":"sjsqdqdglnzys",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u201C\u65F6\u533A\u201D\u7684\u8D77\u70B9\u683C\u6797\u5C3C\u6CBB\u539F\u662F",
		"id":18442
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u628A\u5E8A\u653E\u4E0B\u6765",
		"indexes":"xtdzcyss",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0B\u69BB\u201D\u7684\u6700\u521D\u610F\u601D\u662F",
		"id":18443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8179\u6CFB",
		"indexes":"kfwssCjlmrcg1kkdz",
		"question":"\u53E3\u670D\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20C\u5242\u91CF\u6BCF\u65E5\u8D85\u8FC71\u514B\u53EF\u5BFC\u81F4\uFF1A",
		"id":18444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C",
		"indexes":"dlgyhhbsgqwgszwyzpyrpsrhdzzs",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u8054\u201C\u8D35\u6709\u6052\u4F55\u5FC5\u4E09\u66F4\u8D77\u4E94\u66F4\u7761\uFF0C\u6700\u65E0\u76CA\u53EA\u6015\u4E00\u65E5\u66DD\u5341\u65E5\u5BD2\u201D\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18445
	},
	{
		"answer":"65",
		"indexes":"c1901nd1973nd72nzgydsmytrhdnbej",
		"question":"\u4ECE1901\u5E74\u52301973\u5E74\u768472\u5E74\u4E2D\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u540D\u72B9\u592A\u4EBA\u83B7\u5F97\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\uFF1F",
		"id":18446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"xxlymldfnsngr",
		"question":"\u73B0\u6548\u529B\u4E8E\u66FC\u8054\u7684\u8303\u5C3C\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E03\u9C81\u585E\u5C14",
		"indexes":"snxhtxzly",
		"question":"\u6492\u5C3F\u5C0F\u5B69\u94DC\u50CF\u5750\u843D\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EE\u57CE\u4E2D\u6587\u56FD\u9645\u8FA9\u8BBA\u8D5B",
		"indexes":"zmxsjjysncgjzwblsdpw",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u91D1\u5EB8\u662F\u54EA\u6B21\u56FD\u9645\u4E2D\u6587\u8FA9\u8BBA\u8D5B\u7684\u8BC4\u59D4",
		"id":18449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EC1\u8005",
		"indexes":"jyxsyydzdyysdydskzwdlydskzsm",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5EB8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u9E33\u9E2F\u5200\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u9E33\u9E2F\u53CC\u5200\uFF0C\u4E00\u5200\u4E0A\u523B\u7740\u201C\u65E0\u654C\u201D\uFF0C\u53E6\u4E00\u5200\u4E0A\u523B\u7740\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":18450
	},
	{
		"answer":"191",
		"indexes":"shszbqdzbgynyyzsjrxsdmqwgmjysmnd",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u5E02\u95F8\u5317\u533A\u7684\u95F8\u5317\u516C\u56ED\u5185\uFF0C\u6709\u4E00\u5EA7\u5B8B\u6559\u4EC1\u5148\u751F\u7684\u5893\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8BE5\u5893\u5EFA\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E74\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9521",
		"indexes":"qtsthnzjsdhj",
		"question":"\u9752\u94DC\u662F\u94DC\u548C\u54EA\u79CD\u91D1\u5C5E\u7684\u5408\u91D1\uFF1F",
		"id":18452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5B50",
		"indexes":"ymzzdgsssjd",
		"question":"\u63E0\u82D7\u52A9\u957F\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u662F\u8C01\u8BB2\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A6\u5F97",
		"indexes":"tdzmwxjlyxz",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u5B57",
		"id":18454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6444\u6C0F-273.15\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"jdlds",
		"question":"\u201C\u7EDD\u5BF9\u96F6\u5EA6\u201D\u662F",
		"id":18455
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u664F\u5B50\u6625\u79CB\u300B",
		"indexes":"zzqlbyysyc",
		"question":"\u667A\u8005\u5343\u8651\uFF0C\u5FC5\u6709\u4E00\u5931\u8BED\u51FA",
		"id":18456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5E",
		"indexes":"zcwztxwycxytdjssnz",
		"question":"\u5728\u5E38\u6E29\u72B6\u6001\u4E0B\u552F\u4E00\u5448\u73B0\u6DB2\u6001\u7684\u91D1\u5C5E\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":18457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"jllytdwyjsxlgc",
		"question":"\u4F3D\u5229\u7565\u7528\u4ED6\u7684\u671B\u8FDC\u955C\u9996\u5148\u6765\u89C2\u5BDF\uFF1A",
		"id":18458
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u897F\u91CC\u5C9B",
		"indexes":"lmdwkzdygmbjsjtjzld",
		"question":"\u7F57\u9A6C\u5BF9\u5916\u6269\u5F20\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u76EE\u6807\u5C31\u662F\u8FE6\u592A\u57FA\u5360\u9886\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u672B",
		"indexes":"sccxz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u66F9\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":18460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5357",
		"indexes":"sbfhltxbbkdsqs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u5317\u9632\u62A4\u6797\u4F53\u7CFB\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u7684\u7701\u533A\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C5\u5178\u5A1C",
		"indexes":"gxlshzbczzhnsdsnyw",
		"question":"\u53E4\u5E0C\u814A\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C\u667A\u6167\u5973\u795E\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":18462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u6559\u540D\u8BCD",
		"indexes":"jyxstlbbdsmysmhy",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5EB8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u5929\u9F99\u516B\u90E8\u300B\u7684\u4E66\u540D\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u542B\u4E49",
		"id":18463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5144\u59B9\u5173\u7CFB",
		"indexes":"zzggdcszfxhnwssmgx",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4F0F\u7FB2\u548C\u5973\u5A32\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB\uFF1F",
		"id":18464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5B9E\u752B",
		"indexes":"xxjsyzjdsdaqjzytdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u897F\u53A2\u8BB0\u300B\u662F\u5143\u6742\u5267\u7684\u56DB\u5927\u7231\u60C5\u5267\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u5B83\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FE1\u5929\u7FC1",
		"indexes":"sjsyyzddnsnyzn",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7FBD\u7FFC\u6700\u5927\u7684\u9E1F\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":18466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CF0\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlsgdzgdnggjdch",
		"question":"\u201C\u66B9\u7F57\u201D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u5BF9\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u79F0\u547C\uFF1F",
		"id":18467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u5C45\u6613",
		"indexes":"rcjhhshcljslwlssdzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E5\u51FA\u6C5F\u82B1\u7EA2\u4F3C\u706B\uFF0C\u6625\u6765\u6C5F\u6C34\u7EFF\u4E3A\u84DD\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1A",
		"id":18468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809D\u7EC6\u80DE",
		"indexes":"dzysmqgfm",
		"question":"\u80C6\u6C41\u7531\u4EC0\u4E48\u5668\u5B98\u5206\u6CCC\uFF1A",
		"id":18469
	},
	{
		"answer":"3\u5E74",
		"indexes":"yhjwrshpctqgsdsxqjwjn",
		"question":"\u56E0\u73AF\u5883\u6C61\u67D3\u635F\u5BB3\u8D54\u507F\u63D0\u8D77\u516C\u8BC9\u7684\u65F6\u6548\u671F\u95F4\u4E3A\u51E0\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6ED1\u94C1\u5362\u6865",
		"indexes":"zmyphdlqdqsnzq",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u5F71\u7247\u300A\u9B42\u65AD\u84DD\u6865\u300B\u7684\u6865\u662F\u54EA\u5EA7\u6865\uFF1F",
		"id":18471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u64E6\u5242",
		"indexes":"yglmydjlzzfqdzys",
		"question":"\u7259\u818F\u91CC\u9762\u6709\u7684\u52A0\u4E86\u73CD\u73E0\u7C89\uFF0C\u8D77\u7684\u4F5C\u7528\u662F",
		"id":18472
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9541",
		"indexes":"wmrcsydybdfbslhsmdhj",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u65E5\u5E38\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u786C\u5E01\u7684\u5206\u5E01\u77F3\u94DD\u548C\u4EC0\u4E48\u7684\u5408\u91D1\uFF1F",
		"id":18473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u6E90",
		"indexes":"bzwnpsshcsrdsnwzmhj",
		"question":"\u88AB\u5C0A\u4E3A\u5357\u6D3E\u5C71\u6C34\u753B\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u7684\u662F\u90A3\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u516C\u671B",
		"indexes":"fcsjtssdmz",
		"question":"\u300A\u5BCC\u6625\u5C71\u5C45\u56FE\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u540D\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18475
	},
	{
		"answer":"1938",
		"indexes":"mgdzgcshszcsjsdykjcdl",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u7535\u5B50\u5DE5\u7A0B\u5E08\u4F55\u65F6\u5236\u6210\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u5757\u96C6\u6210\u7535\u8DEF?",
		"id":18476
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u8111",
		"indexes":"rnkzrphlds",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u8111\u63A7\u5236\u4EBA\u5E73\u8861\u529B\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18477
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u4F5B\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"mglssdysgdxfs",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6240\u9AD8\u7B49\u5B66\u5E9C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18478
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u53C2",
		"indexes":"bckylwz",
		"question":"\u68D2\u68F0\u201D\u53EF\u7528\u6765\u5A49\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":18479
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F6A\u884C\u6781\u5176\u4E25\u91CD\u7684",
		"indexes":"sxzsyyfzfz",
		"question":"\u6B7B\u5211\u53EA\u9002\u7528\u4E8E\uFF08\uFF09\u72AF\u7F6A\u5206\u5B50",
		"id":18480
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u80A0",
		"indexes":"yywzdbfznyqgxs",
		"question":"\u8425\u517B\u7269\u8D28\u5927\u90E8\u5206\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5668\u5B98\u5438\u6536\uFF1A",
		"id":18481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"wgssjsjyyjlsdgjwggdldrmksltdlssqs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u5177\u6709\u60A0\u4E45\u5386\u53F2\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u52B3\u52A8\u4EBA\u6C11\u5F00\u59CB\u70BC\u94C1\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u65F6\u671F\u662F",
		"id":18482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E8B\u9E7F",
		"indexes":"yyzjxltxmsxltxnddwscsbxtdxmjsm",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E00\u79CD\u89D2\u8C61\u9E7F\u3001\u5934\u8C61\u9A6C\u3001\u8EAB\u8C61\u9A74\u3001\u8E44\u8C61\u725B\u7684\u52A8\u7269\u4FD7\u79F0\u201C\u56DB\u4E0D\u50CF\u201D\u5B83\u7684\u5B66\u540D\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732B\u718A\u79D1",
		"indexes":"xmswgdgbnmxmsynyk",
		"question":"\u718A\u732B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u56FD\u5B9D\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u718A\u732B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u79D1\uFF1F",
		"id":18484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62B9\u9999\u9CB8",
		"indexes":"lxxczsmj",
		"question":"\u9F99\u6D8E\u9999\u51FA\u81EA\u4EC0\u4E48\u9CB8\uFF1F",
		"id":18485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809D",
		"indexes":"rtfjhdxjjdqgs",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u5206\u89E3\u548C\u4EE3\u8C22\u9152\u7CBE\u7684\u5668\u5B98\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CA9\u77F3\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"zczzqhd",
		"question":"\u7D2B\u83DC\u957F\u5728\u6D45\u6D77\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u7136\u9009\u62E9",
		"indexes":"swjhdfxjdy",
		"question":"\u751F\u7269\u8FDB\u5316\u7684\u65B9\u5411\u51B3\u5B9A\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FC5\u8180",
		"indexes":"xssksmfcmjsd",
		"question":"\u87CB\u87C0\u662F\u9760\u4EC0\u4E48\u53D1\u51FA\u9E23\u53EB\u58F0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67D3\u8272\u4F53\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"DNAwzzyczy",
		"question":"DNA\u7269\u8D28\u4E3B\u8981\u5B58\u5728\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F20\u75AB",
		"indexes":"ozzsjlxdhsbsjs",
		"question":"\u6B27\u6D32\u4E2D\u4E16\u7EAA\u6D41\u884C\u7684\u201C\u9ED1\u6B7B\u75C5\u201D\u5B9E\u9645\u662F",
		"id":18491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u575A\u679C\u7C7B",
		"indexes":"yxsysmzlsg",
		"question":"\u94F6\u674F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u79CD\u7C7B\u6C34\u679C\uFF1F",
		"id":18492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u5B63",
		"indexes":"qecldjjybs",
		"question":"\u4F01\u9E45\u4EA7\u5375\u7684\u5B63\u8282\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9632\u6C34",
		"indexes":"hdcbsdfmysmzy",
		"question":"\u8774\u8776\u7FC5\u8180\u4E0A\u7684\u7C89\u672B\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u4F5C\u7528\uFF1A",
		"id":18494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u9E43",
		"indexes":"xlnznlzhsdbhfd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u7C7B\u53EA\u4F1A\u751F\u86CB\u4E0D\u4F1A\u5B75\u86CB\uFF1A",
		"id":18495
	},
	{
		"answer":"206",
		"indexes":"crgygdsk",
		"question":"\u6210\u4EBA\u5171\u6709\u9AA8\u591A\u5C11\u5757\uFF1F",
		"id":18496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34",
		"indexes":"rtkyddsywrtzhy",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u53EF\u4EE5\u5BFC\u7535\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u4EBA\u4F53\u4E2D\u542B\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":18497
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BA1\u80DE\u3001\u7B5B\u7EC6\u80DE",
		"indexes":"jlzwdsdzzzysshwjydjghysyjwdjgfbs",
		"question":"\u8568\u7C7B\u690D\u7269\u7684\u8F93\u5BFC\u7EC4\u7EC7\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8FD0\u9001\u6C34\u548C\u65E0\u673A\u76D0\u7684\u7ED3\u6784\u548C\u8FD0\u9001\u6709\u673A\u7269\u7684\u7ED3\u6784\u5206\u522B\u662F",
		"id":18498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA7\u5375",
		"indexes":"qtdsswl",
		"question":"\u873B\u8713\u70B9\u6C34\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86",
		"id":18499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u500D\u4F53",
		"indexes":"xjsjbt",
		"question":"\u9999\u8549\u662F\u51E0\u500D\u4F53",
		"id":18500
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u86CB\u767D\u8D28",
		"indexes":"swtnzddyjws",
		"question":"\u751F\u7269\u4F53\u5185\u6700\u591A\u7684\u6709\u673A\u7269\u662F",
		"id":18501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CDD\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"nzszzdy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u771F\u6B63\u7684\u9C7C\uFF1F",
		"id":18502
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72D7",
		"indexes":"sdxtzk",
		"question":"\u8C01\u7684\u5FC3\u8DF3\u6700\u5FEB\uFF1F",
		"id":18503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A",
		"indexes":"xlnzdwdjyyrldjyzxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u7684\u57FA\u56E0\u4E0E\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u57FA\u56E0\u6700\u76F8\u4F3C\uFF1A",
		"id":18504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u74DC",
		"indexes":"xlnzzwbnzykdlxzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u690D\u7269\u4E0D\u80FD\u5728\u4E00\u5757\u5730\u8FDE\u7EED\u79CD\u690D\uFF1F",
		"id":18505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E35\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xcnlzdzddnds",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5B58\u9E1F\u7C7B\u4E2D\u7684\u6700\u5927\u7684\u9E1F\u86CB\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E2D\u5634\u517D",
		"indexes":"jsybrdwyyksdlfzhdds",
		"question":"\u65E2\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\uFF0C\u53C8\u8981\u9760\u751F\u86CB\u6765\u7E41\u6B96\u540E\u4EE3\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u6C57",
		"indexes":"zqwhgsrzytgnzfssrybczctw",
		"question":"\u5728\u6C14\u6E29\u5F88\u9AD8\u65F6\uFF0C\u4EBA\u4E3B\u8981\u901A\u8FC7\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u6563\u70ED\u4EE5\u4FDD\u6301\u6B63\u5E38\u4F53\u6E29\u3002",
		"id":18508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u7528\u6765\u7167\u660E",
		"indexes":"xddwdyyddhfgdqgdzxqgytsfbzqds",
		"question":"\u8BB8\u591A\u52A8\u7269\u90FD\u62E5\u6709\u5E26\u7535\u6216\u53D1\u5149\u7684\u5668\u5B98\uFF0C\u5BF9\u8FD9\u4E9B\u5668\u5B98\u7528\u9014\u8BF4\u6CD5\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E26\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"xlscpznzyycjhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6C34\u4EA7\u54C1\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u53C8\u79F0\u201C\u51C0\u6D77\u9F99\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6",
		"indexes":"dbfrdxzspxnyb",
		"question":"\u5927\u90E8\u5206\u4EBA\u7684\u5FC3\u810F\u662F\u504F\u5411\u54EA\u4E00\u8FB9\uFF1F",
		"id":18511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u677E\u6811",
		"indexes":"xlnzsdyszxd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u6811\u7684\u53F6\u662F\u9488\u5F62\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80C3\u3001\u5341\u4E8C\u6307\u80A0\u6E83\u75A1",
		"indexes":"sxhdcxzcjdyyssm",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D88\u5316\u9053\u51FA\u8840\u6700\u5E38\u89C1\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u547C\u5438",
		"indexes":"pxtcdbmysmzy",
		"question":"\u8783\u87F9\u5410\u51FA\u7684\u767D\u6CAB\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u4F5C\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":18514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624B\u638C\u548C\u811A\u5E95",
		"indexes":"rthxfbzddbwssmdf",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6C57\u817A\u5206\u5E03\u6700\u591A\u7684\u90E8\u4F4D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\u3002",
		"id":18515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D8\u77ED",
		"indexes":"djrssjrhysmbh",
		"question":"\u5F53\u808C\u8089\u6536\u7F29\uFF0C\u808C\u8089\u4F1A\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u53D8\u5316\uFF1F",
		"id":18516
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"mmdszzqydj",
		"question":"\u7709\u6BDB\u7684\u751F\u957F\u5468\u671F\u6709\u591A\u4E45\uFF1F",
		"id":18517
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8349\u8393",
		"indexes":"sdplssmsg",
		"question":"\u58EB\u591A\u5564\u68A8\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6C34\u679C\uFF1F",
		"id":18518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809D\u810F",
		"indexes":"rtzddjdqgs",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u5927\u7684\u89E3\u6BD2\u5668\u5B98\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809A\u80A0",
		"indexes":"hctbwxshypdssdngqg",
		"question":"\u6D77\u53C2\u9003\u907F\u5371\u9669\u65F6\u5019\u8981\u629B\u6389\u8EAB\u4E0A\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u5668\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":18520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3E\u5DF4",
		"indexes":"ydseyhystdngbfjxgj",
		"question":"\u9047\u654C\u65F6\uFF0C\u9CC4\u9C7C\u4F1A\u7528\u8EAB\u4F53\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u90E8\u5206\u8FDB\u884C\u653B\u51FB\uFF1A",
		"id":18521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u725B\u3001\u7280\u725B",
		"indexes":"dwxjbnxdwczhpdw",
		"question":"\u52A8\u7269\u5B66\u5BB6\u628A\u54EA\u4E9B\u52A8\u7269\u79F0\u4F5C\u539A\u76AE\u52A8\u7269\uFF1A",
		"id":18522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D2B\u8840\u75C7",
		"indexes":"zjcbzdjysmb",
		"question":"\u6307\u7532\u82CD\u767D\u6700\u591A\u89C1\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u75C5\uFF1F",
		"id":18523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8702\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"wyngqhzyfxdns",
		"question":"\u552F\u4E00\u80FD\u591F\u524D\u540E\u5DE6\u53F3\u98DE\u884C\u7684\u9E1F\u662F",
		"id":18524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u624B\u672F",
		"indexes":"wkssassndfwdzxslgyqcsssy",
		"question":"\u5916\u79D1\u624B\u672F\u6309\u624B\u672F\u96BE\u5EA6\u5206\u4E3A\u5927\u4E2D\u5C0F\u4E09\u7C7B\uFF0C\u809D\u53F6\u5207\u9664\u624B\u672F\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":18525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u6D32\u7D2B\u7F57\u5170",
		"indexes":"yxnzsnpzzwscnkhd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u5BA4\u5185\u76C6\u683D\u690D\u7269\u662F\u5E38\u5E74\u5F00\u82B1\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5FC3\u5BA4",
		"indexes":"xzzngbzh",
		"question":"\u5FC3\u810F\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E2A\u58C1\u6700\u539A\uFF1F",
		"id":18527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u9E26",
		"indexes":"ydnzdhhzswwmqbcwfbxlnznhfb",
		"question":"\u6709\u7684\u9E1F\u957F\u5927\u540E\u4F1A\u627E\u98DF\u7269\u5582\u6BCD\u4EB2\uFF0C\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u53CD\u54FA\u201D\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u4F1A\u201C\u53CD\u54FA\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67FF\u5B50",
		"indexes":"wljkybmsryxnzgsp",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u5065\u5EB7\uFF0C\u5E94\u907F\u514D\u98DF\u5165\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u679C\u852C\u76AE\uFF1F",
		"id":18529
	},
	{
		"answer":"1800\u4EBF\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"ygzcdcnrssdyydsgxb",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u6B63\u5E38\u7684\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u8EAB\u4E0A\uFF0C\u5927\u7EA6\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u7EC6\u80DE\uFF1F",
		"id":18530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8840\u6DB2",
		"indexes":"azbdzycbtjs",
		"question":"\u827E\u6ECB\u75C5\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u4F20\u64AD\u9014\u5F84\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u751F\u4EE3\u7684\u53A5\u7C7B\u690D\u7269",
		"indexes":"msysmddjlzwbcd",
		"question":"\u7164\u662F\u7531\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EE3\u7684\u53A5\u7C7B\u690D\u7269\u53D8\u6210\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u6781\u71D5\u9E25",
		"indexes":"yjldsjsfxjlzydssmn",
		"question":"\u6709\u8BB0\u5F55\u7684\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u98DE\u7FD4\u8DDD\u79BB\u6700\u8FDC\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":18533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8840\u5C0F\u677F",
		"indexes":"xgplsxyzdsmwzhnjckdzplbfyzx",
		"question":"\u8840\u7BA1\u7834\u88C2\u65F6\uFF0C\u8840\u6DB2\u4E2D\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u8D28\u4F1A\u51DD\u7ED3\u6210\u5757\uFF0C\u5835\u4F4F\u7834\u88C2\u90E8\u5206\u4EE5\u6B62\u8840\uFF1F",
		"id":18534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u626C\u5B50\u9CC4",
		"indexes":"bcwhhsdpxdw",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u6D3B\u5316\u77F3\u201D\u7684\u722C\u884C\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":18535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732B\u7684\u77B3\u5B54\u653E\u5927\u7F29\u5C0F\u80FD\u529B\u5F3A",
		"indexes":"rzhylkbjdxmzhylwsmnkjls",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u5728\u9ED1\u591C\u91CC\u770B\u4E0D\u89C1\u4E1C\u897F\uFF0C\u732B\u5728\u9ED1\u591C\u91CC\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u80FD\u770B\u89C1\u8001\u9F20\uFF1F",
		"id":18536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934\u9885",
		"indexes":"nlbfsmdyrlhxddwyynlzsbxdxsbtblrdnlz",
		"question":"\u5E74\u8F6E\u5E76\u975E\u6811\u6728\u72EC\u6709\uFF0C\u4EBA\u7C7B\u548C\u8BB8\u591A\u52A8\u7269\u4E5F\u6709\u5E74\u8F6E\uFF0C\u53EA\u662F\u8868\u73B0\u7684\u5F62\u5F0F\u4E0D\u540C\u7F62\u4E86\u3002\u4EBA\u7684\u5E74\u8F6E\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":18537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u559C\u6B22\u5403\u82B1\u854A\u91CC\u7684\u871C\u6C41",
		"indexes":"hdwsmzzhclflfqyxnygdaszqd",
		"question":"\u8774\u8776\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u603B\u5728\u82B1\u4E1B\u91CC\u98DE\u6765\u98DE\u53BB\uFF1F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u7B54\u6848\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u6781\u71D5\u9E25",
		"indexes":"sjsqxlczyddws",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u8FC1\u5F99\u8DEF\u7A0B\u6700\u8FDC\u7684\u52A8\u7269\u662F",
		"id":18539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99\u8475\u7D20",
		"indexes":"fydtdzhyyzdsrgsrgdkyhxmbedzswzzdsssm",
		"question":"\u53D1\u82BD\u7684\u571F\u8C46\u4E2D\u542B\u6709\u4E00\u79CD\u6BD2\u7D20\uFF0C\u5982\u679C\u6444\u5165\u8FC7\u591A\uFF0C\u53EF\u56E0\u547C\u5438\u9EBB\u75F9\u800C\u5BFC\u81F4\u6B7B\u4EA1\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u6BD2\u7D20\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u9CB5",
		"indexes":"wwyyqxxwwjsylsxetkgedmwwynzdwwydxmssmm",
		"question":"'\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C'\u56E0\u5176\u5F62\u50CF\u5A03\u5A03\uFF0C\u53EB\u58F0\u53C8\u7C7B\u4F3C\u5C0F\u513F\u557C\u54ED\uFF0C\u6545\u800C\u5F97\u540D'\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C'\u3002\u60A8\u77E5\u9053'\u5A03\u5A03\u9C7C'\u7684\u5B66\u540D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u5E73\u6446\u52A8",
		"indexes":"zxqhhswbhcsmxz",
		"question":"\u732A\u5FC3\u60C5\u5F88\u597D\u65F6\u5C3E\u5DF4\u4F1A\u5448\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F62\u72B6\uFF1F",
		"id":18542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CA9\u77F3\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"zczzqhd",
		"question":"\u7D2B\u83DC\u957F\u5728\u6D45\u6D77\u7684",
		"id":18543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"rldpfzzbddtqhszywzccnrdpfqbgxycxyjjdzsj",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u76AE\u80A4\u603B\u5728\u4E0D\u65AD\u5730\u8131\u53BB\u548C\u751F\u957F\u3002\u4E00\u4F4D\u6B63\u5E38\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u7684\u76AE\u80A4\u5168\u90E8\u66F4\u65B0\u4E00\u6B21\u9700\u8981\u5C06\u8FD1\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":18544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80BA\u548C\u76AE\u80A4",
		"indexes":"qwdhxqgs",
		"question":"\u9752\u86D9\u7684\u547C\u5438\u5668\u5B98\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20B1",
		"indexes":"stgdhdztnnzwlysdqf",
		"question":"\u98DF\u7CD6\u8FC7\u591A\u4F1A\u5BFC\u81F4\u4F53\u5185\u54EA\u79CD\u5FAE\u91CF\u5143\u7D20\u7684\u7F3A\u4E4F\uFF1F",
		"id":18546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u94DC",
		"indexes":"zzjtlxyyhzclzt",
		"question":"\u5236\u4F5C\u666F\u6CF0\u84DD\u5148\u8981\u4EE5\u4F55\u79CD\u6750\u6599\u5236\u80CE\uFF1F",
		"id":18547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u811A\u5148\u7740\u5730",
		"indexes":"mwlysmzsckzlxzs",
		"question":"\u732B\u65E0\u8BBA\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u59FF\u52BF\u4ECE\u7A7A\u4E2D\u843D\u4E0B\uFF0C\u603B\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5012\u9000\u7740\u6E38",
		"indexes":"myzszydsqfxs",
		"question":"\u58A8\u9C7C\u5728\u6C34\u4E2D\u6E38\u52A8\u65F6\uFF0C\u5176\u65B9\u5411\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8717\u725B",
		"indexes":"yxnyzkchdqcszcswh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u4F1A\u5BF9\u9752\u83DC\u751F\u957F\u4EA7\u751F\u5371\u5BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":18550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9632\u6C34",
		"indexes":"hdcbsdfmysmzy",
		"question":"\u8774\u8776\u7FC5\u8180\u4E0A\u7684\u7C89\u672B\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u4F5C\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":18551
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8759\u8760",
		"indexes":"yxbsynlds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9E1F\u7C7B\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u566C\u83CC\u4F53",
		"indexes":"yxmyxbjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6CA1\u6709\u7EC6\u80DE\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5408\u4F19\u4EBA\u51FA\u8D44\u8BC1\u660E",
		"indexes":"hhqysqyyzzsxlnxbsbxtjd",
		"question":"\u5408\u4F19\u4F01\u4E1A\u7533\u8BF7\u8425\u4E1A\u6267\u7167\u65F6\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5FC5\u987B\u63D0\u4EA4\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18554
	},
	{
		"answer":"3\u5E74",
		"indexes":"azgsfgdgfyxgsfqrdgfzgssljnnbnzr",
		"question":"\u6309\u7167\u516C\u53F8\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u80A1\u4EFD\u6709\u9650\u516C\u53F8\u53D1\u8D77\u4EBA\u7684\u80A1\u4EFD\u5728\u516C\u53F8\u8BBE\u7ACB\u51E0\u5E74\u5185\u4E0D\u80FD\u8F6C\u8BA9\uFF1F",
		"id":18555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"shzyddyccssznggj",
		"question":"\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5C1D\u8BD5\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u897F\u5170",
		"indexes":"1997n8ynyggjcwdygtzgjzgjrsmzzdcsbxydgj",
		"question":"1997\u5E748\u6708\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6210\u4E3A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u540C\u4E2D\u56FD\u5C31\u4E2D\u56FD\u52A0\u5165\u4E16\u8D38\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8FBE\u6210\u53CC\u8FB9\u534F\u8BAE\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18557
	},
	{
		"answer":"2002\u5E741\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"csmshkszgkslxrsdgxcn",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u5F00\u59CB\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u5F00\u59CB\u5C65\u884C\u5165\u4E16\u7684\u5404\u9879\u627F\u8BFA\uFF1F",
		"id":18558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9632\u6CBB\u6C61\u67D3",
		"indexes":"gjwghbfdgdxyjdwzddcbzpwfydyy",
		"question":"\u6839\u636E\u6211\u56FD\u300A\u73AF\u4FDD\u6CD5\u300B\u7684\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u5411\u5E94\u7F34\u5355\u4F4D\u5F81\u5F97\u7684\u8D85\u6807\u51C6\u6392\u6C61\u8D39\uFF0C\u5E94\u5F53\u7528\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u4E5D",
		"indexes":"jy2008nzwgbjjbdayhsdjj",
		"question":"\u5C06\u4E8E2008\u5E74\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u5317\u4EAC\u4E3E\u529E\u7684\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u662F\u7B2C\u51E0\u5C4A\uFF1F",
		"id":18560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6536\u53D6\u90E8\u5206\u4FDD\u9669\u8D39",
		"indexes":"bxzrkshtbryqjchtdbxrky",
		"question":"\u4FDD\u9669\u8D23\u4EFB\u5F00\u59CB\u540E\uFF0C\u6295\u4FDD\u4EBA\u8981\u6C42\u89E3\u9664\u5408\u540C\u7684\uFF0C\u4FDD\u9669\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5\uFF1A",
		"id":18561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"dygzbzygjs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18562
	},
	{
		"answer":"2002\u5E749\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zhrmghgrkyjhsyfysmshkssx",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u4EBA\u53E3\u4E0E\u8BA1\u5212\u751F\u80B2\u6CD5\u300B\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u5F00\u59CB\u65BD\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":18563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5728\u5176\u4ED6\u7ECF\u6D4E\u7EC4\u7EC7\u517C\u804C",
		"indexes":"syyxdgzrybd",
		"question":"\u5546\u4E1A\u94F6\u884C\u7684\u5DE5\u4F5C\u4EBA\u5458\u4E0D\u5F97\uFF1A",
		"id":18564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79BB\u5F02\u53CC\u65B9\u90FD\u6709\u8D23\u4EFB",
		"indexes":"fqlyhdwcnrzndjysfyzr",
		"question":"\u592B\u59BB\u79BB\u5F02\u540E\u5BF9\u672A\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u5B50\u5973\u7684\u6559\u80B2\u8C01\u8D1F\u6709\u8D23\u4EFB\uFF1F",
		"id":18565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u65AF\u5170\u6559",
		"indexes":"alsyxlnyzj",
		"question":"\u201C\u963F\u62C9\u201D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E00\u5B97\u6559",
		"id":18566
	},
	{
		"answer":"1991\u5E742\u6708",
		"indexes":"zgdyctcsbayhsnnny",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u63D0\u51FA\u7533\u529E\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u5E74\u54EA\u6708\uFF1F",
		"id":18567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E34\u65F6\u4EE3\u529E",
		"indexes":"yxngbsysggzdjb",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F7F\u9986\u9986\u957F\u7684\u7EA7\u522B\uFF1F",
		"id":18568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u4E0A\u90FD\u6B63\u786E",
		"indexes":"gyjjfymfxlsfzqds",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u7ECF\u6D4E\u6CD5\u4E0E\u6C11\u6CD5\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8BF4\u6CD5\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u7136\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bncwsbqztds",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u80FD\u6210\u4E3A\u5546\u6807\u6743\u4E3B\u4F53\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E94",
		"indexes":"2003n7y22rzkdsgqtdjcqgdbdh",
		"question":"2003\u5E747\u670822\u65E5\u53EC\u5F00\u7684\u662F\u5171\u9752\u56E2\u7B2C\u51E0\u6B21\u5168\u56FD\u4EE3\u8868\u5927\u4F1A\uFF1F",
		"id":18571
	},
	{
		"answer":"50\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"gjgsfyxgsdgdzgrsw",
		"question":"\u6839\u636E\u516C\u53F8\u6CD5\uFF0C\u6709\u9650\u516C\u53F8\u7684\u80A1\u4E1C\u6700\u9AD8\u4EBA\u6570\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18572
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"qslhfypjbzlhddzsjhcnzcqs",
		"question":"\u8D77\u8BC9\u79BB\u5A5A\uFF0C\u6CD5\u9662\u5224\u51B3\u4E0D\u51C6\u79BB\u5A5A\u7684\uFF0C\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\u540E\u624D\u80FD\u518D\u6B21\u8D77\u8BC9\uFF1F",
		"id":18573
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"zcsbdqxwjn",
		"question":"\u6CE8\u518C\u5546\u6807\u7684\u671F\u9650\u4E3A\u51E0\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79D1\u5B66\u6280\u672F",
		"indexes":"smsdyscl",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u662F\u7B2C\u4E00\u751F\u4EA7\u529B",
		"id":18575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D41\u52A8\u6027\u5F3A",
		"indexes":"fdctzbjydtds",
		"question":"\u623F\u5730\u4EA7\u6295\u8D44\u4E0D\u5177\u6709\u7684\u7279\u70B9\u662F",
		"id":18576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D1\u8FBE\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u56FD\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"zgjgxdbszyygcydchjxfgjgyzggnzqdljygs",
		"question":"\u5728\u56FD\u9645\u5173\u7CFB\u7684\u8868\u8FF0\u4E2D\u6709\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E38\u7528\u7684\u8BCD\u6C47\u53EB\u201C\u897F\u65B9\u56FD\u5BB6\u201D\uFF0C\u5173\u4E8E\u8FD9\u4E2A\u6982\u5FF5\uFF0C\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u7406\u89E3\u5E94\u8BE5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u518D\u5C31\u4E1A\u670D\u52A1\u4E2D\u5FC3\u7F34\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"gqgrwmy1998n8yxgnmqjbylbxfysfz",
		"question":"\u56FD\u4F01\u5DE5\u4EBA\u5FD8\u67D0\u4E8E1998\u5E748\u6708\u4E0B\u5C97\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u5176\u57FA\u672C\u533B\u7597\u4FDD\u9669\u8D39\u7531\u8C01\u8D1F\u8D23\uFF1F",
		"id":18578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u652F\u4ED8\u8D54\u507F\u91D1",
		"indexes":"gjpcdzyfss",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u8D54\u507F\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u65B9\u5F0F\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EAA\u5FF5\u6027\u7684\u6587\u5B57\u548C\u56FE\u5F62",
		"indexes":"jzzyczpsbsbzdzyhtxs",
		"question":"\u7981\u6B62\u5728\u70DF\u8349\u5236\u54C1\u5546\u6807\u4E0A\u6807\u6CE8\u7684\u5B57\u6837\u6216\u56FE\u5F62\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF13\uFF10\u65E5",
		"indexes":"blyczmxkzdbghzxsxyzypzjgpzzrqdsrndfzjgblbgzxsx",
		"question":"\u529E\u7406\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\u7684\u53D8\u66F4\u548C\u6CE8\u9500\u624B\u7EED\uFF0C\u5E94\u5728\u539F\u6279\u51C6\u673A\u5173\u6279\u51C6\u4E4B\u65E5\u8D77\u591A\u5C11\u65E5\u5185\uFF0C\u5230\u53D1\u8BC1\u673A\u5173\u529E\u7406\u53D8\u66F4\u3001\u6CE8\u9500\u624B\u7EED\uFF1F",
		"id":18581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF11\uFF10\uFF10\uFF10\u5143",
		"indexes":"sygqsxxkzhzrxkzyyczmxzzgbmcydsyyxdfk",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u8FC7\u671F\u3001\u5931\u6548\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\u6216\u8F6C\u8BA9\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\uFF0C\u7531\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u884C\u653F\u4E3B\u7BA1\u90E8\u95E8\u5904\u4EE5\u591A\u5C11\u5143\u4EE5\u4E0B\u7684\u7F5A\u6B3E\uFF1F",
		"id":18582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u5C40",
		"indexes":"yczmpzyzdggsyhqfzyzzyyzdyzsyystyzd",
		"question":"\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u54C1\u51C6\u8FD0\u8BC1\u7684\u89C4\u683C\u3001\u5F0F\u6837\u548C\u7B7E\u53D1\u51C6\u8FD0\u8BC1\u4E13\u7528\u5370\u7AE0\u7684\u5370\u7AE0\u5F0F\u6837\u7531\u8C01\u7EDF\u4E00\u5236\u5B9A\uFF1F",
		"id":18583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF17\uFF10\uFF05",
		"indexes":"yczmxzzgbmyfsgwfsgdyysgjgazgyczmpscpfjgddsjs",
		"question":"\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u884C\u653F\u4E3B\u7BA1\u90E8\u95E8\u4F9D\u6CD5\u6536\u8D2D\u8FDD\u6CD5\u6536\u8D2D\u7684\u70DF\u53F6\uFF0C\u6536\u8D2D\u4EF7\u683C\u6309\u7167\u8BE5\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u54C1\u5E02\u573A\u6279\u53D1\u4EF7\u683C\u7684\u591A\u5C11\u8BA1\u7B97\uFF1F",
		"id":18584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u516B\u8F6E",
		"indexes":"wlghhsgmzxdwjqhysxxddbmytzezmybhzymyefdddjldbmytp",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E4C\u62C9\u572D\u56DE\u5408\u201D\u662F\u5173\u8D38\u603B\u534F\u5B9A\u4E3A\u52A0\u5F3A\u548C\u5EF6\u4F38\u73B0\u884C\u7684\u591A\u8FB9\u8D38\u6613\u4F53\u5236\uFF0C\u904F\u5236\u8D38\u6613\u4FDD\u62A4\u4E3B\u4E49\u8513\u5EF6\u800C\u53D1\u52A8\u7684\u7B2C\u51E0\u8F6E\u591A\u8FB9\u8D38\u6613\u8C08\u5224\uFF1F",
		"id":18585
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"1982nzgldrxhfwljggj",
		"question":"1982\u5E74\u4E2D\u56FD\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u5148\u540E\u8BBF\u95EE\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u8001\u3001\u75BE\u75C5\u6216\u4E27\u5931\u52B3\u52A8\u80FD\u529B",
		"indexes":"wgxfgdzhrmghgzqkxycgjhshhdwzbzdql",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u300A\u5BAA\u6CD5\u300B\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF1A\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u5728()\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0B\uFF0C\u6709\u4ECE\u56FD\u5BB6\u548C\u793E\u4F1A\u83B7\u5F97\u7269\u8D28\u5E2E\u52A9\u7684\u6743\u5229\u3002",
		"id":18587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5171\u4EA7\u4E3B\u4E49\u6559\u80B2",
		"indexes":"xlnxbswgjyfgdgjbxyzsjyzzkzdjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6559\u80B2\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5FC5\u987B\u8981\u5728\u53D7\u6559\u80B2\u8005\u4E2D\u5F00\u5C55\u7684\u6559\u80B2\uFF1F",
		"id":18588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u6CD5\u9662\u548C\u4EF2\u88C1\u673A\u6784",
		"indexes":"kcxhtdbghcxxyngjgzc",
		"question":"\u53EF\u64A4\u6D88\u5408\u540C\u7684\u53D8\u66F4\u6216\u64A4\u6D88\u987B\u7531\u54EA\u4E2A\u673A\u6784\u4F5C\u51FA\u3002",
		"id":18589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EFA\u7B51\u6750\u6599\u8D28\u91CF\uFF1B",
		"indexes":"xlnlcpsycpzlfdzdfw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u7C7B\u4EA7\u54C1\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u4EA7\u54C1\u8D28\u91CF\u6CD5\u300B\u8C03\u6574\u7684\u8303\u56F4\uFF1F",
		"id":18590
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u4E2A\u5B63\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"jrybbkddybxydyysnsqxw",
		"question":"\u91D1\u878D\u4E1A\uFF08\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u5178\u5F53\u4E1A\u3001\u4FDD\u9669\u4E1A\uFF09\u7684\u8425\u4E1A\u7A0E\u7EB3\u7A0E\u671F\u9650\u4E3A",
		"id":18591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u4E8B\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"yxngjgshyqydzgqljg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u673A\u6784\u662F\u5408\u8425\u4F01\u4E1A\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u6743\u5229\u673A\u6784",
		"id":18592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u8BC1\u636E\u8BC1\u660E\u5176\u4E0D\u77E5\u9053\u8BE5\u4EA7\u54C1\u4E3A\u7981\u6B62\u9500\u552E\u7684\u4EA7\u54C1\uFF0C\u5E76\u5982\u5B9E\u8BF4\u660E\u5176\u8FDB\u8D27\u6E20\u9053",
		"indexes":"acpzlfgdxszdxlxwkyjqhcqcfdsnzqk",
		"question":"\u6309\u300A\u4EA7\u54C1\u8D28\u91CF\u6CD5\u300B\u89C4\u5B9A\u9500\u552E\u8005\u7684\u4E0B\u5217\u884C\u4E3A\u53EF\u4EE5\u51CF\u8F7B\u6216\u4ECE\u8F7B\u5904\u7F5A\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5",
		"id":18593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nygslhgalhcrlsgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5B89\u7406\u4F1A\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1A",
		"id":18594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u4EE3\u8868",
		"indexes":"wgxxxfgdqgrdcwhdzcryzydysdmedw",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u884C\u5BAA\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u5168\u56FD\u4EBA\u5927\u5E38\u59D4\u4F1A\u7684\u7EC4\u6210\u4EBA\u5458\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5E94\u5F53\u6709\u9002\u5F53\u540D\u989D\u7684\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u4EE3\u4E3B\u9898\u7684\u8F6C\u6362\u548C\u65B0\u6280\u672F\u9769\u547D\u6D6A\u6F6E\u7684\u5174\u8D77",
		"indexes":"dxpllxcdsdyqs",
		"question":"\u9093\u5C0F\u5E73\u7406\u8BBA\u5F62\u6210\u7684\u65F6\u4EE3\u8981\u6C42\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7985\u5B97",
		"indexes":"zzgzxzjfhbhssdsy",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u54F2\u5B66\u4E2D\uFF0C\u201C\u673A\u950B\u201D\u548C\u201C\u68D2\u559D\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u672F\u8BED",
		"id":18597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECE\u5C5E\u5173\u7CFB",
		"indexes":"zfjghgjqljgdgxs",
		"question":"\u653F\u5E9C\u673A\u6784\u548C\u56FD\u5BB6\u6743\u5229\u673A\u6784\u7684\u5173\u7CFB\u662F",
		"id":18598
	},
	{
		"answer":"1982",
		"indexes":"wgxzldtxnnqyzswyz",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u884C\u653F\u9886\u5BFC\u4F53\u73B0\u54EA\u5E74\u524D\uFF0C\u4E00\u76F4\u662F\u59D4\u5458\u5236\u3002",
		"id":18599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5168\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u4EE3\u8868\u5927\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"wgdzggjqljgs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u56FD\u5BB6\u6743\u5229\u673A\u5173\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18600
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xzpcdqqsxw",
		"question":"\u884C\u653F\u8D54\u507F\u7684\u8BF7\u6C42\u65F6\u6548\u4E3A",
		"id":18601
	},
	{
		"answer":"180",
		"indexes":"wgsxwhgzckcpbghdstbxjxhx",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5B9E\u884C\u5916\u6C47\u7BA1\u5236\uFF0C\u51FA\u53E3\u4EA7\u54C1\u62A5\u5173\u540E\u591A\u5C11\u5929\u5FC5\u987B\u8FDB\u884C\u6838\u9500\uFF1F",
		"id":18602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2A\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"bjfxlxbfpygxfkjdfprgzljjjzgssy",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u53D1\u884C\u4E86\u65B0\u7248\u53D1\u7968\uFF0C\u56E0\u516C\u6D88\u8D39\u5F00\u636E\u7684\u53D1\u7968\uFF0C\u5982\u679C\u4E2D\u4E86\u5956\uFF0C\u5956\u91D1\u5219\u5F52\u8C01\u6240\u6709\uFF1F",
		"id":18603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7A57\u5361",
		"indexes":"mqwgtzezgdxykssmk",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6211\u56FD\u900F\u652F\u989D\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u4FE1\u7528\u5361\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5361\uFF1F",
		"id":18604
	},
	{
		"answer":"8\u5E74",
		"indexes":"csyhgzbncg",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u4E8B\u6709\u5BB3\u5DE5\u79CD\u4E0D\u80FD\u8D85\u8FC7\uFF1A",
		"id":18605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5168\u90E8\u540C\u610F",
		"indexes":"hhqyxrhbxjg",
		"question":"\u5408\u4F19\u4F01\u4E1A\u65B0\u5165\u4F19\u5FC5\u987B\u7ECF\u8FC7\uFF1A",
		"id":18606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8155\u9F99",
		"indexes":"yzdzzdklssm",
		"question":"\u5DF2\u77E5\u7684\u6700\u91CD\u7684\u6050\u9F99\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199",
		"indexes":"qchdzzqfhxds",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\u4E2D\u6700\u52E4\u594B\u597D\u5B66\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C88\u56ED",
		"indexes":"lyytwflhsnyznlzfg",
		"question":"\u9646\u6E38\u4E0E\u5510\u5A49\u5206\u79BB\u540E\u6570\u5E74\u53C8\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u91CD\u9022\u8FC7",
		"id":18609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgdymypssmsqfxd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u90AE\u7968\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\u53D1\u884C\u7684",
		"id":18610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"zggdngxpdzzylshpzzdsxxj",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B66\u6D3E\u7684\u4E3B\u5F20\uFF0C\u4E0E\u7EFF\u8272\u548C\u5E73\u7EC4\u7EC7\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u76F8\u8FD1\uFF1F",
		"id":18611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E",
		"indexes":"zddmjgddjy",
		"question":"\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6728\u7ED3\u6784\u5927\u6BBF\u5EFA\u4E8E",
		"id":18612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F13\u7BAD",
		"indexes":"xsnzwqbszsjqsdbxzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u8FF0\u54EA\u79CD\u6B66\u5668\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E2D\u4E16\u7EAA\u9A91\u58EB\u7684\u5FC5\u9700\u88C5\u5907",
		"id":18613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u6842",
		"indexes":"galpkjsyszydsysmbcdwg",
		"question":"\u53E4\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u7ADE\u8D5B\u4F18\u80DC\u8005\u8981\u6234\u4E0A\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u7F16\u6210\u7684\u738B\u51A0",
		"id":18614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5217\u5BBE",
		"indexes":"yxbswyfxsqhjds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u662F\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u753B\u5BB6\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18615
	},
	{
		"answer":"19",
		"indexes":"sjsdyzzpcxzngsj",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u5F20\u7167\u7247\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E16\u7EAA?",
		"id":18616
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u5FC5\u70C8",
		"indexes":"mnstyqgdychdss",
		"question":"\u706D\u5357\u5B8B\u7EDF\u4E00\u5168\u56FD\u7684\u5143\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18617
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9996\u9640\u7F57",
		"indexes":"gyddzxzdznygdwzd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u5370\u5EA6\u7684\u79CD\u59D3\u5236\u5EA6\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5730\u4F4D\u6700\u4F4E",
		"id":18618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u827E\u68EE\u8C6A\u5A01\u5C14",
		"indexes":"nmddlsmjdzgslss",
		"question":"\u8BFA\u66FC\u5E95\u767B\u9646\u65F6\uFF0C\u76DF\u519B\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u53F8\u4EE4\u662F\u8C01\uFF1A",
		"id":18619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9662\u8BD5",
		"indexes":"mdkjzdksdjbbk",
		"question":"\u660E\u4EE3\u79D1\u4E3E\u5236\u5EA6\u8003\u8BD5\u7B49\u7EA7\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\uFF1A",
		"id":18620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u82F1\u5B97\u6731\u7941\u9547",
		"indexes":"bwcbfqhyfpdhds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u74E6\u523A\u5175\u4FD8\u53BB\uFF0C\u540E\u53C8\u590D\u8F9F\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F",
		"id":18621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58A8\u7D22\u91CC\u5C3C",
		"indexes":"decsjdzzydlfxstms",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u610F\u5927\u5229\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u5934\u76EE\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u516C\u6734",
		"indexes":"qmnzbfhgmdfdpzkmshdmmzywys",
		"question":"\u5168\u9762\u5185\u6218\u7206\u53D1\u540E\uFF0C\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u53CD\u52A8\u6D3E\u5728\u6606\u660E\u6740\u5BB3\u7684\u6C11\u76DF\u4E2D\u592E\u59D4\u5458\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u56FD",
		"indexes":"slgcqjdjysznysqjzd",
		"question":"\u6C34\u5229\u5DE5\u7A0B\u5947\u8FF9\u90FD\u6C5F\u5830\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u65F6\u671F\u5EFA\u9020\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5ED6\u4EF2\u607A",
		"indexes":"hpjxclsdrddbds",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u57D4\u519B\u6821\u6210\u7ACB\u65F6\uFF0C\u62C5\u4EFB\u515A\u4EE3\u8868\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u677E\u7CD5\u978B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxpsddxzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B09\u76AE\u58EB\u7684\u5178\u578B\u88C5\u626E",
		"id":18626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u8058",
		"indexes":"xlngrbscysctdccd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u4E0D\u662F\u4ECE\u8881\u7ECD\u5904\u6295\u5230\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72B6\u5143\u699C\u773C\u63A2\u82B1",
		"indexes":"mdyhtsdqsmycs",
		"question":"\u660E\u4EE3\u4EE5\u540E\u5EF7\u8BD5\u7684\u524D\u4E09\u540D\u4F9D\u6B21\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5E03\u201C\u516B\u5366\u9635\u201D",
		"indexes":"xlnyjsszsd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4EF6\u4E8B\u662F\u771F\u5B9E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u5E86\u7AE5",
		"indexes":"smycjmsccdhd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u6CA1\u6709\u53C2\u52A0\u5BC6\u6740\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":18630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5496\u5561\u9986",
		"indexes":"scsjjzbsjxddds",
		"question":"\u9996\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u4E3E\u91CD\u6BD4\u8D5B\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\u5730\u70B9\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u672B",
		"indexes":"yqzhscrwg",
		"question":"\u626C\u7434\u5728\u4F55\u65F6\u4F20\u5165\u6211\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":18632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7535\u8BDD\u516C\u53F8\u5185",
		"indexes":"sjzzdgydhtsz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u516C\u7528\u7535\u8BDD\u4EAD\u662F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":18633
	},
	{
		"answer":"103",
		"indexes":"brwxgcxldst",
		"question":"\u201C\u767E\u65E5\u7EF4\u65B0\u201D\u5171\u6301\u7EED\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5929",
		"id":18634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u671D",
		"indexes":"syfzs____qtqzdjp",
		"question":"\u56DB\u7F8A\u65B9\u5C0A\u662F:____\u9752\u94DC\u5668\u4E2D\u7684\u7CBE\u54C1",
		"id":18635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u5927\u6797\u683C\u52D2\u4FDD\u536B\u6218",
		"indexes":"decsjdzdzzds",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u7684\u8F6C\u6298\u70B9\u662F:",
		"id":18636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u6865\u5175\u53D8",
		"indexes":"xlnysjjyzbxz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E8B\u4EF6\u5177\u6709\u653F\u53D8\u6027\u8D28\uFF1A",
		"id":18637
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"clyszntwgxhsfjgyd",
		"question":"\u8521\u4F26\u4E00\u751F\u5728\u5185\u5EF7\u4E3A\u5B98\uFF0C\u5148\u540E\u4F8D\u5949\u51E0\u4E2A\u5E7C\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":18638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8282\u5EA6\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"fdaszldalsdsfs",
		"question":"\u53D1\u52A8\u5B89\u53F2\u4E4B\u4E71\u7684\u5B89\u7984\u5C71\u7684\u8EAB\u4EFD\u662F?",
		"id":18639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"zgdsxjmbjyksy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u79C1\u5B66\u5373\u6C11\u529E\u6559\u80B2\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjszzdzbcxznggj",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u7EB8\u5E01\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6.",
		"id":18641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5C3C\u5E03\u695A\u6761\u7EA6\u300B",
		"indexes":"zedcddygbjtys",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u4FC4\u8FBE\u6210\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u8FB9\u754C\u6761\u7EA6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18642
	},
	{
		"answer":"1399",
		"indexes":"zywdjygyjn",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u767B\u57FA\u4E8E\u516C\u5143\u51E0\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18643
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D",
		"indexes":"jxlswgngcdsdcz",
		"question":"\u7EAA\u6653\u5C9A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u4E0A\u7684\u624D\u5B50",
		"id":18644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA3\u7EDF",
		"indexes":"qczhyghds",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18645
	},
	{
		"answer":"11\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zhmssdztlyzzcxl",
		"question":"\u5728\u8377\u9A6C\u53F2\u8BD7\u5F53\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7279\u6D1B\u4F0A\u6218\u4E89\u6301\u7EED\u4E86\uFF1A",
		"id":18646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u57A9\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"bwlshzngsq",
		"question":"\u9738\u738B\u9F99\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":18647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9632\u6B62\u4EA4\u5934\u63A5\u8033",
		"indexes":"bssgydgmdszylbschzdedqyys",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u5B98\u5458\u7684\u5B98\u5E3D\u90FD\u662F\u5DE6\u53F3\u4E24\u8FB9\u4F38\u51FA\u5F88\u957F\u7684\u201C\u8033\u6735\u201D\uFF0C\u5176\u539F\u56E0\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u9B4F",
		"indexes":"tcyydjtzscy",
		"question":"\u5510\u521D\u6CBF\u7528\u7684\u5747\u7530\u5236\u59CB\u521B\u4E8E",
		"id":18649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zgstcmwgjwqdsxjs",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u63D0\u51FA'\u6C11\u4E3A\u8D35','\u541B\u4E3A\u8F7B'\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u51E1\u56DB\u4E16",
		"indexes":"bcwyflds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A'\u4F0A\u51E1\u96F7\u5E1D'\u662F",
		"id":18651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D2A\u5BAA\u5143\u5E74",
		"indexes":"1915n12y12ryskfpnhw",
		"question":"1915\u5E7412\u670812\u65E5\uFF0C\u8881\u4E16\u51EF\u590D\u8F9F\uFF0C\u5E74\u53F7\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u72EC\u79C0",
		"indexes":"1920nwgdyggczyxzclxzsjs",
		"question":"1920\u5E74\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5171\u4EA7\u4E3B\u4E49\u5C0F\u7EC4\u6210\u7ACB\uFF0C\u5C0F\u7EC4\u4E66\u8BB0\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u5357",
		"indexes":"hgydzzxdldsfs",
		"question":"\u62A4\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6700\u5148\u72EC\u7ACB\u7684\u7701\u4EFD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5723\u7956",
		"indexes":"kxhddmhs",
		"question":"\u5EB7\u7199\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u5E99\u53F7\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u7384\u5B97",
		"indexes":"kysssytcnghdkcd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5F00\u5143\u76DB\u4E16\u201D\u662F\u7531\u5510\u671D\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5F00\u521B\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CD\u5BF9\u5C01\u5EFA\u7EDF\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"zgtmhzzglzqcdlhfzhdszyys",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u540C\u76DF\u4F1A\u653F\u6CBB\u7EB2\u9886\u4E2D\u201C\u9A71\u9664\u9791\u864F\uFF0C\u6062\u590D\u4E2D\u534E\u201D\u7684\u5B9E\u8D28\u610F\u4E49\u662F",
		"id":18657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D7\u62D3",
		"indexes":"cqzgsqdsdssbbknyg",
		"question":"\u6625\u79CB\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u56DB\u5927\u6B7B\u58EB\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A",
		"id":18658
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"dwgzzdxqslyjwys",
		"question":"\u5230\u536B\u56FD\u6218\u4E89\u6253\u54CD\u524D,\u82CF\u8054\u6709\u51E0\u4F4D\u5143\u5E05",
		"id":18659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u865E\u59EC",
		"indexes":"xylssztddygnrss",
		"question":"\u9879\u7FBD\u4E34\u6B7B\u8BD7\u4E2D\u63D0\u5230\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u5973\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18660
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u67089\u65E5",
		"indexes":"qsqybfy1927n",
		"question":"\u79CB\u6536\u8D77\u4E49\u7206\u53D1\u4E8E1927\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":18661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F2\u8F95\u7281",
		"indexes":"tcnmgjldgzzzl",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u519C\u6C11\u6539\u8FDB\u7281\u7684\u6784\u9020\uFF0C\u5236\u9020\u4E86",
		"id":18662
	},
	{
		"answer":"29\u4F4D",
		"indexes":"ssyxdxwwjdlhddzzglssgyjg",
		"question":"\u5341\u5C81\u4EE5\u4E0B\u7684\u5C0F\u5A03\u5A03\u5C31\u5F53\u4E86\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\uFF0C\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u964D\u4F5C\u6218",
		"indexes":"anmzysezzmjssdzddycsmzy",
		"question":"\u963F\u7EB3\u59C6\u6218\u5F79\u662F\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\u7F8E\u519B\u5B9E\u65BD\u7684\u6700\u5927\u7684\u4E00\u6B21\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79\uFF1F",
		"id":18664
	},
	{
		"answer":"5\u5957",
		"indexes":"xzgclhwggfxgjtrmb",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u6210\u7ACB\u540E\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5171\u53D1\u884C\u8FC7\u51E0\u5957\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\uFF1F",
		"id":18665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u53E4",
		"indexes":"mwscdsls",
		"question":"\u706D\u4EA1\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u52BF\u529B\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EAC\u5F20",
		"indexes":"wgzxsjhxjddyttlsnttl",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u81EA\u884C\u8BBE\u8BA1\u548C\u4FEE\u5EFA\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6761\u94C1\u8DEF\u662F\u54EA\u6761\u94C1\u8DEF\uFF1F",
		"id":18667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5929\u7965",
		"indexes":"zqgsnwmzyxzyzxdbxagsp",
		"question":"\u300A\u6B63\u6C14\u6B4C\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u6C11\u65CF\u82F1\u96C4\u5728\u72F1\u4E2D\u5199\u7684\u4E0D\u673D\u7231\u56FD\u8BD7\u7BC7\uFF1F",
		"id":18668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u5958\u897F\u6E38\u53D6\u7ECF",
		"indexes":"xllssjzfsdzzds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E2D\uFF0C\u53D1\u751F\u5F97\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EB8\u5F20\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"jswmdszbfdssbknsxz",
		"question":"\u4E3E\u4E16\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u300A\u5B59\u5B50\u5175\u6CD5\u300B\u8BDE\u751F\u65F6\uFF0C\u4E0D\u53EF\u80FD\u4E66\u5199\u5728",
		"id":18670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7535\u6905",
		"indexes":"xgcqdsxsysmxszxd",
		"question":"\u9999\u6E2F\u521D\u671F\u7684\u6B7B\u5211\u662F\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F62\u5F0F\u6267\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18671
	},
	{
		"answer":"18\u5E74",
		"indexes":"bjgglsdsnjc",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u6545\u5BAB\u5386\u65F6\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\u5EFA\u6210?",
		"id":18672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u87CB\u87C0",
		"indexes":"gdssdczszxzd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u6240\u8BF4\u7684\u4FC3\u7EC7\u662F\u6307\u73B0\u5728\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18673
	},
	{
		"answer":"2006.1.1",
		"indexes":"wgzfqmjzsyflaCFC113hslywTCAdsjs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u653F\u5E9C\u5168\u9762\u7981\u6B62\u4F7F\u7528\u6C1F\u91CC\u6602\uFF08CFC-113\uFF09\u548C\u4E09\u6C2F\u4E59\u70F7\uFF08TCA\uFF09\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18674
	},
	{
		"answer":"2003\u5E742\u6708",
		"indexes":"xcdhhlscjxzxsznyn",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5B58\u7684\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C\u9996\u6B21\u8FDB\u884C\u6574\u4FEE\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u90FD",
		"indexes":"xlngbsnjdgchbm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u4EAC\u7684\u53E4\u79F0\u6216\u522B\u540D",
		"id":18676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5185\u74E6\u516C\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"qdrhbhzzsnzdxds",
		"question":"\u786E\u5B9A\u5982\u4F55\u4FDD\u62A4\u6218\u4E89\u53D7\u96BE\u8005\u7684\u534F\u5B9A\u662F",
		"id":18677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9",
		"indexes":"lgzngzxbqsm",
		"question":"\u516D\u56FD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u56FD\u6700\u5148\u88AB\u79E6\u6240\u706D\uFF1F",
		"id":18678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B11\u91CC\u85CF\u5200",
		"indexes":"sgssqjyygyjhyyshjzdjcs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\uFF0C\u5B59\u6743\u5047\u610F\u4E0E\u5173\u7FBD\u4EA4\u597D\uFF0C\u7528\u4EE5\u6536\u56DE\u8346\u5DDE\u7684\u8BA1\u7B56\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u65AF\u7279\u6CD5\u5229\u4E9A\u548C\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"jdgjfdsdbzs",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u56FD\u9645\u6CD5\u8BDE\u751F\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"yzdygtcsbayhdcssng",
		"question":"\u4E9A\u6D32\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u63D0\u51FA\u7533\u529E\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"zycycjzzyxscngcdks",
		"question":"\u6B63\u6708\u521D\u4E00\u5403\u997A\u5B50\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E60\u4FD7\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u5F00\u59CB\uFF1F",
		"id":18682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjszzfmhydgjsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u53D1\u660E\u706B\u836F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9756\u5EB7\u4E4B\u53D8",
		"indexes":"bzbsmwdlssjs",
		"question":"\u6807\u5FD7\u5317\u5B8B\u706D\u4EA1\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u662F",
		"id":18684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"rbdcdqyy",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u7684\u8336\u9053\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\uFF1F",
		"id":18685
	},
	{
		"answer":"1099\u5E747\u6708",
		"indexes":"szjdzsysmshdycgxlylsl",
		"question":"\u5341\u5B57\u519B\u4E1C\u5F81\u65F6\uFF0C\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u653B\u9677\u4E86\u8036\u8DEF\u6492\u51B7\uFF1F",
		"id":18686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"hbsrmlybdzbshxddjydxmqyy10sjd",
		"question":"\u6ED1\u51B0\u662F\u4EBA\u4EEC\u5229\u7528\u51B0\u5200\u5728\u51B0\u4E0A\u6ED1\u884C\u7684\u51AC\u5B63\u8FD0\u52A8\u9879\u76EE\u3002\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E10\u4E16\u7EAA\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5764\u5B81\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"zggzhhdjss",
		"question":"\u5728\u6545\u5BAB\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7687\u540E\u7684\u5C45\u6240\u662F",
		"id":18688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9B\uFF0C\u90AF\u90F8",
		"indexes":"xlzgcsznyzsdszmdytzx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6218\u56FD\u57CE\u5E02\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u7EC4\u662F\u5F53\u65F6\u8457\u540D\u7684\u51B6\u94C1\u4E2D\u5FC3\uFF1F",
		"id":18689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u6C38\u6C11",
		"indexes":"wbzxsrfssscd",
		"question":"\u4E94\u7B14\u5B57\u578B\u8F93\u5165\u6CD5\u662F\u8C01\u9996\u521B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"nzdsjsdylqcsngrzzdm",
		"question":"\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u8F86\u6C7D\u8F66\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u5236\u9020\u7684\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":18691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u65AF\u5C3C\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"ycdzsbegldsngdsd",
		"question":"\u4E00\u6B21\u5927\u6218\u662F\u8D1D\u5C14\u683C\u83B1\u5FB7\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7684\u9996\u90FD\uFF1F",
		"id":18692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F",
		"indexes":"wgcsmshqjyllf",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8D77\u5C31\u6709\u4E86\u5386\u6CD5",
		"id":18693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u7080\u5E1D\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"dyhkzy",
		"question":"\u5927\u8FD0\u6CB3\u5F00\u51FF\u4E8E?",
		"id":18694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F66\u88C2",
		"indexes":"qcsyzhszmsd",
		"question":"\u79E6\u671D\u5546\u9785\u6700\u540E\u662F\u600E\u4E48\u6B7B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18695
	},
	{
		"answer":"200\u4E07\u82F1\u9551",
		"indexes":"zczwnbejjjjdnbeycydsq",
		"question":"\u6700\u521D\u4F5C\u4E3A\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u91D1\u57FA\u91D1\u7684\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u9057\u4EA7\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u94B1\uFF1F",
		"id":18696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B\u5F0F",
		"indexes":"ezqjnzbsdgtrzddtkxh",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u6218\u671F\u95F4\uFF0C\u90A3\u79CD\u4E0D\u662F\u5FB7\u56FD\u6295\u5165\u6218\u6597\u7684\u5766\u514B\u578B\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":18697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u5730\u5C71",
		"indexes":"lhssnwzjddbz",
		"question":"\u300A\u843D\u82B1\u751F\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u4F5C\u5BB6\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":18698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5927\u6E05\u65B0\u5211\u5F8B\u300B",
		"indexes":"zgqchbbddybxfds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8D77\u8349\u548C\u9881\u5E03\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u5211\u6CD5\u5178\u662F",
		"id":18699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5F00\u7687\u5F8B\u300B",
		"indexes":"zzqlsezmdfjfds",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u786E\u7ACB\u5341\u6076\u7F6A\u540D\u7684\u5C01\u5EFA\u6CD5\u5178\u662F",
		"id":18700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u9093\u5927\u519B\u633A\u8FDB\u5927\u522B\u5C71",
		"indexes":"rmjfzzzlfgksy",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u6218\u7565\u53CD\u653B\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18701
	},
	{
		"answer":"1952\u5E74\u5E95",
		"indexes":"tdggjbwcsz",
		"question":"\u571F\u5730\u6539\u9769\u57FA\u672C\u5B8C\u6210\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"hjywzzcxy",
		"question":"\u4F1A\u8BA1\u4E1A\u52A1\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"cbsctzzfwclbds",
		"question":"\u66FE\u88AB\u5B8B\u671D\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u5C01\u4E3A\u201C\u660C\u9ECE\u4F2F\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u67A2",
		"indexes":"xlrwzbsyzlqxds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4EBA\u7269\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u7AF9\u6797\u4E03\u8D24\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"xzgsdyszmycjzzds",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6CA1\u6709\u53C2\u52A0\u957F\u5F81\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18706
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"wgrsgtljn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5165\u4E16\u5171\u8C08\u4E86\u51E0\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u7528\u548C\u5236\u9020\u9676\u5668",
		"indexes":"sddrwzwdldjns",
		"question":"\u5C71\u9876\u6D1E\u4EBA\u672A\u638C\u63E1\u7684\u52B3\u52A8\u6280\u80FD\u662F",
		"id":18708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"zgrzcwyhzszdhsz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u81EA\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u708E\u9EC4\u5B50\u5B59\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u9EC4\u201D\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":18709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u9876\u6D1E\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"wgzzrgqhds",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u4EBA\u5DE5\u53D6\u706B\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u9633\u9547",
		"indexes":"sdmzbbk",
		"question":"\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u9547\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC",
		"id":18711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5FBD",
		"indexes":"txdysjhsfhswy",
		"question":"\u5929\u4E0B\u7B2C\u4E00\u677E\uFF1A\u4E5D\u534E\u5C71\u51E4\u51F0\u677E\u4F4D\u4E8E",
		"id":18712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u591C\u697C",
		"indexes":"sdmlbbk",
		"question":"\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u697C\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC",
		"id":18713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u76C6\u5730",
		"indexes":"zgjnzddwlpds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5883\u5185\u6700\u5927\u7684\u5916\u6D41\u76C6\u5730\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7231\u65B0\u89C9\u7F57\u00B7\u5F18\u5386",
		"indexes":"wglsszgsdhd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u9AD8\u5BFF\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1A",
		"id":18715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6743",
		"indexes":"lszzzccjjdrss",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E2D\u771F\u6B63\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":18716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"zsdxhnfzdsxzd",
		"question":"\u5728\u5B8B\u4EE3\u897F\u6CB3\u5357\u5E9C\u6307\u7684\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u7684",
		"id":18717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u89E3\u653E",
		"indexes":"1956n7y13rzcdyqccscxzgddypqczzqcdmzssm",
		"question":"1956\u5E747\u670813\u65E5\uFF0C\u957F\u6625\u7B2C\u4E00\u6C7D\u8F66\u5382\u751F\u4EA7\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6279\u6C7D\u8F66\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u6C7D\u8F66\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u4E3B\u6559",
		"indexes":"sfsjdjngjpdsz",
		"question":"\u795E\u7236\u662F\u57FA\u7763\u6559\u54EA\u4E2A\u6559\u6D3E\u7684\u795E\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":18719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC",
		"indexes":"1977nhfgkhddycgkszngjjjxd",
		"question":"1977\u5E74\u6062\u590D\u9AD8\u8003\u540E\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u9AD8\u8003\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B63\u8282\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18720
	},
	{
		"answer":"1979\u5E741\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"________zmjjtywgzfldrdxpfmfw",
		"question":"________\u4E2D\u7F8E\u5EFA\u4EA4\uFF0C\u540C\u6708\u6211\u56FD\u653F\u5E9C\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u9093\u5C0F\u5E73\u8D74\u7F8E\u8BBF\u95EE\u3002",
		"id":18721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57C3\u53CA",
		"indexes":"sjszzbfddgmnlqyfsz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7206\u53D1\u7684\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u5974\u96B6\u8D77\u4E49\u53D1\u751F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":18722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5362\u6D77\u6021",
		"indexes":"xmbswggddsdmnds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u56DB\u5927\u7F8E\u5973\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":18723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u5C39",
		"indexes":"stztjtzsqcxdhjmdyynwztyldfz",
		"question":"\u5546\u6C64\u81F3\u592A\u7532\u7EDF\u6CBB\u65F6\u671F\u51FA\u73B0\u5927\u597D\u5C40\u9762\uFF0C\u5F97\u76CA\u4E8E\u54EA\u4F4D\u653F\u575B\u5143\u8001\u7684\u8F85\u4F50\uFF1F",
		"id":18724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9",
		"indexes":"lgzngzxbqsm",
		"question":"\u516D\u56FD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u56FD\u6700\u5148\u88AB\u79E6\u6240\u706D",
		"id":18725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u5229\u65F6",
		"indexes":"nplbbhtlcedztzzsmdjshtlwynggj",
		"question":"\u62FF\u7834\u4ED1\u5175\u8D25\u6ED1\u94C1\u5362\uFF0C\u4ECE\u800C\u5BFC\u81F4\u4ED6\u653F\u6CBB\u751F\u547D\u7684\u7ED3\u675F\u3002\u6ED1\u94C1\u5362\u4F4D\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"dygcyyzbmdgjsng",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u91C7\u7528\u90AE\u653F\u7F16\u7801\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18727
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u56FD\u8054\u519B\u4FB5\u534E\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"xctyszglssjglnczzhqdd",
		"question":"\u300A\u8F9B\u4E11\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7ECF\u8FC7\u4E86\u54EA\u6B21\u6218\u4E89\u540E\u7B7E\u8BA2\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF11\uFF19\uFF11\uFF14\uFF0D\uFF11\uFF19\uFF11\uFF18",
		"indexes":"dycsjdzdsmsjs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u7684\u59CB\u672B\u65F6\u95F4\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7814\u836F\u672F",
		"indexes":"zgcslsdfmxmngbssdfmzy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EA7\u751F\u4E86\u56DB\u5927\u53D1\u660E,\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u56DB\u5927\u53D1\u660E\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":18730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"ymzyywnascfjkdnmsskdd",
		"question":"\u56E0\u67D0\u79CD\u539F\u56E0\u672A\u80FD\u6309\u65F6\u5403\u996D\u53EB\u201C\u625B\u5200\u201D\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u662F\u8C01\u625B\u7684\u5200\uFF1F",
		"id":18731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05",
		"indexes":"cxqsncdr",
		"question":"\u66F9\u96EA\u82B9\u662F\u54EA\u671D\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18732
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u67083\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgkrzzsljnrs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u80DC\u5229\u7EAA\u5FF5\u65E5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u7F57\u9A6C\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"wmxzydxqynzrzxsyd",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u73B0\u5728\u7528\u7684\u201C\u661F\u671F\u201D\u7531\u54EA\u79CD\u4EBA\u6700\u5148\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u6D32",
		"indexes":"tgqyy",
		"question":"\u63A2\u6208\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18735
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgfjjzchdsyngcd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5C01\u5EFA\u541B\u4E3B\u79F0\u201C\u7687\u5E1D\u201D\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"zhmycdylylssnwryg",
		"question":"\u201C\u8D70\u540E\u95E8\u201D\u4E00\u8BCD\u7684\u7531\u6765\u4E0E\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u54EA\u4F4D\u4EBA\u6709\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":18737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FFC\u738B",
		"indexes":"sdkdrds",
		"question":"\u77F3\u8FBE\u5F00\u62C5\u4EFB\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u819D\u76D6\u9AA8",
		"indexes":"wggdjsjsbszbxhbcwsbdbsz",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u519B\u4E8B\u5BB6\u5B59\u8191\u662F\u5728\u201C\u8191\u5211\u201D\u540E\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u5B59\u8191\u7684\uFF0C\u201C\u8191\u201D\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":18739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u523B\u5728\u6728\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"zzdcls",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6625\u8054\u662F",
		"id":18740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510",
		"indexes":"zgzzzjdasy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7EB8\u8BB0\u6863\u6848\u59CB\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u91CC\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zjhblzymxszwzxdaxhyds",
		"question":"\u81F3\u4ECA\u8FD8\u4FDD\u7559\u7740\u4EE5\u6BCD\u7CFB\u6C0F\u65CF\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5FC3\u7684\u201C\u963F\u590F\u201D\u5A5A\u59FB\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54",
		"indexes":"bssdbjxyzjsqkxsdyzbjxyhxjs",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u7684\u300A\u767E\u5BB6\u59D3\u300B\u4EE5\u201C\u8D75\u201D\u5C45\u9996\uFF0C\u6E05\u5EB7\u7199\u65F6\u7684\u300A\u5FA1\u5236\u767E\u5BB6\u59D3\u300B\u4EE5\u4F55\u59D3\u5C45\u9996\uFF1F",
		"id":18743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u5942",
		"indexes":"sgswgdzhyghds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\uFF0C\u9B4F\u56FD\u7684\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18744
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u664B",
		"indexes":"sgdzhslgs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u6700\u540E\u80DC\u5229\u56FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18745
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"szjdzdmslkzxdsdljczydzxd",
		"question":"\u5341\u5B57\u519B\u4E1C\u5F81\u5BF9\u7A46\u65AF\u6797\u63A7\u5236\u4E0B\u7684\u5723\u5730\u4E86\u51E0\u6B21\u4E3B\u8981\u4E1C\u5F81\u884C\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":18746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u8037",
		"indexes":"yxsbsyzbg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\uFF1F",
		"id":18747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u6E90\u9601",
		"indexes":"skqsqssxqbfbzywywywjwzwhwswlqgzbyfljfhds",
		"question":"\u300A\u56DB\u5E93\u5168\u4E66\u300B\u5168\u4E66\u7F2E\u5199\u4E03\u90E8\u5206\u522B\u85CF\u4E8E\u6587\u6E0A\u3001\u6587\u6E90\u3001\u6587\u6D25\u3001\u6587\u5B97\u3001\u6587\u6C47\u3001\u6587\u6EAF\u3001\u6587\u6F9C\u4E03\u9601\u4E2D\uFF0C\u88AB\u82F1\u6CD5\u8054\u519B\u711A\u6BC1\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18748
	},
	{
		"answer":"53",
		"indexes":"2003njbdsjxjdssddsj",
		"question":"2003\u5E74\u4E3E\u529E\u7684\u4E16\u754C\u5C0F\u59D0\u5927\u8D5B\u662F\u7B2C\u591A\u5C11\u5C4A",
		"id":18749
	},
	{
		"answer":"1988",
		"indexes":"tamcldyczsxzghsjsyrkfksynynyd",
		"question":"\u5929\u5B89\u95E8\u57CE\u697C\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u6B63\u5F0F\u5411\u4E2D\u56FD\u548C\u4E16\u754C\u6240\u6709\u4EBA\u5F00\u653E\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5143\u65E6",
		"id":18750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5357\u7701",
		"indexes":"xjhggsywgnygs",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4ECA,\u51FD\u8C37\u5173\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u90A3\u4E00\u4E2A\u7701?",
		"id":18751
	},
	{
		"answer":"1911",
		"indexes":"znynmzdcjrhnqydxj",
		"question":"\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF0C\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u66FE\u52A0\u5165\u6E56\u5357\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u65B0\u519B\uFF1A",
		"id":18752
	},
	{
		"answer":"1955",
		"indexes":"znynyjybsyysjx",
		"question":"\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF0C\u53F6\u5251\u82F1\u88AB\u6388\u4E88\u5143\u5E05\u519B\u8854\uFF1A",
		"id":18753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u864E\u95E8",
		"indexes":"lzxzgdncxhyp",
		"question":"\u6797\u5219\u5F90\u5728\u5E7F\u4E1C\u54EA\u5904\u9500\u6BC1\u9E26\u7247\uFF1F",
		"id":18754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8036\u7A23\u57FA\u7763\u6559",
		"indexes":"mqsjjygyqhdhfdffsysmwbz",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u4E16\u754C\u7EAA\u5143(\u516C\u5143\u524D\u540E\u7684\u5212\u5206)\u7684\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E3A\u6807\u51C6\uFF1A",
		"id":18755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u501F\u53E3\u4E00\u4E2A\u58EB\u5175\u5931\u8E2A",
		"indexes":"20sj30ndrbzzgzjktqqhzzqzqqsblyds",
		"question":"20\u4E16\u7EAA30\u5E74\u4EE3\u65E5\u672C\u5236\u9020\u5404\u79CD\u501F\u53E3\u6311\u8D77\u4FB5\u534E\u6218\u4E89\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u4E03\u4E03\u4E8B\u53D8\u5229\u7528\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EC1\u5FB7\u5929\u7687\u9675",
		"indexes":"sjdymzdsnyzlm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u4E00\u5893\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u90A3\u4E00\u5EA7\u9675\u5893\uFF1F",
		"id":18757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FC4\u56FD",
		"indexes":"decypzzsqqzwgltzddgjs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F,\u4FB5\u5360\u6211\u56FD\u9886\u571F\u6700\u591A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u56DB\u6B21",
		"indexes":"wxmnyczdzzsyalbgjsxjgd",
		"question":"\u95EE\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u6B21\u4E2D\u4E1C\u6218\u4E89\u662F\u7531\u963F\u62C9\u4F2F\u56FD\u5BB6\u9996\u5148\u8FDB\u653B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18759
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5951\u4E39",
		"indexes":"cypdaszldtddjlgbbfhrtsngmzr",
		"question":"\u53C2\u4E0E\u8BC4\u5B9A\u201C\u5B89\u53F2\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u7684\u5510\u4EE3\u5927\u5C06\u674E\u5149\u5F3C\u5E76\u975E\u6C49\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5B83\u662F\u54EA\u5404\u6C11\u65CF\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":18760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE0\u4F2F\u94A7",
		"indexes":"xzgdyrjtbbzss",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u4EA4\u901A\u90E8\u90E8\u957F\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u79B9",
		"indexes":"zcsbsyshwd",
		"question":"\u6307\u51FA\u8C01\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E09\u7687\u4E94\u5E1D\u3002",
		"id":18762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF1\u5733\u3001\u73E0\u6D77\u3001\u6C55\u5934\u3001\u53A6\u95E8",
		"indexes":"syjszqhyhwgzzjldsgjjtqsnjg",
		"question":"\u5341\u4E00\u5C4A\u4E09\u4E2D\u5168\u4F1A\u4EE5\u540E\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684\u56DB\u4E2A\u7ECF\u6D4E\u7279\u533A\u662F\u54EA\u51E0\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":18763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u7EE7\u660C\u9686\u201D",
		"indexes":"zgdygmzzbjydjqsscs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u8D44\u672C\u7ECF\u8425\u7684\u673A\u5668\u7F2B\u4E1D\u5382\u662F",
		"id":18764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u6709\u4E3A",
		"indexes":"xmnwmrbsxwhyddxq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u4F4D\u540D\u4EBA\u4E0D\u662F\u65B0\u6587\u5316\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u5148\u9A71?",
		"id":18765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u9053",
		"indexes":"xlcymzngbszeld",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u66FE\u7528\u540D\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5468\u6069\u6765\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18766
	},
	{
		"answer":"1971",
		"indexes":"zhrmghgzlhgdhfxwddhfsz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u5728\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u7684\u5408\u6CD5\u5E2D\u4F4D\u5F97\u5230\u6062\u590D\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18767
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5175\u4E66\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u7BC7",
		"indexes":"xlhswzglsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4F55\u4E66\u4E3A\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6240\u8457\uFF1F",
		"id":18768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u53F2\u6148",
		"indexes":"dzfsylsddscjlbszgjszwsnhshwhrsy",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u4E08\u592B\u751F\u4E8E\u4E71\u4E16\uFF0C\u5F53\u5E26\u4E09\u5C3A\u5251\u7ACB\u4E0D\u4E16\u4E4B\u529F\uFF0C\u4ECA\u6240\u5FD7\u672A\u9042\uFF0C\u5948\u4F55\u6B7B\u4E4E\uFF01\u201D\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u8A00\uFF1F",
		"id":18769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"zglhsxypsqqyd",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u706B\u70E7\u65B0\u91CE\u6D3E\u8C01\u524D\u53BB\u8BF1\u654C\uFF1F",
		"id":18770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u81EA\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"zyhzzwkrexsdd33jtjzsls",
		"question":"\u67A3\u5B9C\u4F1A\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E3A\u6297\u65E5\u800C\u727A\u7272\u7684\u7B2C33\u96C6\u56E2\u519B\u603B\u53F8\u4EE4\u662F",
		"id":18771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"kzkshzgxbzlhjgbwbljrzzhs",
		"question":"\u6297\u6218\u5F00\u59CB\u540E\u4E2D\u56FD\u897F\u5317\u4E3B\u529B\u7EA2\u519B\u6539\u7F16\u4E3A\u516B\u8DEF\u519B\uFF0C\u4EFB\u603B\u6307\u6325\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E0A",
		"indexes":"tcjlzs",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u5EFA\u7ACB\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C74\u6881",
		"indexes":"kfgc",
		"question":"\u5F00\u5C01\u53E4\u79F0\uFF1A",
		"id":18774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DB5\u7A81\u6CC9",
		"indexes":"qlhdbtxdyqmmjlngq",
		"question":"\u4E7E\u9686\u7687\u5E1D\u628A\u201C\u5929\u4E0B\u7B2C\u4E00\u6CC9\u201D\u7F8E\u540D\u7ED9\u4E86\u54EA\u4E2A\u6CC9",
		"id":18775
	},
	{
		"answer":"1911\u5E74",
		"indexes":"qczsmshbtf",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u88AB\u63A8\u7FFB?",
		"id":18776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u97EC",
		"indexes":"zggdbfltzbhxmnyt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5175\u6CD5\u201C\u516D\u97EC\u201D\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0D\u542B\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u97EC",
		"id":18777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4E91\u5FE0\u4E00",
		"indexes":"drztdhzrfhkmjzgjdzhds",
		"question":"\u62C5\u4EFB\u4E2D\u9014\u5C9B\u6D77\u6218\u65E5\u65B9\u822A\u7A7A\u6BCD\u8230\u4E3B\u653B\u8230\u961F\u6307\u6325\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18778
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u7C73",
		"indexes":"hzacddjfstdzyylky",
		"question":"\u6C49\u957F\u5B89\u57CE\u7684\u5927\u8857\u5206\u4E09\u6761\u9053\uFF0C\u4E2D\u592E\u5FA1\u8DEF\u5BBD\u7EA6\uFF1A",
		"id":18779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9707\u9F99",
		"indexes":"dmqwzwmsfxdzddkls",
		"question":"\u5230\u76EE\u524D\u4E3A\u6B62\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u6240\u53D1\u73B0\u7684\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6050\u9F99\u662F",
		"id":18780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u82F1",
		"indexes":"dldhzsnlgjz",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u5170\u5927\u6D77\u6218\u662F\u54EA\u4E24\u56FD\u4EA4\u6218\uFF1F",
		"id":18781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FAE\u751F\u7269\u5DE5\u4E1A\u578B\u519C\u4E1A",
		"indexes":"jjntcdbsnysz",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u51E0\u5E74\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\u767D\u8272\u519C\u4E1A\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":18782
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u768B\u9676",
		"indexes":"sfgdzss",
		"question":"\u53F8\u6CD5\u5B98\u7684\u7956\u5E08\u662F",
		"id":18783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"gy1368nzyzcdjlmcddz",
		"question":"\u516C\u51431368\u5E74\uFF0C\u6731\u5143\u748B\u79F0\u5E1D\uFF0C\u5EFA\u7ACB\u660E\u671D\uFF0C\u5B9A\u90FD\u5728\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":18784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"17sjdxydgssnggjzdwzmkzsjld",
		"question":"17\u4E16\u7EAA\u7684\u897F\u5370\u5EA6\u516C\u53F8\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u5BF9\u5916\u6B96\u6C11\u6269\u5F20\u65F6\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684?",
		"id":18785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u83B2\u82F1",
		"indexes":"ystjygcesdzzhxdtjs",
		"question":"\u56E0\u68B3\u5934\u6280\u827A\u9AD8\u8D85\u800C\u6DF1\u5F97\u4E3B\u5B50\u6B22\u5FC3\u7684\u592A\u76D1\u662F",
		"id":18786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u7687\u5F8B",
		"indexes":"cztlswxzdzzgdz",
		"question":"\u7B1E\u3001\u6756\u3001\u5F92\u3001\u6D41\u3001\u6B7B\u4E94\u5211\u5236\u5EA6\u6700\u65E9\u89C4\u5B9A\u5728",
		"id":18787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"zgnlzwjxxdzjjyqgbcwfsy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5974\u96B6\u5236\u74E6\u89E3\uFF0C\u65B0\u5174\u5730\u4E3B\u9636\u7EA7\u8981\u6C42\u516C\u5E03\u6210\u6587\u6CD5\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199\u7687\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"qcdnwhdyseqdlnbcty",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u4E0E\u6C99\u4FC4\u7B7E\u8BA2\u4E86\u300A\u5C3C\u5E03\u695A\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":18789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143",
		"indexes":"zglssdygssmztzqgdwcsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u7EDF\u6CBB\u5168\u56FD\u7684\u738B\u671D\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1A",
		"id":18790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7261\u4E39\u82B1",
		"indexes":"cszwztxlfsdhssmh",
		"question":"\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u4E0B\u4EE4\u711A\u70E7\u7684\u82B1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u82B1",
		"id":18791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u6B21",
		"indexes":"lssyzjmyfddszjdzqhjxljc",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\uFF0C\u4EE5\u5B97\u6559\u540D\u4E49\u53D1\u52A8\u7684\u5341\u5B57\u519B\u4E1C\u5F81\uFF0C\u524D\u540E\u8FDB\u884C\u4E86\u51E0\u6B21\uFF1F",
		"id":18792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7FF0\u7684\u300A\u51C9\u5DDE\u8BCD\u4E8C\u9996\u300B\u5176\u4E00",
		"indexes":"ptmjygbdccs",
		"question":"\u201C\u8461\u8404\u7F8E\u9152\u591C\u5149\u676F\u201D\u7684\u51FA\u5904\u662F",
		"id":18793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u5F8B\u662F\u541B\u4E3B\u6CBB\u7406\u5929\u4E0B\u7684\u5DE5\u5177",
		"indexes":"hfzfzsxdszs",
		"question":"\u97E9\u975E\u5B50\u201C\u6CD5\u6CBB\u201D\u601D\u60F3\u7684\u5B9E\u8D28\u662F",
		"id":18794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5199\u4EA1\u56FD\u5267\u75DB\u7684\u8BCD",
		"indexes":"lyczzgrdzps",
		"question":"\u674E\u715C\u8BCD\u4E2D\u6700\u611F\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F",
		"id":18795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"wyfxydfyy",
		"question":"\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u8FD0\u52A8\u53D1\u6E90\u4E8E",
		"id":18796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u54F2\u4F26",
		"indexes":"zoztsxhlgczsxhqhxds",
		"question":"\u5728\u6B27\u6D32\u63A2\u7D22\u65B0\u822A\u8DEF\u8FC7\u7A0B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5B9E\u73B0\u73AF\u7403\u822A\u884C\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18797
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"dsssyqgzzhhstfdz",
		"question":"\u5F53\u65F6\u662F\u8C01\u9080\u8BF7\u5404\u9547\u8BF8\u4FAF\u4F1A\u5E08\u8BA8\u4F10\u8463\u5353",
		"id":18798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62C9\u6590\u5C14",
		"indexes":"ydlwyfxzbzwhsdhjs",
		"question":"\u610F\u5927\u5229\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u4E2D\u88AB\u5C0A\u4E3A\u201C\u753B\u5723\u201D\u7684\u753B\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u5730",
		"indexes":"ldmzdygdldgjs",
		"question":"\u62C9\u4E01\u7F8E\u6D32\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u72EC\u7ACB\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18800
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u5BB6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"jkgyjfxmqsjszzdcqcxznl",
		"question":"\u636E\u8003\u53E4\u7814\u7A76\u53D1\u73B0\uFF0C\u76EE\u524D\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":18801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u3001\u96C5\u3001\u9882",
		"indexes":"sjdctfls",
		"question":"\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u5206\u7C7B\u662F",
		"id":18802
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u5546\u4E3B\u4E49",
		"indexes":"zbzyzqbjsxdjjsxs",
		"question":"\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u65E9\u671F\u6BD4\u8F83\u76DB\u884C\u7684\u7ECF\u6D4E\u601D\u60F3\u662F",
		"id":18803
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3C\u5FB7\u5170\u9769\u547D",
		"indexes":"sjlssdyccgdzcjjgms",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u6210\u529F\u7684\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u662F",
		"id":18804
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u610F\u5FD7",
		"indexes":"xodzjggksy",
		"question":"\u897F\u6B27\u7684\u5B97\u6559\u6539\u9769\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E0\u4E3A\u53D8\u6CD5\u89E6\u52A8\u4E86\u8D35\u65CF\u5229\u76CA",
		"indexes":"sywsmbcs",
		"question":"\u5546\u9785\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u88AB\u5904\u6B7B?",
		"id":18806
	},
	{
		"answer":"1895",
		"indexes":"gcssfsznyn",
		"question":"\u201C\u516C\u8F66\u4E0A\u4E66\u201D\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18807
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u540C\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"cxfdzbsznygdwqj",
		"question":"\u6148\u79A7\u53D1\u52A8\u653F\u53D8\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E1D\u738B\u671F\u95F4\uFF1A",
		"id":18808
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u4E16\u7EAA\u672B",
		"indexes":"ygdbzmdgxbycwhsqgsz",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u6253\u8D25\u6B96\u6C11\u5E1D\u56FD\u897F\u73ED\u7259\u6210\u4E3A\u6D77\u4E0A\u5F3A\u56FD\u662F\u5728()",
		"id":18809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FBE\u82AC\u5947",
		"indexes":"xlnwsxowyfxsqddbysj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u897F\u6B27\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u827A\u672F\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u94ED\u4F20",
		"indexes":"1885ntwzsjlxsdyrxfs",
		"question":"1885\u5E74\uFF0C\u53F0\u6E7E\u6B63\u5F0F\u5EFA\u7ACB\u884C\u7701\uFF0C\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u5DE1\u629A\u662F",
		"id":18811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u8868",
		"indexes":"208ncczxyzzzmls",
		"question":"208\u5E74\u66F9\u64CD\u5728\u8944\u9633\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\u706D\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":18812
	},
	{
		"answer":"15\u4E16\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"xfzmzscsmshkszfzjxldxdnlmyd",
		"question":"\u897F\u65B9\u6B96\u6C11\u8005\u662F\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u5F00\u59CB\u5728\u975E\u6D32\u8FDB\u884C\u63A0\u593A\u6027\u7684\u201C\u5974\u96B6\u8D38\u6613\u201D\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AD\u4EE3\u53F2",
		"indexes":"hsssdlsbztls",
		"question":"\u300A\u6C49\u4E66\u300B\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u7F16\u7E82\u4F53\u4F8B\u662F",
		"id":18814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u6D4E\u6781\u7AEF\u8D2B\u56F0\u7684\u72B6\u51B5",
		"indexes":"xhctzzsxkszcdgbyys",
		"question":"\u897F\u6C49\u521D\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u5B9E\u884C\u5BBD\u8212\u653F\u7B56\u7684\u6839\u672C\u539F\u56E0\u662F",
		"id":18815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB0\u8FF0\u91CD\u8981\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u5BB6\u5EAD\u5174\u8870",
		"indexes":"sjdwztlzsjzztls",
		"question":"\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\u7684\u4E94\u79CD\u4F53\u4F8B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u201C\u4E16\u5BB6\u201D\u8FD9\u79CD\u4F53\u4F8B\u662F",
		"id":18816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u96C0",
		"indexes":"qddgfspzcyddhlyssgwdxzbzhlsqzsmdwdm",
		"question":"\u6E05\u4EE3\u7684\u5B98\u670D\u9970\u54C1\u4E2D\u5E38\u6709\u201C\u9876\u6234\u82B1\u7FCE\u201D\u4E00\u8BF4\uFF0C\u662F\u5B98\u4F4D\u7684\u8C61\u5F81\u6807\u5FD7\uFF0C\u201C\u82B1\u7FCE\u201D\u662F\u53D6\u81EA\u4EC0\u4E48\u52A8\u7269\u7684\u6BDB\uFF1F",
		"id":18817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"yczfzqggflxsz",
		"question":"\u996E\u8336\u4E4B\u98CE\u5728\u5168\u56FD\u5E7F\u6CDB\u6D41\u884C\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5929\u738B\u9001\u5B50\u56FE\u300B",
		"indexes":"wdzyyfmhtmxlsjmnjshtdfqjfwbztbytsdqjzfmhs",
		"question":"\u5434\u9053\u5B50\u6709\u4E00\u5E45\u540D\u753B\uFF0C\u5B83\u63CF\u5199\u4E86\u91CA\u8FE6\u725F\u5C3C\u964D\u751F\u540E\uFF0C\u4ED6\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u51C0\u996D\u738B\u62B1\u7740\u4ED6\u62DC\u8C12\u5929\u795E\u7684\u60C5\u666F\uFF0C\u8FD9\u5E45\u540D\u753B\u662F",
		"id":18819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"bjbsyxngcdddc",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u4E0D\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\uFF1F",
		"id":18820
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE",
		"indexes":"snbzwghgjychthczydmdnss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5546\u5973\u4E0D\u77E5\u4EA1\u56FD\u6068\uFF0C\u9694\u6C5F\u72B9\u5531\u540E\u5EAD\u82B1\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u675C\u7267\u7684\u90A3\u9996\u8BD7",
		"id":18821
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BD2\u6B66\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"xmnygsdbsklshdsd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u65F6\u4EE3\u4E0D\u662F\u6050\u9F99\u751F\u6D3B\u7684\u65F6\u4EE3",
		"id":18822
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6006\u7136",
		"indexes":"tdsrczadmjntdzyydetx",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u7684\u540D\u53E5\u201C\u5FF5\u5929\u5730\u4E4B\u60A0\u60A0\uFF0C\u72EC\u00D7\u00D7\u800C\u6D95\u4E0B\u201D",
		"id":18823
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u9002",
		"indexes":"zxwhydzzjllzyycdxldzlxqxth",
		"question":"\u5728\u65B0\u6587\u5316\u8FD0\u52A8\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E2D\u575A\u529B\u91CF\u4E3B\u8981\u6709\u9648\u72EC\u79C0\uFF0C\u674E\u5927\u948A\uFF0C\u9C81\u8FC5\uFF0C\u94B1\u7384\u540C\u548C\uFF1A",
		"id":18824
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u6536\u8D77\u4E49",
		"indexes":"dgmsbhncqywmzdqzld",
		"question":"\u5927\u9769\u547D\u5931\u8D25\u540E\uFF0C\u54EA\u6B21\u8D77\u4E49\u4E3A\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u4EB2\u81EA\u9886\u5BFC\uFF1F",
		"id":18825
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u56DB\u8FD0\u52A8",
		"indexes":"blhhdjgdzl",
		"question":"\u5DF4\u9ECE\u548C\u4F1A\u7684\u7ED3\u679C\u5BFC\u81F4\u4E86",
		"id":18826
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u00B7\u4E09\u60E8\u6848",
		"indexes":"xlnygsjyjfdqrwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0E\u519B\u9600\u6BB5\u797A\u745E\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":18827
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"1925n3y12rszsbsy",
		"question":"1925\u5E743\u670812\u65E5\uFF0C\u5B59\u4E2D\u5C71\u75C5\u901D\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":18828
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672F\u8D64",
		"indexes":"cjshdzzss",
		"question":"\u6210\u5409\u601D\u6C57\u7684\u957F\u5B50\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18829
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u649E\u51FB\u51B0\u5C71",
		"indexes":"tdnhylsywzylsmsjcmd",
		"question":"\u94C1\u8FBE\u5C3C\u53F7\u6E38\u8F6E\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u906D\u9047\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E8B\u4EF6\u6C89\u6CA1\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18830
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9152",
		"indexes":"szzggdsysmdqj",
		"question":"\u52FA\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u662F\u8200\u4EC0\u4E48\u7684\u5668\u5177\uFF1F",
		"id":18831
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u601D\u9088",
		"indexes":"zwggdywmyhd101sbcwbssyts",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6709\u4F4D\u540D\u533B\u6D3B\u5230101\u5C81\uFF0C\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u767E\u5C81\u795E\u533B\u201D\uFF0C\u4ED6\u662F",
		"id":18832
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u811A",
		"indexes":"zggdysdmndrwwrtmdygzdqxqwwzjdqdssm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6709\u56DB\u5927\u7F8E\u5973\uFF0C\u4F46\u4EBA\u65E0\u5B8C\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4ED6\u4EEC\u90FD\u6709\u5404\u81EA\u7684\u7F3A\u9677\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u738B\u662D\u541B\u7684\u7F3A\u70B9\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18833
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"cltzsyhs",
		"question":"\u201C\u5782\u5E18\u542C\u653F\u201D\u59CB\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":18834
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u4E94\u5345\u201D\u8FD0\u52A8\u671F\u95F4",
		"indexes":"zzggcdldxshzghcly",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u9886\u5BFC\u4E0B\uFF0C\u4E0A\u6D77\u603B\u5DE5\u4F1A\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E",
		"id":18835
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DEF\u6613\u00B7\u6CE2\u62FF\u5DF4",
		"indexes":"yffddecypzzsfgdtzzs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u6CD5\u53D1\u52A8\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\uFF0C\u6CD5\u56FD\u7684\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u662F",
		"id":18836
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u6728\u5076\u5934",
		"indexes":"sjsdygcxzdsypsdxxs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u7535\u89C6\u8367\u5C4F\u4E0A\u7684\u5F62\u8C61\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18837
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"sjszzjlhlhxszngsq",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u8BB0\u5F55\u54C8\u96F7\u5F57\u661F\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":18838
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC6\u897F\u897F\u6BD4\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"zzdbmzmdzxbyygfgdczlgdtydqs",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E89\u593A\u5317\u7F8E\u6B96\u6C11\u5730\u4E2D\uFF0C\u897F\u73ED\u7259\u82F1\u56FD\u6CD5\u56FD\u90FD\u66FE\u5360\u9886\u8FC7\u7684\u540C\u4E00\u5730\u533A\u662F",
		"id":18839
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519C\u6751\u516C\u793E",
		"indexes":"gyqeqndzqylarjrydhxcl",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143\u524D\u4E8C\u5343\u5E74\u4EE3\u4E2D\u671F\u96C5\u5229\u5B89\u4EBA\u8FDB\u5165\u5370\u5EA6\u540E\uFF0C\u5F62\u6210\u4E86",
		"id":18840
	},
	{
		"answer":"1927\u5E74",
		"indexes":"ldzbzzlshsz",
		"question":"\u674E\u5927\u948A\u88AB\u5F20\u4F5C\u9716\u6740\u5BB3\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18841
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CD\u6E05\u7EDF\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"hxqclbsdhdmds",
		"question":"\u6D2A\u79C0\u5168\u521B\u7ACB\u62DC\u4E0A\u5E1D\u4F1A\u7684\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18842
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"dodqdsdzjlzgmydzhysqs",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6B27\u5730\u533A\u7684\u5546\u961F\u76F4\u63A5\u6765\u4E2D\u56FD\u8D38\u6613\u7684\u6700\u6D3B\u8DC3\u65F6\u671F\u662F",
		"id":18843
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53B3\u54D2",
		"indexes":"dyswgz5sjhbywyszs",
		"question":"\u5927\u6708\u6C0F\u738B\u56FD\u57285\u4E16\u7EAA\u540E\u534A\u53F6\u4EA1\u4E8E\u8C01\u4E4B\u624B",
		"id":18844
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u7075\u987F\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"jbnpldhtlzydffljzhgs",
		"question":"\u51FB\u8D25\u62FF\u7834\u4ED1\u7684\u6ED1\u94C1\u5362\u6218\u5F79\u7684\u53CD\u6CD5\u8054\u519B\u6307\u6325\u5B98\u662F",
		"id":18845
	},
	{
		"answer":"1912\u5E741\u6708",
		"indexes":"zhmgzsxgclsz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u534E\u6C11\u56FD\u6B63\u5F0F\u5BA3\u544A\u6210\u7ACB\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18846
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u8FBE\u5F00",
		"indexes":"1855nzpyhdbxjdtpjjls",
		"question":"1855\u5E74\u5728\u9131\u9633\u6E56\u5927\u8D25\u6E58\u519B\u7684\u592A\u5E73\u519B\u5C06\u9886\u662F",
		"id":18847
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u54C1\u7ECF\u6D4E\u7684\u53D1\u5C55",
		"indexes":"byzmdcwpbltdhbqzyyys",
		"question":"\u767D\u94F6\u5728\u660E\u4EE3\u6210\u4E3A\u666E\u904D\u6D41\u901A\u7684\u8D27\u5E01\uFF0C\u5176\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u56E0\u662F",
		"id":18848
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u5219\u5F90",
		"indexes":"jdzgkyksjddyrs",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u201C\u5F00\u773C\u770B\u4E16\u754C\u201D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":18849
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u519B\u8FDB\u653B\u9A7B\u8D8A\u4E2D\u56FD\u519B\u961F",
		"indexes":"zfzzbfdbzs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u6CD5\u6218\u4E89\u7206\u53D1\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18850
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A80\u9999\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xzhclddds",
		"question":"\u5174\u4E2D\u4F1A\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\u5730\u70B9\u662F",
		"id":18851
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5C3E\u6D77\u6218\u540E",
		"indexes":"qzfxzxfgzsxzsz",
		"question":"\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u4E0B\u8BCF\u5411\u6CD5\u56FD\u6B63\u5F0F\u5BA3\u6218\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18852
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89\u540E",
		"indexes":"zgywpcsy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6D0B\u52A1\u6D3E\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E",
		"id":18853
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u6D59\u7701\u7BA1\u8F96",
		"indexes":"ycstwdlsy",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u65F6\uFF0C\u53F0\u6E7E\u5C9B\u96B6\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":18854
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E2D\u6CD5\u65B0\u7EA6\u300B",
		"indexes":"jybdkzgxnmhbpdtys",
		"question":"\u8FDB\u4E00\u6B65\u6253\u5F00\u4E2D\u56FD\u897F\u5357\u95E8\u6237\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\u662F",
		"id":18855
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5B66\u793E\u3001\u5171\u8FDB\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"wcqyqxlqhcdszjtzzhfdzcqydtts",
		"question":"\u6B66\u660C\u8D77\u4E49\u6572\u54CD\u4E86\u6E05\u7687\u671D\u7684\u4E27\u949F\uFF0C\u5177\u4F53\u7EC4\u7EC7\u548C\u53D1\u52A8\u8FD9\u6B21\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u56E2\u4F53\u662F",
		"id":18856
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB3\u9633",
		"indexes":"sgyyzdzysybqsxzd",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u5468\u745C\u6B7B\u4E8E\u5DF4\u4E18\uFF0C\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u7684",
		"id":18857
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u5B9A\u5927\u5C0F\u548C\u5353\u53DB\u4E71\u540E\u6E05\u671D\u9996\u6B21\u7EDF\u4E00\u65B0\u7586",
		"indexes":"yxgyqqqxjdqzkdbscwds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5173\u4E8E\u6E05\u524D\u671F\u65B0\u7586\u5730\u533A\u72B6\u51B5\u7684\u8868\u8FF0\uFF0C\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18858
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548F\u53F2\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"lyxzcltyzcfxsjzzxdczcpqfgbsqtwmczsssys",
		"question":"\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u5728\u300A\u916C\u4E50\u5929\u626C\u5DDE\u521D\u9022\u5E2D\u4E0A\u89C1\u8D60\u300B\u4E2D\u5199\u5230\u201C\u6C89\u821F\u4FA7\u7554\u5343\u5E06\u8FC7\uFF0C\u75C5\u6811\u524D\u5934\u4E07\u6728\u6625\u201D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u9996\u8BD7\u662F\u4E00\u9996",
		"id":18859
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6291\u5236\u4E86\u571F\u5730\u517C\u5E76\u73B0\u8C61",
		"indexes":"dbwsxjtzdhgbsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u5317\u9B4F\u5B9E\u884C\u5747\u7530\u5236\u7684\u540E\u679C\uFF0C\u8868\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18860
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FBD\u6CB3\u4E0A\u6E38",
		"indexes":"qdzqyddqs",
		"question":"\u5951\u4E39\u65CF\u8D77\u6E90\u7684\u5730\u533A\u662F",
		"id":18861
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C5\u5C14\u5854\u4F1A\u8BAE",
		"indexes":"ezzjdzzhcllhgdgjhys",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\u51B3\u5B9A\u5728\u6218\u540E\u6210\u7ACB\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u7684\u56FD\u9645\u4F1A\u8BAE\u662F",
		"id":18862
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u4E16\u51EF",
		"indexes":"cdxhgmslgsdyxjs",
		"question":"\u7BE1\u593A\u8F9B\u4EA5\u9769\u547D\u80DC\u5229\u679C\u5B9E\u7684\u91CE\u5FC3\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18863
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9A6C\u5173\u6761\u7EA6\u300B",
		"indexes":"gdgrtwhphlddbpdtys",
		"question":"\u89C4\u5B9A\u5272\u8BA9\u53F0\u6E7E\u548C\u6F8E\u6E56\u5217\u5C9B\u7684\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\u662F",
		"id":18864
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EAC\u5E08\u5927\u5B66\u5802",
		"indexes":"wxbfzcbdzgjdzzdystzwbdgdxfs",
		"question":"\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u4E2D\u521B\u529E\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u4EE3\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u6240\u4F53\u5236\u5B8C\u5907\u7684\u9AD8\u7B49\u5B66\u5E9C\u662F",
		"id":18865
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u4EAC\u9677\u843D",
		"indexes":"tptgydsbdbzs",
		"question":"\u592A\u5E73\u5929\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5931\u8D25\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18866
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u731C\u79D1\u4E3E\u5F20\u699C",
		"indexes":"cpzwgfxlsyjnmzzdcps",
		"question":"\u5F69\u7968\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u53D1\u884C\u5386\u53F2\u60A0\u4E45\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5F69\u7968\u662F",
		"id":18867
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u4E16\u7EAA\u201418\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E0B\u534A\u671F",
		"indexes":"zbzygcsgysqzozcxdsjsc",
		"question":"\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u5DE5\u573A\u624B\u5DE5\u4E1A\u65F6\u671F\u5728\u6B27\u6D32\u6301\u7EED\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F\u4ECE",
		"id":18868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u514B\u601D\u4E3B\u4E49",
		"indexes":"wsydhxsczls",
		"question":"\u4E94\u56DB\u8FD0\u52A8\u540E\u65B0\u601D\u6F6E\u4E3B\u6D41\u662F",
		"id":18869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9886\u5BFC\u5DE5\u4EBA\u8FD0\u52A8",
		"indexes":"zgydqddclhdzxrws",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u5171\u201C\u4E00\u5927\u201D\u786E\u5B9A\u515A\u6210\u7ACB\u540E\u7684\u4E2D\u5FC3\u4EFB\u52A1\u662F",
		"id":18870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54E5\u4F26\u5E03",
		"indexes":"xlrwzkpltwmzdxhlds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4EBA\u7269\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5F00\u8F9F\u4E86\u901A\u5F80\u7F8E\u6D32\u7684\u65B0\u822A\u8DEF\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u4E0B\u7EA7\u6B66\u58EB",
		"indexes":"rbwzdmdzylls",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u6B66\u88C5\u5012\u5E55\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u529B\u91CF\u662F",
		"id":18872
	},
	{
		"answer":"1964",
		"indexes":"zgdykyzdsznynyzcgd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9897\u539F\u5B50\u5F39\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7814\u5236\u6210\u529F\u7684",
		"id":18873
	},
	{
		"answer":"27\u5929",
		"indexes":"zwsjzddhdsdhdlhtzdldjdhdjbfcl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4F4D\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u77ED\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u4E1C\u6C49\u7684\u5218\u8D3A\uFF0C\u4ED6\u53EA\u5F53\u4E86\u591A\u4E45\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u5C31\u88AB\u5E9F\u9664\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":18874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"zzdxyjyyclsdxy",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u8840\u538B\u8BA1\u7528\u4E8E\u6D4B\u91CF\u8C01\u7684\u8840\u538B\uFF1F",
		"id":18875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u5FB7\u77DB\u76FE",
		"indexes":"dycsjdzqdgzygjjdzymds",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u524D\u5E1D\u56FD\u4E3B\u4E49\u56FD\u5BB6\u95F4\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u77DB\u76FE\u662F",
		"id":18876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B\u987F\u529B\u5B66\u4F53\u7CFB\u7684\u5EFA\u7ACB",
		"indexes":"jdkxxcdbzs",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u79D1\u5B66\u5F62\u6210\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"bcwrkzcjjdgzydgjs",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5BB9\u514B\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u5E1D\u56FD\u4E3B\u4E49\u201D\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE\u516C\u793E\u9769\u547D",
		"indexes":"wcjjtfzcjjtzjlwcjjzzddyccss",
		"question":"\u65E0\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u63A8\u7FFB\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u7EDF\u6CBB\uFF0C\u5EFA\u7ACB\u65E0\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u4E13\u653F\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5C1D\u8BD5\u662F",
		"id":18879
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u670810\u65E5",
		"indexes":"mndjsjsnyt",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u5E74\u7684\u6559\u5E08\u8282\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":18880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5217\u5B81\u4E3B\u4E49\u8BDE\u751F",
		"indexes":"egbeswzydcxbzz",
		"question":"\u4FC4\u56FD\u5E03\u5C14\u4EC0\u7EF4\u4E3B\u4E49\u7684\u51FA\u73B0\uFF0C\u6807\u5FD7\u7740",
		"id":18881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u56E2\u5927\u6218",
		"indexes":"krzzxcjdzhbjxdycdgmdrzzs",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u76F8\u6301\u9636\u6BB5\uFF0C\u5728\u534E\u5317\u8FDB\u884C\u7684\u4E00\u573A\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u5BF9\u65E5\u4F5C\u6218\u662F",
		"id":18882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u590F\u3001\u91D1\u3001\u5357\u5B8B",
		"indexes":"xlzqmwdxhsxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u653F\u6743\u706D\u4EA1\u7684\u5148\u540E\u987A\u5E8F\u662F",
		"id":18883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u5BA3\u8A00\u300B",
		"indexes":"gjgczyydddygzdgls",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5171\u4EA7\u4E3B\u4E49\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6218\u6597\u7EB2\u9886\u662F",
		"id":18884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u6742\u5267\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u6B4C\u8BCD\u79F0\u4E3A\u5143\u66F2",
		"indexes":"yxdyzjdxszcwds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5BF9\u5143\u6742\u5267\u7684\u53D9\u8FF0\u4E2D\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18885
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"rbqlzqtzzgjldegwmzgddqs",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u4FB5\u7565\u8005\u4F01\u56FE\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7B2C\u4E8C\u4E2A\u4F2A\u6EE1\u6D32\u56FD\u7684\u5730\u533A\u662F",
		"id":18886
	},
	{
		"answer":"1970\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgdykrzwxfscgssmsh",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9897\u4EBA\u9020\u536B\u661F\u53D1\u5C04\u6210\u529F\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":18887
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D48\u707E",
		"indexes":"gdzfslycszsmyd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u653F\u5E9C\u8BBE\u7ACB\u201C\u4E49\u4ED3\u201D\u662F\u505A\u4EC0\u4E48\u7528\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u695A\u56FD",
		"indexes":"qyscqsdngr",
		"question":"\u5C48\u539F\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u4EE3\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"id":18889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5229\u6BD4\u91CC\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"18901896nfzwydldgjs",
		"question":"1890-1896\u5E74\u975E\u6D32\u552F\u4E00\u72EC\u7ACB\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u4E03\u00B7\u4E03\u201D\u4E8B\u53D8",
		"indexes":"jkqgkrzzxmdbzs",
		"question":"\u63ED\u5F00\u5168\u56FD\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u5E8F\u5E55\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u4E1A\u9769\u547D\u5B8C\u6210",
		"indexes":"zygzbzyscfszzzsfjscfsdbzs",
		"question":"\u5728\u82F1\u56FD\uFF0C\u8D44\u672C\u4E3B\u4E49\u751F\u4EA7\u65B9\u5F0F\u6700\u7EC8\u6218\u80DC\u5C01\u5EFA\u751F\u4EA7\u65B9\u5F0F\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9A6C\u5173\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\u7684\u7B7E\u8BA2",
		"indexes":"dzlqgfzgdsjs",
		"question":"\u5BFC\u81F4\u5217\u5F3A\u74DC\u5206\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6\u662F",
		"id":18893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC\u4EBA\u3001\u5C71\u9876\u6D1E\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"ysrzwgjndfbcjsfgkqzhdfwzwjjds",
		"question":"\u539F\u59CB\u4EBA\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u5883\u5185\u7684\u5206\u5E03\u66FE\u7ECF\u5341\u5206\u5E7F\u9614\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6D3B\u52A8\u8303\u56F4\u6700\u4E3A\u63A5\u8FD1\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u5143\u57F9",
		"indexes":"xwhydzzjysxscqjrbbfzdbdxzs",
		"question":"\u65B0\u6587\u5316\u8FD0\u52A8\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5728\u6559\u80B2\u601D\u60F3\u4E0A\u91C7\u53D6\u201C\u517C\u5BB9\u5E76\u5305\u201D\u65B9\u9488\u7684\u5317\u5927\u6821\u957F\u662F",
		"id":18895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u201C\u4E00\u5927\u201D\u53EC\u5F00",
		"indexes":"gglddychzsxdbzs",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5171\u4E24\u515A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5408\u4F5C\u5B9E\u73B0\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":18896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5BBE\u8679",
		"indexes":"xlzmhjzysshhyjhlhswmds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4EE5\u5C71\u6C34\u753B\u548C\u7814\u7A76\u753B\u8BBA\u753B\u53F2\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA4\u5B50",
		"indexes":"sjszzdzbcxzwgscqmcs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u7EB8\u5E01\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u5B8B\u671D\uFF0C\u5176\u540D\u79F0\u662F",
		"id":18898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u516B\u4E03\u201D\u4F1A\u8BAE",
		"indexes":"zggcdjzcdxyqtjzycwdhys",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u7EA0\u6B63\u9648\u72EC\u79C0\u53F3\u503E\u6295\u964D\u4E3B\u4E49\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u4F1A\u8BAE\u662F",
		"id":18899
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"mczcddy",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u6700\u521D\u5B9A\u90FD\u4E8E:",
		"id":18900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"wggdhylldwmyzhydsqs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6D77\u8FD0\u3001\u9646\u8DEF\u5BF9\u5916\u8D38\u6613\u6700\u6D3B\u8DC3\u7684\u65F6\u671F\u662F",
		"id":18901
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u7B2C\u5B89\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zsxozmzcchtsdmztzjms",
		"question":"\u906D\u53D7\u897F\u6B27\u6B96\u6C11\u8005\u6467\u6B8B\u548C\u5C60\u6740\u7684\u7F8E\u6D32\u571F\u8457\u5C45\u6C11\u662F",
		"id":18902
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"xyznlzs",
		"question":"\u9879\u7FBD\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u81EA\u6740\uFF1F",
		"id":18903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u9002",
		"indexes":"ssz1926n7y22rwclygthbfgzpkebb",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u57281926\u5E747\u670822\u65E5\u4E3A\u5904\u7406\u82F1\u56FD\u9000\u8FD8\u90E8\u5206\u5E9A\u5B50\u8D54\u6B3E\u800C\u5954\u6CE2\uFF1F",
		"id":18904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u955C\u5F00",
		"indexes":"dygdpsjjldzgrs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6253\u7834\u4E16\u754C\u7EAA\u5F55\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":18905
	},
	{
		"answer":"1924",
		"indexes":"lnssynyn",
		"question":"\u5217\u5B81\u901D\u4E16\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18906
	},
	{
		"answer":"1958\u5E747\u6708",
		"indexes":"ylkghgclynyn",
		"question":"\u4F0A\u62C9\u514B\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u89C9\u6C11",
		"indexes":"yxbsywxbfljzds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u201C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18908
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"hjzzkyldsgs",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u519B\u957F\u5F81\u8DE8\u8D8A\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":18909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D",
		"indexes":"htjsnctz",
		"question":"\u7687\u592A\u6781\u662F\u54EA\u671D\u592A\u7956",
		"id":18910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA3\u7EDF",
		"indexes":"wgmdhddnhs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u672B\u4EE3\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\u662F",
		"id":18911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E7E\u9686",
		"indexes":"yjbjsstxd",
		"question":"\u71D5\u4EAC\u516B\u666F\u662F\u8C01\u9898\u5199\u7684",
		"id":18912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"sjzzdxygqcxz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6821\u56ED\u6B4C\u66F2\u51FA\u73B0\u5728",
		"id":18913
	},
	{
		"answer":"1879",
		"indexes":"dgxlxjftynynjllsjsdygxlsys",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u5FC3\u7406\u5B66\u5BB6\u51AF\u7279\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5EFA\u7ACB\u4E86\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5FC3\u7406\u5B9E\u9A8C\u5BA4\uFF1F",
		"id":18914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D",
		"indexes":"wsmszngcd",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E4C\u7EB1\u5E3D\u201D\u59CB\u81EA\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18915
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5AE1\u957F\u7EE7\u627F\u5236",
		"indexes":"zfdjzdhxnrs",
		"question":"\u5B97\u6CD5\u7B49\u7EA7\u5236\u7684\u6838\u5FC3\u5185\u5BB9\u662F",
		"id":18916
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B50\u4EA7",
		"indexes":"scjxfzzdsgbcwfdrs",
		"question":"\u9996\u6B21\u5C06\u5211\u6CD5\u94F8\u5728\u9F0E\u4E0A\uFF0C\u516C\u5E03\u6210\u6587\u6CD5\u7684\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":18917
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CA7",
		"indexes":"dydfqss",
		"question":"\u5927\u79B9\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18918
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65BD\u74E6\u8328\u79D1\u592B",
		"indexes":"hwzzzdgbddzgslss",
		"question":"\u6D77\u6E7E\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u591A\u56FD\u90E8\u961F\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u53F8\u4EE4\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18919
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u7267",
		"indexes":"yxnwbsytsbdj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u971E\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"sszggdzmdlxj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u65C5\u884C\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":18921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E03\u9C81\u56FE",
		"indexes":"ksddbscsd",
		"question":"\u607A\u6492\u5927\u5E1D\u88AB\u8C01\u523A\u6B7B\u7684",
		"id":18922
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u6210\u90FD",
		"indexes":"zwjysmxrsbhznlmj",
		"question":"\u5353\u6587\u541B\u4E0E\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982\u79C1\u5954\u540E\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u5356\u9152",
		"id":18923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E54\u6258",
		"indexes":"xmnywbsydlwyfxsqdsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u610F\u5927\u5229\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u201C\u4E09\u6770\u201D\uFF1A",
		"id":18924
	},
	{
		"answer":"1992.5.17",
		"indexes":"xmnhjcqysjs",
		"question":"\u65B0\u6155\u5C3C\u9ED1\u673A\u573A\u542F\u7528\u65F6\u95F4\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u8FBE",
		"indexes":"yxsbpllb",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u80CC\u53DB\u4E86\u5218\u5907\uFF1F",
		"id":18926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"ccjbwyqdzsblzhlhmswmz",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u7F34\u699C\u6587\u4EE5\u64D2\u8463\u5353\uFF0C\u5341\u516B\u8DEF\u8BF8\u4FAF\u6765\u4F1A\u76DF\uFF0C\u8C01\u4E3A\u76DF\u4E3B\uFF1F",
		"id":18927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u627F\u5F66",
		"indexes":"zgldbztbspl",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u201C\u516B\u9635\u56FE\u201D\u88AB\u8C01\u7834\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":18928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"sbcwxbw",
		"question":"\u8C01\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5C0F\u9738\u738B\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":18929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F",
		"indexes":"wgdnlshksy",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u5974\u96B6\u793E\u4F1A\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":18930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u4E4C\u62C9\u572D\u56DE\u5408\u201D\u8C08\u5224",
		"indexes":"sjmyzzWTOsznjhyszscld",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u8D38\u6613\u7EC4\u7EC7(WTO)\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u754C\u4F1A\u8BAE\u4E0A\u6B63\u5F0F\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u521A\u7ECF",
		"indexes":"tdyzdsjsxczzbyqqrqddbysps",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5370\u5236\u7684\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u73B0\u5B58\u6700\u65E9\u6807\u6709\u786E\u5207\u65E5\u671F\u7684\u96D5\u7248\u5370\u5237\u54C1\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":18932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u65BD",
		"indexes":"zggdsdmrzcysylxrnyw",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u56DB\u5927\u7F8E\u4EBA\u4E2D\u201C\u6C89\u9C7C\u201D\u662F\u7528\u6765\u5F62\u5BB9\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":18933
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E0C\u7F57\u591A\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"lszfzds",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E4B\u7236\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u817E\u4E0E\u9A6C\u8D85",
		"indexes":"sgsqhdrjbwyzyfxlnydbsyzyfgx",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u5F88\u591A\u4EBA\u7ED3\u62DC\u4E3A\u4E49\u5B50\u3001\u4E49\u7236\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9\u4E0D\u662F\u4E49\u5B50\u3001\u4E49\u7236\u5173\u7CFB\uFF1F",
		"id":18935
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E8C\u5C81",
		"indexes":"glddnjcwxg",
		"question":"\u7518\u7F57\u591A\u5927\u5E74\u7EAA\u6210\u4E3A\u76F8\u56FD",
		"id":18936
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjdygsgyeznygds",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BD5\u7BA1\u5A74\u513F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u56FD\u8BDE\u751F",
		"id":18937
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u7B49\u5B66\u5E9C",
		"indexes":"gddgzjs",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u56FD\u5B50\u76D1\u662F",
		"id":18938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83DC\u5E02\u53E3",
		"indexes":"9y28rtstdlrbshybj",
		"question":"9\u670828\u65E5\uFF0C\u8C2D\u55E3\u540C\u7B49\u516D\u4EBA\u88AB\u6740\u5BB3\u4E8E\u5317\u4EAC",
		"id":18939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468",
		"indexes":"wztdjhgghw",
		"question":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u767B\u57FA\u540E\uFF0C\u6539\u56FD\u53F7\u4E3A",
		"id":18940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5149",
		"indexes":"qxzzwsdnhw",
		"question":"\u6E05\u5BA3\u5B97\u5728\u4F4D\u65F6\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\u4E3A",
		"id":18941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u632A\u5A01",
		"indexes":"gjawhhqsnggjy1920nzsd",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u4F1A\u65D7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E8E1920\u5E74\u8D60\u9001\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5468",
		"indexes":"bjzzjcssmcd",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u6700\u65E9\u5EFA\u6210\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u50E7\u4E00\u884C",
		"indexes":"sjsdycsczwxzddwggdkxjs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5B9E\u6D4B\u5B50\u5348\u7EBF\u957F\u5EA6\u7684\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":18944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"jksnysqdqj",
		"question":"\u5D47\u5EB7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u7434\u5BB6",
		"id":18945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7435\u7436",
		"indexes":"tddldsydzylqs",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u7684\u4E50\u961F\uFF0C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u4E50\u5668\u662F",
		"id":18946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"xhyxzs",
		"question":"\u8427\u4F55\u6708\u4E0B\u8FFD\u8C01",
		"id":18947
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"gyzhrdfzls",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5728\u534E\u5BB9\u9053\u653E\u8D70\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":18948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8E\u7981\u3001\u5E9E\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"gysyqjqhdjlss",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u6C34\u6DF9\u4E03\u519B\u64D2\u83B7\u7684\u5C06\u9886\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u6770",
		"indexes":"zfyzbphslnwcjdj",
		"question":"\u5F20\u98DE\u4E8E\u957F\u5742\u5761\u543C\u6B7B\u4E86\u54EA\u4F4D\u66F9\u519B\u5927\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":18950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6062",
		"indexes":"ssfmctjlb",
		"question":"\u8C01\u8BF4\u670D\u9A6C\u8D85\u6295\u964D\u5218\u5907\uFF1F",
		"id":18951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u5B81",
		"indexes":"jyybgbjdccdydrss",
		"question":"\u4EC5\u7528\u4E00\u767E\u4E2A\u5175\u52AB\u6389\u66F9\u64CD\u5927\u8425\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":18952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u65AD\u5934\u53F0",
		"indexes":"mtlqxsxqfgzycyhzfsxx",
		"question":"\u5BC6\u7279\u6717\u53D6\u6D88\u6B7B\u5211\u524D\uFF0C\u6CD5\u56FD\u4E3B\u8981\u91C7\u7528\u4F55\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u884C\u5211",
		"id":18953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"crbdbmjszbspl",
		"question":"\u66F9\u4EC1\u5E03\u7684\u201C\u516B\u95E8\u91D1\u9501\u9635\u201D\u88AB\u8C01\u7834\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":18954
	},
	{
		"answer":"1936",
		"indexes":"sjsdycygbgszsbsdsjmsnn",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u7531\u5E7F\u64AD\u516C\u53F8\u6B63\u5F0F\u64AD\u9001\u7535\u89C6\u8282\u76EE\u662F\u54EA\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"ybscywgngcd",
		"question":"\u5143\u5B9D\u59CB\u521B\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":18956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8857",
		"indexes":"hdccsgdw",
		"question":"\u6C49\u4EE3\u79F0\u57CE\u5E02\u5E72\u9053\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18957
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzgllcqsqzsjtzmsszdjccqsdsh",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u516D\u51FA\u7941\u5C71\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u5931\u8857\u4EAD\uFF0C\u65A9\u9A6C\u8C21\u662F\u5728\u7B2C\u51E0\u6B21\u51FA\u7941\u5C71\u7684\u65F6\u5019",
		"id":18958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5143\u748B",
		"indexes":"sscldxjezye",
		"question":"\u8C01\u9996\u521B\u4E86\u5927\u5199\u91D1\u989D\u5B57'\u58F9,\u8D30....'",
		"id":18959
	},
	{
		"answer":"1827\u5E74",
		"indexes":"rlddyzzpssmshdsd",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u5F20\u7167\u7247\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8BDE\u751F\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":18960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99\u3001\u51E4\u3001\u9F9F\u3001\u9E92\u9E9F",
		"indexes":"zggdxzjxdsl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8C61\u5F81\u5409\u7965\u7684\u56DB\u7075\uFF1A",
		"id":18961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"wgdhxdgchyjyzzzwzdjldssnygcd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5BF9\u5F57\u661F\u7684\u89C2\u6D4B\u548C\u7814\u7A76\u6709\u6700\u65E9\u6700\u5B8C\u6574\u7684\u8BB0\u5F55\u3002\u5F53\u65F6\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3",
		"id":18962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE8\u9E7F\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"xsnczyfsdsjzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u8FF0\u54EA\u573A\u6218\u5F79\u53D1\u751F\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u65E9",
		"id":18963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u65AF",
		"indexes":"byzewds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u8170\u65A9\u800C\u4EA1\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E94\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E5D\u5341\u5E74\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"glbfxxdlsz",
		"question":"\u54E5\u4F26\u5E03\u53D1\u73B0\u65B0\u5927\u9646\u662F\u5728",
		"id":18965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u9016",
		"indexes":"wjqwdss",
		"question":"\u95FB\u9E21\u8D77\u821E\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":18966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u8C0B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zgjnqjszndzzdzlrsnzr",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5883\u5185\u8FC4\u4ECA\u6240\u77E5\u5E74\u4EE3\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u76F4\u7ACB\u4EBA\u662F\u90A3\u79CD\u4EBA?",
		"id":18967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u6D25\u767D\u6CB3\u53E3",
		"indexes":"zdycypzzzyjdddzbds",
		"question":"\u5728\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D,\u82F1\u519B\u5230\u8FBE\u7684\u6700\u5317\u7AEF\u662F:",
		"id":18968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F46\u4E01",
		"indexes":"zsjzhywsrxsdzcywsrzds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u4E16\u7EAA\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u65B0\u65F6\u4EE3\u6700\u521D\u4E00\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468",
		"indexes":"gy690wztcdgghw",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143690\uFF0C\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u79F0\u5E1D\uFF0C\u6539\u56FD\u53F7\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E09\u6B21\u4E2D\u4E1C\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"yslzlylslstg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u8272\u5217\u5360\u9886\u8036\u8DEF\u6492\u51B7\u662F\u901A\u8FC7",
		"id":18971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u7EEA",
		"indexes":"wxbffszqcnghdsq",
		"question":"\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6E05\u671D\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1A",
		"id":18972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73ED\u8D85",
		"indexes":"tbcrds",
		"question":"\u6295\u7B14\u4ECE\u620E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":18973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5B\u513F\u53EA\u65A4",
		"indexes":"qwcjshxsm",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u6210\u5409\u601D\u6C57\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u7389\u73AF",
		"indexes":"tzsscjsddh",
		"question":"\u592A\u771F\u662F\u8C01\u51FA\u5BB6\u65F6\u7684\u9053\u53F7",
		"id":18975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D6B\u9C81\u6653\u592B",
		"indexes":"gbddwjsszcd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u5DF4\u5BFC\u5F39\u5371\u673A\u662F\u8C01\u9020\u6210\u7684",
		"id":18976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F14\u594F\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"bdfzelqbxwcw",
		"question":"\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC\u5728\u8033\u804B\u524D\u672C\u5E0C\u671B\u6210\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":18977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E",
		"indexes":"zycycjzzyxgscsmcdks",
		"question":"\u6B63\u6708\u521D\u4E00\u5403\u997A\u5B50\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E60\u60EF\u662F\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u671D\u4EE3\u5F00\u59CB",
		"id":18978
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u601D\u5B97",
		"indexes":"mczhyghdczhddhssm",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5D07\u796F\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u53F7\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4E2D\u5B97",
		"indexes":"wztsxmnghddmq",
		"question":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u6BCD\u4EB2\uFF1F",
		"id":18980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687",
		"indexes":"hjjfyzhjxlsdsnghd",
		"question":"\u201C\u6325\u5251\u51B3\u6D6E\u4E91\uFF0C\u8BF8\u4FAF\u5C3D\u897F\u6765\u201D\u8BF4\u7684\u662F\u90A3\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":18981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u6E05",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbsfsz20sj50nd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u572820\u4E16\u7EAA50\u5E74\u4EE3",
		"id":18982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"zzbpdqpmdccjzwdsgmjs",
		"question":"\u5728\u957F\u5742\u5761\uFF0C\u5355\u67AA\u5339\u9A6C\u72EC\u95EF\u66F9\u519B\u91CD\u56F4\u7684\u4E09\u56FD\u540D\u5C06\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"rmrbcky",
		"question":"\u300A\u4EBA\u6C11\u65E5\u62A5\u300B\u521B\u520A\u4E8E",
		"id":18984
	},
	{
		"answer":"1969",
		"indexes":"rldycdysznn",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u767B\u6708\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9676\u6D3B\u5B57",
		"indexes":"jzsydhzs",
		"question":"\u8F83\u65E9\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u6D3B\u5B57\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519B\u4E8B\u76EE\u7684",
		"indexes":"zcdfzsylzsmd",
		"question":"\u6700\u521D\u7684\u98CE\u7B5D\u662F\u7528\u6765\u505A\u4EC0\u4E48\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E",
		"indexes":"mdtssmshdxj",
		"question":"\u300A\u7261\u4E39\u4EAD\u300B\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u7684\u620F\u5267\uFF1F",
		"id":18988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u9E64",
		"indexes":"ypwgdyfsxzyzsmn",
		"question":"\u4E00\u54C1\u6587\u5B98\u7684\u8863\u670D\u4E0A\u7EE3\u7740\u4E00\u53EA\u4EC0\u4E48\u9E1F?",
		"id":18989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u5C39",
		"indexes":"zsjsscytyzbds",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u9996\u521B\u7528\u6C64\u836F\u6CBB\u75C5\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18990
	},
	{
		"answer":"1999\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xzgclhwgscfxjncsznn",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u6210\u7ACB\u540E\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u9996\u6B21\u53D1\u884C\u7EAA\u5FF5\u949E\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":18991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C99\u6F20\u98CE\u66B4",
		"indexes":"bswzzzmgdjsdhssm",
		"question":"\u6CE2\u65AF\u6E7E\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u519B\u4E8B\u4EE3\u53F7\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":18992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u8FB9",
		"indexes":"mqsqcjkysxsytgdbswwbtybsymltd",
		"question":"\u660E\u6E05\u65F6\u671F\u79F0\u954C\u523B\u7EA6\u675F\u5B66\u751F\u5458\u6761\u89C4\u7684\u7891\u77F3\u4E3A\u5367\u7891\uFF0C\u5B83\u4E00\u822C\u6811\u4E8E\u660E\u4F26\u5802\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":18993
	},
	{
		"answer":"19\u4E16\u7EAA50\u5E74\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"mqlzzcxcsmsh",
		"question":"\u7164\u6C14\u7089\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u51FA\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":18994
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E0C\u6D1B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"yxnzrbsygdremmz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u65E5\u8033\u66FC\u6C11\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":18995
	},
	{
		"answer":"37\u5E74",
		"indexes":"scjlldsn",
		"question":"\u968B\u671D\u7ECF\u5386\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5E74:",
		"id":18996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7235",
		"indexes":"gdrmyldjbdqtqj",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u4EBA\u4EEC\u7528\u6765\u5F53\u9152\u676F\u7684\u9752\u94DC\u5668\u53EB\uFF1A",
		"id":18997
	},
	{
		"answer":"1917\u5E74",
		"indexes":"mgqrztkndsz",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u524D\u4EFB\u603B\u7EDF\u80AF\u5C3C\u8FEA\u751F\u5728",
		"id":18998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u62EC",
		"indexes":"zgszstbzzbbdzgjls",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\uFF0C\u201C\u7EB8\u4E0A\u8C08\u5175\u201D\u62DB\u81F4\u5175\u8D25\u7684\u8D75\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":18999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"cbzzzjztjyjjcjdwgjls",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5047\u88C5\u6295\u964D\u4EE5\u63A5\u8FD1\u66F9\u519B\u7684\u5434\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AF\u5B50\u624D",
		"indexes":"zfzzzzhqdzngdjdzgjls",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u6CD5\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6307\u6325\u53D6\u5F97\u9547\u5357\u5173\u5927\u6377\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u5321\u80E4",
		"indexes":"cqbbsysfdd",
		"question":"\u201C\u9648\u6865\u5175\u53D8\u201D\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u53D1\u52A8\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19002
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"qjgqzdsngqlz",
		"question":"\u621A\u7EE7\u5149\u9A71\u9010\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u4FB5\u7565\u8005\uFF1A",
		"id":19003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u6069\u6765",
		"indexes":"fxahpjjsbdzgldrs",
		"question":"\u8D74\u897F\u5B89\u548C\u5E73\u89E3\u51B3\u4E8B\u53D8\u7684\u4E2D\u5171\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D",
		"indexes":"zwggdcyycrkpctszngcdjxd",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u66FE\u6709\u4E00\u6B21\u4EBA\u53E3\u666E\u67E5\uFF0C\u5B83\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u8FDB\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19005
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"hsdsmjnyc",
		"question":"\u4F1A\u8BD5\uFF0C\u6BBF\u8BD5\u6BCF\u51E0\u5E74\u4E00\u6B21",
		"id":19006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143",
		"indexes":"wgzyzzzsmshdtwjxgx",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u4E2D\u592E\u6700\u65E9\u5728\u4EC0\u9EBD\u65F6\u5019\u5BF9\u53F0\u6E7E\u8FDB\u884C\u7BA1\u8F96",
		"id":19007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F9F\u9AA8",
		"indexes":"jgwsxznsmd",
		"question":"\u7532\u9AA8\u6587\u662F\u5199\u5728\u54EA\u4E0A\u9762\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19008
	},
	{
		"answer":"1936.10.19",
		"indexes":"lxssy",
		"question":"\u9C81\u8FC5\u901D\u4E16\u4E8E?",
		"id":19009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u53E0\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"sycmjydzndzd",
		"question":"\u4E09\u53F6\u866B\u706D\u7EDD\u4E8E\u5730\u8D28\u5E74\u4EE3\u4E2D\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5C11\u5947",
		"indexes":"xlnwlgmjbcwkcdjcwzgdsszddya",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8001\u9769\u547D\u5BB6\u88AB\u9519\u8BEF\u5F00\u9664\u515A\u7C4D\uFF0C\u6210\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5171\u515A\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u51A4\u6848\uFF1F",
		"id":19011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5728\u5404\u7701\u7701\u57CE",
		"indexes":"xldqmldxsksddjszqds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5BF9\u6E05\u660E\u4E24\u4EE3\u201C\u4E61\u8BD5\u201D\u8003\u8BD5\u5730\u70B9\u89E3\u91CA\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u671D",
		"indexes":"wgdkjzdsyngcd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u79D1\u4E3E\u5236\u5EA6\u59CB\u4E8E\u90A3\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":19013
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u82F1\u56FD\u4EBA\u548C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C3C\u6CCA\u5C14\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"1953nrldycdsxmlysmzmlmfqwdsddds",
		"question":"1953\u5E74\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u767B\u4E0A\u559C\u9A6C\u62C9\u96C5\u5C71\u8109\u73E0\u7A46\u62C9\u9A6C\u5CF0\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u5F53\u65F6\u767B\u9876\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19014
	},
	{
		"answer":"1974",
		"indexes":"qshbmyynnbfx",
		"question":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u5175\u9A6C\u4FD1\u4E8E\u54EA\u5E74\u88AB\u53D1\u73B0",
		"id":19015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u5317\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgdngzzshscxd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C3C\u59D1\u6700\u65E9\u662F\u4F55\u65F6\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19016
	},
	{
		"answer":"129\u5E08",
		"indexes":"kzsqbljxx3gshygzsdlbcz",
		"question":"\u6297\u6218\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u201C\u516B\u8DEF\u519B\u201D\u4E0B\u8F963\u4E2A\u5E08\u548C\u4E00\u4E2A\u76F4\u5C5E\u961F\uFF0C\u5218\u4F2F\u627F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19017
	},
	{
		"answer":"1986",
		"indexes":"3y23rztkgzsjzzdkjzhphzhtsznnfsskd",
		"question":"3\u670823\u65E5\uFF0C\u5728\u592A\u7A7A\u5DE5\u4F5C\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u957F\u7684\u7A7A\u95F4\u7AD9\u201C\u548C\u5E73\u53F7\u201D\u5760\u6BC1\uFF0C\u5B83\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u5E74\u53D1\u5C04\u5347\u7A7A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"jyswgnyghdsydnh",
		"question":"'\u5EFA\u5143\u201D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":19019
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"bjc2002n11y_____rkszxybypxdzgj",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u4ECE2002\u5E7411\u6708_____\u65E5\u5F00\u59CB\u6267\u884C\u533B\u4FDD\u836F\u54C1\u9650\u5B9A\u6700\u9AD8\u4EF7",
		"id":19020
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"____sqslynxzssynszccwsm",
		"question":"____\u65F6\u671F\u8BBE\u7ACB\u4E91\u5357\u884C\u4E2D\u4E66\u7701\uFF0C\u4E91\u5357\u7701\u81EA\u6B64\u6210\u4E3A\u7701\u540D",
		"id":19021
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u793E\u4F1A\u6C11\u4E3B\u5DE5\u515A",
		"indexes":"sjsdygwcjjzds",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u65E0\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u653F\u515A\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19022
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"grcdyyssm",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u79F0\u7684\u9C7C\u96C1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":19023
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"cqfcjgbf",
		"question":"\u300A\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u5206\u6210\u51E0\u4E2A\u90E8\u5206\uFF1F",
		"id":19024
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982",
		"indexes":"bcwxhlsmdclsmqhys",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u897F\u6C49\u4E24\u53F8\u9A6C\u7684\u9664\u4E86\u53F8\u9A6C\u8FC1\u8FD8\u6709\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19025
	},
	{
		"answer":"6000\u5E74\u524D",
		"indexes":"mffyy",
		"question":"\u6728\u7B4F\u53D1\u6E90\u4E8E",
		"id":19026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B",
		"indexes":"ccsysmsh",
		"question":"\u8BCD\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"ssws",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u6B66\u5723\uFF1F",
		"id":19028
	},
	{
		"answer":"19\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zcqzbzjwgczwctdsn",
		"question":"\u5728\u6625\u79CB\u4E89\u9738\u4E2D\uFF0C\u664B\u6587\u516C\u66FE\u5728\u5916\u51FA\u9003\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19029
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"mczhygxljcxy",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u90D1\u548C\u4E00\u5171\u4E0B\u4E86\u51E0\u6B21\u897F\u6D0B",
		"id":19030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62D6\u96F7",
		"indexes":"hblssdez",
		"question":"\u5FFD\u5FC5\u70C8\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u513F\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":19031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E99\u53F7",
		"indexes":"ttzdtzzdstd",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u7684\u201C\u592A\u5B97\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4ED6\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"llysgjqlgnnyddzygz",
		"question":"\u5386\u6765\u7528\u201C\u4E09\u516C\u4E5D\u537F\u201D\u6765\u5F52\u7EB3\u54EA\u4E00\u4EE3\u7684\u4E2D\u592E\u5B98\u5236\uFF1F",
		"id":19033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"sjsdyggjbbdydcxz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u9881\u5E03\u7684\u836F\u5178\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F18\u80DC\u676F",
		"indexes":"sjszgldzqsjb",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u8DB3\u7403\u8D5B\u5956\u676F",
		"id":19035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5965\u53E4\u65AF\u4E01",
		"indexes":"yxnwbslmlssymddycstzzzdcy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u7F57\u9A6C\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6709\u540D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u201C\u4E09\u5934\u6267\u653F\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u6210\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":19036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u6807",
		"indexes":"zywdfqs",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60E0\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"zywdmhs",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u7684\u5E99\u53F7\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E5D\u5C81",
		"indexes":"zywsfs",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u4E27\u7236\u65F6",
		"id":19039
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D",
		"indexes":"bgqssyhs",
		"question":"\u516B\u80A1\u53D6\u58EB\u59CB\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":19040
	},
	{
		"answer":"5\u67B6",
		"indexes":"wpfxyzzsyjljjfjdkjzs",
		"question":"\u201C\u738B\u724C\u98DE\u884C\u5458\u201D\u6700\u65E9\u6388\u4E88\u51FB\u843D\u51E0\u67B6\u98DE\u673A\u7684\u7A7A\u519B\u6218\u58EB\uFF1F",
		"id":19041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u708E",
		"indexes":"wgxjddydhdmj",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u897F\u664B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EE3\u7687\u5E1D\u540D\u53EB\uFF1A",
		"id":19042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6587\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"hczxxzfcrxdhds",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u6700\u5148\u4E0B\u8BCF\u5E9F\u9664\u8089\u5211\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19043
	},
	{
		"answer":"1918\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zmlsxjhrycsynyn",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u5386\u53F2\u5B66\u5BB6\u9EC4\u4EC1\u5B87\u51FA\u751F\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74",
		"id":19044
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E7E\u9686",
		"indexes":"pcmhbthzgzxds",
		"question":"\u7834\u9664\u6EE1\u6C49\u4E0D\u901A\u5A5A\u8FD9\u4E2A\u7956\u8BAD\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19045
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634",
		"indexes":"wggdcszbsznwsm",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u79F0\u5C71\u4E4B\u5317\uFF0C\u6C34\u4E4B\u5357\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19046
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"tptgddnjsdsjnjgmw",
		"question":"\u592A\u5E73\u5929\u56FD\u5B9A\u90FD\u5357\u4EAC\u65F6\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u5C06\u5357\u4EAC\u6539\u540D\u4E3A",
		"id":19047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7981\u6212",
		"indexes":"gsjzylbs",
		"question":"\u53E4\u65F6\u6212\u6307\u7528\u6765\u8868\u793A\uFF1F",
		"id":19048
	},
	{
		"answer":"1974",
		"indexes":"zlqxslscsznyn",
		"question":"\u667A\u5229\u7403\u661F\u8428\u62C9\u65AF\u51FA\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u884D\u5386",
		"indexes":"wgtdxzyxhstzdlsmlf",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5510\u4EE3\u5B66\u8005\u4E00\u884C\u548C\u5C1A\uFF0C\u4ED6\u5236\u8BA2\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48\u5386\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":19050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9020\u623F",
		"indexes":"zqrljtdjbynzsygxzmq",
		"question":"\u65E9\u671F\u4EBA\u7C7B\u5BB6\u5EAD\u7684\u8FDB\u6B65\uFF0C\u4E0E\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8B\u4E1A\u5173\u7CFB\u6700\u5BC6\u5207\uFF1F",
		"id":19051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD\u6587\u5B98\u5236",
		"indexes":"gjgwyzdqyy",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u516C\u52A1\u5458\u5236\u5EA6\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\uFF1F",
		"id":19052
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u6CE2\u7F5711\u53F7",
		"indexes":"amstlscngfccgdyd",
		"question":"\u963F\u59C6\u65AF\u7279\u6717\u662F\u4E58\u54EA\u4E2A\u98DE\u8239\u6210\u529F\u767B\u6708\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u9636\u5927\u5C0F\u7684\u533A\u522B",
		"indexes":"qcgydlmsqygdzysgbxttdzys",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5B98\u5458\u7684\u793C\u5E3D\u4E0A\u5D4C\u4E00\u4E2A\u9876\u73E0\uFF0C\u989C\u8272\u5404\u4E0D\u76F8\u540C\u5B83\u7684\u4F5C\u7528\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6700\u9AD8\u6CD5\u9662",
		"indexes":"mg1787nxfgdjsxfdqlz",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD1787\u5E74\u5BAA\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u89E3\u91CA\u5BAA\u6CD5\u7684\u6743\u529B\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5168\u56FD\u4EBA\u5927\u5E38\u59D4\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"wgxfdjdqsy",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5BAA\u6CD5\u7684\u76D1\u7763\u6743\u5C5E\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19056
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u4EBF",
		"indexes":"d21sjzyzgrkzlzddfzhjhmxjzyfzs",
		"question":"\u523021\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E2D\u53F6\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u53E3\u603B\u91CF\u5728\u8FBE\u5230\u5CF0\u503C\u540E\u5C06\u7F13\u6162\u4E0B\u964D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E00\u5CF0\u503C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19057
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D",
		"indexes":"yjtzrlyljssy",
		"question":"\u7528\u7126\u70AD\u4F5C\u71C3\u6599\u51B6\u70BC\u91D1\u5C5E\u59CB\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u699C\u773C",
		"indexes":"mqldkjksdzgjbdsddymjzydemj",
		"question":"\u660E\u6E05\u4E24\u4EE3\u79D1\u4E3E\u8003\u8BD5\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u7EA7\u522B\u201C\u6BBF\u8BD5\u201D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u540D\u53EB\u72B6\u5143,\u7B2C\u4E8C\u540D\u53EB\uFF1A",
		"id":19059
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B",
		"indexes":"mysngcddhj",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u8FDC\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u753B\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8",
		"indexes":"zywzyhgspbdhytsdsjdszs",
		"question":"\u6731\u5141\u6587\u4F5C\u4E8E\u9EC4\u679C\u6811\u7011\u5E03\u7684\u7EA2\u5D16\u5929\u4E66\u7B2C\u56DB\u53E5\u7B2C\u56DB\u5B57\u662F",
		"id":19061
	},
	{
		"answer":"25\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"xchdyjgez",
		"question":"\u76F8\u4F20\u9EC4\u5E1D\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u513F\u5B50",
		"id":19062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u671D",
		"indexes":"zmdzzqsznysqzjd",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u8D75\u5DDE\u6865\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u65F6\u671F\u9020\u5EFA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19063
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B",
		"indexes":"wxjytfwztdybqcltwsxdsrs",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u5F90\u656C\u4E1A\u8BA8\u4F10\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u7684\u4E49\u5175\u8D77\u8349\u4E86\u8BA8\u6B66\u6C0F\u6A84\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\u662F\u2026\u2026",
		"id":19064
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"zgrzzfxcsszgyqjsj",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6700\u65E9\u53D1\u73B0\u78C1\u77F3\u662F\u5728\u516C\u5143\u524D\u51E0\u4E16\u7EAA\uFF1F",
		"id":19065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D35\u65CF",
		"indexes":"zzgzqbxsdsmrdzc",
		"question":"\u5728\u6218\u56FD\u4E4B\u524D\u201C\u767E\u59D3\u201D\u662F\u5BF9\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EBA\u7684\u603B\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":19066
	},
	{
		"answer":"1997",
		"indexes":"xgxqhdsdznynzstc",
		"question":"\u9999\u6E2F\u897F\u533A\u6D77\u5E95\u96A7\u9053\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6B63\u5F0F\u901A\u8F66\uFF1F",
		"id":19067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u997C",
		"indexes":"hdfmzdsptczwsm",
		"question":"\u6C49\u4EE3\uFF0C\u51E1\u9762\u5236\u7684\u98DF\u54C1\u7EDF\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8058\u5A36\u5A5A",
		"indexes":"zggdztxdjhfssyxnyz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6700\u901A\u884C\u7684\u7ED3\u5A5A\u65B9\u5F0F\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":19069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5143\u524D2500\u5E74",
		"indexes":"ajdssrmxjyhs",
		"question":"\u57C3\u53CA\u7684\u72EE\u8EAB\u4EBA\u9762\u50CF\u5EFA\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":19070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7528\u6765\u8BB0\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"gddcscsssnzdxzhhbzcdyts",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5927\u81E3\u4E0A\u671D\u65F6\u624B\u4E0A\u62FF\u7740\u7684\u72ED\u957F\u7B0F(h\u01DC)\u677F\uFF0C\u6700\u521D\u7684\u7528\u9014\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19071
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u671D",
		"indexes":"zggdkjxcyngcd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u79D1\u4E3E\u5F62\u6210\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":19072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5468",
		"indexes":"wgngdsyzcszsmsh",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u725B\u8015\u7684\u4F7F\u7528\u6700\u521D\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19073
	},
	{
		"answer":"1991.12",
		"indexes":"qwslszsmshjtd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u82CF\u8054\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u89E3\u4F53\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u9075\u5BAA",
		"indexes":"zgssbcwsjzglbydbcdagsrs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53F2\u4E0A\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u8BD7\u754C\u4E4B\u54E5\u4F26\u5E03\u201D\u201C\u4E00\u4EE3\u9738\u624D\u201D\u7684\u7231\u56FD\u8BD7\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9EA6\u5965\u5730\u5229\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"plsz19sjlqsnddtyzzzxhhnjggjfszz",
		"question":"\u666E\u9C81\u58EB\u572819\u4E16\u7EAA\u516D\u4E03\u5341\u5E74\u4EE3\u7684\u7EDF\u4E00\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u5148\u540E\u548C\u54EA\u51E0\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53D1\u751F\u6218\u4E89\uFF1F",
		"id":19076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"tcddczasjtdnl",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\u957F\u5B89\u662F\u4ECA\u5929\u7684\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E03\u4E03\u4E8B\u53D8",
		"indexes":"fszbjlgqdlssbmj",
		"question":"\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u5362\u6C9F\u6865\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u53D8\u540D\u53EB\uFF1F",
		"id":19078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u4E0A\u4FDD\u9669",
		"indexes":"qyzzdbxs",
		"question":"\u8D77\u6E90\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4FDD\u9669\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9020\u623F",
		"indexes":"zqrljtdjbynzsygxzmq",
		"question":"\u65E9\u671F\u4EBA\u7C7B\u5BB6\u5EAD\u7684\u8FDB\u6B65\uFF0C\u4E0E\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8B\u4E1A\u5173\u7CFB\u6700\u5BC6\u5207\uFF1F",
		"id":19080
	},
	{
		"answer":"1986\u5E74",
		"indexes":"qenblhwrfsz",
		"question":"\u5207\u5C14\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5229\u6838\u6C61\u67D3\u53D1\u751F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5174\u5E86",
		"indexes":"xxddcz",
		"question":"\u897F\u590F\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\u5728",
		"id":19082
	},
	{
		"answer":"907\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wdsgsqksy",
		"question":"\u4E94\u4EE3\u5341\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":19083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F1A\u7A3D\u90E1",
		"indexes":"qftxwssljjtdjssy",
		"question":"\u79E6\u5206\u5929\u4E0B\u4E3A\u4E09\u5341\u516D\u90E1\uFF0C\u4ECA\u5929\u7684\u6C5F\u82CF\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":19084
	},
	{
		"answer":"3000\u4E07\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xsdjjydsn",
		"question":"\u65B0\u751F\u4EE3\u8DDD\u4ECA\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E35\u9E1F\u9F99",
		"indexes":"klsjddpgjssml",
		"question":"\u6050\u9F99\u4E16\u754C\u7684\u77ED\u8DD1\u51A0\u519B\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u9F99\uFF1F",
		"id":19086
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9707\u9F99",
		"indexes":"yzdzdklssm",
		"question":"\u5DF2\u77E5\u7684\u6700\u5927\u6050\u9F99\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7F8A\u57CE\u4F53\u80B2\u62A5\u300B",
		"indexes":"z1998ndljfbznjbzbtsft",
		"question":"\u57281998\u5E74\u7684\u201C\u9646\u4FCA\u98CE\u6CE2\u201D\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u5BB6\u62A5\u7EB8\u88AB\u63A8\u4E0A\u6CD5\u5EAD\uFF1F",
		"id":19088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zdyzbzcxzqsnggjdrzxzdzbzsdxw",
		"question":"\u5728\u7B2C\u4E00\u5F20\u62A5\u7EB8\u51FA\u73B0\u4E4B\u524D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4EBA\u6700\u5148\u5728\u5927\u5B57\u62A5\u7EB8\u4E0A\u8BFB\u65B0\u95FB\uFF1F",
		"id":19089
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u5175\u9A6C\u4FD1",
		"indexes":"bcwsjdbqgds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u516B\u5947\u89C2\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510",
		"indexes":"wggdhjwdzshzngcd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u753B\u5BB6\u5434\u9053\u5B50\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":19091
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u708E",
		"indexes":"xjdcjz",
		"question":"\u897F\u664B\u7684\u521B\u5EFA\u8005\uFF1A",
		"id":19092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74",
		"indexes":"rlysyldycdysznn",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u6709\u53F2\u4EE5\u6765\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u767B\u6708\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468",
		"indexes":"qwgmsy",
		"question":"\u537F\u4E3A\u5B98\u540D\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E:",
		"id":19094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5DF4\u6587",
		"indexes":"bswqrldzgwhycmqsjswyhhzdxxwzs",
		"question":"\u88AB\u89C6\u4E3A\u5168\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u73CD\u8D35\u6587\u5316\u9057\u4EA7\uFF0C\u76EE\u524D\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u552F\u4E00\u8FD8\u6D3B\u7740\u7684\u8C61\u5F62\u6587\u5B57\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19095
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u626C\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"wgzmnhjzylcsyyxngdf",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u5973\u753B\u5BB6\u5F20\u7389\u826F\u51FA\u751F\u4E8E\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9:",
		"id":19096
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81F4\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"zzrjwzzzdscjsnszjcxdjbxclwgjq",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u65E5\u7532\u5348\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\uFF0C\u9093\u4E16\u660C\u9A7E\u9A76\u54EA\u8258\u6218\u8230\u51B2\u5411\u654C\u8230\uFF0C\u4E0D\u5E78\u89E6\u96F7\uFF0C\u4E3A\u56FD\u6350\u8EAF\uFF1F",
		"id":19097
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C38\u9675",
		"indexes":"qcddyzlsnz",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u5EA7\u9675\u662F\u54EA\u5EA7",
		"id":19098
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u859B\u5CB3",
		"indexes":"krzzqjzhsczshzdzggmdjls",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u671F\u95F4\uFF0C\u6307\u6325\u4E09\u6B21\u957F\u6C99\u4F1A\u6218\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u5C06\u9886\u662F",
		"id":19099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u6C11\u5728\u906D\u53D7\u81EA\u7136\u707E\u5BB3",
		"indexes":"gjwgxfgdxlxxznyzqkbsgmhdwzbzqdtj",
		"question":"\u6839\u636E\u6211\u56FD\u5BAA\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u9009\u9879\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0D\u662F\u516C\u6C11\u83B7\u5F97\u7269\u8D28\u5E2E\u52A9\u6743\u7684\u6761\u4EF6?",
		"id":19100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64",
		"indexes":"gdwltxgldgwgdezxqbhgzykfxbzgjgpddjbzsdtaygybtnzdypwgdbzsxysmtam",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E3A\u4E86\u4F53\u73B0\u5B98\u540F\u7684\u5B98\u4F4D\u9AD8\u4F4E\u800C\u5728\u80F8\u524D\u3001\u80CC\u540E\u5404\u7F00\u4E00\u5757\u65B9\u5F62\u8865\u5B50\uFF0C\u6839\u636E\u5B98\u54C1\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF0C\u201C\u8865\u5B50\u201D\u4E0A\u7684\u56FE\u6848\u4E5F\u5404\u6709\u4E0D\u540C\uFF0C\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u4E00\u54C1\u6587\u5B98\u7684\u8865\u5B50\u4E0A\u7EE3\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u56FE\u6848\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":19101
	},
	{
		"answer":"1900\u5E745\u670826\u65E5",
		"indexes":"dhzjdsdswylfxdzycjds600dnjdj6wjzgwwtfxy",
		"question":"\u6566\u714C\u85CF\u7ECF\u6D1E\u662F\u9053\u58EB\u738B\u5706\u7B93\u53D1\u73B0\u7684\uFF0C\u85CF\u6709\u4ECE\u664B\u5230\u5B8B600\u591A\u5E74\u95F4\u7684\u8FD16\u4E07\u4EF6\u73CD\u8D35\u6587\u7269\u3002\u5B83\u53D1\u73B0\u4E8E",
		"id":19102
	},
	{
		"answer":"1906",
		"indexes":"sjsfnzzqdxjqdgjsflsy_________n",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u5987\u5973\u6700\u65E9\u53D6\u5F97\u9009\u4E3E\u6743\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u82AC\u5170\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E_________\u5E74\u3002",
		"id":19103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9003\u907F\u731B\u517D",
		"indexes":"zygtyswl",
		"question":"\u5728\u8FDC\u53E4\u8DF3\u8FDC\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\uFF1A",
		"id":19104
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"cltzsyhs",
		"question":"\u5782\u5E18\u542C\u653F\u59CB\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":19105
	},
	{
		"answer":"1999",
		"indexes":"zjdqjszjwlsnynsjhjrdztkh",
		"question":"\u201C\u62EF\u6551\u5730\u7403\u5C31\u662F\u62EF\u6551\u672A\u6765\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u4E16\u754C\u73AF\u5883\u65E5\u7684\u4E3B\u9898\u53E3\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":19106
	},
	{
		"answer":"1860\u5E74",
		"indexes":"yfljcynnhsymy",
		"question":"\u82F1\u6CD5\u8054\u519B\u66FE\u4E8E\u54EA\u5E74\u706B\u70E7\u5706\u660E\u56ED\uFF1F",
		"id":19107
	},
	{
		"answer":"1958",
		"indexes":"hypyfajslhypyssdwljmqwhypyfadsynyn",
		"question":"\u6C49\u8BED\u62FC\u97F3\u65B9\u6848\u7ED3\u675F\u4E86\u6C49\u8BED\u62FC\u97F3\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7D0A\u4E71\u5C40\u9762\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6C49\u8BED\u62FC\u97F3\u65B9\u6848\u8BDE\u751F\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u3002",
		"id":19108
	},
	{
		"answer":"1959",
		"indexes":"azbzzfxznyn",
		"question":"\u7231\u6ECB\u75C5\u6700\u65E9\u53D1\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19109
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u5DF4\u6BD4\u4F26",
		"indexes":"xxwzsgdnydqdwz",
		"question":"\u6954\u5F62\u6587\u5B57\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u54EA\u4E00\u5730\u533A\u7684\u6587\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":19110
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"gwlcdssqjsfszngcd",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u4E3A\u6D41\u4F20\u7684\u300A\u82CF\u4E09\u8D77\u89E3\u300B\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3?",
		"id":19111
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u516B",
		"indexes":"bdgsjysmsj",
		"question":"\u5F7C\u5F97\u5BAB\u59CB\u5EFA\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E16\u7EAA\uFF1A",
		"id":19112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u539F\u5408\u6218",
		"indexes":"smzhdcjkkzltxds",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E4B\u540E\uFF0C\u5FB7\u5DDD\u5BB6\u5EB7\u63A7\u5236\u4E86\u5929\u4E0B\u5927\u52BF\uFF1F",
		"id":19113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E9A\u5386\u5C71\u5927\u706F\u5854",
		"indexes":"sjqdqjjzsjzwds",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E03\u5927\u5947\u8FF9\u5EFA\u9020\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u665A\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19114
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E30\u81E3\u79C0\u5409",
		"indexes":"ssbystjhxzksdxzzfmdfmljsnwjc",
		"question":"\u77F3\u5C71\u672C\u613F\u5BFA\u6295\u964D\u540E\uFF0C\u4FE1\u957F\u5F00\u59CB\u591A\u7EBF\u4F5C\u6218\uFF0C\u5949\u547D\u5BF9\u4ED8\u6BDB\u5229\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u5BB6\u81E3\uFF1F",
		"id":19115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5948\u826F",
		"indexes":"rblssdpcjzdsxzd",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u5E73\u57CE\u4EAC\u6307\u7684\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u70DC",
		"indexes":"zczmzgyxjrdgddglj",
		"question":"\u5468\u671D\u4E13\u95E8\u638C\u7BA1\u5143\u5BB5\u8282\u71C3\u706F\u3001\u89C2\u706F\u7684\u5B98\u540F\u53EB\uFF1A",
		"id":19117
	},
	{
		"answer":"1832\u5E74",
		"indexes":"afecsy",
		"question":"\u827E\u83F2\u5C14\u51FA\u751F\u4E8E?",
		"id":19118
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5211\u5177\u540D",
		"indexes":"fxsdcwsrhyld",
		"question":"\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u7684\u79F0\u8C13\u662F\u5982\u4F55\u7531\u6765\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u9633",
		"indexes":"grswhdsnzttyxzndgd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u6240\u8C13\u9EC4\u9053\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u5929\u4F53\u8FD0\u884C\u5468\u5E74\u7684\u8F68\u9053\uFF1F",
		"id":19120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u918B",
		"indexes":"grsdzzdsjtd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u8BF4\u7684\u9162\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4ECA\u5929\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19121
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u6A90\u5E91\u6BBF\u9876",
		"indexes":"gdwdzdjzgds",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5C4B\u9876\u4E2D\u7B49\u7EA7\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":19122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u81EA\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"zkrzzzgmdxsdzgjls",
		"question":"\u5728\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u727A\u7272\u7684\u6700\u9AD8\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u9053\u9675",
		"indexes":"djsyscld",
		"question":"\u9053\u6559\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u521B\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19124
	},
	{
		"answer":"1918\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgdbyjfzyzzhsxdaxz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5317\u6D0B\u519B\u9600\u5728\u4E00\u6218\u4E2D\u4F55\u65F6\u5411\u5FB7\u5965\u5BA3\u6218\uFF1F",
		"id":19125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5316\u5986\u54C1",
		"indexes":"mlkgssyjjyhzspdgs",
		"question":"\u73AB\u7433\u51EF\u516C\u53F8\u662F\u4E00\u5BB6\u7ECF\u8425\u4F55\u79CD\u5546\u54C1\u7684\u516C\u53F8\uFF1F",
		"id":19126
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C88\u96C1\u51B0",
		"indexes":"xzgdyrwhbbzss",
		"question":"\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u6587\u5316\u90E8\u90E8\u957F\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u5B9D\u77F3",
		"indexes":"qcsqwwypgdcgdxqy",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u6587\u3001\u6B66\u4E00\u54C1\u5B98\u7684\u671D\u51A0\u9876\u9576\u5D4C\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":19128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u56FD",
		"indexes":"djygcdxjsqwsq",
		"question":"\u90FD\u6C5F\u5830\u5DE5\u7A0B\u7684\u4FEE\u5EFA\u65F6\u671F\u4E3A\uFF08\uFF09\u65F6\u671F\u3002",
		"id":19129
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E00\u66FC",
		"indexes":"yxjwmzyxnwsnx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u51E0\u4F4D\u6C11\u65CF\u82F1\u96C4\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u5973\u6027\uFF1F",
		"id":19130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E94\u6B21",
		"indexes":"zyhyppjfldjcfwjdcw",
		"question":"\u9075\u4E49\u4F1A\u8BAE\u6279\u8BC4\u63ED\u53D1\u4E86\u7B2C\u51E0\u6B21\u53CD\u56F4\u527F\u7684\u9519\u8BEF\uFF1F",
		"id":19131
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"gdyddzxzdfwjj",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5370\u5EA6\u7684\u201C\u79CD\u59D3\u5236\u5EA6\u201D\u5206\u4E3A\u51E0\u7EA7\uFF1F",
		"id":19132
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"2001nqgpxcldszmyy",
		"question":"2001\u5E74\u5168\u56FD\u8BC4\u9009\u51FA\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u79CD\u540D\u4F18\u70DF?",
		"id":19133
	},
	{
		"answer":"1861\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zmgbblbzfhnbblzzjjxdmgnzqsynyn",
		"question":"\u5728\u7F8E\u56FD\u5317\u90E8\u8054\u90A6\u653F\u5E9C\u548C\u5357\u90E8\u90A6\u8054\u5DDE\u4E4B\u95F4\u8FDB\u884C\u7684\u7F8E\u56FD\u5185\u6218\u8D77\u59CB\u4E8E\u90A3\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5854",
		"indexes":"zggdjzzsljdxszwdydyzjzlxs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5EFA\u7B51\u4E2D\u6570\u91CF\u6781\u5927\u3001\u5F62\u5F0F\u6700\u4E3A\u591A\u6837\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u5EFA\u7B51\u7C7B\u578B\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5F\u9E9F\u9601",
		"indexes":"krzzzdywwkjrkxsdzggjjls",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\uFF0C\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E3A\u6297\u51FB\u65E5\u5BC7\u727A\u7272\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u9AD8\u7EA7\u5C06\u9886\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19136
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510",
		"indexes":"gy618907nswggddngcd",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143618\u2014907\u5E74\uFF0C\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":19137
	},
	{
		"answer":"204",
		"indexes":"zzgzqswsxfxdwsrhsjjydswn",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF0C\u91CD\u5E86\u5E02\u5DEB\u5C71\u53BF\u53D1\u73B0\u7684\u5DEB\u5C71\u4EBA\u5316\u77F3\uFF0C\u8DDD\u4ECA\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E07\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19138
	},
	{
		"answer":"1982\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zsmsjzhrmghgmzbzrzzzwgmls",
		"question":"\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\uFF0C\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u6C11\u653F\u90E8\u8FFD\u8BA4\u5F20\u81EA\u5FE0\u4E3A\u9769\u547D\u70C8\u58EB\uFF1F",
		"id":19139
	},
	{
		"answer":"1206",
		"indexes":"znyntmzzwnhjmgenhyzkhltdhjmggdhwhcjsh",
		"question":"\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u94C1\u6728\u771F\u5728\u65A1\u96BE\u6CB3\uFF08\u4ECA\u8499\u53E4\u9102\u5AE9\u6CB3\uFF09\u6E90\u53EC\u5F00\u5FFD\u91CC\u53F0\u5927\u4F1A\uFF0C\u5373\u8499\u53E4\u56FD\u5927\u6C57\u4F4D\uFF0C\u53F7\u6210\u5409\u601D\u6C57\uFF1A",
		"id":19140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u585E\u5C14\u7EF4\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"csaxdghcfdndgsnyggjdqn",
		"question":"\u523A\u6740\u5965\u5308\u5E1D\u56FD\u7687\u50A8\u83F2\u8FEA\u7537\u5927\u516C\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u9752\u5E74:",
		"id":19141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F5C\u6C34\u8247",
		"indexes":"dgzezzzyyklqzsqwdjzezzqlzsm",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u5728\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E3B\u8981\u4F9D\u9760\u72FC\u7FA4\u6218\u672F\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u5FB7\u519B\u5728\u4E8C\u6218\u4E2D\u7FA4\u72FC\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"zgjdzzlszzcdzddgcs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5EFA\u90FD\u6700\u65E9\uFF0C\u5386\u65F6\u6700\u957F\uFF0C\u671D\u4EE3\u6700\u591A\u7684\u53E4\u57CE\u662F",
		"id":19143
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"lsslmjtzzgjcszjdz",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7F57\u9A6C\u6559\u5EF7\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8FC7\u51E0\u6B21\u5341\u5B57\u519B\u4E1C\u5F81",
		"id":19144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"nywhdpzqcsxy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u6D3E\u5F20\u9A9E\u51FA\u4F7F\u897F\u57DF",
		"id":19145
	},
	{
		"answer":"1915",
		"indexes":"yskdszhdgdhdsz",
		"question":"\u8881\u4E16\u51EF\u5F53\u4E0A\u201C\u4E2D\u534E\u5E1D\u56FD\u201D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u5728",
		"id":19146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E34\u65F6\u653F\u5E9C\u8FC1\u90FD\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"byjfzqjldbzs",
		"question":"\u5317\u6D0B\u519B\u9600\u653F\u6743\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":19147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E30\u5C9B\u6D77\u6218",
		"indexes":"jwzzbfdbzs",
		"question":"\u7532\u5348\u6218\u4E89\u7206\u53D1\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F",
		"id":19148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"gj1931nmzdqddtdgglxfxdsncgmddrs",
		"question":"\u6839\u69101931\u5E74\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u786E\u5B9A\u7684\u571F\u5730\u6539\u9769\u8DEF\u7EBF\u5206\u6790\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u519C\u6751\u9769\u547D\u7684\u654C\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":19149
	},
	{
		"answer":"1983\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gdjyzxkszdscnynkszqgtgsxd",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u7B49\u6559\u80B2\u81EA\u5B66\u8003\u8BD5\u5236\u5EA6\u662F\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5F00\u59CB\u5728\u5168\u56FD\u63A8\u5E7F\u65BD\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19150
	},
	{
		"answer":"1878\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgdymptypdlphsfxd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u666E\u901A\u90AE\u7968----\u5927\u9F99\u7968\u4F55\u65F6\u53D1\u884C\u7684?",
		"id":19151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u519B",
		"indexes":"wcqydzylls",
		"question":"\u6B66\u660C\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u529B\u91CF\u662F",
		"id":19152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5609\u5E86\u65F6",
		"indexes":"qcgsslksy",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u56FD\u52BF\u8870\u843D\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":19153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88F4\u79C0",
		"indexes":"zgzzdlsdtjsszbd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u5730\u56FE\u96C6\u662F\u8C01\u4E3B\u7F16\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6881\u542F\u8D85",
		"indexes":"gxsdsznywswxbflxzy",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5B66\u56DB\u5927\u5E08\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u9886\u8896\u4E4B\u4E00",
		"id":19155
	},
	{
		"answer":"1973",
		"indexes":"rllssdycxqdgmdybhdqwzzdqzxydbcccsldqrsnyn",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\uFF0C\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u6380\u8D77\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u7684\u4EE5\u4FDD\u62A4\u5730\u7403\u4E3A\u5B97\u65E8\u7684\u7FA4\u4F17\u6027\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF0C\u5E76\u4ECE\u6B64\u4EA7\u751F\u4E86\u5730\u7403\u65E5\uFF0C\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19156
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"fxgajjdmnwhnflttmnydnkgxjqaflcsnggjdr",
		"question":"\u53D1\u73B0\u53E4\u57C3\u53CA\u7EDD\u4EE3\u7F8E\u5973\u738B\u540E\u8BFA\u5F17\u96F7\u6258\u6258\u6728\u4E43\u4F0A\u7684\u5973\u8003\u53E4\u5B66\u5BB6\u4E54\u5B89-\u5F17\u96F7\u5F7B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19157
	},
	{
		"answer":"27",
		"indexes":"zglcssddnj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u51FA\u5C71\u65F6\u591A\u5927\u5E74\u7EAA\uFF1F",
		"id":19158
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"hsthssdjw",
		"question":"\u6C49\u5BFF\u4EAD\u5019\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u7235\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u79C0",
		"indexes":"gyqlzdqzsddygjlss",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5343\u91CC\u8D70\u5355\u9A91\u4E2D\u6740\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C06\u9886\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5357\u4EAC\u6761\u7EA6\u300B",
		"indexes":"ngbpdtysygbzgqdd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\u662F\u82F1\u56FD\u903C\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B7E\u5B9A\u7684?",
		"id":19161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB9\u56FD\u56E2",
		"indexes":"zglssdywhdtysjgjds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u83B7\u5F97\u4F53\u80B2\u4E16\u754C\u51A0\u519B\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":19162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u603B\u7406\u8859\u95E8\u7684\u5EFA\u7ACB",
		"indexes":"jdzgzyjgbzmdhksdbzs",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E2D\u592E\u673A\u6784\u534A\u6B96\u6C11\u5730\u5316\u5F00\u59CB\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19163
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"zglsshg70sdhdyjw",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6D3B\u8FC770\u5C81\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u6709\u51E0\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u747E",
		"indexes":"sjbxqjmbddqhjykhshrsx",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u53E5\u201C\u4E0D\u60DC\u5343\u91D1\u4E70\u5B9D\u5200\uFF0C\u8C82\u88D8\u6362\u9152\u4E5F\u582A\u8C6A\u201D\u662F\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u5199\uFF1F",
		"id":19165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u671D",
		"indexes":"fldwzwyzflxssy",
		"question":"\u201C\u6CD5\u5F8B\u7B54\u95EE\u201D\u4F5C\u4E3A\u4E00\u79CD\u6CD5\u5F8B\u5F62\u5F0F\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":19166
	},
	{
		"answer":"120\u4E07",
		"indexes":"fedzysfgssldsjd",
		"question":"\u51E1\u5C14\u767B\u6218\u5F79\u53CC\u65B9\u5171\u635F\u5931\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u519B\u961F\uFF1F",
		"id":19167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59EC",
		"indexes":"qcszxddgwtx",
		"question":"\u201C\u542F\u201D\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u590F\u4EE3\u7684\u56FD\u738B\uFF0C\u4ED6\u59D3\uFF1F",
		"id":19168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5468",
		"indexes":"mgdssmsddqtq",
		"question":"\u201C\u6BDB\u516C\u9F0E\u201D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u4EE3\u7684\u9752\u94DC\u5668\uFF1F",
		"id":19169
	},
	{
		"answer":"1965\u5E74",
		"indexes":"z19561966ndjszwgsyqbzjszsmsj",
		"question":"\u57281956\u2014\u20141966\u5E74\u7684\u5EFA\u8BBE\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u77F3\u6CB9\u5168\u90E8\u81EA\u7ED9\u662F\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4",
		"id":19170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u4E3B\u5F00\u653E\u5916\u4EA4",
		"indexes":"zzxpgdwgrzqwgxcdbdfbgftxdwjsxs",
		"question":"\u300A\u81EA\u653F\u65B0\u7BC7\u300B\u89C4\u5B9A\u5916\u56FD\u4EBA\u201C\u51C6\u5176\u4E3A\u56FD\u732E\u7B56\uFF0C\u4F46\u4E0D\u5F97\u8BFD\u8C24\u56FD\u6CD5\u201D\uFF0C\u4F53\u73B0\u7684\u5916\u4EA4\u601D\u60F3\u662F",
		"id":19171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u4E94\u8FD0\u52A8",
		"indexes":"wfssrbddlqzjcdlssjs",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u7C89\u788E\u56DB\u4EBA\u5E2E\u5960\u5B9A\u4E86\u7FA4\u4F17\u57FA\u7840\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u662F",
		"id":19172
	},
	{
		"answer":"1962\u5E74",
		"indexes":"qqrdhdzksznyn",
		"question":"\u4E03\u5343\u4EBA\u5927\u4F1A\u7684\u53EC\u5F00\u662F\u5728\u90A3\u4E00\u5E74",
		"id":19173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B63\u786E\u6307\u51FA\u4E86\u56FD\u5185\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u77DB\u76FE",
		"indexes":"zgbddzygxs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u5171\u516B\u5927\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u8D21\u732E\u662F",
		"id":19174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u5171\u4E03\u5C4A\u4E8C\u4E2D\u5168\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"jjlzgyxmzzygmxshzygmzbdzdwtdhys",
		"question":"\u89E3\u51B3\u4E86\u4E2D\u56FD\u6709\u65B0\u6C11\u4E3B\u4E3B\u4E49\u9769\u547D\u5411\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u9769\u547D\u8F6C\u53D8\u7684\u91CD\u5927\u95EE\u9898\u7684\u4F1A\u8BAE\u662F",
		"id":19175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u521D\u671F",
		"indexes":"mzdtcyqfdpdszlhdzmldsz",
		"question":"\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u63D0\u51FA\u201C\u4E00\u5207\u53CD\u52A8\u6D3E\u90FD\u662F\u7EB8\u8001\u864E\u201D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u8BBA\u65AD\u662F\u5728",
		"id":19176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6297\u65E5\u6839\u636E\u5730\u5927\u751F\u4EA7\u8FD0\u52A8",
		"indexes":"xlcszwzqkrzzdslddlwzjcds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u63AA\u65BD\u4E2D\u4E3A\u4E89\u53D6\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u7684\u80DC\u5229\u5960\u5B9A\u4E86\u7269\u8D28\u57FA\u7840\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u56E2\u5927\u6218",
		"indexes":"zkzdxcjdjdlqgrmkzslxxdzys",
		"question":"\u5728\u6297\u6218\u7684\u76F8\u6301\u9636\u6BB5\uFF0C\u575A\u5B9A\u4E86\u5168\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u6297\u6218\u80DC\u5229\u4FE1\u5FC3\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F",
		"id":19178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5317\u6297\u8054",
		"indexes":"yxjdzylzlygds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u519B\u961F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0E\u674E\u5146\u9E9F\u6709\u5173\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u6069\u6765",
		"indexes":"zwgzycppwgdzzdxnsdltzbbk",
		"question":"\u5728\u6587\u9769\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E25\u8F9E\u6279\u8BC4\u6587\u9769\u7684\u79CD\u79CD\u5012\u884C\u9006\u65BD\u7684\u8001\u540C\u5FD7\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC",
		"id":19180
	},
	{
		"answer":"18\u4E16\u7EAA\u672B",
		"indexes":"gdsnysqdgdwdsrsxj",
		"question":"\u6B4C\u5FB7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u65F6\u671F\u5FB7\u56FD\u7684\u4F1F\u5927\u8BD7\u4EBA\u3001\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6",
		"id":19181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u4E03\u4E03\u201D\u4E8B\u53D8\u540E",
		"indexes":"gglddechzsxkrmztyzxzsxcsz",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5171\u4E24\u515A\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u5408\u4F5C\u5B9E\u73B0\uFF0C\u6297\u65E5\u6C11\u65CF\u7EDF\u4E00\u6218\u7EBF\u6B63\u5F0F\u5F62\u6210\u662F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E09\u7B49\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"ychfdsdrzqdnzzsy",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u5212\u5206\u7684\u56DB\u7B49\u4EBA\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5951\u4E39\u3001\u5973\u771F\u65CF\u5C5E\u4E8E",
		"id":19183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4E4B\u6D1E",
		"indexes":"gy1890nsszhbhycblhytc",
		"question":"\u516C\u51431890\u5E74\uFF0C\u662F\u8C01\u5728\u6E56\u5317\u6C49\u9633\u521B\u529E\u4E86\u6C49\u9633\u94C1\u5382\uFF1F",
		"id":19184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4E08\u539F",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzzglbsyhc",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u300B\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u75C5\u901D\u4E8E\u4F55\u5904\uFF1F",
		"id":19185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u8D77",
		"indexes":"zgsqcjxlksjhmsswzjdqgjlss",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u66FE\u7ECF\u4E0B\u4EE4\u5751\u6740\uFF08\u5373\u6D3B\u57CB\uFF09\u56DB\u5341\u4E07\u8D75\u519B\u7684\u79E6\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19186
	},
	{
		"answer":"18000",
		"indexes":"wgmqfxdzzdsssjjdsnqdysxl",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u76EE\u524D\u53D1\u73B0\u7684\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u9996\u9970\u662F\u8DDD\u4ECA\u591A\u5C11\u5E74\u524D\u7684\u539F\u59CB\u9879\u94FE\uFF1F",
		"id":19187
	},
	{
		"answer":"1936",
		"indexes":"lxynynss",
		"question":"\u9C81\u8FC5\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u901D\u4E16\uFF1F",
		"id":19188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE8\u9E7F\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"pfczzgcycynczz",
		"question":"\u7834\u91DC\u6C89\u821F\u8FD9\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED\u51FA\u4E8E\u54EA\u6B21\u6218\u4E89\uFF1F",
		"id":19189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929",
		"indexes":"wzjllykwzbyghrpsdwggdzzjs",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u81EA\u5DF1\u7ACB\u4E86\u4E00\u5757\u300A\u65E0\u5B57\u7891\u300B\u4EE5\u4F9B\u540E\u4EBA\u8BC4\u8BF4\u7684\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u653F\u6CBB\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19190
	},
	{
		"answer":"3\u6761",
		"indexes":"zggdbfdsczlyjt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5317\u65B9\u7684\u201C\u4E1D\u7EF8\u4E4B\u8DEF\u201D\u6709\u51E0\u6761\uFF1F",
		"id":19191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"xlrwzssqddhd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4EBA\u7269\u4E2D\u8C01\u662F\u6E05\u4EE3\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":19192
	},
	{
		"answer":"1980\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgnckstxjtlccbzrzs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u519C\u6751\u5F00\u59CB\u63A8\u884C\u5BB6\u5EAD\u8054\u4EA7\u627F\u5305\u8D23\u4EFB\u5236\u662F",
		"id":19193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zsjlsszztjrkdgjs",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E16\u754C\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7EDF\u8BA1\u4EBA\u53E3\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":19194
	},
	{
		"answer":"1991.12",
		"indexes":"qwslsmshjtd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u82CF\u8054\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u89E3\u4F53\u7684",
		"id":19195
	},
	{
		"answer":"1901",
		"indexes":"dycnbejsnynbfd",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u9881\u53D1\u7684",
		"id":19196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58EE\u65CF",
		"indexes":"lsjswgngssmzcszdrw",
		"question":"\u201C\u5218\u4E09\u59D0\u201D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7236\u5B50",
		"indexes":"lqchlscssmgx",
		"question":"\u6881\u542F\u8D85\u548C\u6881\u601D\u6210\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB\uFF1F",
		"id":19198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5AB3",
		"indexes":"lhyhlqcssmgx",
		"question":"\u6797\u5FBD\u56E0\u548C\u6881\u542F\u8D85\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB\uFF1F",
		"id":19199
	},
	{
		"answer":"1936\u5E7410\u670819\u65E5",
		"indexes":"lxssy",
		"question":"\u9C81\u8FC5\u901D\u4E16\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19200
	},
	{
		"answer":"1924\u5E74",
		"indexes":"aycsnnksjd",
		"question":"\u5965\u8FD0\u6751\u662F\u54EA\u5E74\u5F00\u59CB\u5EFA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u5C1A",
		"indexes":"xlnygbsqtrdxd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5176\u4ED6\u4EBA\u7684\u5144\u5F1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ppqsy19sjdnggj",
		"question":"\u4E52\u4E53\u7403\u59CB\u4E8E19\u4E16\u7EAA\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19203
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u67083\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgkrzzsljnrs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u80DC\u5229\u7EAA\u5FF5\u65E5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u9053\u6218",
		"indexes":"krzzsqzjzpysjcdhkzdrmqzfml",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u5728\u5180\u4E2D\u5E73\u539F\u4E0A\uFF0C\u575A\u6301\u654C\u540E\u6297\u6218\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u7FA4\u4F17\u53D1\u660E\u4E86\uFF1A",
		"id":19205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F6\u633A",
		"indexes":"krzzsqxsjddyrjzs",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u65B0\u56DB\u519B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u519B\u957F\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u5609\u5E9A",
		"indexes":"krzzsqgddaghqdzgdkzzclzydgxqwnyhqdlxss",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u5E7F\u5927\u7684\u7231\u56FD\u534E\u4FA8\u5BF9\u7956\u56FD\u7684\u6297\u6218\u4F5C\u51FA\u4E86\u5353\u8D8A\u7684\u8D21\u732E\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\u5357\u6D0B\u534E\u4FA8\u7684\u9886\u8896\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u5B66\u4E49",
		"indexes":"krzzqjlyswzsdgsjyhxqwtydyszcfbzgzlwsyxytx",
		"question":"\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u671F\u95F4\uFF0C\u72FC\u7259\u5C71\u4E94\u58EE\u58EB\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u5BB6\u55BB\u6237\u6653\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8DF3\u5D16\u7684\u52C7\u58EB\u4E2D\u9664\u526F\u73ED\u957F\u845B\u632F\u6797\u5916\u8C01\u4E5F\u5E78\u8FD0\u8131\u9669\uFF1F",
		"id":19208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97",
		"indexes":"lzybszszysfgrfzdyyjzdrfswmfzswlbsdhegcd",
		"question":"\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u300A\u6355\u86C7\u8005\u8BF4\u300B\u4E2D\u201C\u4EE5\u4FDF\u592B\u89C2\u4EBA\u98CE\u8005\u5F97\u7109\u201D\u4E00\u53E5\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4EBA\u98CE\u201D\u5B9E\u4E3A\u201C\u6C11\u98CE\u201D\uFF0C\u8FD9\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u907F\u8C01\u7684\u8BB3\u800C\u6539\u79F0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u85CF\u65CF",
		"indexes":"tddtfsjtngzdzx",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u7684\u5410\u8543\u662F\u4ECA\u5929\u54EA\u4E2A\u65CF\u7684\u7956\u5148\uFF1A",
		"id":19210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"wgzzcxzbsz",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u7EB8\u5E01\u662F\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5468",
		"indexes":"wggdyyzjtzwtsngcdcxd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6709\u4E00\u79CD\u4E95\u7530\u5236\uFF0C\u95EE\u5B83\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\u3002",
		"id":19212
	},
	{
		"answer":"1928",
		"indexes":"nynlbclxyslflzjsxy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF0C\u5218\u4F2F\u627F\u7559\u5B66\u4E8E\u82CF\u8054\u4F0F\u9F99\u829D\u519B\u4E8B\u5B66\u9662\uFF1A",
		"id":19213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u5B50\u6602",
		"indexes":"sbsyctsj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u521D\u5510\u56DB\u6770\uFF1A",
		"id":19214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687",
		"indexes":"hdzwgjysdzschsy",
		"question":"\u7687\u5E1D\u4F5C\u4E3A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5143\u9996\u7684\u6B63\u5F0F\u79F0\u53F7\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"wgzzfxgjxykdyxs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u53D1\u884C\u56FD\u9645\u4FE1\u7528\u5361\u7684\u94F6\u884C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8205\u8205",
		"indexes":"hdjjwqspqjjhqbdsmr",
		"question":"\u6C49\u5927\u5C06\u519B\u536B\u9752\u662F\u9AA0\u9A91\u5C06\u519B\u970D\u53BB\u75C5\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u5178\u7406\u8BBA\u9047\u5230\u56F0\u96BE",
		"indexes":"lssdzwzns",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u201C\u7D2B\u5916\u707E\u96BE\u201D\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E0C\u814A",
		"indexes":"bqlsnggjfmd",
		"question":"\u51B0\u6DC7\u6DCB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53D1\u660E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u6CE2\u7F57",
		"indexes":"zgxlbcwstysds",
		"question":"\u5728\u53E4\u5E0C\u814A\u88AB\u6210\u4E3A\u662F\u201C\u592A\u9633\u795E\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"ssyzjcwlfrylxrnglsrw",
		"question":"\u201C\u751F\u6B7B\u4E00\u77E5\u5DF1\uFF0C\u5B58\u4EA1\u4E24\u5987\u4EBA\u201D\u7528\u6765\u5F62\u5BB9\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F4\u6851",
		"indexes":"sgslbwldkcjpzglzneysqjm",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u4E3A\u4E86\u5BF9\u6297\u66F9\u519B\uFF0C\u6D3E\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u54EA\u513F\u4E0E\u5B59\u6743\u7ED3\u76DF\uFF1F",
		"id":19222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u601D\u9088",
		"indexes":"zwggdnwmyhd101s",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u54EA\u4F4D\u540D\u533B\u6D3B\u5230101\u5C81",
		"id":19223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E93\u65AF\u7279",
		"indexes":"bqmwsjdzxds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u53D6\u540D\u4E3A\u201C\u4E16\u754C\u7684\u4E2D\u5FC3\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u6CD5\u6218\u4E89\u7ED3\u675F\u540E",
		"indexes":"lssqzfztwslxssy",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u5728\u53F0\u6E7E\u8BBE\u7ACB\u884C\u7701\u59CB\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236\u9020\u548C\u4F7F\u7528\u5DE5\u5177",
		"indexes":"ylrybjrlyxdbtdtdswxjbxlnyxzwryfjdzzybz",
		"question":"\u4E0E\u7C7B\u4EBA\u733F\u6BD4\u8F83\uFF0C\u4EBA\u7C7B\u6709\u8BB8\u591A\u4E0D\u540C\u7684\u7279\u70B9\uFF0C\u751F\u7269\u5B66\u5BB6\u628A\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4F5C\u4E3A\u4EBA\u733F\u5206\u754C\u7684\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u6807\u51C6",
		"id":19226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F",
		"indexes":"zgdygcdsngc",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u662F\u90A3\u4E2A\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":19227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8006\uFF0C\u53E4\u7A00\uFF0C\u800B\uFF0C\u8004\uFF0C\u671F\u9890",
		"indexes":"xljwggdnlcwaxddsxplzqds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C06\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5E74\u9F84\u79F0\u8C13\u6309\u5C0F\u5230\u5927\u987A\u5E8F\u6392\u5217\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E0A",
		"indexes":"tcddyghdss",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":19229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8759\u8760",
		"indexes":"lddfmsmf",
		"question":"\u96F7\u8FBE\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u662F\u6A21\u4EFF\uFF1A",
		"id":19230
	},
	{
		"answer":"1923\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zmdgdddzfsz",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u5173\u4E1C\u5927\u5730\u9707\u201D\u53D1\u751F\u5728",
		"id":19231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEE\u5357\u738B\u5218\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xcdfssfmd",
		"question":"\u76F8\u4F20\u8C46\u8150\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u660E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u56FD",
		"indexes":"gy230njjwwddlywrdcdddtw",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143230\u5E74\uFF0C\uFF08\uFF09\u5C06\u519B\u536B\u6E29\u7B49\u5E26\u9886\u4E00\u4E07\u4EBA\u7684\u8239\u961F\u8FBE\u5230\u53F0\u6E7E\u3002",
		"id":19233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u5E86",
		"indexes":"zgdwdznl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u201C\u96FE\u90FD\u201D\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"femstaqjdzzakndesnyggjdr",
		"question":"\u300A\u798F\u5C14\u6469\u65AF\u63A2\u6848\u5168\u96C6\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u963F.\u67EF\u5357\u9053\u5C14\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FFD\u6C42\u5229\u6DA6",
		"indexes":"zscjjzqyjxscjyhddzjmds",
		"question":"\u5728\u5E02\u573A\u7ECF\u6D4E\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4F01\u4E1A\u8FDB\u884C\u751F\u4EA7\u7ECF\u8425\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u76F4\u63A5\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u62C9\u4F2F",
		"indexes":"yzlzzcxznl",
		"question":"\u5706\u5468\u7387\u6700\u65E9\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zzlzzbpslccjydj",
		"question":"\u8D75\u5B50\u9F99\u5728\u957F\u5742\u5761\u6740\u4E86\u66F9\u64CD\u51E0\u5458\u5927\u5C06?",
		"id":19238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E03\u5EA7",
		"indexes":"hzyyzzldqpmtlccjzdy",
		"question":"\u6C49\u4E2D\u4E00\u5F79\u8D75\u5B50\u9F99\u5355\u67AA\u5339\u9A6C\u6311\u4E86\u66F9\u64CD\u51E0\u5EA7\u5927\u8425?",
		"id":19239
	},
	{
		"answer":"215",
		"indexes":"lx7gyzdydst",
		"question":"\u8FDE\u7EED7\u4E2A\u6708\u6700\u591A\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":19240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9",
		"indexes":"qshdygmddzhgs",
		"question":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u706D\u6389\u7684\u8BF8\u4FAF\u56FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5965\u591A\u00B7\u7F57\u65AF\u798F",
		"indexes":"jzsznqdmgzts",
		"question":"\u5C31\u804C\u65F6\u6700\u5E74\u8F7B\u7684\u7F8E\u56FD\u603B\u7EDF\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19242
	},
	{
		"answer":"1919\u5E743\u6708",
		"indexes":"gcgjcldsjs",
		"question":"\u5171\u4EA7\u56FD\u9645\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F",
		"id":19243
	},
	{
		"answer":"18\u5468\u5C81\u4EE5\u4E0A\u6709\u653F\u6CBB\u6743\u5229\u7684\u516C\u6C11",
		"indexes":"xfgdwgxyxjqhbxjqdrs",
		"question":"\u300A\u5BAA\u6CD5\u300B\u89C4\u5B9A\u6211\u56FD\u4EAB\u6709\u9009\u4E3E\u6743\u548C\u88AB\u9009\u4E3E\u6743\u7684\u4EBA\u662F()",
		"id":19244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5FE0\u8D24",
		"indexes":"bssdwzbztddrws",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u5927\u65E0\u5B57\u7891\u4E2D\u63D0\u5230\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u662F",
		"id":19245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u6B87\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"cgzjwgy29wwwhdqzzxds",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u53E4\u81F3\u4ECA\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u670929\u4F4D\u5A03\u5A03\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u79CD\u6587\u5B66\u601D\u6F6E",
		"indexes":"xfxdpwxzds",
		"question":"\u897F\u65B9\u73B0\u4EE3\u6D3E\u6587\u5B66\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19247
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"dwmy100wdddzmsjxstjxhydd",
		"question":"\u5F53\u6211\u4EEC\u7528100\u74E6\u7684\u7535\u706F\u7167\u660E\u65F6\uFF0C\u7ECF()\u5C0F\u65F6\u5B83\u5C06\u6D88\u8017\u4E00\u5EA6\u7535\u3002",
		"id":19248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468",
		"indexes":"wztygy655nbgzlwhhkscyczgy690nzlwdghw",
		"question":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u4E8E\u516C\u5143655\u5E74\u88AB\u9AD8\u5B97\u7ACB\u4E3A\u7687\u540E\uFF0C\u5F00\u59CB\u53C2\u4E0E\u671D\u653F\uFF0C\u516C\u5143690\u5E74\u81EA\u7ACB\u4E3A\u5E1D\uFF0C\u56FD\u53F7\u4E3A:",
		"id":19249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5B97\u68E0",
		"indexes":"wzxhlsmjsnbywlsz",
		"question":"\u6587\u7AE0\u897F\u6C49\u4E24\u53F8\u9A6C\uFF0C\u7ECF\u4E16\u5357\u5317\u4E00\u5367\u9F99\u662F\u6307()\u3002",
		"id":19250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zynsxsynggjsjmgd",
		"question":"\u81EA\u7531\u5973\u795E\u50CF\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u9001\u7ED9\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":19251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u4F2F\u627F",
		"indexes":"jfzzcqsdzcdldrss",
		"question":"\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u521D\u671F\u5C71\u4E1C\u6218\u573A\u7684\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":19252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A8A\u5C71",
		"indexes":"qshljzzhc",
		"question":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u9675\u5EFA\u9020\u5728\u4F55\u5904?",
		"id":19253
	},
	{
		"answer":"150\u4E07",
		"indexes":"decsjdzqjzddyczysdlgldhzzdjgssldsry",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u671F\u95F4\u6700\u5927\u7684\u4E00\u6B21\u6218\u5F79--\u65AF\u5927\u6797\u683C\u52D2\u5927\u4F1A\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5FB7\u519B\u5171\u635F\u5931\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":19254
	},
	{
		"answer":"60\u5E74\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"AMX30zztkssmsjscd",
		"question":"AMX-30\u4E3B\u6218\u5766\u514B\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u95F4\u751F\u4EA7\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6539\u9020\u6211\u4EEC\u7684\u5B66\u4E60\u300B",
		"indexes":"mzdtzznpwzzdgyssqsjyxdkxdjs",
		"question":"\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u540C\u5FD7\u5728\u54EA\u7BC7\u6587\u7AE0\u4E2D\u5BF9\u53E4\u8BED\u201C\u5B9E\u4E8B\u6C42\u662F\u201D\u7ED9\u4E88\u65B0\u7684\u79D1\u5B66\u7684\u89E3\u91CA\uFF1F",
		"id":19256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u5357",
		"indexes":"znzzzdxsjsm",
		"question":"\u6307\u5357\u9488\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5F62\u5F0F\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"nzdzgscsmshqksznysczsytqdm",
		"question":"\u60A8\u77E5\u9053\u4E2D\u56FD\u662F\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8D77\u5F00\u59CB\u5728\u519C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u79CD\u4F7F\u7528\u94C1\u5668\u7684\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":19258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u56E0\u5B66\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDE\u751F",
		"indexes":"nzdxmnyxbzbcwdssxwhlyldsdbglm",
		"question":"\u60A8\u77E5\u9053\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u5728\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u5F53\u65F6\u601D\u60F3\u6587\u5316\u9886\u57DF\u91CC\u7684\u4E09\u5927\u53D8\u9769\u91CC\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":19259
	},
	{
		"answer":"120",
		"indexes":"b2zztksxfzzzdsmmhtpdtk",
		"question":"\u8C792\u4E3B\u6218\u5766\u514B\u662F\u897F\u65B9\u6700\u65E9\u88C5\u591A\u5C11mm\u6ED1\u819B\u70AE\u7684\u5766\u514B\uFF1A",
		"id":19260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8303\u747E",
		"indexes":"zgdygnszs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5973\u5E02\u957F\u662F",
		"id":19261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u707F\u829D",
		"indexes":"zgdygnfxys",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5973\u98DE\u884C\u5458\u662F",
		"id":19262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u56DB\u4EE3\u6218\u6597\u673A",
		"indexes":"mgdF22mqzdjsydjdzdj",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684F\uFF0D22\u731B\u79BD\u6218\u6597\u673A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u51E0\u4EE3\u6218\u6597\u673A\uFF1F",
		"id":19263
	},
	{
		"answer":"1227\u5E74",
		"indexes":"cjshbsynyn",
		"question":"\u6210\u5409\u601D\u6C57\u75C5\u901D\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":19264
	},
	{
		"answer":"2000",
		"indexes":"xb20ydrmbsnynfxd",
		"question":"\u65B0\u724820\u5143\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53D1\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5927\u948A",
		"indexes":"1927nzbjbjfzzlshdgcdcsrs",
		"question":"1927\u5E74\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u88AB\u519B\u9600\u5F20\u4F5C\u9716\u6740\u5BB3\u7684\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u662F",
		"id":19266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u6C49\u548C\u5357\u4EAC\u56FD\u6C11\u653F\u5E9C\u5408\u5E76",
		"indexes":"lssdnhhlsz",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u201C\u5B81\u6C49\u5408\u6D41\u201D\u662F\u6307",
		"id":19267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6539\u9769\u5E01\u5236",
		"indexes":"gmzfscqdwdczdcszcxjwmxds",
		"question":"\u56FD\u6C11\u653F\u5E9C\u6240\u91C7\u53D6\u7684\u7A33\u5B9A\u8D22\u653F\u7684\u63AA\u65BD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6210\u6548\u8F83\u4E3A\u660E\u663E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8E\u8C26",
		"indexes":"qcwjcsslhfsrdxfssgqbpylqbzrjdzzss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u9524\u4E07\u51FB\u51FA\u6DF1\u5C71\uFF0C\u70C8\u706B\u711A\u70E7\u82E5\u7B49\u95F2\u3002\u7C89\u8EAB\u788E\u9AA8\u5168\u4E0D\u6015\uFF0C\u8981\u7559\u6E05\u767D\u5728\u4EBA\u95F4\u3002\u201D\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE0\u90AF",
		"indexes":"xyzjldbqhksl30wqjjzdslqjtjdzjs",
		"question":"\u9879\u7FBD\u5728\u5DE8\u9E7F\u5927\u8D25\u79E6\u540E\uFF0C\u5751\u6740\u4E8630\u4E07\u79E6\u519B\u964D\u5352\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u7387\u79E6\u519B\u6295\u964D\u7684\u4E3B\u5C06\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u4EE3\u738B\u61FF\u8363",
		"indexes":"wgdygfxhyjjgwdxzss",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u53D1\u73B0\u548C\u7814\u7A76\u7532\u9AA8\u6587\u7684\u5B66\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"mxlwyngdf",
		"question":"\u660E\u5B5D\u9675\u4F4D\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\uFF1A",
		"id":19272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199\u51FA\u8FC7\u5929\u82B1",
		"indexes":"kx6sjwhdsywdsdwgrnhrtclsmjy",
		"question":"\u5EB7\u71996\u5C81\u7EE7\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u5F53\u65F6\u7684\u5916\u56FD\u4EBA\u5357\u6000\u4EC1\u63D0\u51FA\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48\u5EFA\u8BAE\uFF1F",
		"id":19273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u951F",
		"indexes":"xlsrzsbsbysj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u56DB\u4EBA\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u5317\u6D0B\u4E09\u6770\u201D",
		"id":19274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u695A",
		"indexes":"cqsqtjgzbzydzhgs",
		"question":"\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u540C\u664B\u56FD\u4E89\u9738\u4E2D\u539F\u7684\u8BF8\u4FAF\u56FD\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u671D",
		"indexes":"wgywzkkdlsschsksd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6709\u6587\u5B57\u53EF\u8003\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u662F\u4ECE\u4F55\u65F6\u5F00\u59CB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u901A",
		"indexes":"bcwzgjddycds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u4EE3\u7B2C\u4E00\u57CE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F",
		"indexes":"jasrdsds",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5B89\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u65F6\u4EE3\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7530\u6587",
		"indexes":"mcjdmzs",
		"question":"\u5B5F\u5C1D\u541B\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F",
		"id":19279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E56\u5317\u7701",
		"indexes":"fmhzyssdbssxzngsdr",
		"question":"\u53D1\u660E\u6D3B\u5B57\u5370\u5237\u672F\u7684\u6BD5\u5347\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19280
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"1981ncjzgdldyctfksdydsr",
		"question":"1981\u5E74\uFF0C\u53C2\u52A0\u7956\u56FD\u5927\u9646\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u201C\u6258\u798F\u201D\u8003\u8BD5\u7684\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"htbsss",
		"question":"\u534E\u4F57\u88AB\u8C01\u6240\u6740\uFF1F",
		"id":19282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968F\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlnyxbsygjzzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u201C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"sgyyzlbsyhrzs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u5415\u5E03\u6B7B\u4E8E\u4F55\u4EBA\u4E4B\u624B",
		"id":19284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D0",
		"indexes":"zgxlrmgmnlsy",
		"question":"\u5728\u53E4\u5E0C\u814A,\u4EBA\u4EEC\u8D2D\u4E70\u5974\u96B6\u662F\u7528\uFF1A",
		"id":19285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u5B8B\u4E4B\u4EA4",
		"indexes":"jcncrlqzshzngsq",
		"question":"\u6770\u51FA\u5973\u8BCD\u4EBA\u674E\u6E05\u7167\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":19286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u524D\u79E6",
		"indexes":"wgzzdjsyxsngcd",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u519B\u4E8B\u9662\u6821\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1A",
		"id":19287
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"qshtyzghzqgsljxyzlgjtbtxfcldsgj",
		"question":"\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u7EDF\u4E00\u4E2D\u56FD\u540E\uFF0C\u5728\u5168\u56FD\u8BBE\u7ACB\u90E1\u53BF\u4EE5\u6CBB\u7406\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF0C\u4ED6\u628A\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u6210\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u90E1\uFF1F",
		"id":19288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6749\u8C26\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"rbfmzmfzfhmds",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u53D1\u660E\u5728\u7C73\u996D\u4E2D\u653E\u7EA2\u6885\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6BBF\u82F1",
		"indexes":"ljdqdlddldds",
		"question":"\u7387\u519B\u76D7\u53D6\u4E1C\u9675\u7684\u4E1C\u9675\u5927\u76D7\u662F",
		"id":19290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u900A",
		"indexes":"sgzyjhslyblbdddbdss",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u7528\u8BA1\u706B\u70E7\u8FDE\u8425\u628A\u5218\u5907\u6253\u5F97\u5927\u8D25\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u9537",
		"indexes":"tyhgjsxyszzfq",
		"question":"\u8BA8\u8881\u62A4\u56FD\u519B\u9996\u5148\u7531\u8C01\u7EC4\u7EC7\u53D1\u8D77",
		"id":19292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zzdjydbxcynggj",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5BB6\u7528\u7535\u51B0\u7BB1\u4EA7\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjszzdfldjscxznggj",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u98CE\u529B\u7B49\u7EA7\u662F\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u4E09\u4E00\u516B\u201D",
		"indexes":"jnlhzjzdlhzsnccazdyhz",
		"question":"\u300A\u8BB0\u5FF5\u5218\u548C\u73CD\u541B\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u5218\u548C\u73CD\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u6B21\u60E8\u6848\u4E2D\u7684\u9047\u5BB3\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":19295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF11\uFF19\uFF19\uFF11\u5E74\u5E95",
		"indexes":"swashzyghglmjtsznyn",
		"question":"\u82CF\u7EF4\u57C3\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u8054\u76DF\u89E3\u4F53\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19296
	},
	{
		"answer":"1985\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xcdhhlsnynjcd",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5B58\u7684\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u5EFA\u6210\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u592B\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"wggdrwsjswzgcbylrdzgysedlczdsxjs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BA4\u4E3A\u4E16\u754C\u662F\u7269\u8D28\u6784\u6210\uFF0C\u4E0D\u4F9D\u8D56\u4EBA\u7684\u4E3B\u89C2\u610F\u8BC6\u800C\u72EC\u7ACB\u5B58\u5728\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u8D35\u5983",
		"indexes":"zggdsdmnzbczxhdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u56DB\u5927\u7F8E\u5973\u4E2D\uFF0C\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C\u201C\u7F9E\u82B1\u201D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9178\u6885",
		"indexes":"gddrbrshqkzyddwsjbdrjcdshcnzyxcwsysmxcxf",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u65E5\u672C\u4EBA\u751F\u6D3B\u6E05\u82E6\uFF0C\u53EA\u6709\u8FBE\u5230\u6B66\u58EB\u7EA7\u522B\u7684\u4EBA\u8FDB\u9910\u7684\u65F6\u5019\u624D\u80FD\u4F50\u4EE5\u5C0F\u83DC\uFF0C\u6B66\u58EB\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u5C0F\u83DC\u4E0B\u996D\uFF1F",
		"id":19300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u53A6\u6761\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"qzfhmgqdddygbpdtys",
		"question":"\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u548C\u7F8E\u56FD\u7B7E\u5B9A\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\u662F",
		"id":19301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F25\u8861\u8BF4\u9EC4\u7956",
		"indexes":"rsmzzsssjshwlyssss",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C5D\u4F3C\u5E99\u4E2D\u4E4B\u795E\uFF0C\u867D\u53D7\u796D\u7940\uFF0C\u6068\u65E0\u7075\u9A8C\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u8BF4\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FDD\u52A0\u5229\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"mgzgzdsnggj",
		"question":"\u201C\u73AB\u7470\u4E4B\u56FD\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"qmzjsccshrsldbhmwdgdsexsjxlewm",
		"question":"\u9752\u6885\u716E\u9152\u65F6\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u8BF4\u4F55\u4EBA\u8272\u5389\u80C6\u8584\uFF0C\u597D\u8C0B\u65E0\u65AD\uFF1B\u5E72\u5927\u4E8B\u800C\u60DC\u8EAB\uFF0C\u89C1\u5C0F\u5229\u800C\u4EA1\u547D\uFF1F",
		"id":19304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E01\u78CA",
		"indexes":"2003ndzgsfss",
		"question":"2003\u5E74\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u9996\u5BCC\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19305
	},
	{
		"answer":"7\u6708",
		"indexes":"zgdlfzsdbdsngyf",
		"question":"\u5728\u53E4\u4EE3\u5386\u6CD5\u4E2D\uFF0C\u201C\u7533\u201D\u4EE3\u8868\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u6708\u4EFD\uFF1F",
		"id":19306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49",
		"indexes":"mwdyhgmsngcd",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u738B\u5806\u4E00\u53F7\u53E4\u5893\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3",
		"id":19307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u7406\u77F3",
		"indexes":"bsxtsysmstqc",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u8428\u659C\u5854\u662F\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u77F3\u5934\u780C\u6210\uFF1F",
		"id":19308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\uFF11\uFF19\uFF18\uFF18\u5E74\uFF17\u6708\uFF11\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgrmjfjc1955nsxjxz1966nbqxwjxykssxxdjxzdssmsh",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u4ECE1955\u5E74\u5B9E\u884C\u519B\u8854\u5236\uFF0C1966\u5E74\u88AB\u53D6\u6D88\u3002\u6211\u519B\u73B0\u53C8\u5F00\u59CB\u5B9E\u884C\u65B0\u7684\u519B\u8854\u5236\u5EA6\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u996E\u9152\u98DF\u8089\uFF0C\u8C08\u7B11\u5F08\u68CB",
		"indexes":"htjgyggldsgyshxt",
		"question":"\u534E\u4F57\u7ED9\u5173\u7FBD\u522E\u9AA8\u7597\u6BD2\u65F6\u5173\u7FBD\u662F\u4F55\u5F62\u6001\uFF1F",
		"id":19310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5510\u516D\u5178\u300B",
		"indexes":"zggdzzdybbjwzdxzfds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u6BD4\u8F83\u5B8C\u6574\u7684\u884C\u653F\u6CD5\u5178\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u98DF",
		"indexes":"tczzsjxlnygjcdoz",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u9020\u7EB8\u672F\u7ECF\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u56FD\u5BB6\u4F20\u5230\u6B27\u6D32",
		"id":19312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u5C1A",
		"indexes":"mckghdzyzczgsm",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\u6731\u5143\u748B\u66FE\u505A\u8FC7\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"hxqfdjtqyjghtptgzctwxfsnddtjtjsxzdsmdf",
		"question":"\u6D2A\u79C0\u5168\u53D1\u52A8\u91D1\u7530\u8D77\u4E49\uFF0C\u5EFA\u56FD\u53F7\u592A\u5E73\u5929\u56FD\uFF0C\u81EA\u79F0\u5929\u738B\u3002\u54B8\u4E30\u4E09\u5E74\u5B9A\u90FD\u5929\u4EAC\uFF0C\u5929\u4EAC\u662F\u73B0\u5728\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":19314
	},
	{
		"answer":"1972\u5E74",
		"indexes":"mgztnksnynfh",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u603B\u7EDF\u5C3C\u514B\u677E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8BBF\u534E\uFF1F",
		"id":19315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u6C49",
		"indexes":"wgymwrlytsy",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u4EE5\u7164\u4E3A\u71C3\u6599\u51B6\u94C1\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":19316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795E\u5B97",
		"indexes":"wasbffszscnghdzwqj",
		"question":"\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5B8B\u671D\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5728\u4F4D\u671F\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":19317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B63\u7EA2\u65D7",
		"indexes":"qcsbjcdxzmsymznyqzsd",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u65F6\uFF0C\u5317\u4EAC\u57CE\u7684\u897F\u76F4\u95E8\u662F\u7531\u6EE1\u65CF\u54EA\u4E00\u65D7\u9A7B\u5B88\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19318
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjsdybyxzrgsfsynggjzdd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u300A\u6709\u9650\u8D23\u4EFB\u516C\u53F8\u6CD5\u300B\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5236\u5B9A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u77F3\u5668",
		"indexes":"yswhswglssngsdzqdwh",
		"question":"\u4EF0\u97F6\u6587\u5316\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u54EA\u4E2A\u65F6\u4EE3\u4E2D\u671F\u7684\u6587\u5316\uFF1F",
		"id":19320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6728\u5934",
		"indexes":"sjsdylmtcdzycls",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u8F86\u6469\u6258\u8F66\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u6750\u6599\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u5143\u57F9",
		"indexes":"zwgzztcxfzds",
		"question":"\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u63D0\u5021\u5B66\u5206\u5236\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79D1\u4E3E\u5236\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"mzlczzsscrppdsd",
		"question":"\u201C\u8C2C\u79CD\u6D41\u4F20\u201D\u6700\u65E9\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u4EBA\u6279\u8BC4\u5F53\u65F6\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793C",
		"indexes":"zggdhyfzzydyyssm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5A5A\u59FB\u6CD5\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u7684\u6E0A\u6E90\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u7F8E\u5C14\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zzdxxwzsyzs",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6954\u5F62\u6587\u5B57\u4F7F\u7528\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968B\u671D",
		"indexes":"kjzdscyhs",
		"question":"\u79D1\u4E3E\u5236\u5EA6\u59CB\u521B\u4E8E\u4F55\u65F6\uFF1F",
		"id":19326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546",
		"indexes":"chsqdzgtzzcw",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u4F55\u65F6\u8D77\uFF0C\u5BF9\u6700\u9AD8\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u79F0\u201C\u738B\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":19327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7279\u52A1\u673A\u5173",
		"indexes":"mdddchxcs",
		"question":"\u660E\u4EE3\u7684\u4E1C\u5382\u548C\u897F\u5382\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19328
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"dyjged",
		"question":"\u9F0E\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u201C\u8033\u6735\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":19329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u4F57",
		"indexes":"gdtcwqxwssc",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u4F53\u64CD\u4E94\u79BD\u620F\u4E3A\u8C01\u6240\u521B\uFF1F",
		"id":19330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8340\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zglsszzjlhfjhqlyfzcslzdsxjs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u5C06\u793C\u548C\u6CD5\u7ED3\u5408\u8D77\u6765\uFF0C\u4EE5\u201C\u6CD5\u6CBB\u201D\u5145\u5B9E\u201C\u793C\u6CBB\u201D\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"dygcczwxzddrs",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6D4B\u51FA\u5B50\u5348\u7EBF\u957F\u5EA6\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6559\u80B2\u754C\u300B",
		"indexes":"zgzzdjyzykws",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6559\u80B2\u4E13\u4E1A\u520A\u7269\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6881\u601D\u6210",
		"indexes":"zggjzxkdktzs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51\u5B66\u79D1\u7684\u5F00\u62D3\u8005\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19334
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u98DE\u71D5",
		"indexes":"xcwggdnzzswdmns",
		"question":"\u76F8\u4F20\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u80FD\u4F5C\u201C\u638C\u4E0A\u821E\u201D\u7684\u7F8E\u5973\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u4E1C",
		"indexes":"cqsdqghlgzxzdngs",
		"question":"\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u7684\u9F50\u56FD\u548C\u9C81\u56FD\uFF0C\u5728\u73B0\u5728\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\uFF1F",
		"id":19336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u540D",
		"indexes":"fmzcsz",
		"question":"\u201C\u9A78\u9A6C\u201D\u6700\u521D\u662F\u6307\uFF1A",
		"id":19337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99",
		"indexes":"zgdymypsysmtawzt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u90AE\u7968\u662F\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u56FE\u6848\u4E3A\u4E3B\u56FE",
		"id":19338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BAB\u5EF7",
		"indexes":"zzblwcxy",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u82AD\u857E\u821E\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u5531\u620F\u4E3A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zggdlrzds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u4F36\u4EBA\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"ssflhz",
		"question":"\u8C01\u6536\u670D\u4E86\u9EC4\u5FE0\uFF1F",
		"id":19341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u9AE6",
		"indexes":"smzzxlrjzsssdh",
		"question":"\u201C\u53F8\u9A6C\u662D\u4E4B\u5FC3\uFF0C\u8DEF\u4EBA\u7686\u77E5\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":19342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7126\u89E6\u3001\u5F20\u5357",
		"indexes":"zcbzzqcccysqdlyzjgcjdblydjbstmss",
		"question":"\u5728\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u524D\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u66FE\u4E0E\u5B59\u6743\u6253\u4E86\u4E00\u4ED7\uFF0C\u7ED3\u679C\u66F9\u519B\u5927\u8D25\uFF0C\u4E24\u5458\u5927\u5C06\u88AB\u6740\uFF0C\u4ED6\u4EEC\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":19343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5E73",
		"indexes":"sscccctdlbcd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4ECE\u66F9\u64CD\u5904\u6295\u5230\u5218\u5907\u5904\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u7726",
		"indexes":"xlwrnygbsysdbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u4EBA\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u8881\u7ECD\u7684\u90E8\u4E0B\uFF1F",
		"id":19345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u535A\u671B\u5761",
		"indexes":"zglccdszsznl",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u521D\u6B21\u6253\u80DC\u4ED7\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u6853",
		"indexes":"zmdgchsccgdsmdfsxd",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u300A\u89C2\u6CA7\u6D77\u300B\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u653B\u6253\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\u65F6\u5199\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E34\u6CAE",
		"indexes":"gyfzznlbq",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u7236\u5B50\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u88AB\u64D2\uFF1F",
		"id":19348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A4\u9A7E\u6709\u529F",
		"indexes":"dzyhdsxg",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u56E0\u4F55\u5F53\u4E0A\u76F8\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u65B9\u8C37",
		"indexes":"smyfzznczyzjhsm",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF\u7236\u5B50\u5728\u54EA\u6B21\u6218\u5F79\u4E2D\u51E0\u4E4E\u4E27\u547D\uFF1F",
		"id":19350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF4\u4E86\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u574F\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"kryhlybccsl",
		"question":"\u5B54\u878D\u56E0\u4F55\u7406\u7531\u88AB\u66F9\u64CD\u6740\u4E86\uFF1F",
		"id":19351
	},
	{
		"answer":"1931\u5E74",
		"indexes":"jybsbsy",
		"question":"\u4E5D\u4E00\u516B\u4E8B\u53D8\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":19352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"ygsdssmshdqq",
		"question":"\u300A\u9633\u5173\u4E09\u53E0\u300B\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u7684\u7434\u66F2\uFF1F",
		"id":19353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u4E2D\u5C71",
		"indexes":"sszszdcsr",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u201C\u4E2D\u5C71\u88C5\u201D\u7684\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4EE3",
		"indexes":"xcgyyzjcdzzdfgcsy",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5B58\u5173\u4E8E\u9057\u5631\u7EE7\u627F\u7684\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u6CD5\u89C4\u4EA7\u751F\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19355
	},
	{
		"answer":"30\u5206\u949F",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzstcsdjtzxyzsqdjjxbm",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u8BD5\u56FE\u53C2\u8D5B\u7684\u519B\u56E2\u957F\u9700\u8981\u5728\u8D5B\u524D\u591A\u4E45\u8FDB\u884C\u62A5\u540D\uFF1F",
		"id":19356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BCF\u5468\u661F\u671F\u516D",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzmgxqsmshjx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u661F\u671F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8FDB\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":19357
	},
	{
		"answer":"50\u7EA7\u53CA\u4EE5\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzjtcywjddjyqs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u519B\u56E2\u53C2\u4E0E\u73A9\u5BB6\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7\u8981\u6C42\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19359
	},
	{
		"answer":"70\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzmgjtcywjslsxs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u519B\u56E2\u53C2\u4E0E\u73A9\u5BB6\u6570\u91CF\u4E0A\u9650\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7387\u5148\u51FB\u7834\u5BF9\u624B\u519B\u56E2\u957F\u96D5\u50CF\u7684\u961F\u4F0D",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzzzpdsfdyjs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u6700\u7EC8\u8BC4\u5B9A\u80DC\u8D1F\u7684\u4F9D\u636E\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u6597\u79EF\u5206",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzyxsfppdjdxyjs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u5F71\u54CD\u53CC\u65B9\u5339\u914D\u7684\u51B3\u5B9A\u6027\u4F9D\u636E\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FB\u6740\u6570\u548C\u51FB\u7834\u8282\u70B9\u6570",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzjtzdjfsrhjsd",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u519B\u56E2\u6218\u6597\u79EF\u5206\u662F\u5982\u4F55\u8BA1\u7B97\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19363
	},
	{
		"answer":"F9",
		"indexes":"scdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5546\u57CE\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":19366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzssgqylzhcswysjpXkzhxXsz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D,\u5728\u6C5C\u6C34\u5173\u524D\u6709\u8DEF\u8BF8\u4FAF\u66FE\u8BF4'\u543E\u6709\u4E0A\u5C06\u6F58X\u53EF\u65A9\u534E\u96C4'X\u662F\u6307\uFF1F",
		"id":19367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4",
		"indexes":"mchxzqsspyxjsrqjwlzyssjybxrszsssdssgyyzlbhccdydgszggss",
		"question":"\u52C9\u4ECE\u864E\u7A74\u6682\u6816\u8EAB\uFF0C\u8BF4\u7834\u82F1\u96C4\u60CA\u715E\u4EBA\uFF0E\u5DE7\u5C06\u95FB\u96F7\u4F5C\u63A9\u9970\uFF0C\u968F\u673A\u5E94\u53D8\u4FE1\u5982\u795E>\u8FD9\u9996\u8BD7\u8BF4\u7684\u662F<\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49>\u4E2D\u5218\u5907\u548C\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E00\u6BB5\u6545\u4E8B\uFF0E\u8FD9\u4E2A\u6545\u4E8B\u662F",
		"id":19368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"gycldmsnxszqd",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u8349\u6599\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19369
	},
	{
		"answer":"1945",
		"indexes":"gdyzdsnynbzd",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u5C9B\u539F\u5B50\u5F39\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7206\u70B8\u7684",
		"id":19370
	},
	{
		"answer":"6\u67086\u65E5",
		"indexes":"nmddlfsy1944n",
		"question":"\u8BFA\u66FC\u5E95\u767B\u9646\u53D1\u751F\u4E8E1944\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":19371
	},
	{
		"answer":"88\u5C42",
		"indexes":"shjmdsg4205mjbsjzgdygjzwyjc",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u91D1\u8302\u5927\u53A6\u9AD8420.5\u7C73,\u5C45\u672C\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9AD8\u5EFA\u7B51,\u95EE\u6709\u51E0\u5C42?",
		"id":19372
	},
	{
		"answer":"1.1--1.4\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xhczhcsgdddssbxgmxhp",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u5B69\u4E58\u5750\u706B\u8F66\u8EAB\u9AD8\u8FBE\u5230\u591A\u5C11\u65F6\u5FC5\u987B\u8D2D\u4E70\u5C0F\u5B69\u7968\uFF1F",
		"id":19373
	},
	{
		"answer":"22.4%",
		"indexes":"lwzsgxszzrkdbfzds",
		"question":"\u674E\u3001\u738B\u3001\u5F20\u4E09\u4E2A\u59D3\u6C0F\u5360\u603B\u4EBA\u53E3\u7684\u767E\u5206\u4E4B\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F",
		"id":19374
	},
	{
		"answer":"1842\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zynjtyszgjdssdygbpdtynynqdd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u82F1\u3008\u5357\u4EAC\u6761\u7EA6\u3009\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u4EE3\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7B7E\u5B9A\u7684",
		"id":19375
	},
	{
		"answer":"1941",
		"indexes":"rbsnntxmgdzzg",
		"question":"\u65E5\u672C\u662F\u54EA\u5E74\u5077\u88AD\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u73CD\u73E0\u6E2F",
		"id":19376
	},
	{
		"answer":"8\u670815\u65E5",
		"indexes":"1945nrbzfzsxbwtjtjdsjs",
		"question":"1945\u5E74\u65E5\u672C\u653F\u5E9C\u6B63\u5F0F\u5BA3\u5E03\u65E0\u6761\u4EF6\u6295\u964D\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19377
	},
	{
		"answer":"14\u7ACB\u65B9\u7C73",
		"indexes":"cnrdbzytycldydslfmdkq",
		"question":"\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u7684\u9F3B\u5B50\u4E00\u5929\u8981\u5904\u7406\u5927\u7EA6\u591A\u5C11\u7ACB\u65B9\u7C73\u7684\u7A7A\u6C14",
		"id":19378
	},
	{
		"answer":"1946",
		"indexes":"NBAznyncl",
		"question":"NBA\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u521B\u7ACB\uFF1F",
		"id":19379
	},
	{
		"answer":"1948\u5E7412\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgrmyxclsnyncld",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u94F6\u884C\u6210\u7ACB\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19380
	},
	{
		"answer":"1997\u5E744\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"wgtldyctssznyn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u94C1\u8DEF\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u63D0\u901F\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u4E16\u540C\u5802",
		"indexes":"lsczy40nddzps",
		"question":"\u8001\u820D\u521B\u4F5C\u4E8E40\u5E74\u4EE3\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19382
	},
	{
		"answer":"46\u6761",
		"indexes":"zcrttxbydstrst",
		"question":"\u6B63\u5E38\u4EBA\u4F53\u4F53\u7EC6\u80DE\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6761\u67D3\u8272\u4F53",
		"id":19383
	},
	{
		"answer":"43.1\u2103",
		"indexes":"rzsswdtwljxs",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4E2D\u6691\u6B7B\u4EA1\u7684\u4F53\u6E29\u4E34\u754C\u7EBF\u662F",
		"id":19384
	},
	{
		"answer":"mx0.4%",
		"indexes":"drtxyzdjjnddddsrhsqzj",
		"question":"\u5F53\u4EBA\u4F53\u8840\u6DB2\u4E2D\u7684\u9152\u7CBE\u6D53\u5EA6\u8FBE\u5230\u591A\u5C11\uFF0C\u4EBA\u4F1A\u5931\u53BB\u77E5\u89C9\uFF1F",
		"id":19385
	},
	{
		"answer":"1949\u5E7411\u670811\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgrmjfjkjldjgshscl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u7A7A\u519B\u9886\u5BFC\u673A\u6784\u662F\u4F55\u65F6\u6210\u7ACB?",
		"id":19386
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u670824\u65E5",
		"indexes":"lhgrwnyt",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u65E5\u4E3A\u54EA\u4E00\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":19387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"1924nalpkydhdjbds",
		"question":"1924\u5E74\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A\u7684\u4E3E\u529E\u5730\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19388
	},
	{
		"answer":"24\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"mqwgfhtjdsyrylqsybxjdzzqxw",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6211\u56FD\u7B26\u5408\u6761\u4EF6\u7684\u5931\u4E1A\u4EBA\u5458\u9886\u53D6\u5931\u4E1A\u4FDD\u9669\u91D1\u7684\u6700\u957F\u671F\u9650\u4E3A",
		"id":19389
	},
	{
		"answer":"4\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gjzrkxydjz1977nclylzdyglxjnkq",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u81EA\u7136\u79D1\u5B66\u4E00\u7B49\u5956\u81EA1977\u5E74\u521B\u7ACB\u4EE5\u6765\u6700\u591A\u6709\u8FC7\u8FDE\u7EED\u51E0\u5E74\u7A7A\u7F3A",
		"id":19390
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"1347nnggjdywsrqfldyzhybxd",
		"question":"1347\u5E74\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u4E00\u4F4D\u5546\u4EBA\u7B7E\u53D1\u4E86\u7B2C\u4E00\u5F20\u6D77\u8FD0\u4FDD\u9669\u5355\uFF1F",
		"id":19391
	},
	{
		"answer":"1914\u5E74",
		"indexes":"slrwsjsdycsjdzddhxtfsz",
		"question":"\u201C\u8428\u62C9\u70ED\u7A9D\u4E8B\u4EF6\u201D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u7684\u5BFC\u706B\u7EBF\uFF0C\u5B83\u53D1\u751F\u5728",
		"id":19392
	},
	{
		"answer":"45\u4EBF",
		"indexes":"dqxcldsn",
		"question":"\u5730\u7403\u5F62\u6210\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5E74",
		"id":19393
	},
	{
		"answer":"841\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgyqqjnkssnn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6709\u786E\u5207\u7EAA\u5E74\u5F00\u59CB\u662F\u54EA\u5E74?",
		"id":19394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D59\u6C5F\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"1992ny4sdxhbds",
		"question":"1992\u5E74\u75314\u6240\u5927\u5B66\u5408\u5E76\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19395
	},
	{
		"answer":"24\u4E07\u4EE5\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"tsddzsdsrsw",
		"question":"\u5510\u5C71\u5927\u5730\u9707\u4F7F\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\u6B7B\u4EA1\uFF1A",
		"id":19396
	},
	{
		"answer":"4.6\u4E07\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"gmgmjdbljclsgydsr",
		"question":"\u56FD\u6C11\u9769\u547D\u519B\u7B2C\u516B\u8DEF\u519B\u6210\u7ACB\u65F6\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA\u3002",
		"id":19397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u6069\u6765\u3001\u738B\u82E5\u98DE",
		"indexes":"1945n8yymzdyqfzqtgmdtpdy",
		"question":"1945\u5E748\u6708\uFF0C\u4E0E\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C\u4E00\u8D77\u8D74\u91CD\u5E86\u540C\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u8C08\u5224\u7684\u6709",
		"id":19398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5ED6\u4EF2\u607A",
		"indexes":"1924nhpjxjljxdddbs",
		"question":"1924\u5E74\uFF0C\u9EC4\u57D4\u519B\u6821\u5EFA\u7ACB\uFF0C\u519B\u6821\u7684\u515A\u4EE3\u8868\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19399
	},
	{
		"answer":"1984\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgxxxfbbynyn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u884C\u5BAA\u6CD5\u9881\u5E03\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u7EEA\u4E8C\u5341\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zrjwzzs18941895nzgjmkjrbqldzz1894ngzwjwsqgxjn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u65E5\u7532\u5348\u6218\u4E89\u662F1894\uFF5E1895\u5E74\u4E2D\u56FD\u519B\u6C11\u6297\u51FB\u65E5\u672C\u4FB5\u7565\u7684\u6218\u4E89\u30021894\u5E74\u5E72\u652F\u4E3A\u7532\u5348\uFF0C\u662F\u6E05\u5149\u7EEA\u51E0\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":19401
	},
	{
		"answer":"1840",
		"indexes":"ypzzfsznyn",
		"question":"\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19402
	},
	{
		"answer":"1934\u5E74",
		"indexes":"dgrqblsznyn",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u5165\u4FB5\u6CE2\u5170\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":19403
	},
	{
		"answer":"1940\u5E74\u6625",
		"indexes":"wjwclnjwgmzfdsjs",
		"question":"\u6C6A\u7CBE\u536B\u6210\u7ACB\u5357\u4EAC\u4F2A\u56FD\u6C11\u653F\u5E9C\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F",
		"id":19404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4E8C\uFF2F\u60E8\u6848",
		"indexes":"1947ngmdfdpckzygtqfjefnzfphdxsydzzdlxcas",
		"question":"1947\u5E74\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u53CD\u52A8\u6D3E\u6B8B\u9177\u9547\u538B\u56FD\u7EDF\u533A\u201C\u53CD\u9965\u997F\u3001\u53CD\u5185\u6218\u3001\u53CD\u8FEB\u5BB3\u201D\u7684\u5B66\u751F\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF0C\u5236\u9020\u7684\u6D41\u8840\u60E8\u6848\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19405
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u670816\u65E5",
		"indexes":"zgdykyzdbzdrqs1964nd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9897\u539F\u5B50\u5F39\u7206\u70B8\u7684\u65E5\u671F\u662F1964\u5E74\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":19406
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AF\u7389\u7965",
		"indexes":"1924nfdbjzbdzxjls",
		"question":"1924\u5E74\u53D1\u52A8\u5317\u4EAC\u653F\u53D8\u7684\u76F4\u7CFB\u5C06\u9886\u662F",
		"id":19407
	},
	{
		"answer":"1847",
		"indexes":"sjzmdfmjadsdsynyn",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u8457\u540D\u7684\u53D1\u660E\u5BB6\u7231\u8FEA\u751F\u8BDE\u751F\u4E8E\u90A3\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":19408
	},
	{
		"answer":"1949\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wsqnjzsqdy",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u56DB\u201D\u9752\u5E74\u8282\u6B63\u5F0F\u786E\u5B9A\u4E8E\uFF1A",
		"id":19409
	},
	{
		"answer":"14\u5E74\u591A",
		"indexes":"alsssmzlstczddycplqlsdj",
		"question":"\u5B89\u7984\u5C71\u3001\u53F2\u601D\u660E\u4E4B\u4E71\u662F\u5510\u671D\u6700\u5927\u7684\u4E00\u6B21\u53DB\u4E71\uFF0C\u5176\u5386\u65F6\u591A\u4E45\uFF1F",
		"id":19410
	},
	{
		"answer":"1949",
		"indexes":"bybdxygyzzcly_________n4y4r",
		"question":"\u5317\u7EA6\uFF08\u5317\u5927\u897F\u6D0B\u516C\u7EA6\u7EC4\u7EC7\uFF09\uFF0C\u6210\u7ACB\u4E8E_________\u5E744\u67084\u65E5\u3002",
		"id":19411
	},
	{
		"answer":"45\u53F7",
		"indexes":"lqjxqddycfchscdqysdsh",
		"question":"\u7BEE\u7403\u5DE8\u661F\u4E54\u4E39\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u590D\u51FA\u540E\u6240\u7A7F\u7684\u7403\u8863\u662F\u591A\u5C11\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":19412
	},
	{
		"answer":"1946\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zgrmjfjdsy1927n8y1rqchyjjbgqznyngczgrmjfjd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u8BDE\u751F\u4E8E1927\u5E748\u67081\u65E5\uFF0C\u5176\u79F0\u547C\u4E5F\u51E0\u7ECF\u53D8\u66F4\uFF0C\u5176\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6539\u79F0\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19413
	},
	{
		"answer":"1234",
		"indexes":"asjsxplyxlssj1zhswadycqgdbdh2wmzgjl3gmddscwjbdp4zhghgrmzfcl",
		"question":"\u6309\u65F6\u95F4\u987A\u5E8F\u6392\u5217\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\uFF1A1\u4E2D\u534E\u82CF\u7EF4\u57C3\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5168\u56FD\u4EE3\u8868\u5927\u4F1A\uFF1B2\u4F2A\u6EE1\u6D32\u56FD\u5EFA\u7ACB\uFF1B3\u56FD\u6C11\u515A\u7B2C\u56DB\u6B21\u56F4\u527F\u88AB\u6253\u7834\uFF1B4\u4E2D\u534E\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u653F\u5E9C\u6210\u7ACB",
		"id":19414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u4F2F\u627F\u3001\u9093\u5C0F\u5E73",
		"indexes":"1947n6ylljjlyjfjzlqlyjdbsds",
		"question":"1947\u5E746\u6708\uFF0C\u7387\u9886\u664B\u5180\u9C81\u8C6B\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u4E3B\u529B\u5343\u91CC\u8DC3\u8FDB\u5927\u522B\u5C71\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19415
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u67082\u65E5",
		"indexes":"1945nrbzsqstjsdsjs",
		"question":"1945\u5E74\u65E5\u672C\u6B63\u5F0F\u7B7E\u7F72\u6295\u964D\u4E66\u7684\u65F6\u95F4\u662F",
		"id":19416
	},
	{
		"answer":"4\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"1940nczgjnbcdzqyjg",
		"question":"1940\u5E74\u6625\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u5883\u5185\u5E76\u5B58\u7684\u653F\u6743\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A",
		"id":19417
	},
	{
		"answer":"1.45\u4EBF\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zljdycgyq205yndgqyqdsn",
		"question":"\u4F8F\u7F57\u7EAA\u5927\u7EA6\u4ECE\u516C\u5143\u524D2.05\u4EBF\u5E74\u5230\u516C\u524D\u5143\u524D\u591A\u5C11\u5E74?",
		"id":19418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"lhgjykxjwhzzslhgzmjgzy1946n11y4rclzbsz",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u6559\u80B2\u3001\u79D1\u5B66\u53CA\u6587\u5316\u7EC4\u7EC7\u662F\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u4E13\u95E8\u673A\u6784\u4E4B\u4E00\u30021946\u5E7411\u67084\u65E5\u6210\u7ACB\uFF0C\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":19419
	},
	{
		"answer":"14",
		"indexes":"qwnplz1794nbrydrjjldst",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u62FF\u7834\u4ED1\u57281794\u5E74\u88AB\u70ED\u6708\u515A\u4EBA\u76D1\u7981\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5929\uFF1F",
		"id":19420
	},
	{
		"answer":"14\u5E74\u591A",
		"indexes":"alsssmzlstczddycplqlsdj",
		"question":"\u5B89\u7984\u5C71\u3001\u53F2\u601D\u660E\u4E4B\u4E71\u662F\u5510\u671D\u6700\u5927\u7684\u4E00\u6B21\u53DB\u4E71\uFF0C\u5176\u5386\u65F6\u591A\u4E45\uFF1A",
		"id":19421
	},
	{
		"answer":"1954\u5E74",
		"indexes":"qzgltcsj",
		"question":"\u9752\u85CF\u516C\u8DEF\u901A\u8F66\u65F6\u95F4",
		"id":19422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C10\u65CF",
		"indexes":"4sjxbqtyhhlydzqsngssmzjld",
		"question":"4\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E0B\u534A\u671F\u7EDF\u4E00\u9EC4\u6CB3\u6D41\u57DF\u7684\u653F\u6743\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684",
		"id":19423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u56FD",
		"indexes":"gyq594nsxcsmamssdgjs",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143\u524D594\u5E74\uFF0C\u5B9E\u884C\u201C\u521D\u7A0E\u4EA9\u201D\uFF0C\u6309\u4EA9\u6536\u7A0E\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19424
	},
	{
		"answer":"94\u5E74",
		"indexes":"Internetwznynjrzg",
		"question":"Internet\u7F51\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8FDB\u5165\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19425
	},
	{
		"answer":"40\u5206\u949F",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzycbsdbsszsxs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u4E00\u573A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u7684\u6BD4\u8D5B\u65F6\u957F\u4E0A\u9650\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F9\u679C",
		"indexes":"yxngsysg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u679C",
		"id":19427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u835E\u9EA6",
		"indexes":"yxngslxsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u51C9\u6027\u98DF\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5170\u82B1",
		"indexes":"nghhbyfrfj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u82B1\u5349\u4E0D\u5B9C\u653E\u5165\u623F\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":19429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u86CB",
		"indexes":"ngswbysc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u98DF\u7269\u4E0D\u5B9C\u751F\u5403\uFF1F",
		"id":19430
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8783\u87F9",
		"indexes":"yxngsyfbycdsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B55\u5987\u4E0D\u5B9C\u5403\u7684\u98DF\u7269",
		"id":19431
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u8C5A",
		"indexes":"yxngdwhyy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u4F1A\u6E38\u6CF3\uFF1F",
		"id":19432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99\u4E95",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbfjc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8336\u662F\u4E0D\u53D1\u9175\u8336\uFF1F",
		"id":19433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u9E21",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsshcs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u662F\u7701\u4F1A\u57CE\u5E02",
		"id":19434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u6E56",
		"indexes":"yxngswgddsh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6DE1\u6C34\u6E56",
		"id":19435
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u94C3\u85AF",
		"indexes":"yxngswszzdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u98DF\u7269\u751F\u957F\u5728\u5730\u4E0B\uFF1F",
		"id":19436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7CB3\u7C73",
		"indexes":"yxngsywg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u8C37\uFF1F",
		"id":19437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u76AE",
		"indexes":"yxngsytrdwp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5929\u7136\u8C03\u5473\u54C1",
		"id":19438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5409\u4ED6",
		"indexes":"yxnzbsyzhmzlq",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u534E\u6C11\u65CF\u4E50\u5668",
		"id":19439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A",
		"indexes":"yxngdwsjc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u5BB6\u755C\uFF1F",
		"id":19440
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21",
		"indexes":"yxngdwbsnl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u9E1F\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u773C\u775B",
		"indexes":"yxngsrdgjqg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4EBA\u7684\u611F\u89C9\u5668\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":19442
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3B\u677F",
		"indexes":"yxngdzyjkyzzdndzjl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u7535\u5B50\u5143\u4EF6\u53EF\u4EE5\u88C5\u5728\u7535\u8111\u7684\u4E3B\u673A\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AA8\u9AD3",
		"indexes":"yxngqgzzlxy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5668\u5B98\u5236\u9020\u4E86\u8840\u6DB2\uFF1F",
		"id":19444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u62C9\u4F2F",
		"indexes":"yxngbswgsyydmz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6240\u62E5\u6709\u7684\u6C11\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":19445
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3C\u6CCA\u5C14",
		"indexes":"yxngswglslg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u9646\u4E0A\u90BB\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u534E\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzzbj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":19447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73AB\u7470",
		"indexes":"yxngzwsygm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u690D\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u704C\u6728\uFF1F",
		"id":19448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E58\u5750\u98DE\u673A",
		"indexes":"yxngcnrdrcxwbxsysfz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u7684\u65E5\u5E38\u884C\u4E3A\u5FC5\u987B\u4F7F\u7528\u8EAB\u4EFD\u8BC1\uFF1F",
		"id":19449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u53C2",
		"indexes":"yxngbsysc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u852C\u83DC\uFF1F",
		"id":19450
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5546\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsgyzyx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u6709\u5236\u94F6\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":19451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8106\u76AE\u4E73\u732A",
		"indexes":"yxngbscc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5DDD\u83DC\uFF1F",
		"id":19452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u5E386+1",
		"indexes":"yxngsmqzydstdlm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u76EE\u524D\u4E2D\u592E\u7535\u89C6\u53F0\u7684\u680F\u76EE",
		"id":19453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u548F",
		"indexes":"yxngsmqzydstdlmzcr",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u76EE\u524D\u4E2D\u592E\u7535\u89C6\u53F0\u7684\u680F\u76EE\u4E3B\u6301\u4EBA",
		"id":19454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u864E",
		"indexes":"yxnzdwsrsdw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u8089\u98DF\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19455
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64AD\u653E\u7535\u5F71",
		"indexes":"yxngbsyzrxx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u81EA\u7136\u73B0\u8C61\uFF1F",
		"id":19456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CA8\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"yxngbsdsy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6DE1\u6C34\u9C7C\uFF1F",
		"id":19457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"dmcbszdfbyzlbtqcsseqdjzxdssmzy",
		"question":"\u675C\u7267<\u8D64\u58C1>\u8BD7\u4E2D\u4E1C\u98CE\u4E0D\u4E0E\u5468\u90CE\u4FBF,\u94DC\u96C0\u6625\u6DF1\u9501\u4E8C\u4E54\u7684\u53E5\u5B50\u5199\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79;.",
		"id":19458
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u751F\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xmnzssbnghd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u79CD\u6C34\u662F\u4E0D\u80FD\u591F\u559D\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8179\u90E8\u624B\u672F\u540E\u7684\u60A3\u8005",
		"indexes":"xmngrbyhnn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5B9C\u559D\u725B\u5976",
		"id":19460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6253\u795D\u5BB6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlgszbssgyyzdyxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6545\u4E8B\u4E2D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u9879\u662F:",
		"id":19461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u534E\u9C9F",
		"indexes":"yxngdwycx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u6709\u89E6\u987B",
		"id":19462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u9633\u51FA\u6765\u559C\u6D0B\u6D0B",
		"indexes":"yxnggqsscmg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u6B4C\u66F2\u662F\u56DB\u5DDD\u6C11\u6B4C",
		"id":19463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FBE\u82AC\u5947\u5BC6\u7801",
		"indexes":"yxngxsbszgzjdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F5C\u5BB6\u7684\u8457\u4F5C",
		"id":19464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7CD6\u918B\u9EC4\u6CB3\u9CA4\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"yxngcysylc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u83DC\u80B4\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9C81\u83DC",
		"id":19465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6843",
		"indexes":"yxngsgzdsctdwg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C34\u679C\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4F20\u7EDF\u7684\u4E94\u679C\uFF1F",
		"id":19466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ECD",
		"indexes":"yxngszgctdwg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F20\u7EDF\u7684\u4E94\u8C37",
		"id":19467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590D\u6D3B\u8282",
		"indexes":"yxbszgctjrds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"ydxxkhraqxrkzdss",
		"question":"\uFF02\u4E00\u4EE3\u67AD\u96C4\uFF0C\u5BBD\u539A\u4EC1\u7231\uFF0C\u6C42\u8D24\u82E5\u6E34\uFF02\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":19469
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73BB\u7483\u7FE0",
		"indexes":"yxnghhshscfz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u82B1\u5349\u9002\u5408\u6C34\u63D2\u7E41\u6B96",
		"id":19470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u559C\u9A6C\u62C9\u96C5\u5C71\u8109",
		"indexes":"xmsyyzsmds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32\u5C71\u8109\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3",
		"indexes":"yxngsyzyzdwz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u533B\u4E2D\u7684\u4E94\u810F",
		"id":19472
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u632F\u5B81",
		"indexes":"yxngrhdgnbewlxj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u7269\u7406\u5B66\u5956",
		"id":19473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u9E45\u6E56",
		"indexes":"qqzmdblwjs",
		"question":"\u5168\u7403\u8457\u540D\u7684\u82AD\u857E\u821E\u5267\u662F",
		"id":19474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50\u767D\u77F3",
		"indexes":"zgjxdzmhjs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u73B0\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":19475
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgyyzdwhsjzds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":19476
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A\u8089\u4E32",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjyxbfw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C0F\u5403\u5177\u6709\u897F\u5317\u98CE\u5473\uFF1F",
		"id":19477
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C89\u5E95",
		"indexes":"yxngsmrhzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7F8E\u5BB9\u5316\u5986\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":19478
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80A5\u7682",
		"indexes":"yxngbscydhfhzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5E38\u7528\u7684\u62A4\u53D1\u5316\u5986\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":19479
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1",
		"indexes":"yxngsgzjs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D35\u91CD\u91D1\u5C5E\uFF1F",
		"id":19480
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u6885",
		"indexes":"yxngsswsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9178\u5473\u98DF\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u6D77",
		"indexes":"hhljyxngsf",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u6CB3\u6D41\u7ECF\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u4EFD\uFF1F",
		"id":19482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5609\u58EB\u4F2F",
		"indexes":"yxngpjbsgypp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5564\u9152\u4E0D\u662F\u56FD\u6709\u54C1\u724C\uFF1F",
		"id":19483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C11\u6797\u529F\u592B",
		"indexes":"yxbsyzxccygddys",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5468\u661F\u9A70\u53C2\u4E0E\u8FC7\u7684\u7535\u5F71\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjcwlscddgx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u59D3\u66FE\u7ECF\u6210\u4E3A\u5386\u53F2\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u56FD\u59D3\uFF1F",
		"id":19485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u52A0\u5761",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsyzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"ngcscjsgdhdddc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u66FE\u7ECF\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\uFF1F",
		"id":19487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u7CAE\u6DB2",
		"indexes":"yxngjcdzsc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9152\u4EA7\u5730\u5728\u56DB\u5DDD\uFF1F",
		"id":19488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u4E1A\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"ngszgyxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u94F6\u884C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FAE\u8F6F",
		"indexes":"ngsITqyzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662FIT\u4F01\u4E1A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u91CF\u5185\u5B58",
		"indexes":"ngsITqyjszy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662FIT\u524D\u6CBF\u6280\u672F\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u9650\u8D23\u4EFB\u516C\u53F8",
		"indexes":"ngsgsqylx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u516C\u53F8\u4F01\u4E1A\u7C7B\u578B\uFF1F",
		"id":19492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u5F53\u52B3",
		"indexes":"ngscjkcdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E38\u89C1\u5FEB\u9910\u5E97\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u949F",
		"indexes":"ngsmdqdsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5356\u7535\u5668\u7684\u5546\u5E97\uFF1F",
		"id":19494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519C\u4E1A",
		"indexes":"ngswdwzscbm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E94\u5927\u7269\u8D28\u751F\u4EA7\u90E8\u95E8\uFF1F",
		"id":19495
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5DE5\u5546\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"ngsgywdyxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u6709\u4E94\u5927\u94F6\u884C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u6E56\u9F99\u4E95",
		"indexes":"ngszgsdmczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u201C\u5341\u5927\u540D\u8336\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19497
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ACB\u6625",
		"indexes":"ngs24jqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F24\u8282\u6C14\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E3",
		"indexes":"ngsxxzrtwgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u76F8\u5B66\u4E2D\u4EBA\u4F53\u4E94\u5B98\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AEF\u5348\u8282",
		"indexes":"ngszgdctjr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\uFF1F",
		"id":19500
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1\u62D0\u674E",
		"indexes":"bxghzdbxynyg",
		"question":"\u516B\u4ED9\u8FC7\u6D77\u4E2D\u7684\u516B\u4ED9\u6709\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5403\u5BD2\u98DF",
		"indexes":"qmsjrmhjxnxhd",
		"question":"\u6E05\u660E\u65F6\u8282\u4EBA\u4EEC\u4F1A\u8FDB\u884C\u54EA\u9879\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":19502
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u2103",
		"indexes":"ngsrtzsydwjwd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u9002\u5B9C\u7684\u5916\u754C\u6E29\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":19503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E3",
		"indexes":"ngsxxzrtwgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u76F8\u5B66\u4E2D\u4EBA\u4F53\u4E94\u5B98\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxngsswyzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C71\u662F\u4E94\u5CB3\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5317\u5E73\u539F",
		"indexes":"ngpywyzg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5E73\u539F\u4F4D\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"ngszgsqjczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7701\u533A\u7B80\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u82CF",
		"indexes":"ngdqymyjj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u533A\u6709\u6885\u96E8\u5B63\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":19509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F0\u98CE",
		"indexes":"ngsyqhzcdzrzh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C14\u5019\u9020\u6210\u7684\u81EA\u7136\u707E\u5BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":19510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u9762\u521D\u671F\u9707\u52A8",
		"indexes":"ngsdzqdyj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5730\u9707\u524D\u7684\u9884\u8B66\uFF1F",
		"id":19511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E8A\u4E0B",
		"indexes":"nlssnbzjaqddf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u91CC\u662F\u5BA4\u5185\u907F\u9707\u8F83\u5B89\u5168\u7684\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":19512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5B63\u4E0D\u5206\u660E",
		"indexes":"rdjfhyxqhyngtz",
		"question":"\u70ED\u5E26\u5B63\u98CE\u6D77\u6D0B\u6027\u6C14\u5019\u6709\u54EA\u4E2A\u7279\u5F81\uFF1F",
		"id":19513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53C8\u53EB\u793E\u98CE",
		"indexes":"nxsdhlfdzqjs",
		"question":"\u54EA\u9879\u662F\u5BF9\u5BD2\u9732\u98CE\u7684\u6B63\u786E\u89E3\u91CA\uFF1F",
		"id":19514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B0\u96F9",
		"indexes":"ngsdnyncswhdqhxx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5BF9\u519C\u4E1A\u80FD\u4EA7\u751F\u5371\u5BB3\u7684\u6C14\u5019\u73B0\u8C61\uFF1F",
		"id":19515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u539F\u610F\u4E3A\u5723\u5A74",
		"indexes":"ngdeenndjszq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5BF9\u5384\u5C14\u5C3C\u8BFA\u7684\u89E3\u91CA\u6B63\u786E\uFF1F",
		"id":19516
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E72\u51B0",
		"indexes":"rgjyszlyzbshzwz",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u5DE5\u964D\u96E8\u662F\u5728\u51B7\u4E91\u4E2D\u64AD\u6492\u4F55\u79CD\u7269\u8D28\uFF1F",
		"id":19517
	},
	{
		"answer":"60-100\u6B21",
		"indexes":"yxngplfwsyzcrmfzxtplfw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9891\u7387\u8303\u56F4\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6B63\u5E38\u4EBA\u6BCF\u5206\u949F\u5FC3\u8DF3\u9891\u7387\u8303\u56F4\uFF1F",
		"id":19518
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u5206",
		"indexes":"yxngmzbsmqzzltdrmbmz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9762\u503C\u4E0D\u662F\u76EE\u524D\u6B63\u5728\u6D41\u901A\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u9762\u503C\uFF1F",
		"id":19519
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u7EA7",
		"indexes":"ngsyrddytfdjb",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u70ED\u5E26\u4F4E\u538B\u53F0\u98CE\u7684\u7EA7\u522B\uFF1F",
		"id":19520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngscyd31jtfwyhtfmmhddgjhdq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53C2\u4E0E\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u53F0\u98CE\u547D\u540D\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u548C\u5730\u533A\uFF1F",
		"id":19521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u5154",
		"indexes":"ngsd31jtfwyhzsmmdtfmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u4E2D\u6240\u547D\u540D\u7684\u53F0\u98CE\u540D\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":19522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u609F\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"ngsd31jtfwyhzzgsmmdtfmzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u4E2D\u4E2D\u56FD\u6240\u547D\u540D\u7684\u53F0\u98CE\u540D\u5B57\u6709\uFF1F",
		"id":19523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70ED\u5E26\u96E8\u6797\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"zlyjwz15ysdsynzqh",
		"question":"\u6700\u51B7\u6708\u5747\u6E29\u572815\u2103\u4EE5\u4E0A\u7684\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54EA\u79CD\u6C14\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u8272",
		"indexes":"sdssmys",
		"question":"\u95EA\u7535\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u989C\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":19525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u5C14\u5351\u65AF\u5C71",
		"indexes":"ffhcxzsmdf",
		"question":"\u711A\u98CE\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":19526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u5B57\u5854",
		"indexes":"xlnygjgbsybj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u89C2\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":19527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlngjqsy24jq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8282\u6C14\u5C5E\u4E8E24\u8282\u6C14\uFF1F",
		"id":19528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64",
		"indexes":"ngsrlrykykddqcg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4EBA\u7C7B\u8089\u773C\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u5230\u7684\u4E03\u5F69\u5149\uFF1F",
		"id":19529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E72\u65F1",
		"indexes":"ngsdwgyxzddqxzh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5BF9\u6211\u56FD\u5F71\u54CD\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6C14\u8C61\u707E\u5BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":19530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u6DC0",
		"indexes":"xlngsbjsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u5E02\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E8A\u4E0B",
		"indexes":"nlssnbzjaqddf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u91CC\u662F\u5BA4\u5185\u907F\u9707\u8F83\u5B89\u5168\u7684\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":19532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5B63\u4E0D\u5206\u660E",
		"indexes":"rdjfhyxqhyngtz",
		"question":"\u70ED\u5E26\u5B63\u98CE\u6D77\u6D0B\u6027\u6C14\u5019\u6709\u54EA\u4E2A\u7279\u5F81\uFF1F",
		"id":19533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53C8\u53EB\u793E\u98CE",
		"indexes":"nxsdhlfdzqjs",
		"question":"\u54EA\u9879\u662F\u5BF9\u5BD2\u9732\u98CE\u7684\u6B63\u786E\u89E3\u91CA\uFF1F",
		"id":19534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u539F\u610F\u4E3A\u5723\u5A74",
		"indexes":"ngdeenndjszq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5BF9\u5384\u5C14\u5C3C\u8BFA\u7684\u89E3\u91CA\u6B63\u786E\uFF1F",
		"id":19535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E72\u51B0",
		"indexes":"rgjyszlyzbshzwz",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u5DE5\u964D\u96E8\u662F\u5728\u51B7\u4E91\u4E2D\u64AD\u6492\u4F55\u79CD\u7269\u8D28\uFF1F",
		"id":19536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u8272",
		"indexes":"sdssmys",
		"question":"\u95EA\u7535\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u989C\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":19537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u5C14\u5351\u65AF\u5C71",
		"indexes":"ffhcxzsmdf",
		"question":"\u711A\u98CE\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":19538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u5B57\u5854",
		"indexes":"xlnygjgbsybj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u89C2\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":19539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlngjqsy24jq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8282\u6C14\u5C5E\u4E8E24\u8282\u6C14\uFF1F",
		"id":19540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64",
		"indexes":"ngsrlrykykddqcg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4EBA\u7C7B\u8089\u773C\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u5230\u7684\u4E03\u5F69\u5149\uFF1F",
		"id":19541
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"xlsyzrsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u81EA\u7136\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19542
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"xlsyqsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5947\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19543
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlsyosdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5076\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u2160",
		"indexes":"xlsylmszdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7F57\u9A6C\u6570\u5B57\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B49\u4E8E\u53F7",
		"indexes":"xlsygxfhdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5173\u7CFB\u7B26\u53F7\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19546
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlsyzsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8D28\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5206\u4E4B\u4E94",
		"indexes":"xlsyjfsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5047\u5206\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlsyzddwdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u957F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19549
	},
	{
		"answer":"33",
		"indexes":"xlnb3zcdssnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u80FD\u88AB3\u6574\u9664\u7684\u6570\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19550
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"xlsyhsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5408\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19551
	},
	{
		"answer":".",
		"indexes":"xlsycxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7EAF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlsysjdwdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19553
	},
	{
		"answer":"3.4",
		"indexes":"xlsydxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5E26\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u5206\u4E4B\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"xlsyzfsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u771F\u5206\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5206\u4E4B\u5341\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"xlsykyhczsdfssnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5316\u6210\u6574\u6570\u7684\u5206\u6570\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u5206\u4E4B\u56DB",
		"indexes":"xlsyzjfsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6700\u7B80\u5206\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19557
	},
	{
		"answer":"35\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsydyxxdjdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u8C61\u9650\u7684\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19558
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"xlkykpfgdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u53EF\u4EE5\u5F00\u5E73\u65B9\u6839\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19559
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.333\u2026\u2026",
		"indexes":"xlsyxhxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5FAA\u73AF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19560
	},
	{
		"answer":"54\u00B0\u548C36\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwyjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u4F59\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9\uFF1F",
		"id":19561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsdlzdddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u5EA6\u91CF\u957F\u5EA6\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5428",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8D28\u91CF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u65B9\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsymjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9762\u79EF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ACB\u65B9\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsytjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F53\u79EF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsypmjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5E73\u9762\u89D2\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u514B\/\u7C733",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsymddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BC6\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsysjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u7C73\/\u5C0F\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsysddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u901F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FBE\u56E0",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsylddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u529B\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19570
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"xlnygssqs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5947\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19571
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlnygssos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5076\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19572
	},
	{
		"answer":"9",
		"indexes":"xlnygsqs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5947\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A0\u53F7",
		"indexes":"xlnygssxysfh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u8FD0\u7B97\u7B26\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":19574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731",
		"indexes":"mcdgxs",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u7684\u56FD\u59D3\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":19575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u65F6\u73CD",
		"indexes":"bcgmdzzw",
		"question":"\u300A\u672C\u8349\u7EB2\u76EE\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u4E3A\uFF1F",
		"id":19576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C01\u5EFA\u5236\u5EA6\u7684\u8150\u673D",
		"indexes":"ywydsbdgbyyzy",
		"question":"\u6D0B\u52A1\u8FD0\u52A8\u5931\u8D25\u7684\u6839\u672C\u539F\u56E0\u5728\u4E8E\uFF1F",
		"id":19577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D1\u52A8\u6B66\u88C5\u8D77\u4E49",
		"indexes":"zcjjgmpmcdzgmzgmddybs",
		"question":"\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u6D3E\u8FC8\u51FA\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u4E3B\u9769\u547D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B65\u662F?",
		"id":19578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"ngssgwhsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8700\u56FD\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":19579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E59\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E42\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"bzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5315\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"jzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E5D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5341\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"bzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u535C\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19586
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"szyyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E00\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19587
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"szsyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E09\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19588
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"szwyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E94\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19589
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"szlyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u516D\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19590
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"szqyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E03\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19591
	},
	{
		"answer":"9",
		"indexes":"szjyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E5D\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A",
		"indexes":"yxsybrdwds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"dzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E01\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"qzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E03\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"qzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"czyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5DDD\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E49\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19598
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E5F\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58F9",
		"indexes":"szyyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E00\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19600
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53C1",
		"indexes":"szsyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E09\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0D",
		"indexes":"szwyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E94\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67D2",
		"indexes":"szqyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E03\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7396",
		"indexes":"szjyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E5D\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1",
		"indexes":"yxsyjsds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u91D1\u5C5E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"gzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5E72\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E8E\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0A\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"xzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0B\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"wzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5348\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"rzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u58EC\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5347\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u592D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"zzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u957F\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19615
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"szeyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E8C\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19616
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"szsyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u56DB\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19617
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"szbyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u516B\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u52C7",
		"indexes":"xmsybycds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":19619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"fzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E30\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"kzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5F00\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"jzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E95\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"fzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u592B\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"tzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5143\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"wzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E0\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"bzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u751F\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":19628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D30",
		"indexes":"szeyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E8C\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8086",
		"indexes":"szsyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u56DB\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646",
		"indexes":"szlyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u516D\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u634C",
		"indexes":"szbyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u516B\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":19632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u4E0D\u97E6",
		"indexes":"xmsbsshczdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u6C34\u6D52\u4F20\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73\u5362",
		"indexes":"sllzgddycdrsjbjsjd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u7387\u9886\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u6253\u5165\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5",
		"id":19634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u878D",
		"indexes":"ngsjaqzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u5BBE\u72AC",
		"indexes":"xlnzgsydxq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u72D7\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u578B\u72AC",
		"id":19636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718A\u7334",
		"indexes":"xlnzdwsylzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7075\u957F\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269",
		"id":19637
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DF\u8681\u517D",
		"indexes":"xlnzdwystbzlw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u7528\u820C\u5934\u6355\u6349\u730E\u7269",
		"id":19638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u6D32\u72EE",
		"indexes":"nzdwsymkdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u732B\u79D1\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u8747",
		"indexes":"nzczsykc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u866B\u5B50\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E26\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"nzdwsyyl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9C7C\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u8C5A",
		"indexes":"nzbrdwshzhl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6D77\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":19642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyscdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8349\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19643
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21",
		"indexes":"nzdwrydqlg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5BB9\u6613\u5F97\u79BD\u6D41\u611F?",
		"id":19644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"xlnyzsfxlkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u98DE\u884C\u7C7B\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19645
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8682\u8681",
		"indexes":"xlnyzkcshzdb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u5730\u8868?",
		"id":19646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u873B\u8713",
		"indexes":"xlnyzkcsyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u662F\u76CA\u866B?",
		"id":19647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8749",
		"indexes":"yxnygsyhjdcz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F1A\u201C\u53EB\u201C\u7684\u866B\u5B50?",
		"id":19648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u873B\u8713",
		"indexes":"xlnzsgldkczy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u6606\u866B\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":19649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u4E2D\u751F\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"xlnygskcshcszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6606\u866B\u751F\u6D3B\u573A\u6240\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":19650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D88\u706D\u866B\u6E90",
		"indexes":"yxnygsxmzldff",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6D88\u706D\u87D1\u8782\u7684\u65B9\u6CD5?",
		"id":19651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u873B\u8713",
		"indexes":"xlnygbssrrlansxjbhbytdkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u9A9A\u6270\u4EBA\u7C7B\u5B89\u5B81,\u542E\u5438\u75BE\u75C5\u548C\u75C5\u539F\u4F53\u7684\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u8747",
		"indexes":"nzczsykc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u866B\u5B50\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E26\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"nzdwyl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u9C7C\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u873B\u8713",
		"indexes":"xlnzsgldkczy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u6606\u866B\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":19655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u4E2D\u751F\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"xlnygskcshcszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6606\u866B\u751F\u6D3B\u573A\u6240\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":19656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u79CB",
		"indexes":"yxngbsyessjq",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u8282\u6C14\uFF1F",
		"id":19657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u897F",
		"indexes":"xlnggjsymz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7F8E\u6D32",
		"id":19658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82AC\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnggjsyoz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32",
		"id":19659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u86D9",
		"indexes":"xlnzdwsylqdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E24\u6816\u52A8\u7269",
		"id":19660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u8D3C",
		"indexes":"xlnzshszzwdhjgbstdysd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u4F1A\u968F\u7740\u5468\u56F4\u7684\u73AF\u5883\u6539\u53D8\u8EAB\u4F53\u7684\u989C\u8272\u7684",
		"id":19661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u6867",
		"indexes":"zglssdhjsng",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u6C49\u5978\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u4EA5",
		"indexes":"sywghddsnw",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EA1\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u90A6",
		"indexes":"sykghddsnw",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C9F\u88D5",
		"indexes":"zgsddjsnw",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5341\u5927\u5927\u5C06\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u7A46\u516C",
		"indexes":"sycqwbdsnw",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6625\u79CB\u4E94\u9738\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nggjsyzgqxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"xlnwsyzgsdys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05",
		"id":19668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"nwszgsdyszy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u534E\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlngsahdlyjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B89\u5FBD\u7684\u65C5\u6E38\u666F\u533A",
		"id":19670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F13\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"xlngsgxdlyjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E7F\u897F\u7684\u65C5\u6E38\u666F\u533A",
		"id":19671
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5C71\u5929\u6C60",
		"indexes":"xlngsxjdlyjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u65B0\u7586\u7684\u65C5\u6E38\u666F\u533A",
		"id":19672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC\u6545\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlngsysjwdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E16\u754C\u4E94\u5927\u5BAB",
		"id":19673
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u6C49\u4E1C\u6E56",
		"indexes":"xlngshbdlyjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6E56\u5317\u7684\u65C5\u6E38\u666F\u533A",
		"id":19674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9890\u548C\u56ED",
		"indexes":"bjsysjwhycdjdsng",
		"question":"\u5317\u4EAC\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E16\u754C\u6587\u5316\u9057\u4EA7\u7684\u666F\u70B9\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u660E\u5A01",
		"indexes":"cjhdnbewxjdsnw",
		"question":"\u66FE\u7ECF\u83B7\u5F97\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u6587\u5B66\u5956\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DF\u95E8\u70DF\u6811",
		"indexes":"syyjbjdsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u71D5\u4EAC\u516B\u666F\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5B66",
		"indexes":"syzcnbejdzldsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6700\u521D\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u7684\u79CD\u7C7B\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC",
		"indexes":"xlnwssjzmdylj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u8457\u540D\u7684\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6",
		"id":19679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"xlngrszgzmwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6",
		"id":19680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54E5\u767D\u5C3C",
		"indexes":"xlnwssjzmdkxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u8457\u540D\u7684\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6",
		"id":19681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u96C1",
		"indexes":"nznsyhn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5019\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8725\u8734",
		"indexes":"nzdwsypxl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u722C\u884C\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u773C\u775B\u738B\u86C7",
		"indexes":"ntszgcdds",
		"question":"\u54EA\u6761\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EA7\u7684\u6BD2\u86C7\uFF1F",
		"id":19684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u8747",
		"indexes":"nzkcsyhc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BB3\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19685
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718A",
		"indexes":"nzdwdm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u51AC\u7720\uFF1F",
		"id":19686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u888B\u9F20",
		"indexes":"nzdwyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u6709\u888B\uFF1F",
		"id":19687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68D5\u6988\u6811",
		"indexes":"shzrddzw",
		"question":"\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u70ED\u5E26\u7684\u690D\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u9A7C",
		"indexes":"shzsmldsw",
		"question":"\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6C99\u6F20\u91CC\u7684\u751F\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u888B\u9F20",
		"indexes":"nzdwshzadly",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6FB3\u5927\u5229\u4E9A\uFF1F",
		"id":19690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732B\u5934\u9E70",
		"indexes":"nzdwslsdtd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u53EA\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u8001\u9F20\u7684\u5929\u654C\uFF1F",
		"id":19691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u6781\u718A",
		"indexes":"nzdwshzbj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u5317\u6781\uFF1F",
		"id":19692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u677E",
		"indexes":"nwslshh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6881\u5C71\u597D\u6C49\uFF1F",
		"id":19693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u5B97\u5B9D",
		"indexes":"nwsyjjzdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6768\u5BB6\u5C06\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8336\u9986",
		"indexes":"nbxsslsdmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u90E8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u662F\u8001\u820D\u7684\u540D\u8457\uFF1F",
		"id":19695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u8282",
		"indexes":"ngjrszgctjr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8282\u65E5\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\uFF1F",
		"id":19696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nggjcyyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32?",
		"id":19697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5170",
		"indexes":"nggjcyoz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32?",
		"id":19698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u975E",
		"indexes":"nggjcyfz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32?",
		"id":19699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u897F",
		"indexes":"nggjcymz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u7F8E\u6D32?",
		"id":19700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6FB3\u5927\u5229\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"nggjcydyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u5927\u6D0B\u6D32?",
		"id":19701
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F4\u6CB9\u673A\u8F66",
		"indexes":"tygszyzzscngcp",
		"question":"\u901A\u7528\u516C\u53F8\u4E3B\u8981\u5236\u9020\u751F\u4EA7\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EA7\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":19702
	},
	{
		"answer":"VISA",
		"indexes":"ngssjwdxykzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u4E94\u5927\u4FE1\u7528\u5361\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u5357",
		"indexes":"ngszgwdjjtqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E94\u5927\u7ECF\u6D4E\u7279\u533A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D44\u4EA7",
		"indexes":"ngshjdwdflzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4F1A\u8BA1\u7684\u4E94\u5927\u5206\u7C7B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngssjwdjjqgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u4E94\u5927\u7ECF\u6D4E\u5F3A\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19706
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9152",
		"indexes":"nzsjdjyflzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u9152\u7684\u7ECF\u8425\u5206\u7C7B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngsgj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"ngsbjgjz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51\uFF1F",
		"id":19709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6492\u54C8\u62C9\u6C99\u6F20",
		"indexes":"ngssjsdsmzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u5341\u5927\u6C99\u6F20\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532",
		"indexes":"ngstgdmczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5929\u5E72\u7684\u540D\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u85CF\u9AD8\u539F",
		"indexes":"nggywyyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u9AD8\u539F\u4F4D\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32\uFF1F",
		"id":19712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u897F",
		"indexes":"ngsszgzzqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B",
		"indexes":"ngsgdbjcdcyzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u8868\u656C\u79F0\u7684\u8BCD\u8BED\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u677E\u5AE9\u5E73\u539F",
		"indexes":"ngszgzyspljdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E3B\u8981\u5546\u54C1\u7CAE\u57FA\u5730\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u575B",
		"indexes":"ngsbjdjdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u7684\u666F\u70B9\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u952E\u76D8",
		"indexes":"ngsdnyjzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7535\u8111\u786C\u4EF6\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99",
		"indexes":"ngswxqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E94\u5F62\u62F3\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u62C7\u6307",
		"indexes":"ngsszch",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u624B\u6307\u79F0\u547C\uFF1F",
		"id":19719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C11\u6797",
		"indexes":"ngswdmpzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E94\u5927\u95E8\u6D3E\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"ngssdyszy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C",
		"indexes":"ngsjwzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7235\u4F4D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"ngschdyszy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5F69\u8679\u7684\u989C\u8272\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE1\u65CF",
		"indexes":"ngswslssmzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E94\u5341\u516D\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC\u665A\u62A5",
		"indexes":"ngsbjdbkzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u7684\u62A5\u520A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u65B9\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"ngszgqdfyzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E03\u5927\u65B9\u8A00\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"ngszgbdcxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u516B\u5927\u83DC\u7CFB\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19727
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5D47\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"ngszlqxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7AF9\u6797\u4E03\u8D24\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5B50",
		"indexes":"ngscqzgzzbjzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u6218\u56FD\u8BF8\u5B50\u767E\u5BB6\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u540E\u5510",
		"indexes":"ngswdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E94\u4EE3\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434",
		"indexes":"ngssgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5341\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"ngswr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6587\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngsezffxstmgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E8C\u6218\u53CD\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u540C\u76DF\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngsezzxgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E8C\u6218\u8F74\u5FC3\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C88\u94A7\u5112",
		"indexes":"ngsjghqjzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6551\u56FD\u4F1A\u201C\u4E03\u541B\u5B50\u201C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19735
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9E\u96C4",
		"indexes":"ngshhg72lszy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9EC4\u82B1\u5C9772\u70C8\u58EB\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u79C0\u5170",
		"indexes":"ngsbntjrwzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u516B\u5973\u6295\u6C5F\u4EBA\u7269\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"ngszxlyzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7AF9\u6EAA\u516D\u9038\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u91D1\u6606",
		"indexes":"ngsjlwlzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u91D1\u9675\u4E94\u8001\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngseztmgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E8C\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"ngslcgdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u516D\u671D\u53E4\u90FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u83BA",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykyfdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u98DE\u7684\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9738\u738B\u9F99",
		"indexes":"xlnygsysrkl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8089\u6050\u9F99\uFF1F",
		"id":19743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"nzdwzzsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u7AD9\u7740\u7761\u89C9?",
		"id":19744
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73CA\u745A\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"nzyshzhl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6D77\u91CC?",
		"id":19745
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u534E\u9C9F",
		"indexes":"nzyshzdsl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6DE1\u6C34\u91CC?",
		"id":19746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E35\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"nznbhf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u4E0D\u4F1A\u98DE?",
		"id":19747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u661F",
		"indexes":"nzsyjpdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u68D8\u76AE\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7261\u86CE",
		"indexes":"nzsyrtdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8F6F\u4F53\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19749
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u9E25",
		"indexes":"nzsyhn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6D77\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7070\u559C\u9E4A",
		"indexes":"nznsyyn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u76CA\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B47\u65AF\u5E95\u91CC",
		"indexes":"yxngsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":19752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927",
		"indexes":"xmngzbsdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u4E0D\u662F\u591A\u97F3\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":19753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71AC",
		"indexes":"ngsdyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u591A\u97F3\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":19754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C2D\u55E3\u540C",
		"indexes":"wxljzzdsng",
		"question":"\u201C\u620A\u620C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8336\u9986",
		"indexes":"ngbslxdzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":19756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u5251\u6069\u4EC7\u5F55",
		"indexes":"ngbsjydxs",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u91D1\u5EB8\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4\uFF1F",
		"id":19757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u514B\u601D",
		"indexes":"ngbszgdsxj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B\u5C0F\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"ngbsshzdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u6C34\u6D52\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19759
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8424\u706B\u866B",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyqcmdkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9798\u7FC5\u76EE\u7684\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8682\u8681",
		"indexes":"xlnzsymcmdkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u819C\u7FC5\u76EE\u7684\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8749\u7684\u5E7C\u866B",
		"indexes":"nyzkcsztrzscd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u662F\u5728\u571F\u58E4\u4E2D\u751F\u5B58\u7684?",
		"id":19762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DF3\u86A4",
		"indexes":"xlnzsyjslkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BC4\u751F\u7C7B\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"xlnyzkcyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u6606\u866B\u6709\u6BD2?",
		"id":19764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9676\u5BB6\u9A79",
		"indexes":"xlnygsywgdkcxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6606\u866B\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":19765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D8\u8272\u9F99",
		"indexes":"yxnyzczkybhzjdst",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u866B\u5B50\u53EF\u4EE5\u53D8\u5316\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u8EAB\u4F53?",
		"id":19766
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u5149\u706F",
		"indexes":"zxsyjscjdscfssnyg",
		"question":"\u5728\u5B66\u672F\u7814\u7A76\u65F6\u5E38\u89C1\u7684\u641C\u866B\u65B9\u5F0F\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":19767
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6355\u8747\u8349",
		"indexes":"nyzzwskcdtd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u690D\u7269\u662F\u6606\u866B\u7684\u5929\u654C?",
		"id":19768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u96C0",
		"indexes":"nyzdwskcdtd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u6606\u866B\u7684\u5929\u654C?",
		"id":19769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DF3\u86A4",
		"indexes":"nyzsyhdkc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u6709\u5BB3\u7684\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u866B\u590F\u8349",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyykc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u836F\u7528\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8749",
		"indexes":"xlnygsytcmkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u540C\u7FC5\u76EE\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u868A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsylcmkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E24\u7FC5\u76EE\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykcdgmfl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B\u7684\u5404\u76EE\u5206\u7C7B?",
		"id":19774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u9646",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyyxkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u533B\u5B66\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u773C\u8702",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyyxkcdtd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u533B\u5B66\u6606\u866B\u7684\u5929\u654C\uFF1F",
		"id":19776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"xlnygskzshdkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u7A7A\u4E2D\u751F\u6D3B\u7684\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D30",
		"indexes":"xlsywgddxszdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u5927\u5199\u6570\u5B57\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19778
	},
	{
		"answer":"6\u548C35",
		"indexes":"xlsyhzsdsnyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u8D28\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u7EC4\uFF1F",
		"id":19779
	},
	{
		"answer":".333\u2026\u2026",
		"indexes":"xlsycxhxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7EAF\u5FAA\u73AF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":19780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94B1\u5B66\u68EE",
		"indexes":"xlnywssxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnywszgsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19782
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6C14\u538B",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyylddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u538B\u529B\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u529B",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyglddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u529F\u7387\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u57F9",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsydclddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7535\u78C1\u91CF\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7126\u8033",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsynlddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u80FD\u91CF\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7535\u78C1\u4EA8\u5229",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsydgddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7535\u611F\u7684\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyszdzddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5E02\u5236\u7684\u957F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62C5",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyszdzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5E02\u5236\u7684\u8D28\u91CF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5206\u8D1D",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyyxdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u97F3\u54CD\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19790
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlnygss20yndzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F20\u4EE5\u5185\u7684\u8D28\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52FA",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyszdrljldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5E02\u5236\u7684\u5BB9\u91CF\u8BA1\u91CF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlngszggdzmdsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u7F57\u5E9A",
		"indexes":"xlngszgjxdzmdsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u73B0\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u85E4\u6E05",
		"indexes":"xlngsjjxdzmdsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E16\u754C\u8FD1\u73B0\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u65AF",
		"indexes":"xlnygssxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":19796
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlnygszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u8D28\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19797
	},
	{
		"answer":"230",
		"indexes":"xlnygsnbwzc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u80FD\u88AB\u4E94\u6574\u9664\uFF1F",
		"id":19798
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u7684\u5E73\u65B9\u6839",
		"indexes":"xlnygsbsss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u4E0D\u662F\u5B9E\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5706\u67F1\u4F53",
		"indexes":"xlnygsltjhtx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u7ACB\u4F53\u51E0\u4F55\u56FE\u5F62\uFF1F",
		"id":19800
	},
	{
		"answer":"30\u5EA6\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlnygjsrj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u89D2\u662F\u9510\u89D2\uFF1F",
		"id":19801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u4E00\u4E2A\u89D2\u662F\u76F4\u89D2\u7684\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62",
		"indexes":"xlnygszjsjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u76F4\u89D2\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\uFF1F",
		"id":19802
	},
	{
		"answer":"32",
		"indexes":"xlnygss2ddccfsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F2\u7684\u591A\u6B21\u4E58\u65B9\u6570\u503C\uFF1F",
		"id":19803
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"xlnygss2h3dgbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F2\u548C3\u7684\u516C\u500D\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19804
	},
	{
		"answer":"35",
		"indexes":"xlnygssyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u6709\u7406\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":19805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u7F8E\u6D32\u677F\u5757",
		"indexes":"xlnygs8dbkzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F8\u5927\u677F\u5757\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19806
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"xlnygsrjsxdjdzzwjzdnr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u601D\u60F3\u7684\u7ECF\u5178\u8457\u4F5C\u300A\u4E94\u7ECF\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":19807
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5143\u748B\u7684\u7236\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"zmdsqmydghdshbzfwhdjzlydsnw",
		"question":"\u5728\u660E\u4EE3\u751F\u524D\u6CA1\u6709\u5F53\u8FC7\u7687\u5E1D\u6B7B\u540E\u88AB\u8FFD\u5C01\u4E3A\u7687\u5E1D\u5EFA\u9020\u9675\u56ED\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":19808
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u9053\u591A\u96E8\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"xlnygsydjwqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F4E\u7ECF\u7EAC\u6C14\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u526F\u70ED\u5E26\u5E72\u65F1\u4E0E\u534A\u5E72\u65F1\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyzjwqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u7ECF\u7EAC\u6C14\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":19810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"nygszgdsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u9996\u90FD?",
		"id":19811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u7403",
		"indexes":"nygszmdxt",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u8457\u660E\u7684\u661F\u4F53?",
		"id":19812
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u661F",
		"indexes":"ngsyjdxx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u5927\u884C\u661F\uFF1F",
		"id":19813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u5B66\u4EF7\u503C",
		"indexes":"ngsylyzydjz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65C5\u6E38\u8D44\u6E90\u7684\u4EF7\u503C",
		"id":19814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u627F\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"xlngshbsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CB3\u5317\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5305\u5934",
		"indexes":"xlngsnmgzzqddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5185\u8499\u53E4\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u539F",
		"indexes":"xlngssxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C71\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6613\u53BF",
		"indexes":"xlngslnsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8FBD\u5B81\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"xlngsjssddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6C5F\u82CF\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngszjsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6D59\u6C5F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19820
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u978D\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlngsahsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B89\u5FBD\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19821
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u660C",
		"indexes":"xlngsjxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19822
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5143",
		"indexes":"xlngsfjsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u798F\u5EFA\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19823
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D4E\u5357",
		"indexes":"xlngssdsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C71\u4E1C\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19824
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u6D77",
		"indexes":"xlngsgdsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E7F\u4E1C\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19825
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u6797",
		"indexes":"xlngsgxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E7F\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19826
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5747\u53BF",
		"indexes":"xlngshbsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6E56\u5317\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19827
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6843\u6E90",
		"indexes":"xlngshnsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6E56\u5357\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19828
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlngshnsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CB3\u5357\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19829
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6210\u90FD",
		"indexes":"xlngsscsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56DB\u5DDD\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19830
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6606\u660E",
		"indexes":"xlngsynsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E91\u5357\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19831
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62C9\u8428",
		"indexes":"xlngsxzzzqddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u897F\u85CF\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19832
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xlngssxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9655\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19833
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5170\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngsgssddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7518\u8083\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19834
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"xlngsnxhzzzqddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B81\u590F\u56DE\u65CF\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19835
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"xlngsxjsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u65B0\u7586\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19836
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F0\u5317",
		"indexes":"xlngstwddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53F0\u6E7E\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19837
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u548C\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlngsbjggzdgjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u6545\u5BAB\u4E2D\u7684\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51?",
		"id":19838
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C38\u5B89\u5BFA",
		"indexes":"xlngsbjbhzdgjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u5317\u6D77\u4E2D\u7684\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51?",
		"id":19839
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5929\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlngsbjttzdgjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u5929\u575B\u4E2D\u7684\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51?",
		"id":19840
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u5170\u514B\u798F",
		"indexes":"xmngcszdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u5FB7\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":19841
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"xmngcszrb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u65E5\u672C\uFF1F",
		"id":19842
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BDB\u5CB8\u82F1",
		"indexes":"nwlsskmyczcsxsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u70C8\u58EB\u662F\u6297\u7F8E\u63F4\u671D\u6218\u573A\u4E0A\u727A\u7272\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19843
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C48\u539F",
		"indexes":"nwsagwr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u7231\u56FD\u6587\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":19844
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5929\u7965",
		"indexes":"nwsmzyx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6C11\u65CF\u82F1\u96C4\uFF1F",
		"id":19845
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5B58\u745E",
		"indexes":"nwlssjfzzzxsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u70C8\u58EB\u662F\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u727A\u7272\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19846
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u9756\u5B87",
		"indexes":"nwlsskrzzzxsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u70C8\u58EB\u662F\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u727A\u7272\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19847
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F7F\u8F6E",
		"indexes":"ngsghdnr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5FBD\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":19848
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"ngsgqswjxdhy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u65D7\u4E0A\u4E94\u89D2\u661F\u7684\u542B\u4E49\uFF1F",
		"id":19849
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5929\u57F9",
		"indexes":"nwswqyqlzdzzxsdyx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u665A\u6E05\u4E0E\u4FB5\u7565\u8005\u6597\u4E89\u4E2D\u727A\u7272\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\uFF1F",
		"id":19850
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C2D\u55E3\u540C",
		"indexes":"nwswxljzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u620A\u620C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":19851
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC\u6761\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"ngsqzftqlzqddbpdty",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u540C\u4FB5\u7565\u8005\u7B7E\u8BA2\u7684\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":19852
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"nygkcsyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u662F\u76CA\u866B?",
		"id":19853
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68C9\u94C3\u866B",
		"indexes":"nygkcshc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u662F\u5BB3\u866B?",
		"id":19854
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5544\u6728\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"nyznsyn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u9E1F\u662F\u76CA\u9E1F?",
		"id":19855
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u626C\u5B50\u9CC4?",
		"indexes":"nyzsgjyjbhdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E00\u7EA7\u4FDD\u62A4\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19856
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7315\u7334?",
		"indexes":"nyzsgjejbhdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E8C\u7EA7\u4FDD\u62A4\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19857
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718A\u7334",
		"indexes":"nyzssl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u517D\u7C7B?",
		"id":19858
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CC4\u8725",
		"indexes":"nyzslqpxdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u4E24\u6816\u722C\u884C\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19859
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F69\u9E73?",
		"indexes":"nyzsnl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u9E1F\u7C7B?",
		"id":19860
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732B\u72D7\u5927\u6218",
		"indexes":"xlnybdyjsdsdwdgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u7535\u5F71\u8BB2\u8FF0\u7684\u662F\u52A8\u7269\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\uFF1F",
		"id":19861
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u730E\u8C79",
		"indexes":"xlnygsymkdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u732B\u79D1\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19862
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E21\u6E21\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyjmjddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5DF2\u7ECF\u706D\u7EDD\u7684\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19863
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u975E\u6D32\u72EE",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyfzdrsdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32\u7684\u8089\u98DF\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19864
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B\u7F9A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyfzcsdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32\u8349\u98DF\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19865
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E35\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyfzddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32\u7684\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19866
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5317\u864E",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyyzdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19867
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u718A\u732B",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyzxdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u73CD\u7A00\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6BCD",
		"indexes":"xlnygsywjzdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65E0\u810A\u690E\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9C7C\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u4E1D\u96C0",
		"indexes":"xlnygsynl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9E1F\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u86C7",
		"indexes":"xlnygbsyrtdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8F6F\u4F53\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19872
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7231\u6155\u65AF\u6210\u72AC",
		"indexes":"xlnzgbsydxq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u72D7\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u578B\u72AC\uFF1F",
		"id":19873
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u6708\u795E\u4ED9",
		"indexes":"xlnyzbsyrdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u70ED\u5E26\u9C7C\uFF1F",
		"id":19874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u722A\u6C99\u9F20",
		"indexes":"xlnyzbsylzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7075\u957F\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A7C\u9E7F",
		"indexes":"xlnyzsygbjddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u5317\u754C\u7684\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A",
		"indexes":"xlnyzsyotldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5076\u8E44\u7C7B\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u9CD7\u8788",
		"indexes":"xlnyzbsypxdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u722C\u884C\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73CA\u745A",
		"indexes":"xlnzsqcdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u8154\u80A0\u52A8\u7269",
		"id":19879
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A\u516B\u6212",
		"indexes":"xlnygrwdmzzxyjzsydwmmd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u5728\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u4E2D\u662F\u4EE5\u52A8\u7269\u547D\u540D\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u73CA\u745A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsygjyjbhdhydw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E00\u7EA7\u4FDD\u62A4\u7684\u6D77\u6D0B\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u83BA",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykyfdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u98DE\u7684\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyscdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8349\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9738\u738B\u9F99",
		"indexes":"xlnygsysrkl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8089\u6050\u9F99\uFF1F",
		"id":19884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21",
		"indexes":"nzdwrydqlg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u5BB9\u6613\u5F97\u79BD\u6D41\u611F?",
		"id":19885
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u529B\u66FC\u9ED1\u5BE1\u5987",
		"indexes":"nzzzyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u8718\u86DB\u6709\u6BD2?",
		"id":19886
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"nzdwzzsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u7AD9\u7740\u7761\u89C9?",
		"id":19887
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72FC",
		"indexes":"nzdwxhqj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u559C\u6B22\u7FA4\u5C45?",
		"id":19888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73CA\u745A\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"nzyshzhl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6D77\u91CC?",
		"id":19889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u534E\u9C9F",
		"indexes":"nzyshzdsl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6DE1\u6C34\u91CC?",
		"id":19890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u8475",
		"indexes":"nzsyqcdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8154\u80A0\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E35\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"nznbhf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u4E0D\u4F1A\u98DE?",
		"id":19892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u661F",
		"indexes":"nzsyjpdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u68D8\u76AE\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7261\u86CE",
		"indexes":"nzsyrtdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8F6F\u4F53\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u96C1",
		"indexes":"nzsysqnl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u6816\u9E1F\u7C7B?",
		"id":19895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u867E",
		"indexes":"nzsyjzdw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8282\u80A2\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":19896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u9E6E",
		"indexes":"nzsyzxnl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u73CD\u7A00\u9E1F\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":19897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u9E25",
		"indexes":"nzsyhn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6D77\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7070\u559C\u9E4A",
		"indexes":"nznsyyn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u76CA\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":19899
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8774\u8776",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":19900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u873B\u8713",
		"indexes":"ngkchf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u4F1A\u98DE\uFF1F",
		"id":19901
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8757\u866B",
		"indexes":"ngkcbhf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u4E0D\u4F1A\u98DE\uFF1F",
		"id":19902
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u8747",
		"indexes":"ngkcshc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u662F\u5BB3\u866B?",
		"id":19903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"ngkcsyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6606\u866B\u662F\u76CA\u866B?",
		"id":19904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u6E20\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"syyzbjzdsnz",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E<<\u6C38\u5DDE\u516B\u8BB0>>\u4E2D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD?",
		"id":19905
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B11\u91CC\u85CF\u5200",
		"indexes":"syssljdsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E09\u5341\u516D\u8BB0\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":19906
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"qzcnywsfxyjldrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u975E\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u91CC\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB3\u98DE",
		"indexes":"qzcnywswgdmzyx",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6C11\u65CF\u82F1\u96C4?",
		"id":19908
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"qzcnygswgdgdcd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u53E4\u4EE3\u671D\u4EE3?",
		"id":19909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"qzcwgdcssnyg",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":19910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u7EE7\u5149",
		"indexes":"qscnygrwwwgkzsqdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u8BF4\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u4E3A\u6211\u56FD\u6297\u6218\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"nygcsbswgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":19912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u660E\u4E09\u5343\u91CC",
		"indexes":"czzwhxbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u65E9\u671B\u6D77\u971E\u8FB9>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19913
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u4E0A\u592A\u767D\u5CF0",
		"indexes":"czdtbfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767B\u592A\u767D\u5CF0>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EE\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnygsysrdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8089\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19915
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A7C",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyssdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7D20\u98DF\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":19916
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"nygssgyylmdsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u91CC\u9762\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":19917
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u53F0\u90BB\u56DB\u660E",
		"indexes":"czttxwdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5929\u53F0\u6653\u671B>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19918
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u73E0\u6563\u8F7B\u971E",
		"indexes":"czwlspbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19919
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5C14\u66FC",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":19920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u6C5D\u9716",
		"indexes":"nywrwsmgz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u662F\u5356\u56FD\u8D3C?",
		"id":19921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E54\u5BB6\u5927\u9662",
		"indexes":"nybzpbsyzgwtddy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u6587\u575B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00",
		"id":19922
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167",
		"indexes":"nywrwsyzgwtddy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u6587\u575B\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00",
		"id":19923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E8C\u5C0F\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"nybsygkrzzdrwgshyp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6709\u5173\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u6545\u4E8B\u6216\u5F71\u7247?",
		"id":19924
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u96EA\u82B9",
		"indexes":"nywsqcdsr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u6E56\u9634\u5148\u751F\u58C1",
		"indexes":"czywasdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E<<\u738B\u5B89\u77F3>>\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u767B\u5170\u5C71\u5BC4\u5F20\u4E94",
		"indexes":"czymhrdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E<<\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136>>\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u591C\u559C\u96E8",
		"indexes":"czydfdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u675C\u752B\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8776\u604B\u82B1",
		"indexes":"czyoyxdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u601D",
		"indexes":"czylbdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u674E\u767D\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u9898",
		"indexes":"czylsydssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u674E\u5546\u9690\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u51C0\u6C99\u79CB\u601D",
		"indexes":"nybsyq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5143\u66F2?",
		"id":19932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7435\u7436\u884C",
		"indexes":"czybjydssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19933
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u55BB",
		"indexes":"nyzsxcff",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u4FEE\u8F9E\u65B9\u6CD5?",
		"id":19934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u522B",
		"indexes":"czywwdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u738B\u552F\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19935
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE8\u6C5F\u9053",
		"indexes":"nygdqbsbjddm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5730\u533A\u4E0D\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":19936
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FA\u6028",
		"indexes":"czywcldssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19937
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8774\u8776",
		"indexes":"xldwnygsykc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u52A8\u7269\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":19938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u5357\u6625",
		"indexes":"czydmdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u675C\u7267\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7965\u6797\u5AC2",
		"indexes":"nywrwsxszxgdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u662F\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u865A\u6784\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u96EA",
		"indexes":"czylzydssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u5F8C\u70DF\u666F\u7EFF",
		"indexes":"czlryszdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u843D\u65E5\u5FC6\u5C71\u4E2D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u5143\u8C01\u592B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"czsyfrdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E0A\u5143\u592B\u4EBA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"qzcnywstcdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"qzcnywsscdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u671B\u9EC4\u9E64\u5C71",
		"indexes":"czwhhldsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u671B\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D62\u653F",
		"indexes":"nywskghd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":19947
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nygsrjxpdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u5B66\u6D3E\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5112",
		"indexes":"nygsxqsddxslp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u65F6\u4EE3\u7684\u5B66\u672F\u6D41\u6D3E?",
		"id":19949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u6CC9\u6620\u758F\u677E",
		"indexes":"czwyyhdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u671B\u6708\u6709\u6000>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"qzcnywsscdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u5CB8\u733F\u58F0\u557C\u4E0D\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"qzcnyssjbsczlbds",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u9996\u8BD7\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":19952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"nywsqcdhd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":19953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u5411\u4E1C\u5C71\u4E45",
		"indexes":"czydsesdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5FC6\u4E1C\u5C71\u4E8C\u9996>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8700\u56FD\u591A\u4ED9\u5C71",
		"indexes":"czdemsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767B\u5CE8\u5D4B\u5C71>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929",
		"indexes":"qzcnywstcdhd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":19956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nygsrjxpdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u5B66\u6D3E\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u53D1\u56DB\u8001\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"czssshdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5546\u5C71\u56DB\u7693>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"qzcnywsscdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19959
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BBF\u53E4\u767B\u5C98\u9996",
		"indexes":"czxshgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5C98\u5C71\u6000\u53E4>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9999",
		"indexes":"xmngssxjgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":19961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5230",
		"indexes":"xmngszyjgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":19962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CA6\u8001\u5367\u6C5F\u6D77",
		"indexes":"czyxsstdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6E38\u8C22\u6C0F\u5C71\u4EAD>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u884C\u6B4C\u5165\u8C37\u53E3",
		"indexes":"czcrylftdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6625\u65E5\u6E38\u7F57\u6577\u6F6D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75",
		"indexes":"wybjxzqwgxszdsng",
		"question":"\u4F4D\u4E8E\u767E\u5BB6\u59D3\u4E2D\u524D\u4E94\u4E2A\u59D3\u6C0F\u4E2D\u7684\u662F\u90A3\u4E2A?",
		"id":19965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6743",
		"indexes":"nywssgyyzdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u962E\u5C0F\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"nywsshzdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u6C34\u6D52\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60DC\u5F7C\u843D\u65E5\u66AE",
		"indexes":"czynyqlqdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6E38\u5357\u9633\u6E05\u6CE0\u6CC9>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u9E7F\u5954\u91CE\u8349",
		"indexes":"czdgwgzchgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767B\u5E7F\u6B66\u53E4\u6218\u573A\u6000\u53E4>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u8C03\u6B4C\u5934",
		"indexes":"czyssdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E<<\u82CF\u8F7C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3B\u8BED",
		"indexes":"syjzjgdsnz",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E5\u5B50\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD?",
		"id":19971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5982\u68A6\u4EE4",
		"indexes":"czylqzdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E<<\u674E\u6E05\u7167>>\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":19972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6C5F\u56DE\u4E07\u91CC",
		"indexes":"czjlwhjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u91D1\u9675\u671B\u6C49\u6C5F>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DB\u9F99\u6816\u5BD2\u95E8",
		"indexes":"czbfxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5317\u98CE\u884C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F85\u6708\u6708\u672A\u51FA",
		"indexes":"czgxjsdyyhdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6302\u5E2D\u6C5F\u4E0A\u5F85\u6708\u6709\u6000>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u697C\u89C2\u5CB3\u9633\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"czyxsedyyldsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E0E\u590F\u5341\u4E8C\u767B\u5CB3\u9633\u697C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DA4\u8361\u5343\u53E4\u6101",
		"indexes":"czyrhsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u53CB\u4EBA\u4F1A\u5BBF>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u58F6\u7CFB\u9752\u4E1D",
		"indexes":"czdjbzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5F85\u9152\u4E0D\u81F3>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19978
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u8349\u5982\u6709\u610F",
		"indexes":"czdzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u72EC\u914C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"nywsqcdhd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":19980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D62\u653F",
		"indexes":"nywskghd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":19981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529D\u541B\u83AB\u62D2\u676F",
		"indexes":"czdjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BF9\u9152>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u884C\u81F3\u5546\u6D1B",
		"indexes":"czgshmdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8FC7\u56DB\u7693\u5893>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F6E\u9152\u5EF6\u843D\u666F",
		"indexes":"czjlfhtzjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u91D1\u9675\u51E4\u51F0\u53F0\u7F6E\u9152>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5BAB\u6C34\u897F\u5BFA",
		"indexes":"czysxjzmfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6E38\u6C34\u897F\u7B80\u90D1\u660E\u5E9C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929",
		"indexes":"qzcnywstcdhd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":19986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"qzcnywsscdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":19987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u5CB8\u733F\u58F0\u557C\u4E0D\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"qzcnyssjbsczlbds",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u9996\u8BD7\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":19988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nygsrjxpdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u5B66\u6D3E\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":19989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5112",
		"indexes":"nygsxqsddxslp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u65F6\u4EE3\u7684\u5B66\u672F\u6D41\u6D3E?",
		"id":19990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B4C\u9F13\u71D5\u8D75\u513F",
		"indexes":"czhdntgjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u90AF\u90F8\u5357\u4EAD\u89C2\u5993>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u695A\u81E3\u4F24\u6C5F\u67AB",
		"indexes":"cztyrzxytyzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u540C\u53CB\u4EBA\u821F\u884C\u6E38\u53F0\u8D8A\u4F5C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u5BB0\u8BD5\u821F\u696B",
		"indexes":"czqyyldsfyxtcdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u79CB\u591C\u4E0E\u5218\u7800\u5C71\u6CDB\u5BB4\u559C\u4EAD\u6C60>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71D5\u8349\u5982\u78A7\u4E1D",
		"indexes":"czcsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6625\u601D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":19994
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B4C\u8C23",
		"indexes":"ywkfwnz",
		"question":"\u97F5\u6587\u53EF\u5206\u4E3A\u54EA\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":19995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C9C\u82B1\u513F",
		"indexes":"ngkycyhjehy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u53EF\u4EE5\u8BCD\u8BED\u540E\u52A0\u201C\u513F\u201D\u8BDD\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":19996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u5507\u97F3",
		"indexes":"afybwjsmflngszqd",
		"question":"\u6309\u53D1\u97F3\u90E8\u4F4D\u7ED9\u58F0\u6BCD\u5206\u7C7B\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":19997
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u585E\u97F3",
		"indexes":"afyffflsmkfwnz",
		"question":"\u6309\u53D1\u97F3\u65B9\u6CD5\u5206\u7C7B\u58F0\u6BCD\u53EF\u5206\u4E3A\u54EA\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":19998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdzhidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684zhi\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":19999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdzidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684zi\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5403",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdchidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684chi\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B21",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdcidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684ci\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20002
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdshidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684shi\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1D",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdsidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684si\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66FE",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdengdfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684eng\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u771F",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdendfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684en\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E94",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdingdfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684ing\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E0",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdindfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684in\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20008
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"yxnwsqchd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":20009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5143\u748B",
		"indexes":"xlnwsmchd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u660E\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":20010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E",
		"indexes":"xlnggjcjgbgljhsymy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53C2\u52A0\u8FC7\u516B\u56FD\u8054\u519B\uFF0C\u706B\u70E7\u5706\u660E\u56ED\uFF1F",
		"id":20011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5B89\u95E8",
		"indexes":"nzshccm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u5EA7\u662F\u7687\u57CE\u57CE\u95E8\uFF1F",
		"id":20012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EE7",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684i\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20013
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8116",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqd0dfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u76840\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624D",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdaidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684ai\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88AB",
		"indexes":"xlngwzqdeidfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E3A\u6B63\u786E\u7684ei\u7684\u53D1\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":20016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5566",
		"indexes":"ngsqsc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8F7B\u751F\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7684",
		"indexes":"ngszc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u52A9\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8840\u6DB2",
		"indexes":"xlngcyydcxess",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u8BED\u5E94\u8BFB\u6210x\u00F9e\uFF08\u56DB\u58F0\uFF09",
		"id":20019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8840\u8113",
		"indexes":"xlngcyydcxiss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u8BED\u5E94\u8BFB\u6210xi\u011B\uFF08\u4E09\u58F0\uFF09",
		"id":20020
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54E5\u54E5",
		"indexes":"ngsydzmc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E0\u5B57\u540D\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20021
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u542C\u542C",
		"indexes":"ngsydzdc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E0\u5B57\u52A8\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20022
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73B2\u73D1",
		"indexes":"lmcdegyjbdqsdsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u7EF5\u8BCD\u7B2C\u4E8C\u4E2A\u97F3\u8282\u4E0D\u8BFB\u8F7B\u58F0\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20023
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59AF\u5A0C",
		"indexes":"lmcdegyjdqsdsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u7EF5\u8BCD\u7B2C\u4E8C\u4E2A\u97F3\u8282\u8BFB\u8F7B\u58F0\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20024
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C1",
		"indexes":"ngzsypzxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54C1\u5B57\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20025
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u601D",
		"indexes":"ngzsysxxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F",
		"indexes":"ngzsyszxxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E2D\u4E0B\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60EB",
		"indexes":"ngzsyszxxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E2D\u4E0B\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20028
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6751",
		"indexes":"ngzsyzyxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20029
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8857",
		"indexes":"ngzsyzzyxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u4E2D\u53F3\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5706",
		"indexes":"ngzsyqbwxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5168\u5305\u56F4\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u533B",
		"indexes":"ngzsybbwxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u534A\u5305\u56F4\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B0",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssbd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u51AB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE9",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u6C35\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BA8",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u8BA0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssdd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5202\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519B",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssmd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5196\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5B80\uFF1F",
		"id":20038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C37",
		"indexes":"ngzsybzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u5B57\u65C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20039
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED3",
		"indexes":"ngzsyrzt",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EBA\u5B57\u5934\uFF1F",
		"id":20040
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u539F",
		"indexes":"ngzsyczp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5382\u5B57\u65C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52B3",
		"indexes":"ngzsylzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u529B\u5B57\u65C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8270",
		"indexes":"ngzsyyzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53C8\u5B57\u65C1?",
		"id":20043
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EFD",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssrd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u4EBB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20044
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5374",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssjd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5369\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20045
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u961F",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssfzzd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u961D\uFF08\u5728\u5DE6\uFF09\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20046
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E5",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssbd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u52F9\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79C1",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u53B6\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20048
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5321",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssfd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u531A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5188",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssjd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5182\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F71",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5F61\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6084",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssxd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5FC4\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20052
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E95",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5E7F\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A6",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssxd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5915\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9080",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsscd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u8FB6\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C01",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsscd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5BF8\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6253",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u624C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20057
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BED\u8A00",
		"indexes":"dbjsjllgdnxzxmdngnr",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u5DF4\u7ECF\u4E66\u8BB0\u5F55\u4E86\u53E4\u4EE3\u7EB3\u897F\u65CF\u5148\u6C11\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":20058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u9AA8\u6587",
		"indexes":"zgwzdybdtjllngjd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6587\u5B57\u7684\u6F14\u53D8\uFF0C\u5927\u4F53\u7ECF\u5386\u4E86\u54EA\u4E2A\u9636\u6BB5\uFF1F",
		"id":20059
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BC6",
		"indexes":"ngsyszgsfdzt",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E66\u6CD5\u7684\u5B57\u4F53\uFF1F",
		"id":20060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u53E4\u65CF",
		"indexes":"chzwngmzyzjdwz",
		"question":"\u9664\u6C49\u5B57\u5916\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u6709\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u6587\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20061
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u81EA\u7531\u201D",
		"indexes":"mgynjxgsjzzpxhdhdtmds",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u4E8E\uFF12\uFF10\uFF10\uFF10\u5E74\u4E3E\u884C\u8FC7\u201C\u4E16\u7EAA\u4E4B\u5B57\u201D\u8BC4\u9009\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF0C\u83B7\u5F97\u63D0\u540D\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F0B",
		"indexes":"ngssyrydcdhz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BB9\u6613\u8BFB\u9519\u7684\u6C49\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20063
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59EC",
		"indexes":"ngswggldxszmcjygynxwzxdsh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u59D3\u6C0F\uFF0C\u8BC1\u660E\u66FE\u7ECF\u6709\u8FC7\u4EE5\u5973\u6027\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5FC3\u7684\u793E\u4F1A\uFF1F",
		"id":20064
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8884",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u8863\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5979",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssnd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5973\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793E",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u793A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u6587",
		"indexes":"zggwznrbjffdsnzwz",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u53E4\u6587\u5B57\uFF0C\u5185\u5BB9\u6BD4\u8F83\u4E30\u5BCC\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u6587\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u4E61",
		"indexes":"ngcydysszwyldjyddys",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u8BED\u7684\u610F\u601D\uFF0C\u662F\u505A\u4E3A\u201C\u539F\u6765\u7684\u201D\u201C\u65E7\u6709\u7684\u201D\u7684\u610F\u601D\uFF1F",
		"id":20069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u53BB",
		"indexes":"ngcydysszwswdyjbzddys",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u8BED\u7684\u610F\u601D\uFF0C\u662F\u505A\u4E3A\u201C\u6B7B\u4EA1\u7684\uFF0C\u5DF2\u7ECF\u4E0D\u5728\u7684\u201D\u7684\u610F\u601D\uFF1F",
		"id":20070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9093",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssfzyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u961D\uFF08\u5728\u53F3\uFF09\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20071
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u55BB",
		"indexes":"ngsyxcg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4FEE\u8F9E\u683C\uFF1F",
		"id":20072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u8BED",
		"indexes":"ngsylhgyy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u8BED\u8A00\uFF1F",
		"id":20073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u55BB",
		"indexes":"btxcsfyng",
		"question":"\u6807\u9898\u4FEE\u8F9E\u624B\u6CD5\uFF0C\u6709\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ED9",
		"indexes":"ngzsdyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u662F\u591A\u97F3\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71",
		"indexes":"ngzsxxz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u662F\u8C61\u5F62\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DD1\u6B65",
		"indexes":"ngcsdc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u52A8\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F0\u706F",
		"indexes":"ngcsmc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u540D\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u6F88",
		"indexes":"ngcsxrc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u5F62\u5BB9\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6309\u6B65\u5C31\u73ED",
		"indexes":"ngclmycbz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u91CC\u9762\u6709\u9519\u522B\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u55BB",
		"indexes":"ngsxcff",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4FEE\u8F9E\u65B9\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":20081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u4E3D",
		"indexes":"ngsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20082
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u611A\u8822",
		"indexes":"ngsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":20083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77E5\u4E66\u8FBE\u793C",
		"indexes":"ngscy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6210\u8BED\uFF1F",
		"id":20084
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u501F\u5C38\u8FD8\u9B42",
		"indexes":"ngcysssljzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED\u662F\u4E09\u5341\u516D\u8BA1\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A2A",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdybsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E00\u7B14\u662F\u6A2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20086
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6606",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdybss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E00\u7B14\u662F\u7AD6\uFF1F",
		"id":20087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdybsp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E00\u7B14\u662F\u6487\uFF1F",
		"id":20088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdybsn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E00\u7B14\u662F\u637A\uFF1F",
		"id":20089
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdybsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E00\u7B14\u662F\u6298\uFF1F",
		"id":20090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdebsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E8C\u7B14\u662F\u6A2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20091
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A2A",
		"indexes":"xlnygzktdebss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5B57\u5F00\u5934\u7B2C\u4E8C\u7B14\u662F\u7AD6\uFF1F",
		"id":20092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5450\u558A",
		"indexes":"nybslxzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u58EB\u5854",
		"indexes":"nybsyqyzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u4F59\u79CB\u96E8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u9A7C\u7965\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nybslszp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u8001\u820D\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20095
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u51E1\u8BFA\u592B",
		"indexes":"nybsqhfzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5951\u8BC3\u592B\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20096
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE5\u5E74",
		"indexes":"nybsgejzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u9AD8\u5C14\u57FA\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20097
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u57CE\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"nybscesdgszp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u67E5\u5C14\u65AF\u00B7\u72C4\u66F4\u65AF\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20098
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7686\u5927\u6B22\u559C",
		"indexes":"nybsssbyzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u9B47",
		"indexes":"nybszalzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5F20\u7231\u73B2\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u6DE1\u751F\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"nybshyzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6D77\u5CA9\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20101
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u57CE\u51B3",
		"indexes":"nybsjyzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u91D1\u5EB8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20102
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5858\u6708\u8272",
		"indexes":"nybszzqzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6731\u81EA\u6E05\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u4F60\u4E00\u5339\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"nybssmzp",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u4E09\u6BDB\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20104
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u6708\u51FA\u5929\u5C71",
		"indexes":"czmydgsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u660E\u6708\u5EA6\u5173\u5C71>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u5BA2\u7F26\u80E1\u7F28",
		"indexes":"czxkxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4FA0\u5BA2\u884C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20106
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"qzcnywstcdsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":20107
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5219\u5929",
		"indexes":"qzcnywstcdhd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":20108
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u9601\u6A2A\u79C0\u6C14",
		"indexes":"czgcbzstdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8FC7\u5D14\u516B\u4E08\u6C34\u4EAD>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20109
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u843D\u6C99\u660E\u5929\u5012\u5F00",
		"indexes":"czdlmfzesdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E1C\u9C81\u95E8\u6CDB\u821F\u4E8C\u9996>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20110
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u9E23\u53D1\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"czsxhdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BBF\u867E\u6E56>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20111
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5723\u8FBE\u6709\u53BB\u5C31",
		"indexes":"czjnltwssdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u7EAA\u5357\u9675\u9898\u4E94\u677E\u5C71>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6628\u591C\u5DEB\u5C71\u4E0B",
		"indexes":"czswsxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BBF\u5DEB\u5C71\u4E0B>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB1\u5B97\u592B\u5982\u4F55",
		"indexes":"czwydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u671B\u5CB3>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20114
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u90E1\u8D8B\u5EAD\u65E5",
		"indexes":"czdgzcldsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767B\u886E\u5DDE\u57CE\u697C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u9A6C\u5927\u5B9B\u540D",
		"indexes":"czfbchmdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u623F\u5175\u66F9\u80E1\u9A6C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D20\u7EC3\u98CE\u971C\u8D77",
		"indexes":"czhydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u753B\u9E70>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20117
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF2\u4ECE\u62DB\u63D0\u6E38",
		"indexes":"czylmfxsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6E38\u9F99\u95E8\u5949\u5148\u5BFA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20118
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5E74\u5BA2\u4E1C\u90FD",
		"indexes":"czzlbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u8D60\u674E\u767D\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6797\u7EA4\u6708\u843D",
		"indexes":"czyyzszdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u591C\u5BB4\u5DE6\u6C0F\u5E84>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u85E9\u4F4F\u7682\u76D6",
		"indexes":"czplbhylxtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u966A\u674E\u5317\u6D77\u5BB4\u5386\u4E0B\u4EAD>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20121
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u4FAF\u6709\u4F73\u53E5",
		"indexes":"czylsebtxfsyjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E0E\u674E\u5341\u4E8C\u767D\u540C\u5BFB\u8303\u5341\u9690\u5C45>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC2\u5BDE\u4E66\u658B\u91CC",
		"indexes":"czdryhlbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u51AC\u65E5\u6709\u6000\u674E\u767D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u65E5\u6F58\u6000\u53BF",
		"indexes":"czjryfxhbscmfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E5D\u65E5\u6768\u5949\u5148\u4F1A\u767D\u6C34\u5D14\u660E\u5E9C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20124
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u60B2\u9E3F",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgxddhj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u4EE3\u7684\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":20125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgxddzj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u4EE3\u7684\u4F5C\u5BB6?",
		"id":20126
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u543E\u8205\u653F\u5982\u6B64",
		"indexes":"czbsmfjzxydgzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767D\u6C34\u660E\u5E9C\u8205\u5B85\u559C\u96E8\uFF0C\u5F97\u8FC7\u5B57>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u4F5C\u6CB3\u897F\u5C09",
		"indexes":"czgdhxzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5B98\u5B9A\u5F8C\u620F\u8D60>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u4E0D\u89C1\u97B2\u4E0A\u9E70",
		"indexes":"czqyxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u53BB<<\u77E3\u884C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20129
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5C71\u6C14\u9E3F\u8499",
		"indexes":"czftgjstdlqzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5949\u540C\u90ED\u7ED9\u4E8B\u6C64\u4E1C\u7075\u6E6B\u4F5C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5802\u4E0A\u4E0D\u5408\u751F\u67AB\u6811",
		"indexes":"czfxlsfxhsszgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5949\u5148\u5218\u5C11\u5E9C\u65B0\u753B\u5C71\u6C34\u969C\u6B4C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20131
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u9675\u6709\u5E03\u8863",
		"indexes":"czzjffxxyhwbzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u81EA\u4EAC\u8D74\u5949\u5148\u53BF\u548F\u6000\u4E94\u767E\u5B57>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20132
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97F3",
		"indexes":"xmngszqdindfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684in\u7684\u53D1\u97F3?",
		"id":20133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xmngszqdendfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684en\u7684\u53D1\u97F3?",
		"id":20134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963FQ",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywslxxszdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E1.\u9AD8",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgdhj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5916\u56FD\u7684\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":20136
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671D\u5149\u5165\u74EE\u7256",
		"indexes":"czhrxcjlfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6666\u65E5\u5BFB\u5D14\u6222\u674E\u5C01>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20137
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9119\u592B\u884C\u8870\u8C22",
		"indexes":"czslfclhxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u9001<<\u7387\u5E9C\u7A0B\u5F55\u8FD8\u4E61>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20138
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA2\u4ECE\u5357\u53BF\u6765",
		"indexes":"czbsxcsfsjwgzssydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767D\u6C34\u53BF\u5D14\u5C11\u5E9C\u5341\u4E5D\u7FC1\u9AD8\u658B\u4E09\u5341\u97F5>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20139
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u7ECF\u534E\u539F\u6765",
		"indexes":"czscgszesydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E09\u5DDD\u89C2\u6C34\u6DA8\u4E8C\u5341\u97F5>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u907F\u5730\u5C81\u65F6\u665A",
		"indexes":"czbdxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u907F\u5730\u4E0B>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5B89\u57CE\u5934\u5934\u767D\u4E4C",
		"indexes":"czawsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u54C0\u738B\u5B59>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C11\u9675\u91CE\u8001\u541E\u58F0\u54ED",
		"indexes":"czajtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u54C0\u6C5F\u5934>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u51AC\u5341\u90E1\u826F\u5BB6\u5B50",
		"indexes":"czbctdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u60B2\u9648\u9676>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u519B\u9752\u962A\u5728\u4E1C\u95E8",
		"indexes":"czbqbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u60B2\u9752\u962A>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u54ED\u591A\u65B0\u9B3C",
		"indexes":"czdxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BF9\u96EA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FA\u4E2D\u53EA\u72EC\u770B",
		"indexes":"czyydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6708\u591C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u7AE0\u6709\u795E\u4EA4\u6709\u9053",
		"indexes":"czxdxfyjxhzgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u859B\u7AEF\u859B\u590D\u7B75\u7B80\u859B\u534E\u9189\u6B4C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u95FB\u97E6\u6C0F\u59B9",
		"indexes":"czyrjwsmdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5143\u65E5\u5BC4\u97E6\u6C0F\u59B9>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20149
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u7834\u5C71\u6CB3\u5728",
		"indexes":"czcwdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6625\u671B>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20150
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AA5\u5B50\u6625\u72B9\u9694",
		"indexes":"czyyzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5FC6\u5E7C\u5B50>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u5CB1\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnywswgdzxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u54F2\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlnyzswgnfdcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5357\u65B9\u7684\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":20153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72D7",
		"indexes":"xlnygssesx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5341\u4E8C\u5C5E\u76F8?",
		"id":20154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DD\u9A6C\u7F9A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygsyjmjddw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5DF2\u7ECF\u706D\u7EDD\u7684\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":20155
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5A1C\u00B7\u5361\u5217\u5C3C\u5A1C",
		"indexes":"qzcnygbsyfgzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u68B5\u9AD8\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20156
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u5BB6\u5BF9\u5BD2\u98DF",
		"indexes":"czybwrydydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E00\u767E\u4E94\u65E5\u591C\u5BF9\u6708>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AA5\u5B50\u597D\u7537\u513F",
		"indexes":"czqxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9063\u5174>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20158
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u57CE\u4F55\u8FE2\u8FE2",
		"indexes":"czslzxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u585E\u82A6\u5B50>>\u4E0B\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u9A7C\u7965\u5B50",
		"indexes":"qzcnygbsybxdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u51B0\u5FC3\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95F2\u60C5",
		"indexes":"qzcnygsybxdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u51B0\u5FC3\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u68F5\u4E1D\u67CF\u6811",
		"indexes":"qzcnygsyfgzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u68B5\u9AD8\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u9E23\u98CE\u96E8\u4EA4",
		"indexes":"czygsddsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u96E8\u8FC7\u82CF\u7AEF>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u5929\u4E45\u4E0D\u96E8",
		"indexes":"czxqdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u559C\u6674>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793E\u620F",
		"indexes":"qzcxgnybslxdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u66F4\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BDB\u6CFD\u4E1C",
		"indexes":"qzcxgnywswgjgcqdgjldr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u66F4\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5EFA\u56FD\u521D\u671F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA?",
		"id":20166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u65AF\u798F",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywsmgdzt",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u603B\u7EDF?",
		"id":20167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8C13\u751F\u620E\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"czzfmctxyzgwtydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u90D1\u9644\u9A6C\u6C60\u53F0\u559C\u9047\u90D1\u5E7F\u6587\u540C\u996E>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53BB\u5E74\u6F7C\u5173\u7834",
		"indexes":"czshdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8FF0\u6000>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20169
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u65D7\u6E20",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnybswgxddzz",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u73B0\u4EE3\u7684\u8457\u4F5C?",
		"id":20170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6241\u9E4A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddyxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u533B\u5B66\u5BB6",
		"id":20171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B\u987F",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywskxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53BB\u51ED\u6E38\u5BA2\u5BC4",
		"indexes":"czdjsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u5F97\u5BB6\u4E66\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u5F27\u4E0D\u80FD\u5F26",
		"indexes":"czfesssyfhzpgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6A0A\u4E8C\u5341\u4E09\u5BFA\u5FA1\u8D74\u6C49\u4E2D\u5224\u5B98>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7FB2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddsfj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u4E66\u6CD5\u5BB6?",
		"id":20175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F18\u5386",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgqcdhd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":20176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddwj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u6B66\u5C06?",
		"id":20177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AA2\u9A6C\u65B0\u51FF\u8E44",
		"indexes":"czszsjsyfwwpgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u957F\u5B59\u4E5D\u4F8D\u5FA1\u8D74\u6B66\u5A01\u5224\u5B98>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u98CE\u4F5C\u79CB\u58F0",
		"indexes":"czscdyfhxpgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u4ECE\u5F1F\u4E9A\u8D74\u6CB3\u897F\u5224\u5B98>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u7231\u4F60",
		"indexes":"xmngszwdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E3B\u8C13\u77ED\u8BED?",
		"id":20180
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6253\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xmngsdbdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u52A8\u5BBE\u77ED\u8BED?",
		"id":20181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"xmngsbjdxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5DF4\u91D1\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4?",
		"id":20182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6614\u6CA1\u8D3C\u4E2D\u65F6",
		"indexes":"czswslpsctgjfypgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u97E6\u5341\u516D\u8BC4\u4E8B\u5145\u540C\u8C37\u90E1\u9632\u5FA1\u5224\u5B98>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u8FDC\u79CB\u98CE\u843D",
		"indexes":"czsylpgsxfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u6768\u516D\u5224\u5B98\u4F7F\u897F\u8543>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FAF\u80E1\u8165\u56DB\u6D77",
		"indexes":"czslzlpgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u7075\u5DDE\u674E\u5224\u5B98>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03",
		"indexes":"xmnyssdtmslbd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u9996\u8BD7\u7684\u9898\u76EE\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684?",
		"id":20186
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u5CB3",
		"indexes":"xmnyssdtmsdfd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u9996\u8BD7\u7684\u9898\u76EE\u662F\u675C\u752B\u7684?",
		"id":20187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u5C14\u53CD\u5C14",
		"indexes":"nygcsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":20188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u853C\u53EF\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"nygcsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":20189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6248\u5723\u767B\u9EC4\u9601",
		"indexes":"czfzybgldsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5949\u8D60\u4E25\u516B\u9601\u8001>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u4E0A\u79CB\u671F\u8FD1",
		"indexes":"czydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6708>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C1A\u4E66",
		"indexes":"nygsysswj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E<<\u56DB\u4E66>><<\u4E94\u7ECF>>?",
		"id":20192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u4E59\u5DF1",
		"indexes":"nybxsslxxd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u5199\u7684?",
		"id":20193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u80DC",
		"indexes":"nygswggdnmqydlx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u9886\u8896?",
		"id":20194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u8272\u8427\u8427\u66AE",
		"indexes":"czcydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6751\u591C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5DDD\u4E0D\u53EF\u5230",
		"indexes":"czwxkhdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u665A\u884C\u53E3\u53F7>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706F\u82B1\u4F55\u592A\u559C",
		"indexes":"czdzcsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u72EC\u914C\u6210\u8BD7>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u751F\u672A\u82CF\u606F",
		"indexes":"czjdseydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5EFA\u90FD\u5341\u4E8C\u97F5>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u747E",
		"indexes":"xlnygszgjdsdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u4EE3\u53F2\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20199
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987A\u6CBB",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygsqcdnh",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u5E74\u53F7?",
		"id":20200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u679C",
		"indexes":"xlnywsfgdwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6CD5\u56FD\u7684\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F46\u897F",
		"indexes":"xlnywsydlwsfxsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u610F\u5927\u5229\u6587\u4E16\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u5CAD\u7686\u708E\u70ED",
		"indexes":"czjywgztdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BC4\u6768\u4E94\u6842\u5DDE\u8C2D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u9601\u5B98\u6885\u52A8\u8BD7\u5174",
		"indexes":"czhpddszdtskfzmxyjjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u548C\u88F4\u8FEA\u767B\u8700\u5DDE\u4E1C\u4EAD\u9001\u5BA2\u9022\u65E9\u6885\u76F8\u5FC6\u89C1\u5BC4>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C06\u519B\u80C6\u6C14\u96C4",
		"indexes":"czjzwsjjcjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BC4\u8D60\u738B\u5341\u5C06\u519B\u627F\u4FCA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529B\u75BE\u5750\u6E05\u6653",
		"indexes":"czfclddbzzczdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5949\u916C\u674E\u90FD\u7763\u8868\u4E08\u65E9\u6625\u4F5C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u51FA\u78A7\u9E21\u574A",
		"indexes":"czxjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u897F\u90CA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u820D\u5357\u820D\u5317\u7686\u6625\u6C34",
		"indexes":"czkzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BA2\u81F3>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u597D\u96E8\u77E5\u65F6\u8282",
		"indexes":"czcyxydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6625\u591C\u559C\u96E8>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3A\u4EBA\u6027\u50FB\u803D\u4F73\u53E5",
		"indexes":"czjszsrhsldsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6C5F\u4E0A\u503C\u6C34\u5982\u6D77\u52BF\u804A\u77ED\u8FF0>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u6781\u6625\u57CE\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"cztxjbqldjzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9898\u65B0\u6D25\u5317\u6865\u697C\u5F97\u90CA\u5B57>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u50E7\u6765\u4E0D\u8BED\u81EA\u9E23\u949F",
		"indexes":"czmdsaszljpsddsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u66AE\u767B\u56DB\u5B89\u5BFA\u949F\u697C\u5BC4\u88F4\u5341\u8FEA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u5BFA\u6C5F\u5929\u8C41",
		"indexes":"czyxjsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6E38\u4FEE\u89C9\u5BFA>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BFA\u5FC6\u66FE\u6E38\u5904",
		"indexes":"czlydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9646\u6E38>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6708\u6843\u82B1\u6D6A",
		"indexes":"ccsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA<<\u6625\u6C34>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5766\u8179\u6C5F\u4EAD\u5367",
		"indexes":"czjtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6C5F\u4EAD>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6765\u5E38\u65E9\u8D77",
		"indexes":"czzqdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u65E9\u8D77>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B1\u98DE\u6709\u5E95\u6025",
		"indexes":"czkxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u53EF\u60DC>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u65E5\u5728\u5E18\u94A9",
		"indexes":"czlrdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u843D\u65E5>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u6A3D\u72EC\u914C\u8FDF",
		"indexes":"czdzdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u72EC\u914C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6574\u5C65\u6B65\u9752\u829C",
		"indexes":"czxbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5F90\u6B65>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BD2\u98DF\u6C5F\u6751\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"czhsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BD2\u98DF>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8700\u738B\u5C06\u6B64\u955C",
		"indexes":"czsjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u77F3\u955C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8302\u9675\u591A\u75C5\u5F8C",
		"indexes":"czqtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u7434\u53F0>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51C9\u6C14\u6653\u8427\u8427",
		"indexes":"czcydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u671D\u96E8>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6751\u665A\u60CA\u98CE\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"czwqdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u665A\u6674>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6960\u6811\u8272\u51A5\u51A5",
		"indexes":"czgndsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9AD8\u6960>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u7ED5\u865A\u658B\u91CC",
		"indexes":"czesdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6076\u6811>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC\u4E45\u5BA2\u8015\u5357\u4EA9",
		"indexes":"czjtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8FDB\u8247>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u5BA4\u4ED6\u4E61\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"czysdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E00\u5BA4>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u4EBA\u5357\u90E1\u53BB",
		"indexes":"czwhslgwgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u95FB\u659B\u65AF\u516D\u5B98\u672A\u5F52>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D2B\u55DF\u51FA\u5165\u52B3",
		"indexes":"czfqcxccdjtwesdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8D74\u9752\u57CE\u53BF\u51FA\u6210\u90FD\u5BC4\u9676\u738B\u4E8C\u5C11>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u6865\u9F50\u6E21\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"czywygcsxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u91CE\u671B\u56E0\u8FC7\u5E38\u5C11\u4ED9>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u95FB\u5BBD\u6CD5\u79BB\u65B0\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"czjdwdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5BC4\u675C\u4F4D>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5175\u6208\u4E0D\u89C1\u8001\u83B1\u8863",
		"indexes":"czshssjdsjdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u97E9\u5341\u56DB\u6C5F\u4E1C\u7701\u89D0>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u4E3A\u9752\u57CE\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"czzrsdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u4E08\u4EBA\u5C71>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u4EBA\u4EA6\u6D41\u843D",
		"indexes":"czspwfdcdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9001\u88F4\u4E94\u8D74\u4E1C\u5DDD>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDC\u5E08\u865E\u79D8\u76D1",
		"indexes":"czzyswsmdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8D60\u865E\u5341\u4E94\u53F8\u9A6C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u501A\u6C5F\u6960\u6811\u8349\u5802\u524D",
		"indexes":"cznswfysbtdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6960\u6811\u4E3A\u98CE\u96E8\u6240\u62D4\u53F9>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u6708\u79CB\u9AD8\u98CE\u6012\u53F7",
		"indexes":"czmwwqfspgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u8305\u5C4B\u4E3A\u79CB\u98CE\u6240\u7834\u6B4C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5206\u624B\u5F00\u5143\u672B",
		"indexes":"czftxlzbddsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u9022\u5510\u5174\u5218\u4E3B\u7C3F\u5F1F>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F6\u53BF\u90CE\u5B98\u5BB0",
		"indexes":"czjjwmfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u656C\u7B80\u738B\u660E\u5E9C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u5B50\u897F\u5357\u5F02",
		"indexes":"czzjwmfdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u91CD\u7B80\u738B\u660E\u5E9C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC6\u5E74\u5341\u4E94\u5FC3\u5C1A\u5B69",
		"indexes":"czbyjxdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u767E\u5FE7\u96C6\u884C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u4E0D\u89C1\u5F90\u537F\u4E8C\u5B50\u751F\u7EDD\u5947",
		"indexes":"czxqezgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u5F90\u537F\u4E8C\u5B50\u6B4C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6210\u90FD\u731B\u5C06\u6709\u82B1\u537F",
		"indexes":"czxzhqgdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u620F\u4F5C\u82B1\u537F\u6B4C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u67CF\u751F\u5D07\u5188",
		"indexes":"czbbdsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u75C5\u67CF>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":20247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51C6",
		"indexes":"xmngszqdundfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684un\u7684\u53D1\u97F3?",
		"id":20248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62E8\u4E91\u89C1\u65E5",
		"indexes":"xmngscy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6210\u8BED?",
		"id":20249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F6D\u5FB7\u6000",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywsxzgsqdsdys",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05?",
		"id":20250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddzy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":20251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u9053\u5B50",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddhj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":20252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":20253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddwc",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u6587\u81E3?",
		"id":20254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u962A",
		"indexes":"qzcxgnyzsrbdcs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u66F4\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u65E5\u672C\u7684\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":20255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EBD\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnyzsmgdcs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":20256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u987F",
		"indexes":"qzcxgnywsdecsjdzzdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u66F4\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnybsbjdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5DF4\u91D1\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u9A7C\u7965\u5B50",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnybslsdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u8001\u820D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddzz",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u8457\u4F5C?",
		"id":20260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u81EA\u6E05",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8F7C",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgscdwxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u90A6",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswghcdlsrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20263
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgsgsqdlsrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgjfzzsqdgcdjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":20265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u4F69\u5B5A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgmgsqdjf",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6C11\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u519B\u9600?",
		"id":20266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u897F",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygshjzzsqsjgddf",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u7EA2\u519B\u957F\u5F81\u65F6\u671F\u6240\u7ECF\u8FC7\u7684\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":20267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u59D0",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywshyxszdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F<<\u7EA2\u5CA9>>\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygsqlwgdbgljdgj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4FB5\u7565\u6211\u56FD\u7684<<\u516B\u56FD\u8054\u519B<<\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6?",
		"id":20269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u4E16\u6C11",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgtcsqdlsrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5510\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygswggdcddsd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u9996\u90FD?",
		"id":20271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u695A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygswgcqsqdbz",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u9738\u4E3B?",
		"id":20272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u7F57\u5E9A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlznywswgdsxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygdwsjql",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u5BB6\u79BD\u7C7B?",
		"id":20274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u725B",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnyzdwsscdw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u98DF\u8349\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":20275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D2A\u79C0\u5168",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywstptgsqdjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u592A\u5E73\u5929\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":20276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9047\u4E8B\u4E0D\u614C",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnyjbscy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u6210\u8BED?",
		"id":20277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u59C6\u83B1\u7279",
		"indexes":"xlnybsssbydzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"xlnywstsbdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6?",
		"id":20279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5951\u8BC3\u592B",
		"indexes":"xlnywsegdwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u4FC4\u56FD\u7684\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":20280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnywscqzgsqdsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6?",
		"id":20281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u609F\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"xlnywsshzdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C2D\u55E3\u540C",
		"indexes":"xlnywsqcwxbfdljz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u7684\u516D\u541B\u5B50?",
		"id":20283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u9EDB\u7389",
		"indexes":"syhlmzjlsecdsnw",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u300B\u4E2D\u91D1\u9675\u5341\u4E8C\u53C9\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":20284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u609F\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"syxyjzqqjrsnyw",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u4E2D\u53BB\u53D6\u7ECF\u4EBA\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":20285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DD\u9CB8",
		"indexes":"sybrdwdsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CA8\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"syrgyldsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8F6F\u9AA8\u9C7C\u7C7B\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u814A\u516B",
		"indexes":"syzgrmdjrdsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u7684\u8282\u65E5\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u754C\u8282\u4FED\u65E5",
		"indexes":"sysjrmdjrdsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E16\u754C\u4EBA\u6C11\u7684\u8282\u65E5\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u6765\u897F\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"syyzdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82AC\u5170",
		"indexes":"syozdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5766\u6851\u5C3C\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"syfzdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C64\u52A0",
		"indexes":"sydyzdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u6D0B\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u90A6",
		"indexes":"xlnygssywggyqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u516C\u5143\u524D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":20294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6B66",
		"indexes":"xlnywswggddjsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u519B\u4E8B\u5BB6?",
		"id":20295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5A1C\u00B7\u5361\u5217\u5C3C\u5A1C",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygslfnglywqtestdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5217\u592B\u00B7\u5C3C\u53E4\u62C9\u8036\u7EF4\u5947\u00B7\u6258\u5C14\u65AF\u6CF0\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5A1C\u00B7\u5361\u5217\u5C3C\u5A1C",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygsbsygdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E0D\u662F\u96E8\u679C\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u8272\u65D7\u9762",
		"indexes":"qtczczggqdybf",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6311\u51FA\u7EC4\u6210\u4E2D\u56FD\u56FD\u65D7\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u5206\uFF1F",
		"id":20298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u63D0\u5C3C\u514B",
		"indexes":"sybmzdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u7F8E\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u667A\u5229",
		"indexes":"synmzdgjsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5357\u7F8E\u6D32\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EAC\u897F\u7A3B",
		"indexes":"sybjdtcsnyz",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u4EAC\u7684\u7279\u4EA7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\uFF1F",
		"id":20301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"syzgqdgddsnyg",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E03\u5927\u53E4\u90FD\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E7F\u9F0E\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"qzcjyzpdsnyg",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u91D1\u5EB8\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":20303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u94C3\u4E2D\u7684\u5200\u58F0",
		"indexes":"qzcnygsgldzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u53E4\u9F99\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E7F\u9F0E\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"qzcnygbslysdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6881\u7FBD\u751F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":20305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"aycydbycsng",
		"question":"\u6697\u55BB\u5E38\u7528\u7684\u6BD4\u55BB\u8BCD\uFF0C\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7528\u4E8B\u7269\u7279\u5F81\u4EE3\u672C\u4F53\u4E8B\u7269",
		"indexes":"ngsjddzlzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u501F\u4EE3\u7684\u79CD\u7C7B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8868\u793A\u5F15\u6587\u7684\u7701\u7565",
		"indexes":"ngsslhdyf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7701\u7565\u53F7\u7684\u7528\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":20308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A5\u520A\u540D",
		"indexes":"yxngkyysmh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u53EF\u4EE5\u7528\u4E66\u540D\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":20309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F16\u5E74\u4F53",
		"indexes":"yxngtlsyssld",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4F53\u4F8B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53F2\u4E66\u91CC\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6625\u79CB\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngsssygdzmssz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u53F2\u4E66\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u53F2\u4E66\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":20311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5468\u8BED\u300B",
		"indexes":"ngsygyssld",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u56FD\u8BED\u300B\u53F2\u4E66\u91CC\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u516B\u4F2F\u4E4B\u6B4C\u300B",
		"indexes":"ngsysystc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u56DB\u8A00\u8BD7\u4F53\u88C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C49\u5E7F\u300B",
		"indexes":"ngsycgtc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u695A\u6B4C\u4F53\u88C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5112",
		"indexes":"ngsyzzflzd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8BF8\u5B50\u5206\u7C7B\u4E2D\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u89E3\u91CA\u4E8B\u7269\u7684\u72B6\u6001",
		"indexes":"ngsfszqd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BF4\u6CD5\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u611F\u8C22\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"ngsyzysx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E13\u7528\u4E66\u4FE1\uFF1F",
		"id":20317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u901A\u77E5",
		"indexes":"ngsygwl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516C\u6587\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":20318
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u544A\u7A3F",
		"indexes":"ngsyxcl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5BA3\u4F20\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":20319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF7\u67EC",
		"indexes":"ngsylyld",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u793C\u4EEA\u7C7B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6536\u6761",
		"indexes":"ngsyqjld",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5951\u636E\u7C7B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE5\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"xlngbsysdwxtcd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u56DB\u5927\u6587\u5B66\u4F53\u88C1\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u670D\u88C5",
		"indexes":"xlngszdrwwmdmx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9488\u5BF9\u4EBA\u7269\u5916\u8C8C\u7684\u63CF\u5199\uFF1F",
		"id":20323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u95F4",
		"indexes":"ngsyxszjbdys",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53D9\u4E8B\u6700\u57FA\u672C\u7684\u201C\u8981\u7D20\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666F\u7269\u7684\u5F62\u72B6",
		"indexes":"ngsyxjwzwdjbfm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5199\u666F\u7269\u4F5C\u6587\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u65B9\u9762\uFF1F",
		"id":20325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC6\u89C2\u5BDF",
		"indexes":"nzffkytgzwsp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F5C\u6587\u6C34\u5E73\uFF1F",
		"id":20326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u9F84",
		"indexes":"xrdwzyzyxlngfm",
		"question":"\u5199\u4EBA\u7684\u6587\u7AE0\uFF0C\u5E94\u6CE8\u610F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u65B9\u9762\uFF1F",
		"id":20327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6148\u6BCD\u624B\u4E2D\u7EBF",
		"indexes":"xlnjczyyzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u300A\u6E38\u5B50\u541F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20328
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7237\u5A18\u95FB\u5973\u6765",
		"indexes":"xlnjczymlc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u300A\u6728\u5170\u8F9E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u7834\u5C71\u6CB3\u5728",
		"indexes":"xlnjczycw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u300A\u6625\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u4EBA\u542C\u6B64\u51CB\u6731\u989C",
		"indexes":"xlnjczysdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u300A\u8700\u9053\u96BE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8840\u6DB2\u7C98\u7A20",
		"indexes":"bsxyjcdxm",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u5C5E\u8840\u6DB2\u68C0\u67E5\u7684\u9879\u76EE\uFF1A",
		"id":20332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F0E\u7684\u76D6\u5B50\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"cslsjzggbtgjtmbtdxztzsyzcygybtqzdttjcbyyzggdmtcbdbjhmcsnzdtjcbyyzsznlm",
		"question":"\u4F20\u8BF4\u9F99\u751F\u4E5D\u5B50\u4E2A\u4E2A\u4E0D\u540C\uFF0C\u6839\u636E\u5B83\u4EEC\u4E0D\u540C\u7684\u6027\u8D28\u7279\u5F81\uFF0C\u6240\u7528\u4E4B\u5904\u4E5F\u5404\u6709\u4E0D\u540C\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u98F8\u992E\u201D\u7ECF\u5E38\u88AB\u5E94\u7528\u5728\u5E7F\u544A\u7B49\u5A92\u4F53\u4F20\u64AD\u7684\u9881\u5956\u4F1A\u540D\u79F0\u4E0A\uFF0C\u4F60\u77E5\u9053\u5B83\u7ECF\u5E38\u88AB\u7528\u4E8E\u88C5\u9970\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":20333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u661F",
		"indexes":"gjmwwnsdjdxxzys",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u540D\u4E3A\u201C\u7EF4\u7EB3\u65AF\u201D\u7684\u4E5D\u5927\u884C\u661F\u4E4B\u4E00\u662F",
		"id":20334
	},
	{
		"answer":"5\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"mgxlxjmslbrdxyfwjgcc",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u5FC3\u7406\u5B66\u5BB6\u9A6C\u65AF\u6D1B\u628A\u4EBA\u7684\u9700\u8981\u5206\u4E3A\u51E0\u4E2A\u5C42\u6B21",
		"id":20335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u6A80\u6728",
		"indexes":"swhmjjzyszyztmszmwmymhlmjcmzcdjjcczwdmczzjjdbncwhmjjqz_________shmzdjp",
		"question":"\u6240\u8C13\u7EA2\u6728\u5BB6\u5177\u4E3B\u8981\u662F\u6307\u7528\u7D2B\u6A80\u6728\u3001\u9178\u679D\u6728\u3001\u4E4C\u6728\uFF0C\u763F\u6728\u3001\u82B1\u68A8\u6728\u3001\u9E21\u7FC5\u6728\u5236\u6210\u7684\u5BB6\u5177\uFF0C\u9664\u6B64\u4E4B\u5916\u7684\u6728\u6750\u5236\u4F5C\u5BB6\u5177\u90FD\u4E0D\u80FD\u79F0\u4E3A\u7EA2\u6728\u5BB6\u5177\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D_________\u662F\u7EA2\u6728\u4E2D\u7684\u6781\u54C1\u3002",
		"id":20336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE",
		"indexes":"xysjdtfgxysjszzgnzqsjdymddtfgtmjstlfdrblkdlhaxd",
		"question":"\u897F\u57DF\u4E09\u7EDD\u72EC\u7279\u98CE\u5149.\u201C\u897F\u57DF\u4E09\u7EDD\u201D\uFF0C\u662F\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E43\u81F3\u5168\u4E16\u754C\u90FD\u6709\u540D\u7684\u72EC\u7279\u98CE\u5149\u3002\u5B83\u4EEC\u5C31\u662F\uFF1A\u5410\u9C81\u756A\u7684\u70ED\u3001\u5DF4\u91CC\u5764\u7684\u51C9\u548C\u5B89\u897F\u7684\uFF1A",
		"id":20337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u80A0",
		"indexes":"rtzzdqgssm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u957F\u7684\u5668\u5B98\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u809D",
		"indexes":"rtzzydqgssm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u7684\u5668\u5B98\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u956B\u9AA8\u808C",
		"indexes":"rtzxdjrssm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u808C\u8089\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5375\u7EC6\u80DE",
		"indexes":"rtzddxbssm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u6700\u5927\u7684\u7EC6\u80DE\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53E4\u5178\u97F3\u4E50",
		"indexes":"yxnzyllxbslyymz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u97F3\u4E50\u7C7B\u578B\u4E0D\u662F\u6765\u6E90\u4E8E\u7F8E\u6D32\uFF1F",
		"id":20342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yltysyzylxdtydltsyfhzljbdyzyxffqwsjszzyyyltydgjsnggj",
		"question":"\u533B\u7597\u4F53\u80B2\u662F\u4E00\u79CD\u533B\u7597\u6027\u7684\u4F53\u80B2\u953B\u70BC\uFF0C\u5B83\u662F\u9884\u9632\u548C\u6CBB\u7597\u75BE\u75C5\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u6709\u6548\u65B9\u6CD5\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\uFF0C\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u65E9\u5E94\u7528\u533B\u7597\u4F53\u80B2\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u65CF",
		"indexes":"syjswgngmzdctjr",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u6708\u8857\u201D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\uFF1F",
		"id":20344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u67A3",
		"indexes":"brywhwsswds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u4EBA\u8A89\u4E3A\u6D3B\u7EF4\u751F\u7D20\u4E38\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":20345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u4E0E\u5343\u5BFB\u7684\u795E\u9690",
		"indexes":"yxnxzpsgqjdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F\u5BAB\u5D0E\u9A8F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u624E\u7279\u3001\u51EF\u9C81\u6BD4\u5C3C\u3001\u67CF\u8FBD\u5179\u3001\u5A01\u5C14\u7B2C\u3001\u798F\u83B1",
		"indexes":"nwwzqjdahqzzmscwdahq",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E94\u4F4D\u4F5C\u66F2\u5BB6\u7684\u300A\u5B89\u9B42\u66F2\u300B\u6700\u8457\u540D\uFF0C\u4FD7\u79F0\u4E94\u5927\u5B89\u9B42\u66F2\uFF1F",
		"id":20347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u7A8D\u901A",
		"indexes":"yqtqtxxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\u7A8D\u901A\u201D\u8BF7\u586B\u5199\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1A",
		"id":20348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E1D\u529B",
		"indexes":"ddwdsd",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u5E1D\u6C76\u7684\u9996\u90FD\uFF1A",
		"id":20349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u6587\u5E1D\u3001\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"xlnzrwbsfzgx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u7EC4\u4EBA\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u7236\u5B50\u5173\u7CFB",
		"id":20350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u6559\u3001\u7EA2\u6559\u3001\u9EC4\u6559",
		"indexes":"zcfjynjdfz",
		"question":"\u85CF\u4F20\u4F5B\u6559\u6709\u54EA\u51E0\u5927\u5206\u652F\uFF1A",
		"id":20351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u79C0",
		"indexes":"dxtjysyg",
		"question":"\u593A\u5E2D\u8C08\u7ECF\u4E0E\u8C01\u6709\u5173\uFF1A",
		"id":20352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u573A",
		"indexes":"NBAlssjsszzdyjc",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u52A0\u65F6\u8D5B\u6700\u957F\u7684\u6709\u51E0\u573A\uFF1F",
		"id":20353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66FC\u7EBD\u7279\u00B7\u535A\u5C14",
		"indexes":"NBAlsszgdqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u585E",
		"indexes":"NBAdcbsdfzgdsngqd",
		"question":"NBA\u5355\u573A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u7403\u961F\uFF1F",
		"id":20355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6770\u91CC\u00B7\u5362\u5361\u65AF",
		"indexes":"dcbsqdlbqzddqyss",
		"question":"\u5355\u573A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u62A2\u5230\u7BEE\u677F\u7403\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC8\u514B\u5C14.\u4E54\u4E39",
		"indexes":"NBApjdfzgdqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u5E73\u5747\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u51EF\u62C9\u65AF",
		"indexes":"gjawhdyrzxss",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u4E3B\u5E2D\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u83F2\u56FE\u65AF",
		"indexes":"xlnwmydrggjawhzx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u62C5\u4EFB\u8FC7\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u4E3B\u5E2D\uFF1F",
		"id":20359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5B81",
		"indexes":"zgydysdjayhhddjpzd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u8C01\u5355\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u83B7\u5F97\u7684\u91D1\u724C\u6700\u591A\uFF1F",
		"id":20360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u957F\u6625",
		"indexes":"dyccjayhdjzgydyss",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u7684\u65E7\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u6587\u65AF",
		"indexes":"yjcdydcnhhhcjfslncfzdydzzmmds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u6770\u51FA\u7684\u8FD0\u52A8\u624D\u80FD\u548C\u8F89\u714C\u6210\u5C31\u7C89\u788E\u4E86\u7EB3\u7CB9\u5206\u5B50\u7684\u4F18\u7B49\u79CD\u65CF\u7F8E\u68A6\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9093\u4E9A\u840D",
		"indexes":"lxhdsjayhgjdzgydysnyw",
		"question":"\u8FDE\u7EED\u83B7\u5F97\u4E09\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u51A0\u519B\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":20363
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u6B63\u5EF7",
		"indexes":"gjawhddywzgwyss",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E2D\u56FD\u59D4\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u6770\u00B7\u7C73\u62C9",
		"indexes":"sssjbnlzddcsqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u5E74\u9F84\u6700\u5927\u7684\u53C2\u8D5B\u7403\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":20365
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u62C9\u591A\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"sjbsbfgcszdxsss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u4E0A\u88AB\u72AF\u89C4\u6B21\u6570\u6700\u591A\u9009\u624B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA8\u5229\u00B7\u5FB7\u65AF\u683C\u6717\u5409",
		"indexes":"scblhfzxcs",
		"question":"\u8C01\u521B\u529E\u4E86\u73AF\u6CD5\u81EA\u884C\u8F66\u8D5B?",
		"id":20367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5D",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsrjwc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u201C\u4E94\u5E38\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u56E0",
		"indexes":"ycdyqsjtsscyywxbxxsxlnwbsyyjwdj",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u7684\u5143\u66F2\u662F\u7EE7\u5510\u8BD7\u3001\u5B8B\u8BCD\u53C8\u4E00\u6587\u5B66\u8868\u73B0\u5F62\u5F0F\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5143\u5267\u4E94\u5927\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u4E9A\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nssqcmnstmhyxecldzmjbwxttxlnwsnsddbrw",
		"question":"\u5357\u793E\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u672B\u5E74\u53D7\u540C\u76DF\u4F1A\u5F71\u54CD\u800C\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\u8457\u540D\u8FDB\u6B65\u6587\u5B66\u56E2\u4F53\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u5357\u793E\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":20370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u804A\u658B\u5FD7\u5F02\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u4F18\u79C0\u7684\u767D\u8BDD\u77ED\u7BC7\u5C0F\u8BF4\u96C6",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u5B81\u4E8B\u6E14\u9493",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczyzqdzpjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u989C\u771F\u537F\u7684\u300A\u8D60\u88F4\u5C06\u519B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u300A\u6EAA\u5C45\u300B",
		"indexes":"jwzzlxcnyzzjssczngsrdnbzp",
		"question":"\u4E45\u4E3A\u7C2A\u7EC4\u7D2F\uFF0C\u5E78\u6B64\u5357\u5937\u8C2A\u3002\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BD7\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20373
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u76CA\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u66F2\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqyjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u7EDD\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":20374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u8299\u84C9\u697C\u9001\u8F9B\u6E10\u300B",
		"indexes":"hyljyrwpmskcsgcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5BD2\u96E8\u8FDE\u6C5F\u591C\u5165\u5434\uFF0C\u5E73\u660E\u9001\u5BA2\u695A\u5C71\u5B64\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u9119\u4EBA\u300A\u54E5\u8212\u6B4C\u300B",
		"indexes":"bdqxggsyddcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5317\u6597\u4E03\u661F\u9AD8\uFF0C\u54E5\u8212\u591C\u5E26\u5200\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6625\u5BBF\u5DE6\u7701\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlwhdybjxdcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u661F\u4E34\u4E07\u6237\u52A8\uFF0C\u6708\u508D\u4E5D\u9704\u591A\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6843\u6E90\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"ykyczysjrqjshzcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u9065\u770B\u4E00\u5904\u6512\u4E91\u6811\uFF0C\u8FD1\u5165\u5343\u5BB6\u6563\u82B1\u7AF9\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3D\u4EBA\u884C",
		"indexes":"dfxlnbzpsyqylf",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E03\u8A00\u4E50\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":20379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u542C\u8700\u50E7\u6D5A\u5F39\u7434\u300B",
		"indexes":"ssblqxxemfcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u8700\u50E7\u62B1\u7EFF\u7EEE\uFF0C\u897F\u4E0B\u5CE8\u7709\u5CF0\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u7ED3\u300A\u77F3\u9C7C\u6E56\u4E0A\u9189\u6B4C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B",
		"indexes":"ewlznzgyzzcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u800C\u5F80\u6765\u8005\uFF0C\u4E43\u4F5C\u6B4C\u4EE5\u957F\u4E4B\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u5E74\u53D9\u5FD7\u793A\u7FDF\u5904\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsysndzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u865E\u4E16\u5357\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BF9\u9152\u9189\u9898\u5C48\u7A81\u660E\u5E9C\u5385",
		"indexes":"xlnbbswywdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20383
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DEB\u5C71\u5CE1",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpshfrd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u662F\u9EC4\u752B\u5189\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u53F6\u6EE1\u7A7A\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbdcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u300A\u6625\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20385
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u7EA7",
		"indexes":"ngsyrddytfdjb",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u70ED\u5E26\u4F4E\u538B\u53F0\u98CE\u7684\u7EA7\u522B\uFF1F",
		"id":20386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngscyd31jtfwyhtfmmhddgjhdq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53C2\u4E0E\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u53F0\u98CE\u547D\u540D\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u548C\u5730\u533A\uFF1F",
		"id":20387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u5154",
		"indexes":"ngsd31jtfwyhzsmmdtfmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u4E2D\u6240\u547D\u540D\u7684\u53F0\u98CE\u540D\u5B57\uFF1F",
		"id":20388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u609F\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"ngsd31jtfwyhzzgsmmdtfmzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u4E2D\u4E2D\u56FD\u6240\u547D\u540D\u7684\u53F0\u98CE\u540D\u5B57\u6709\uFF1F",
		"id":20389
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70ED\u5E26\u96E8\u6797\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"zlyjwz15ysdsynzqh",
		"question":"\u6700\u51B7\u6708\u5747\u6E29\u572815\u2103\u4EE5\u4E0A\u7684\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54EA\u79CD\u6C14\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":20390
	},
	{
		"answer":"120\u5EA6\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlsydjdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u949D\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20391
	},
	{
		"answer":"123",
		"indexes":"xlsydwsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u591A\u4F4D\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20392
	},
	{
		"answer":"45\u00B0\u548C135\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwbjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u8865\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9\uFF1F",
		"id":20393
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"xlnygsos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5076\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":20394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"16sjoznggjyzgts",
		"question":"16\u4E16\u7EAA\u6B27\u6D32\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0E\u4E2D\u56FD\u901A\u5546\uFF1F",
		"id":20395
	},
	{
		"answer":"1\u5143",
		"indexes":"rmbdmzynx",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u7684\u9762\u503C\u6709\u54EA\u4E9B\uFF1F",
		"id":20396
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"xlnygssdy10xy50dzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5927\u4E8E10\u5C0F\u4E8E50\u7684\u8D28\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":20397
	},
	{
		"answer":"61",
		"indexes":"xlnygssdy50xy100dzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5927\u4E8E50\u5C0F\u4E8E100\u7684\u8D28\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":20398
	},
	{
		"answer":"91\u5EA6\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlnygjsdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u89D2\u662F\u949D\u89D2\uFF1F",
		"id":20399
	},
	{
		"answer":"12.561279\u2026",
		"indexes":"xlnygsswls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u65E0\u7406\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":20400
	},
	{
		"answer":"1948",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u9F20\uFF1F",
		"id":20401
	},
	{
		"answer":"1949",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u725B\uFF1F",
		"id":20402
	},
	{
		"answer":"1950",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u864E\uFF1F",
		"id":20403
	},
	{
		"answer":"1951",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxst",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u5154\uFF1F",
		"id":20404
	},
	{
		"answer":"1940",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u9F99\uFF1F",
		"id":20405
	},
	{
		"answer":"1941",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u86C7\uFF1F",
		"id":20406
	},
	{
		"answer":"1942",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u9A6C\uFF1F",
		"id":20407
	},
	{
		"answer":"1943",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u7F8A\uFF1F",
		"id":20408
	},
	{
		"answer":"1944",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u7334\uFF1F",
		"id":20409
	},
	{
		"answer":"1945",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u9E21\uFF1F",
		"id":20410
	},
	{
		"answer":"1934",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u72D7\uFF1F",
		"id":20411
	},
	{
		"answer":"1947",
		"indexes":"xlnygnfssdsxsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5E74\u4EFD\u6240\u5C5E\u7684\u751F\u8096\u662F\u732A\uFF1F",
		"id":20412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C4",
		"indexes":"sjdszyd65jzz10ggjwg",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u6DE1\u6C34\u8D44\u6E90\u768465\uFF05\u96C6\u4E2D\u572810\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6,\u6211\u56FD\uFF1A",
		"id":20413
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94A2\u82AF\u9540\u94DC\u5408\u91D1",
		"indexes":"zgrmyxy2002n11y18rqzqgfxddwtrmb5jybszwjhsqjscz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u94F6\u884C\u4E8E2002\u5E7411\u670818\u65E5\u8D77\u5728\u5168\u56FD\u53D1\u884C\u7684\u7B2C\u4E94\u5957\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E015\u89D2\u786C\u5E01\u8272\u6CFD\u4E3A\u91D1\u9EC4\u8272\uFF0C\u5176\u91D1\u5C5E\u6750\u8D28\uFF1A",
		"id":20414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC-010",
		"indexes":"gndcsdhqhdpzqds",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5185\u5927\u57CE\u5E02\u7535\u8BDD\u533A\u53F7\u642D\u914D\u6B63\u786E\u5730\u662F:",
		"id":20415
	},
	{
		"answer":"24\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zxnzsqxzjymxs1700gldsdxxfxrdqyznyjdsgxn",
		"question":"\u5728\u65B0\u5E74\u949F\u58F0\u6572\u54CD\u4E4B\u9645\uFF0C\u4EE5\u6BCF\u5C0F\u65F61700\u516C\u91CC\u7684\u901F\u5EA6\u5411\u897F\u98DE\u884C\uFF0C\u7ED5\u5730\u7403\u4E00\u5468\uFF0C\u80FD\u8FCE\u63A5\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u65B0\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":20416
	},
	{
		"answer":"1969\u5E747\u6708",
		"indexes":"dysfwyqdzrabl11hfcsznynfsskd",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u8258\u98DE\u5F80\u6708\u7403\u7684\u8F7D\u4EBA\u201C\u963F\u6CE2\u7F5711\u53F7\u201D\u98DE\u8239\uFF0C\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53D1\u5C04\u5347\u7A7A\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20417
	},
	{
		"answer":"1978\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zhrmghghkdjtlsnynbbssd",
		"question":"<<\u4E2D\u534E\u4EBA\u6C11\u5171\u548C\u56FD\u6237\u53E3\u767B\u8BB0\u6761\u4F8B>>\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u9881\u5E03\u5B9E\u65BD\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20418
	},
	{
		"answer":"184",
		"indexes":"wgtgdyzbmcxtfdhhms",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u63D0\u4F9B\u7684\u90AE\u653F\u7F16\u7801\u67E5\u8BE2\u7279\u670D\u7535\u8BDD\u53F7\u7801\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20419
	},
	{
		"answer":"1%",
		"indexes":"1998nzgkxjjrdrljyzjhzbwclqzdbfzj",
		"question":"1998\u5E74\u4E2D\u56FD\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6\u52A0\u5165\u5230\u300A\u4EBA\u7C7B\u57FA\u56E0\u7EC4\u300B\u8BA1\u5212\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5E76\u5B8C\u6210\u4E86\u5176\u4E2D\u7684\u767E\u5206\u4E4B\u51E0\uFF1F",
		"id":20420
	},
	{
		"answer":"1895\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xdlqydsnynymgcrzgd",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4EE3\u7BEE\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u7531\uFF08\u7F8E\u56FD\uFF09\u4F20\u5165\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":20421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6851\u6258\u65AF",
		"indexes":"1994nsjbjsbqssdqqwbxdsytyssdq",
		"question":"1994\u5E74\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u5DF4\u4E54\u5C04\u5931\u70B9\u7403\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u5DF4\u897F\u961F\u8C01\u4E5F\u540C\u6837\u5C04\u5931\u70B9\u7403\uFF1F",
		"id":20422
	},
	{
		"answer":"10:01",
		"indexes":"sjbbsjgzxsdbfsds",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u6BD4\u8D5B\u7ED3\u679C\u6700\u60AC\u6B8A\u7684\u6BD4\u5206\u662F\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F",
		"id":20423
	},
	{
		"answer":"109.5\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zgzjwznldsgspsgj",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u81F3\u4ECA\u4E3A\u6B62\u62FF\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u4E16\u4E52\u8D5B\u51A0\u519B?",
		"id":20424
	},
	{
		"answer":"1901\u5E74",
		"indexes":"ACmlsznynsdlsgj",
		"question":"AC\u7C73\u5170\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u9996\u593A\u8054\u8D5B\u51A0\u519B?",
		"id":20425
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u771F\u6E90\u4E86\u65E0\u53D6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrsyssfdddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u5BBF\u4E1A\u5E08\u5C71\u623F\u5F85\u4E01\u5927\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u56DB\u4E3A\u541B\u5987",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqsczf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u9001\u9648\u7AE0\u752B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6216\u9A91\u9E92\u9E9F\u7FF3\u51E4\u51F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzyyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u300A\u6E14\u7FC1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u67F3\u6E21\u6C5F\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczccjzsdsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u300A\u5BC4\u5DE6\u7701\u675C\u62FE\u9057\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5E1D\u7960\u524D\u4E91\u6B32\u6563",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczywjm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u7956\u548F\u300A\u671B\u84DF\u95E8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20430
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u820D\u5357\u820D\u5317\u7686\u6625\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u91CE\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20431
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C38\u591C\u89D2\u58F0\u60B2\u81EA\u8BED",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u9601\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5E74\u8C2A\u5BA6\u6B64\u6816\u8FDF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclyxxsshg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u897F\u585E\u5C71\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95F2\u5750\u60B2\u541B\u4EA6\u81EA\u60B2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u9526\u745F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8721\u70AC\u6210\u7070\u6CEA\u59CB\u5E72",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsycy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u6625\u96E8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20435
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5362\u5BB6\u5C11\u5987\u90C1\u91D1\u9999",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscqtypn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u79E6\u97EC\u7389\u300A\u8D2B\u5973\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u521D\u65E5\u90E2\u95E8\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczskszphsrbg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u53F8\u7A7A\u66D9\u300A\u8D3C\u5E73\u540E\u9001\u4EBA\u5317\u5F52\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77E5\u97F3\u4E16\u6240\u7A00",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdmls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u65C5\u5BBF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u81EA\u6545\u4E61\u6765",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6742\u8BD7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529F\u76D6\u4E09\u5206\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdfbzt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u516B\u9635\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20440
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u4E91\u5C06\u91CE\u9E64",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzqssr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u9001\u4E0A\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BE5\u843D\u53E4\u884C\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyzxg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u884C\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20442
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u4E61\u60C5\u66F4\u602F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlpdhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9891\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81F3\u4ECA\u7AA5\u7267\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxbrgsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u897F\u9119\u4EBA\u300A\u54E5\u8212\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E18\u5916\u6625\u5BD2\u8D50\u9526\u888D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclcgq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u6625\u5BAB\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20445
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D7\u964D\u57CE\u5916\u6708\u5982\u971C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyyssjcwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u76CA\u300A\u591C\u4E0A\u53D7\u964D\u57CE\u95FB\u7B1B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u9636\u591C\u8272\u51C9\u5982\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u79CB\u5915\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u9A8F\u65E5\u884C\u4E09\u4E07\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u7476\u6C60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u585E\u5916\u60B2\u98CE\u5207",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmymzckx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u996E\u9A6C\u957F\u57CE\u7A9F\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u971E\u65AD\u7EED\u751F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzgwt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u8FC7\u6E29\u6C64\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20450
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u70AB\u73E0\u5149\u9047\u6CC9\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxsc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u77F3\u6DD9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F05\u60F3\u5C01\u5510\u5904",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljgjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u8FC7\u664B\u9633\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u62B1\u4E5D\u4ED9\u9AA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlhcllmyzwlj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4EA8\u300A\u8D50\u68A8\u674E\u6CCC\u4E0E\u8BF8\u738B\u8054\u53E5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3B\u4EBA\u82E5\u4E5F\u52E4\u6311\u62E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u662A\u300A\u548F\u706F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591A\u8C22\u957F\u6761\u4F3C\u76F8\u8BC6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlycgrqn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u8D50\u5BAB\u4EBA\u5E86\u5974\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20455
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u864F\u969C\u62B5\u7941\u8FDE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlgsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5173\u5C71\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65CC\u60AC\u4E5D\u6708\u971C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzllts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u9647\u5934\u6C34\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u82B1\u4E71\u821E\u8863",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20458
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C11\u5E74\u98DE\u7FE0\u76D6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbysnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5C11\u5E74\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u51E4\u4E0A\u5C42\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyfdwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u8D4B\u5F97\u9B4F\u90FD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F2B\u517C\u53F8\u96B6\u5C40",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzczqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u916C\u90D1\u6C81\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7089\u4EFB\u610F\u718F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzqgdhbywhssxz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D75\u8C26\u5149\u300A\u7B54\u6237\u90E8\u5458\u5916\u8D3A\u9042\u6D89\u620F\u8D60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA3\u738B\u516D\u6708\u5175",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhszszsxb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9001\u5F20\u8BF4\u5DE1\u8FB9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u83BA\u9189\u91CC\u6B4C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjltjqdxydgzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5929\u6D25\u6865\u4E1C\u65EC\u5BB4\u5F97\u6B4C\u5B57\u97F5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8393\u82D4\u70C2\u9526\u7AE0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjwx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5DEB\u5CE1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60B2\u98CE\u6101\u6740\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjzcn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6218\u57CE\u5357\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3D\u6B64\u76C8\u6A3D\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwszlzg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u9001\u8D75\u516D\u8D1E\u56FA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671D\u591C\u7FF3\u4E91\u65CF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwwqzwbjyqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6E29\u6CC9\u5E84\u5367\u75C5\u5BC4\u6768\u4E03\u70AF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u585E\u638C\u4E2D\u6765",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsfhdlsgdymyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5949\u548C\u767B\u9A8A\u5C71\u9AD8\u9876\u5BD3\u76EE\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20469
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FB9\u4E66\u9A7F\u9A91\u5F52",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsbc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u8FB9\u6101\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F73\u671F\u4E0D\u53EF\u9A7B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbclq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u91C7\u83B2\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F8\u4F20\u79F0\u4E71\u77F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsynhlssz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5357\u6D77\u4E71\u77F3\u5C71\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20472
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u884C\u9730\u96EA\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczsjssssfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u749F\u300A\u9001\u82CF\u5C1A\u4E66\u8D74\u76CA\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F8\u547D\u4E14\u8854\u676F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlkszbzxfszw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5914\u300A\u4F7F\u81F3\u6C74\u5DDE\u559C\u9022\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u82B1\u601D\u821E\u5DFE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5BAA\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20475
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A6\u5BD0\u6B8A\u60A0\u54C9",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstscktzlasf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u8700\u57CE\u54ED\u53F0\u5DDE\u4E50\u5B89\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20476
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7530\u79CB\u9EA6\u6C14\u6E05",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxrymlz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u76EE\u804A\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20477
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u88D8\u5341\u4E0A\u8FD8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwtzyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9014\u4E2D\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20478
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60CA\u6708\u7ED5\u758F\u679D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqysywhrz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u9001\u960E\u4E94\u8FD8\u6DA6\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20479
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F13\u58F0\u632F\u539F\u96B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxyjjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5C06\u519B\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20480
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u91CD\u6709\u6B8A\u4F26",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczagjyp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u89C2\u8346\u7389\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u5BFF\u4E3A\u5730\u540D\uFF0C\u4EAD\u4FAF\u4E3A\u5B98\u540D",
		"indexes":"lbbccdbhgybfgysdccfhwhsthhsthzqdjsw",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u88AB\u66F9\u64CD\u6253\u8D25\u540E\uFF0C\u5173\u7FBD\u88AB\u4FD8\u3002\u5173\u7FBD\u53D7\u5230\u66F9\u64CD\u5C01\u53F7\u4E3A\u201C\u6C49\u5BFF\u4EAD\u4FAF\u201D\u3002\u201C\u6C49\u5BFF\u4EAD\u4FAF\u201D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u89E3\u91CA\u4E3A\uFF1F",
		"id":20482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71E7\u4EBA\u6C0F",
		"indexes":"xlnxbslszjzwmdtz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5386\u53F2\u4E2D\u8BB0\u8F7D\u6211\u4EEC\u7684\u592A\u7956\uFF1F",
		"id":20483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DA",
		"indexes":"sdxsm",
		"question":"\u821C\u5E1D\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u821C\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"dwxzjhsngsgxddwhjszh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5FB7\u4E3A\u5148\uFF0C\u91CD\u6559\u5316\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0A\u53E4\u5148\u5E1D\u7684\u6587\u5316\u7CBE\u795E\u4E4B\u9B42\uFF1F",
		"id":20485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u897F\u4E34\u6C7E\u5E02",
		"indexes":"ydlzxjzgngdf",
		"question":"\u5C27\u5E1D\u9675\u5728\u73B0\u4ECA\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\uFF1F",
		"id":20486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EB3\uFF08\u4ECA\u6CB3\u5357\u5546\u4E18\u5E02\uFF09",
		"indexes":"sclcqdcjqhqgwcxlngdfsscddygdc",
		"question":"\u5546\u671D\u5C61\u6B21\u8FC1\u90FD\uFF0C\u66FE\u7ECF\u524D\u540E\u8FC1\u8FC7\u4E94\u6B21\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u662F\u5546\u671D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u90FD\u57CE\uFF1F",
		"id":20487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718A",
		"indexes":"hdbldttssm",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5E1D\u90E8\u843D\u7684\u56FE\u817E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5357\u9093\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xcddczn",
		"question":"\u590F\u671D\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":20489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u5149\u6B66\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"xlnghcddwsydhdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5E1D\u738B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E1C\u6C49\u5E1D\u738B\uFF1F",
		"id":20490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u9547\u8D77\u4E49",
		"indexes":"wxwdshzzryhajjmdjrhzyyflgzrmdqyxlngqysfsbwsqd",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5B5D\u6587\u5E1D\u6B7B\u540E\uFF0C\u653F\u6CBB\u65E5\u76CA\u9ED1\u6697\uFF0C\u9636\u7EA7\u77DB\u76FE\u5C16\u9510\u5316\uFF0C\u7EC8\u4E8E\u5F15\u53D1\u4E86\u5404\u65CF\u4EBA\u6C11\u5927\u8D77\u4E49\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8D77\u4E49\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5317\u9B4F\u65F6\u671F\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u8083",
		"indexes":"swkyxsptsnlr",
		"question":"\u5B59\u609F\u7A7A\u539F\u578B\u77F3\u78D0\u9640\u662F\u54EA\u91CC\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":20492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C88\u62EC",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsbssqymdbswz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u6709\u540D\u7684\u5317\u5B8B\u4E94\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":20493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"tzkskjzxckkmzdygxkmqwtzkcxzngcd",
		"question":"\u7AE5\u5B50\u79D1\u662F\u79D1\u4E3E\u5236\u4E0B\u5E38\u79D1\u79D1\u76EE\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C0F\u79D1\u76EE\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u7AE5\u5B50\u79D1\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u671D",
		"indexes":"lsszmdtdzcjtzscszngcd",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u4E95\u7530\u5236\u662F\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20495
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F66\u9A91\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssgdwjgz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u6B66\u5C06\u5B98\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":20496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u5E84\u5B97\u559C\u6B22\u8E74\u97A0",
		"indexes":"xlgyhdmahdmscwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u7687\u5E1D\u4EEC\u7231\u597D\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20497
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4E30\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglsssxsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u5C71\u897F\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":20498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8000\u5DDE\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglsshbsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6CB3\u5317\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":20499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u516C\u660E",
		"indexes":"csdqypwnkdcsbzyweqsjsdsmyysydeysbtyswzcswcshpcsqwxlnwcszcs",
		"question":"\u8D22\u795E\u7684\u8D77\u6E90\u9887\u4E3A\u96BE\u8003\uFF0C\u4F46\u8D22\u795E\u4E0D\u6B62\u4E00\u4F4D\uFF0C\u800C\u4E14\u6240\u796D\u7940\u7684\u795E\u660E\u4E5F\u56E0\u65F6\u56E0\u5730\u800C\u6709\u6240\u4E0D\u540C\uFF0C\u6709\u6240\u8C13\u201C\u6B63\u8D22\u795E\u201D\u3001\u201C\u6587\u8D22\u795E\u201D\u548C\u201C\u504F\u8D22\u795E\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u624D\u662F\u201C\u6B63\u8D22\u795E\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20500
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99\u6E0A",
		"indexes":"oyzhgjdsgddmzjscszyybjwldzjslsszqwzbjjsm",
		"question":"\u6B27\u51B6\u5B50\u548C\u5E72\u5C06\u90FD\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u540D\u94F8\u5251\u5E08\uFF0C\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u6709\u4E00\u628A\u5251\u4E3A\u4E24\u5927\u94F8\u5251\u5E08\u8054\u624B\u6240\u94F8\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8FD9\u628A\u5251\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EAF\u94A7",
		"indexes":"gdzjtwoyzctmzlybjjchoyzyljsjewqwzbjjsm",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u94F8\u5251\u5929\u738B\u6B27\u51B6\u5B50\u627F\u5929\u547D\u94F8\u4E86\u4E00\u628A\u5251\uFF0C\u5251\u6210\u540E\u6B27\u51B6\u5B50\u4E5F\u529B\u5C3D\u795E\u7AED\u800C\u4EA1\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8FD9\u628A\u5251\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20502
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5308\u5974",
		"indexes":"hcsdzbdatlsgdngmzdsl",
		"question":"\u53F7\u79F0\u201C\u4E0A\u5E1D\u4E4B\u97AD\u201D\u7684\u963F\u63D0\u62C9\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u9996\u9886\uFF1F",
		"id":20503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u5914",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsysdwypcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5B8B\u4EE3\u5A49\u7EA6\u6D3E\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":20504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u5914",
		"indexes":"glcpsyswdb",
		"question":"\u683C\u5F8B\u8BCD\u6D3E\u662F\u4EE5\u8C01\u4E3A\u4EE3\u8868\uFF1F",
		"id":20505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590D\u7167\u9752\u82D4\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwlc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u9E7F\u67F4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u9EEF\u7136\u9500\u9B42\u8005\uFF0C\u60DF\u522B\u800C\u5DF2\u77E3\u201D--\u738B\u52C3(\u819D\u738B\u9601\u5E8F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxzmymjdcccwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E2D\u540D\u8A00\u540D\u53E5\u7684\u51FA\u5904\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5C14\u96C5\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u8BD7\u96C6",
		"indexes":"xlnxgywxzpdmsscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C5F\u6E56\u96C6\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngbszxsdsrddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u5174\u56DB\u5927\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":20509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u97E9\u975E\u5B50\u300B\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\u91CD\u8981\u8457\u4F5C\u3002\u53CD\u6620\u97E9\u975E\u601D\u60F3",
		"indexes":"dyxlzpdmsngscwd",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E8E\u4E0B\u5217\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56DB\u4E66\u300B",
		"indexes":"bsnjdkjslbgjsksmsdxlnbsbsybksm",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u5E74\u95F4\u7684\u79D1\u4E3E\u8BBE\u793C\u90E8\u8D21\u4E3E\uFF0C\u6240\u8003\u4E66\u76EE\u751A\u591A\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E66\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5FC5\u8003\u4E66\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":20511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u79BB\u9A9A\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u9996\u4F18\u79C0\u7684\u957F\u7BC7\u6292\u60C5\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u89C2\u730E\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E03\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C\u7B1B\u4F55\u987B\u6028\u6768\u67F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwzhcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u4E4B\u6DA3\u300A\u51FA\u585E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D41\u6C34\u5341\u5E74\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzqslzcghyby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u9001\u674E\u4E2D\u4E1E\u5F52\u6C49\u9633\u522B\u4E1A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u6708\u62B1\u5BD2\u5149",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrsydfj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9001\u5C39\u5927\u8D74\u4EAC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20516
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BD2\u706F\u72EC\u591C\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrqzgqjysr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u79E6\u4E2D\u611F\u79CB\u5BC4\u8FDC\u4E0A\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20517
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F20\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"xlnzwtbssjzdwt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u6587\u4F53\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u6587\u4F53\uFF1F",
		"id":20518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u5C3A\u9F99\u987B\u65B9\u9526\u8925",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhhyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u5DF2\u51C9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6025\u591C\u6C5F\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwdgbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u6E21\u74DC\u6B65\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u82CD\u8302\u9675\u6811",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwblgt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u4E34\u9AD8\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78A7\u6D77\u9752\u5929\u591C\u591C\u5FC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyce",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u5AE6\u5A25\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u706F\u95FB\u695A\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsylh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u843D\u82B1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6668\u767B\u6BCF\u60C6\u6005",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlfsyzzzafzyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5949\u4F7F\u76CA\u5DDE\u81F3\u957F\u5B89\u53D1\u949F\u9633\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u4F53",
		"indexes":"xlnzztbsstzszdzt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u5B57\u4F53\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u592A\u5B97\u64C5\u957F\u7684\u5B57\u4F53\uFF1F",
		"id":20525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6301\u8861\u4E34\u4E07\u59D3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmzqjsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u6267\u5951\u9759\u4E09\u8FB9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C3F\u5BBF\u5BC6\u4E91\u84B8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwbtcl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u5317\u773A\u8202\u9675\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70AE",
		"indexes":"gjxqdqzhzgxqbyyxlnxbsgjxqdqz",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u8C61\u68CB\u7684\u68CB\u5B50\u548C\u4E2D\u56FD\u8C61\u68CB\u4E0D\u4E00\u6837\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u56FD\u9645\u8C61\u68CB\u7684\u68CB\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":20528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5986\u6210\u72EC\u89C1\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxycnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u6625\u5973\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u56FE\u5F52\u8DEF\u96BE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwtcfmxcdlsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u540C\u5D14\u9A78\u9A6C\u6653\u521D\u767B\u697C\u601D\u4EAC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C\u300B",
		"indexes":"qcllhysfcqqywzcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u6674\u5DDD\u5386\u5386\u6C49\u9633\u6811\uFF0C\u82B3\u8349\u840B\u840B\u9E66\u9E49\u6D32\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u6CF0\u5043\u6208\u8239",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyhxslykmc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u548C\u8BB8\u4F8D\u90CE\u6E38\u6606\u660E\u6C60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC8\u8C22\u5DE8\u5DDD\u821F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlccnwcy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u6555\u8D50\u5B81\u738B\u6C60\u5BB4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u897F",
		"indexes":"cjsjbcszddgjdsng",
		"question":"\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u6B21\u6570\u6700\u591A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u961F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":20534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u5FC6\u8C22\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbybnzhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u591C\u6CCA\u725B\u6E1A\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u6653\u542C\u9E21\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczsjpjyj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u749F\u300A\u84B2\u6D25\u8FCE\u9A7E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E09\u5C4A\uFF1A\u5728\u7F8E\u56FD\u666E\u6797\u65AF\u987F\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"xldymjayhcbdmscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5BF9\u4E8E\u6BCF\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u627F\u529E\u5730\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u4E18\u70DC\u671B\u7940",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjxlx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u897F\u9675\u5CE1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B2\u98D9\u5377\u585E\u84EC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxybhwrx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F90\u5F66\u4F2F\u300A\u80E1\u65E0\u4EBA\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EFF\u534E\u793E\uFF08\u53E3\u6280\uFF09",
		"indexes":"xlnxdsczmylzzmscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5BF9\u5B8B\u671D\u8457\u540D\u5A31\u4E50\u7EC4\u7EC7\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u4EE5\u9677\u90BB\u5883",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscztxzjzljkzetz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5510\u7384\u5B97\u300A\u7ECF\u90B9\u9C81\u796D\u5B54\u5B50\u800C\u53F9\u4E4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5BD2\u68A6\u6CFD\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczqqssgrb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u94B1\u8D77\u300A\u9001\u50E7\u5F52\u65E5\u672C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5143\u524D776\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gddyjalpkydhsnynjxd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F46\u89C1\u6CEA\u75D5\u6E7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6028\u60C5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EFF\u8681\u65B0\u9185\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczbjywlsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u95EE\u5218\u5341\u4E5D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5750\u770B\u4E91\u8D77\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwgxjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u8FC7\u9999\u79EF\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u4EE3\u53E4\u7891",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsdjsbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5927\u89C9\u5BFA\u516B\u666F\uFF1F",
		"id":20547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6682\u5631\u66E6\u8F6E\u52FF\u907D\u659C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxlcryyyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u7ACB\u6625\u65E5\u6E38\u82D1\u8FCE\u6625\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C60\u98CE\u6CDB\u65E9\u51C9",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjsljfsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u4E34\u6D25\u623F\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u9E23\u5411\u5317\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjzlm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u7D2B\u9A9D\u9A6C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"dfyzbxgzjbwsrcwbxxlnwbsbxzy",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u996E\u4E2D\u516B\u4ED9\u6B4C\u300B\u4E2D\u5C06\u516B\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u516B\u4ED9\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u516B\u4ED9\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20551
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E7\u65F6\u738B\u8C22\u5802\u524D\u71D5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyxwyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u4E4C\u8863\u5DF7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u897F",
		"indexes":"bssqdsrhtjswgngsdr",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\u9EC4\u5EAD\u575A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u7684\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":20553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u83F2\u4E0D\u53CA\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BBF\u83BD\u7ADE\u542B\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwzfss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u81F3\u5206\u6C34\u620D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FD\u6E05\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglssjxsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":20556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CF0\u96FE\u62B1\u83B2\u660F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmjpxjzd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u7ECF\u7834\u859B\u4E3E\u6218\u5730\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20557
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5B50\u6309\u96D5\u6208",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlszh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u4E0A\u4E4B\u56DE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9999\u68B5\u904D\u79CB\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhjyjrdcesftyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E5D\u6708\u4E5D\u65E5\u767B\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u6D6E\u56FE\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FBD\u7FEE\u4E24\u9036\u8FE4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczayyp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u9E33\u9E2F\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u522B\u64CD\u7ED5\u7E41\u5F26",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwswmfcxfdh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9001\u738B\u660E\u5E9C\u53C2\u9009\u8D4B\u5F97\u9E64\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F52\u5C71\u6DF1\u6D45\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczpdscj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u88F4\u8FEA\u300A\u9001\u5D14\u4E5D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FDD\u957F",
		"indexes":"xlnzffbswasbfstxdxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u6CD5\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u65F6\u63A8\u884C\u7684\u65B0\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":20563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u78A7\u76F8\u6742\u6577\u6E05\u6D41",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljyhhslh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u749F\u300A\u6E38\u540E\u6E56\u8D4F\u83B2\u82B1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u4E39",
		"indexes":"ljsjbjqzddssss",
		"question":"\u5386\u5C4A\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u8FDB\u7403\u6700\u591A\u7684\u5C04\u624B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8679\u996E\u6C5F\u768B\u9701",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwzhyzszynss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u81EA\u8861\u9633\u81F3\u97F6\u5DDE\u8C12\u80FD\u7985\u5E08\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA2\u820D\u9752\u9752\u67F3\u8272\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwwcq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6E2D\u57CE\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60CA\u6816\u591A\u4F17\u97F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwyydt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u591C\u996E\u4E1C\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63A5\u6C49\u7591\u661F\u843D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlswygd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5341\u4E94\u591C\u89C2\u706F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u82B3\u5E26\u96EA\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgzchrzjlt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9AD8\u6B63\u81E3\u300A\u6666\u65E5\u7F6E\u9152\u6797\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE1\u76D6\u8377\u51CB\u7FE0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzjyjr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u4E5D\u65E5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20571
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E37\u5C4F\u5411\u6708\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5A55\u59A4\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20572
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u6CC9\u6D12\u6DB2\u6052\u7591\u96E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdrjfhszxryscs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u72C4\u4EC1\u6770\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u77F3\u6DD9\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u54C0\u738B\u5B59\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E38\u76EE\u773A\u7687\u757F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzycestzfsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u8C12\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u9898\u5958\u6CD5\u5E08\u623F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u6211\u957F\u53F9\u606F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwtzlss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u9898\u5F20\u8001\u677E\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F53\u541B\u6000\u5F52\u65E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczqwdxxsyzby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90B1\u4E3A\u7684\u300A\u5BFB\u897F\u5C71\u9690\u8005\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u5E1B\u8D44\u738B\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyflj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u8D4B\u793C\u8BB0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71D5\u53F0\u4E00\u53BB\u5BA2\u5FC3\u60CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwwjywczz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u79EF\u96E8\u8F8B\u5DDD\u5E84\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6E05\u6653\u6F0F\u95FB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyqyyljzmfz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u5BB4\u4E34\u6D25\u90D1\u660E\u5E9C\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6252\u6751\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglsszjsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6D59\u6C5F\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":20581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E38\u6CF3",
		"indexes":"zgaysshdjpszddsnxyd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5965\u8FD0\u53F2\u4E0A\u83B7\u5F97\u91D1\u724C\u6570\u6700\u591A\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":20582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u4E8E\u7956\u9F99\u7559\u9762\u76EE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlytjlzh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u9898\u91D1\u697C\u5B50\u540E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5143\u66F4\u5E9F\u5174",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczagysssbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u611F\u9047\u8BD7\u4E09\u5341\u516B\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u56DE\u767E\u5DDD\u6F8D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwjlsncch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u666F\u9F99\u56DB\u5E74\u6625\u7960\u6D77\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6668\u98D9\u65AD\u66D9\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzxjhdwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5B5D\u656C\u7687\u5E1D\u633D\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7317\u6B24\u6B64\u63A8\u62E9",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljczzcsytzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u8D50\u8BF8\u5DDE\u523A\u53F2\u4EE5\u9898\u5EA7\u53F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6000\u541B\u5C5E\u79CB\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwywqyjqyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u5BC4\u90B1\u5458\u5916\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u6258\u514B\u987F",
		"indexes":"NBAqdzddqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u62A2\u65AD\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A35\u4EBA\u5F52\u6B32\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbzyssgcg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5B50\u591C\u56DB\u65F6\u6B4C\uFF1A\u6625\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20590
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u65E9\u6458\u8299\u8556",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxsyzngzdz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5BAA\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u5E74\u4E00\u89C9\u626C\u5DDE\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u9063\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9633\u548C\u4E0D\u6563\u7A77\u9014\u6068",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwywjldyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u5BC4\u674E\u510B\u5143\u9521\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CBE\u88F3\u5373\u6B64\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlwsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u9AD8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u671F\u59CB\u9057\u8204",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczczadbdchg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u7684\u300A\u767D\u5E1D\u57CE\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F52\u671B\u9010\u6625\u6765",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzwzssssfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90D1\u60DF\u5FE0\u300A\u9001\u82CF\u5C1A\u4E66\u8D74\u76CA\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u9999\u6697\u8BC6\u83B2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycydj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u591C\u6E21\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u6C34\u5343\u5BFB\u7011",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjgxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5E7F\u6EAA\u5CE1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20598
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D\u6709\u5C01\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbdjmsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E21\u8346\u95E8\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D6E\u76D6\u4E0B\u5954\u6D9B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbydhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20600
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u5CB8\u733F\u58F0\u557C\u4E0D\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbxjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u4E0B\u6C5F\u9675\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7F15\u6668\u9E21\u672A\u5B66\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhlcyyycyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u7ACB\u6625\u6E38\u82D1\u8FCE\u6625\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624D\u5B50\u80FD\u6B4C\u591C\u672A\u592E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryyyalgzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u591C\u5BB4\u5B89\u4E50\u516C\u4E3B\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676F\u63A5\u8FD1\u81E3\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyzngzdzyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5947\u6BDB\u81EA\u5076\u9E9F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxysynyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u5709\u5E08\u300A\u548F\u725B\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u72EC\u5F02\u4E61\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlyxsxzm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u8700\u5148\u4E3B\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6628\u591C\u4E0A\u7687\u65B0\u6388\u25A1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhjlteszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u96C6\u7075\u53F0\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8\u524D\u8336",
		"indexes":"xlnzcbsgdmczy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u79CD\u8336\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u540D\u8336\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u4E38\u591C\u8BED\u98DE\u7535\u5149",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrdsyssfdddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u4E1A\u5E08\u5C71\u623F\u5F85\u4E01\u5927\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6570\u4E1B\u6C99\u8349\u7FA4\u9E25\u6563",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwtyswm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u82CF\u6B66\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F81\u6218\u4E8C\u5EAD\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzngzcza",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u62DF\u53E4\u8D60\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u92AE\u4EEA\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsqcdzepwzjg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u6B63\u4E8C\u54C1\u6587\u804C\u4EAC\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":20612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"gddrjGDPfzsngcdddd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u4EBA\u5747GDP\u5CF0\u503C\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u8FBE\u5230\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E7E\u9686",
		"indexes":"zglssdhdsdsmzz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u8C01\u7684\u5BFF\u547D\u6700\u957F?",
		"id":20614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199",
		"indexes":"zglssdhdsdzzsjzz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u8C01\u7684\u6267\u653F\u65F6\u95F4\u6700\u957F?",
		"id":20615
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FA\u4E2D\u5C11\u5987\u4E0D\u77E5\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u95FA\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20616
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77ED\u52FA\u6C0F",
		"indexes":"zcdgsnzslgjymfwlzxlnzbslzzy",
		"question":"\u300A\u5DE6\u4F20\u00B7\u5B9A\u516C\u56DB\u5E74\u300B\u4E2D\u8BF4\u9C81\u516C\u5C06\u6BB7\u6C11\u5206\u4E3A\u516D\u65CF\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u516D\u65CF\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20617
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u518D\u987E\u7ED9\u4E8B\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycysctzkhyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u4F8D\u4ECE\u9014\u4E2D\u53E3\u53F7\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u559D\u7C73\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsgdzqjdfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u79CB\u8282\u7684\u98CE\u4FD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"mhqglxhcdjwdxkzjscznwsrzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u540D\u82B1\u503E\u56FD\u4E24\u76F8\u6B22\uFF0C\u5E38\u5F97\u541B\u738B\u5E26\u7B11\u770B\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BD7\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u79CD\u7BF1\u8FB9\u83CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmdcjhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u695A\u6C5F\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8482\u5C3C\u00B7\u535A\u683C\u65AF",
		"indexes":"NBAlsszadqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u77EE\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6167\u5FC3\u5B97",
		"indexes":"xlngpxbsszdfz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D3E\u7CFB\u4E0D\u662F\u7985\u5B97\u7684\u5206\u652F\uFF1F",
		"id":20623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsywtwdsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u665A\u5510\u4E94\u4EE3\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":20624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyhjcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u82B1\u95F4\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":20625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsscdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5546\u671D\u7684\u738B\uFF1F",
		"id":20626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u521D\u95FB\u6D95\u6CEA\u6EE1\u8863\u88F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u767B\u9AD8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u7EEE\u53CC\u9E33\u9E2F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbqyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u957F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u70DF\u671B\u4E94\u6D25",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbwzyycbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u5728\u72F1\u548F\u8749\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u852C\u5145\u81B3\u7518\u957F\u85FF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscyzqbhssze",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9080\u4EBA\u5085\u7C89\u7C89",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdwctj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u6E2D\u5DDD\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u5341\u91CC\u626C\u5DDE\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmzbeszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u8D60\u522B\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC",
		"indexes":"wyhdalpkjzxzdzgrs",
		"question":"\u552F\u4E00\u83B7\u5F97\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u91D1\u8D28\u52CB\u7AE0\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u96E8\u4F94\u6614\u8D24",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljszztskzyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u9001\u5FE0\u5DDE\u592A\u5B88\u5EB7\u662D\u8FDC\u7B49\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59EC",
		"indexes":"dkxsm",
		"question":"\u5E1D\u55BE\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E8B\u5B81\u6020\u9051",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljfszsflzcleez",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u5949\u4F7F\u7B51\u6714\u65B9\u516D\u5DDE\u57CE\u7387\u5C14\u800C\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6307\u6325\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsqcdzspwzjg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u6B63\u4E09\u54C1\u6B66\u804C\u4EAC\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":20637
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u611F\u65F6\u5FC3\u7EEA\u6773\u96BE\u5E73",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyjysros",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u5341\u65E5\u5076\u4E66\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5782\u6761\u62C2\u9AFB\u9B1F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcszyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lqsyngrfmd",
		"question":"\u7BEE\u7403\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u56FD\u4EBA\u53D1\u660E\u5F97\uFF1F",
		"id":20640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u73E0\u5728\u9493\u77F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstkmcyzdwbbxsyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u6606\u660E\u6C60\u664F\u5750\u7B54\u738B\u5175\u90E8\u73E3\u4E09\u97F5\u89C1\u793A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u7269\u51C4\u51C4\u5BBF\u96E8\u6536",
		"indexes":"xlnjbschfrcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u7687\u752B\u5189\u300A\u6625\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u95E8\u9635",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsscdcpm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u8BCD\u7684\u8BCD\u724C\u540D\uFF1F",
		"id":20643
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u821C\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"mzxchhjyssbyfdzcfxcwzmywsgdwdymqwzsnwdw",
		"question":"\u6BDB\u4E3B\u5E2D\u66FE\u6325\u6BEB\u201C\u4E5D\u7591\u5C71\u4E0A\u767D\u4E91\u98DE\uFF0C\u5E1D\u5B50\u4E58\u98CE\u4E0B\u7FE0\u5FAE\u201D\u8D5E\u7F8E\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0A\u53E4\u5E1D\u738B\u7684\u82F1\u540D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8FD9\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u5E1D\u738B\uFF1F",
		"id":20644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u86A9\u5C24",
		"indexes":"zldzshdhszjdzz",
		"question":"\u201C\u6DBF\u9E7F\u5927\u6218\u201D\u662F\u7687\u5E1D\u548C\u8C01\u4E4B\u95F4\u7684\u6218\u4E89\uFF1F",
		"id":20645
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73AF\u4F69\u7A7A\u5F52\u6708\u4E0B\u9B42",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u56DB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u659C\u697C\u4E0A\u4E94\u66F4\u949F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywtesze",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u5BB6\u4F55\u5904\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczchzgxeszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u957F\u5E72\u884C\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u6BDB\u5E26\u96EA\u6C57\u6C14\u84B8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfjhjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BC4\u97E9\u8C0F\u8BAE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u61A9\u738B\u5C11\u5E9C\u4E1C\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsyzqdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u989C\u771F\u537F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529F\u7591\u590D\u590F\u521D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjcxhhdwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3E\u66FE\u300A\u5B5D\u548C\u7687\u5E1D\u633D\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u548C\u897F\u8543\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyshxfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u9001\u548C\u897F\u8543\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60ED\u975E\u718F\u98CE\u5531",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszhjryblcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E2D\u548C\u8282\u65E5\u5BB4\u767E\u50DA\u8D50\u8BD7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u5EAD\u6C99\u6B63\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u662D\u541B\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u751F\u79EF\u77F3\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhsjcgzsxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u76F8\u9A70\u9010",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsdmx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5927\u6F20\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78B0\u5E8A",
		"indexes":"jjtcnzxmbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u7ADE\u6280\u4F53\u64CD\u7537\u5B50\u9879\u76EE\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u5C4F\u8F9E\u91D1\u6BBF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzfhbyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5949\u548C\u522B\u8D8A\u738B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u8F6E\u6CD5\u738B",
		"indexes":"mczxzffdsdfwhwddfzwtcxzbwxlnwbsybwzl",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u5728\u897F\u85CF\u5206\u5C01\u7684\u4E09\u5927\u6CD5\u738B\u548C\u4E94\u5927\u5730\u65B9\u4E4B\u738B\uFF0C\u7EDF\u79F0\u897F\u85CF\u516B\u738B\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9675\u5E78\u65E7\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmzxwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u91CD\u5E78\u6B66\u529F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u6C5F\u4EAC\u201D",
		"indexes":"xlngbsnjlssdcw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u4EAC\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u79F0\u8C13\uFF1F",
		"id":20661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C34\u8C03\u6B4C\u5934\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyqzdqp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u66F2\u4E2D\u7684\u66F2\u724C\uFF1F",
		"id":20662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u77F3\u58D5\u540F\u300B",
		"indexes":"dfpbzhnhbjnszlhdsydzpxlnbbszyqjdzp",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u6F02\u6CCA\u5728\u6E56\u5357\u6E56\u5317\u5883\u5185\u65F6\uFF0C\u4F5C\u4E86\u5F88\u591A\u5931\u610F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u8FD9\u4E00\u671F\u95F4\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E16\u8BF4\u65B0\u8BED\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u7AE0\u56DE\u4F53\u5C0F\u8BF4\u96C6",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u767B\u697C\u8D4B\u300B",
		"indexes":"smxrshcddwrbcwfsxlnbzpbsfsdbz",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5927\u6587\u4EBA\uFF0C\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u8D4B\u5723\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u8D4B\u5723\u201D\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":20665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5305\u8EAB\u5DE5\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u7BC7\u5199\u5B9E\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E66\u738B\u77E5\u8F7D\u6710\u5C71\u6742\u548F\u540E\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsytyspsrdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7530\u56ED\u8BD7\u6D3E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u72C2\u4EBA\u65E5\u8BB0\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6587\u5B66\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u7BC7\u53CD\u5C01\u5EFA\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4",
		"indexes":"xlnxgywxzpdmsscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u900D\u9065\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsxqzzsw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u8BF8\u5B50\u6563\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":20669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u548F\u6000\u4E94\u767E\u5B57\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsywyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20670
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"bshjzzdqmshtzy500yrqzgydswnx",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u753B\u5BB6\u5F20\u62E9\u7AEF\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u4E0A\u6CB3\u56FE\u300B\u4E2D\u6709500\u4F59\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4F4D\u5973\u6027\uFF1F",
		"id":20671
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u5F85\u65E0\u82B1\u7A7A\u6298\u679D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdqnjly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u79CB\u5A18\u300A\u91D1\u7F15\u8863\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5C0F\u77F3\u6F6D\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlspbjytwyytsdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8BD7\u7BC7\u4E0D\u5177\u6709\u6258\u7269\u5BD3\u610F\u7279\u8272\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20673
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u9999\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlngftbszjcdzcft",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4F5B\u5802\u4E0D\u662F\u7D2B\u7981\u57CE\u7684\u85CF\u4F20\u4F5B\u5802\uFF1F",
		"id":20674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u4E45\u4FB5\u7F57\u889C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u7389\u9636\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u5F80\u5C82\u6B8A\u8C03",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbwdyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u7684\u300A\u548F\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u9E21\u8D77\u821E",
		"indexes":"xlngbssgddg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u5178\u6545\uFF1F",
		"id":20677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB5\u56DE\u9053\u6797\u8F99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwjnsxyzjsbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u89C1\u5357\u5C71\u5915\u9633\u53EC\u76D1\u5E08\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u5C71\u9AD8\u6E10\u51FA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbydyxgcyszlm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u767B\u53F6\u53BF\u6545\u57CE\u8C12\u6C88\u8BF8\u6881\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FE7\u4ECE\u671B\u91CC\u5BBD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwwxxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u671B\u4E61\u5915\u6CDB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u5357\u4EAD\u6000\u8F9B\u5927\u300B",
		"indexes":"hfsxqzldqxcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u8377\u98CE\u9001\u9999\u6C14\uFF0C\u7AF9\u9732\u6EF4\u6E05\u54CD\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u6566\u671D\u91CE\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsjysbcblzsyssh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u5341\u516B\u8D50\u767E\u50DA\u8FFD\u8D4F\u56E0\u4E66\u6240\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u79CB\u4E50\u672A\u592E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlslddybl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u9E9F\u5FB7\u6BBF\u5BB4\u767E\u50DA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7CB2",
		"indexes":"jaqzzwxcjzgdss",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u4E2D\u6587\u5B66\u6210\u5C31\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u591A\u6742\u9F13\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20685
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB3\u738B\u5251",
		"indexes":"xlnbjbsyzggdmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u628A\u5251\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u540D\u5251\uFF1F",
		"id":20686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u677E\u58F0\u665A\u7A97\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwcldtcdnzwyysycsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u540C\u4ECE\u5F1F\u5357\u658B\u73A9\u6708\u5FC6\u5C71\u9634\u5D14\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u6237\u58F0\u660E\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzfhtznftpgzcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5949\u548C\u592A\u5B50\u7EB3\u5983\u592A\u5E73\u516C\u4E3B\u51FA\u964D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u6D3D\u671D\u91CE\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszhjcbgyjyssh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E2D\u548C\u8282\u8D50\u767E\u5B98\u71D5\u96C6\u56E0\u793A\u6240\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u6D66\u6E05\u6C5F\u4E07\u91CC\u6865",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfwgjshnhb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u95FB\u5B98\u519B\u6536\u6CB3\u5357\u6CB3\u5317\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BFE\u6210\u5E94\u7B2C\u4E00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljslyzrht",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u9001\u674E\u9095\u4E4B\u4EFB\u6ED1\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8868\u745E\u826F\u5728\u5179",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljwtdx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u6E29\u6C64\u5BF9\u96EA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3\u9A70\u660E\u6708\u5173",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u9500\u65E5\u51FA\u4E0D\u89C1\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczgsygxbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9AD8\u9002\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3E\u5934\u671B\u660E\u6708",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u591C\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D2A\u5DDE\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglssfjsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u798F\u5EFA\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":20696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4EBF",
		"indexes":"bsnjjxzdqzcmzzddswgxlnwbswgzl",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u5E74\u95F4\u5978\u90AA\u4F17\u591A\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u81ED\u540D\u662D\u8457\u7684\u5F53\u5C5E\u201C\u4E94\u9B3C\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u4E94\u9B3C\u201D\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u89C1\u964C\u5934\u6768\u67F3\u8272",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclyjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u7389\u9636\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F3\u845B\u4F3C\u6500\u6A1B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwzfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u81F3\u5206\u9655\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u653F\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsytdymdsbxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u4EE3\u6709\u540D\u7684\u5341\u516B\u5B66\u58EB\uFF1F",
		"id":20700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u4F3C\u6D1E\u5EAD\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlhynbcsykjdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6000\u8FDC\u300A\u51DD\u78A7\u6C60\u4F8D\u5BB4\u770B\u7ADE\u6E21\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20701
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u9E1F\u6816\u521D\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczccdygsxjdcesft",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u7684\u300A\u4E0E\u9AD8\u9002\u859B\u636E\u767B\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u6D6E\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u613F\u541B\u591A\u91C7\u64B7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u76F8\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u56FD\u4E09\u5343\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhhmz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u4F55\u6EE1\u5B50\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DEB\u5C71\u8FDE\u695A\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbjnn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u5F04\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u8D60\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300B",
		"indexes":"zypzsmhbsjcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u9189\u6708\u9891\u4E2D\u5723\uFF0C\u8FF7\u82B1\u4E0D\u4E8B\u541B\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20706
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B7B\u751F\u957F\u522B\u79BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmdcjhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u695A\u6C5F\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u620F\u51EB\u5206\u65AD\u5CB8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlhjzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8FD8\u4EAC\u8D60\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8854\u6CE5\u529B\u5C1A\u5FAE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzzyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u9DDF\u300A\u548F\u71D5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u4E18\u5931\u660E",
		"indexes":"xmngqjbsxybjdzyqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u60C5\u8282\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u9879\u7FBD\u672C\u7EAA\u300B\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u60C5\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":20710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u53F2",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyesssdfc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53F2\u201D\u7684\u8303\u7574\uFF1F",
		"id":20711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u6708\u601C\u7B5D\u67F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxybfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F90\u5F66\u4F2F\u300A\u82B3\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6301\u6B64\u8C22\u9AD8\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbgsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5173\u5C71\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u79B9\u9521",
		"indexes":"bjyzxsybwqljhylwljnzcjhsrczwxsjlqwxlnwbsyjlzl",
		"question":"\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u5728\u9999\u5C71\u4E0E\u516B\u4F4D\u8006\u8001\u96C6\u4F1A\u3001\u71D5\u4E50\uFF0C\u4E3A\u4E86\u7EAA\u5FF5\u8FD9\u6B21\u96C6\u4F1A\uFF0C\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E3A\u201C\u9999\u5C71\u4E5D\u8001\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u8001\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u5149\u8349\u9732\u56E2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycqywy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u671B\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u65E5\u9001\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbsrhd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u4EFB\u534E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8427\u6761\u5F02\u4EE3\u4E0D\u540C\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u524D\u65CC\u9619\u585E\u901A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhsztcszz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9014\u6B21\u9655\u5DDE\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u95E8\u62AB\u7389\u9986",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxdlsgdym",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u767B\u9A8A\u5C71\u9AD8\u9876\u5BD3\u76EE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u6B46",
		"indexes":"xlnwsgrwbscwwjzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u66F9\u9B4F\u4E94\u541B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6307\u9EBE\u516B\u8352\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmxwgqsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u5E78\u6B66\u529F\u5E86\u5584\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF7\u4EBA\u5403\u996D",
		"indexes":"cjszgzzydctjrznlxnzjtzgrdhyyxjhxlnxbszgrgndjh",
		"question":"\u6625\u8282\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\uFF0C\u5728\u519C\u5386\u65B0\u5E74\u8FD9\u51E0\u5929\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u90FD\u4F1A\u6709\u4E00\u4E9B\u5FCC\u8BB3\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u8FC7\u5E74\u7684\u5FCC\u8BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":20722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F6C\u6218\u5165\u768B\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzlm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u7D2B\u9A9D\u9A6C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u796D\u7940",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsydyljddzdhly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u79B9\u9675\u796D\u5178\u7684\u5236\u5EA6\u548C\u793C\u4EEA\uFF1F",
		"id":20724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88F4\u91CC\u5339\u5E95\u65AF",
		"indexes":"mlsspswjnsesld",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u62C9\u677E\u8D5B\u8DD1\u662F\u4E3A\u7EAA\u5FF5\u8C01\u800C\u8BBE\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u5986\u66F2\u672A\u7EC8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydzsysmr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u4EE3\u5F20\u4F8D\u5FA1\u4F24\u7F8E\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8892\u9791",
		"indexes":"zglssyydwhcbdlsjcwhslgxlngmzbswhzl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6709\u4E00\u6BB5\u4E94\u80E1\u79F0\u9738\u7684\u5386\u53F2\uFF0C\u7B80\u79F0\u4E94\u80E1\u5341\u516D\u56FD\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u80E1\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20727
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE2\u8367\u5FC3\u6B32\u65E0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwdth",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6D1E\u5EAD\u6E56\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648",
		"indexes":"xlnglssdgjmyddbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u6CA1\u6709\u5B9A\u90FD\u6C74\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":20729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F50\u5A01\u738B",
		"indexes":"zhzbsfszcqsqdyqzddzzsjgdcycqwbzsxlsbswbzy",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u4FAF\u4E89\u9738\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E00\u8D77\u91CD\u5927\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u4E8B\u4EF6\u3002\u53E4\u4EE3\u66FE\u6709\u201C\u6625\u79CB\u4E94\u9738\u201D\u4E4B\u8BF4\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u9738\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u5CF0\u7ED5\u745E\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyplsdsyfcyznsyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u84EC\u83B1\u4E09\u6BBF\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5949\u6555\u548F\u7EC8\u5357\u5C71\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u751F",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyzjzdzyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u6742\u5267\u4E2D\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u89D2\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":20732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u571F\u9CD6",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzggdzmdjddy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4E5D\u5927\u6BD2\u836F\uFF1F",
		"id":20733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u7CB1\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnzjbsgdjrqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9152\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u8282\u65E5\u5E86\u9152\uFF1F",
		"id":20734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u65E5\u534E\u7EC4\u7EC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljxlycxfdxltjyysqg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u6821\u730E\u4E49\u6210\u559C\u9022\u5927\u96EA\u7387\u9898\u4E5D\u97F5\u4EE5\u793A\u7FA4\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20735
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5173\u671B\u6E10\u8D4A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjsfcwsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u4E30\u57CE\u738B\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u97E9\u7891\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqylf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u4E50\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":20737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u5B97\u9053",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsymdhqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u4EE3\u540E\u4E03\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":20738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6234\u590D\u53E4",
		"indexes":"nscxlygspjhpxlnwdjhpdyxzd",
		"question":"\u5357\u5B8B\u51FA\u73B0\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BD7\u6D3E\u201C\u6C5F\u6E56\u6D3E\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5BF9\u6C5F\u6E56\u6D3E\u7684\u5F71\u54CD\u6700\u5927\uFF1F",
		"id":20739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E3D\u840D",
		"indexes":"xlnwsjydymydpsjjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C04\u7BAD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u6CA1\u6709\u6253\u7834\u4E16\u754C\u7EAA\u5F55\uFF1F",
		"id":20740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F9D\u7136\u8E51\u4E91\u80CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbhmyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u5FFD\u68A6\u6E38\u4ED9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6B21",
		"indexes":"mgcdztzmqdhfsdgmdnmqyhcyblwzzybnmqycdtbwjqwhcygfsljcnmqy",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u5728\u7EDF\u6CBB\u672B\u671F\u90FD\u4F1A\u53D1\u751F\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u7684\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\uFF0C\u6C49\u671D\u4E5F\u4E0D\u4F8B\u5916\uFF0C\u6700\u7EC8\u4E5F\u88AB\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\u50AC\u5F97\u571F\u5D29\u74E6\u89E3\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6C49\u671D\u4E00\u5171\u53D1\u751F\u4E86\u51E0\u6B21\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\uFF1F",
		"id":20742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u51C9",
		"indexes":"xlngdfbshcsqdwhzd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E4C\u6052\u9A7B\u5730\uFF1F",
		"id":20743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B0\u25A1\u5DF2\u9542\u6D25",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u5B88\u5C81\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20744
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9601\u9053\u9042\u6210\u589F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxxqshl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u5E78\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u9675\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20745
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u519B\u971E",
		"indexes":"dyghowsjdzgrss",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u83B7\u6B27\u6587\u65AF\u5956\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u8BCF\u8D4B\u97F5\u5F97\u524D\u5B57",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9880\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlgysrjqzpdjscwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u53CA\u5176\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u4ECB\u7ECD\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BE5\u5ED3\u70DF\u4E91\u8868",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzydces",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u8C12\u5927\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20749
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u7827\u6363\u6587\u7EC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u571F\u8C46",
		"indexes":"ctszgrjjzzsyxsycqhbszsdqsbhzyzhctysgjddfxlnxbsswdqszy",
		"question":"\u4F20\u7EDF\u4E0A\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u8BB2\u7A76\u5728\u6B63\u5F0F\u5BB4\u5E2D\u4E0A\u8981\u5403\u201C\u4E03\u8364\u516B\u7D20\u201D,\u8FD9\u662F\u5BF9\u201C\u4E03\u7D20\u3001\u516B\u8364\u201D\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E2D\u534E\u4F20\u7EDF\u996E\u98DF\u89C4\u77E9\u7684\u98A0\u8986\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6240\u8C13\u7684\u4E03\u7D20\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u6865\u660E\u6708\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjyzhcpg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u5BC4\u626C\u5DDE\u97E9\u7EF0\u5224\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u5BAA",
		"indexes":"sgmjmcdfqnhmxltsxlnwbsxlrw",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u540D\u5C06\u9A6C\u8D85\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u4E43\u6C49\u672B\u897F\u51C9\u592A\u5B88\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u51C9\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":20753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"sgsqywmdwhjshhqyyshhwhsjxlnwbsyshhwhsj",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u6709\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u4E94\u864E\u5C06\uFF0C\u8700\u6C49\u540E\u671F\u4E5F\u6709\u8700\u6C49\u540E\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8700\u6C49\u540E\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":20754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F6D\u6CFD\u83CA\u521D\u6536",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxjyjrxlwtdgdqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u4E5D\u65E5\u5E78\u4E34\u6E2D\u4EAD\u767B\u9AD8\u5F97\u79CB\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52FF\u4EE5\u6076\u5C0F\u800C\u4E3A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczyxqsw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u5148\u79E6\u6563\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":20756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590D\u503C\u63A5\u8206\u9189",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlcqslzcghyby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E38\u537F\u300A\u9001\u674E\u4E2D\u4E1E\u5F52\u6C49\u9633\u522B\u4E1A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B50\u9EC4\u91D1\u52D2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlsyqsydzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u4E09\u6708\u66F2\u6C34\u5BB4\u5F97\u5C0A\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsyhmsp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u97E9\u5B5F\u8BD7\u6D3E\uFF1F",
		"id":20759
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyqgdcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u56FD\u7684\u81E3\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":20760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90A3\u582A\u7384\u9B13\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczszwtdylby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u9898\u5927\u5EBE\u5CAD\u5317\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA6\u7FF0.\u65AF\u6258\u514B\u987F",
		"indexes":"NBApjzgzddqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u5E73\u5747\u52A9\u653B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u5C71\u843D\u65E5\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrshsddz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9001\u4FAF\u56DB\u5F97\u5F39\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C4F\u6B32\u9664\u5962\u653F\u8FD4\u6DF3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzxhdyjczqblt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u54B8\u4EA8\u6BBF\u5BB4\u8FD1\u81E3\u8BF8\u4EB2\u67CF\u6881\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u6B4C\u601D\u6740\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxygs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5F52\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u59C6\u65AF\u7279\u6717",
		"indexes":"hdzgjzddhfzxcxsss",
		"question":"\u83B7\u5F97\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u73AF\u6CD5\u81EA\u884C\u8F66\u9009\u624B\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":20766
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u82B1\u6405\u72EC\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyfdqbm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u8D4B\u5F97\u59BE\u8584\u547D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20767
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6765\u82B1\u9E1F\u82E5\u4E3A\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryjtyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u996F\u5510\u6C38\u660C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u4EE5\u9677\u90BB\u5883",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrdsyssfdddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u4E1A\u5E08\u5C71\u623F\u5F85\u4E01\u5927\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6CC9\u6EE1\u6E05\u542C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwdwctj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u6E2D\u5DDD\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u82B1\u72B9\u4F3C\u5760\u697C\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u91D1\u8C37\u56ED\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D8B\u8D8B\u516E\u8DC4\u8DC4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycyywmep",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u9E66\u9E49\u732B\u513F\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F59\u5F97\u5949\u620E\u65C3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczaxhzsgdqbqzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u897F\u8FD8\u81F3\u6563\u5173\u7B54\u4E54\u8865\u9619\u77E5\u4E4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u79CD\u7BF1\u8FB9\u83CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwzztys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u7AE0\u53F0\u591C\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u4E0A\u76F8\u9022\u65E0\u7EB8\u7B14",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczccfrjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u300A\u9022\u5165\u4EAC\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5E38\u76D1",
		"indexes":"tcdzygzzsywsxlnxbsyws",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u4E2D\u592E\u5B98\u5236\u4E2D\u8BBE\u6709\u4E94\u7F72\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u7F72\uFF1F",
		"id":20776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F6E\u843D\u591C\u6C5F\u659C\u6708\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhtjld",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u9898\u91D1\u9675\u6E21\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u5BB4\u9F7F\u7C2A\u7F28",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyfhzrlcyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5949\u548C\u6B63\u65E5\u4E34\u671D\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20778
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u89C1\u6709\u4EBA\u8FD8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbzgx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u957F\u5E72\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F58\u5CB3",
		"indexes":"xjdsfhsgwmysqzddbwessyxlnwbsyessy",
		"question":"\u897F\u664B\u7684\u58EB\u98CE\u548C\u8BD7\u6B4C\u95FB\u540D\u4E8E\u4E16\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4E3A\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53CB\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53CB\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8\u7591\u5F85\u4F5B\u5F00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcscesjryz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u4E5D\u65E5\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9075\u6E1A\u672A\u6765\u9E3F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyyyhjztb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u6708\u591C\u6709\u6000\u7B80\u8BF8\u540C\u75C5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20782
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73E0\u7B94\u98D8\u706F\u72EC\u81EA\u5F52",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwtylznd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u5229\u6D32\u5357\u6E21\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u9EC4\u6CB3\u7ED5\u9ED1\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzyzry",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u4E2D\u5EB8\u300A\u5F81\u4EBA\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u591C\u504F\u77E5\u6625\u6C14\u6696",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlfpyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u65B9\u5E73\u300A\u6708\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u582A\u95F2\u5750\u7EC6\u601D\u91CF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlydzjwscqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u6E21\u4E2D\u6C5F\u671B\u77F3\u57CE\u6CE3\u4E0B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51EF\u5C14\u7279\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"NBAlsshdgjzddqds",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u83B7\u5F97\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u961F\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u524D\u4E8B\u4E0D\u5FD8\uFF0C\u540E\u4E8B\u4E4B\u5E08",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968F\u610F\u6625\u82B3\u6B47",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhryzzdxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u4E0E\u8BF8\u5B50\u767B\u5C98\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5F81\u9A6C\u4E0D\u80A5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1A\u590D\u4E94\u94E2\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrqmrymdsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u65E5\u5BB4\u6885\u9053\u58EB\u623F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u4F3C\u6D1E\u5EAD\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlhynbcsykjdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6000\u8FDC\u300A\u51DD\u78A7\u6C60\u4F8D\u5BB4\u770B\u7ADE\u6E21\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u751F\u6B32\u95EE\u5929",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjfhsypyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E0A\u5143\u917A\u5BB4\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u622C",
		"indexes":"jcyzszglsshldbaysbsycmzzdlzxlnywbsylz",
		"question":"\u5978\u81E3\u4E00\u76F4\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6DF7\u4E71\u7684\u4E0D\u5B89\u56E0\u7D20\uFF0C\u5317\u5B8B\u6709\u81ED\u540D\u662D\u8457\u7684\u201C\u516D\u8D3C\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u516D\u8D3C\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679D\u4ECE\u70B9\u7F00\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjljc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u526A\u5F69\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u71D5\u516C\u5CB3\u5DDE\u5C71\u57CE",
		"indexes":"xlnbbshzzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u8D3A\u77E5\u7AE0\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u79E6\u4E2D\u611F\u79CB\u5BC4\u8FDC\u4E0A\u4EBA\u300B",
		"indexes":"hjrgjzzznscznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u9EC4\u91D1\u71C3\u6842\u5C3D\uFF0C\u58EE\u5FD7\u9010\u5E74\u8870\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20797
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u83F2\u56FE\u65AF",
		"indexes":"gdayhcsrss",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u9633\u7834\u4E1C\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwcdlhsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u521D\u5230\u9646\u6D51\u5C71\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u62C2\u69DB\u9732\u534E\u6D53",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbqpdsszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E05\u5E73\u8C03\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20800
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"hcsqnxngfxhxlngdfbsnxndzd",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u5357\u5308\u5974\u5F52\u9644\u897F\u6C49\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5308\u5974\u7684\u9A7B\u5730\uFF1F",
		"id":20801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706F\u524D\u9976\u770B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczxsyyxxyt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u77E5\u8D24\u300A\u4E0A\u5143\u591C\u6548\u5C0F\u5EBE\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20802
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E3F\u96C1\u4E0D\u582A\u6101\u91CC\u542C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscchxjhy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u884C\u7ECF\u534E\u9634\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20803
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u522B\u6765\u6CA7\u6D77\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywhsxhlcgr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u6DEE\u4E0A\u559C\u4F1A\u6881\u5DDD\u6545\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20804
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB9\u8272\u671D\u671D\u843D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u82B3\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u6912",
		"indexes":"wjsqdrhcxlxlngbsywx",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u664B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u597D\u5403\u8F9B\u8FA3\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u8F9B\uFF1F",
		"id":20806
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E88\u5367\u5357\u5C71\u963F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwbzwhdsltsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u522B\u4E4B\u671B\u540E\u72EC\u5BBF\u84DD\u7530\u5C71\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20807
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C0\u547D\u8FD4\u7A77\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20808
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F6\u843D\u4ECE\u6B64\u59CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxygsp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5B64\u677E\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u601C\u591C\u534A\u865A\u524D\u5E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u8D3E\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"zglscyjzzcxmnxbsjzzl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u66FE\u6709\u201C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\u4E4B\u79F0\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u4E5D\u5DDE\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u5792\u8427\u8427\u82A6\u837B\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscqqzqxpsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u94B1\u8D77\u300A\u8D60\u9619\u4E0B\u88F4\u820D\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20812
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F59\u6C1B\u5411\u65E5\u9555",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxtzhcygpcks",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u5929\u6B63\u300A\u548C\u9648\u5143\u5149\u5E73\u6F6E\u5BC7\u8BD7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79BB\u9B42\u6697\u9A6C\u60CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcscdltcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u916C\u675C\u9E9F\u53F0\u6625\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D35\u621A\u6743\u95E8\u5F97\u7B14\u8FF9",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczhyss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u6108\u300A\u5C71\u77F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u884C\u5230\u4E2D\u5EAD\u6570\u82B1\u6735",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyxcc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u6625\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u843D\u5F81\u9014\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyqwdgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u79CB\u665A\u767B\u53E4\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72B9\u4E3A\u79BB\u4EBA\u7167\u843D\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzmjr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u6CCC\u300A\u5BC4\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5C71\u5BC7\u76D7\u83AB\u76F8\u4FB5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BBF\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u832B\u832B\u6C5F\u6C49\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsksxwdlljs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u53F8\u7A7A\u66D9\u300A\u559C\u5916\u5F1F\u5362\u7EB6\u89C1\u5BBF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20820
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u7A7A\u7EFF\u91CE\u95F2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjbcw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5180\u5317\u6625\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20821
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u58F0\u5CE1\u5916\u957F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjws",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20822
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u8FDC\u5FA1\u6148\u7559",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsfhsjcgzsxfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20823
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u949F\u9F13\u9707\u5CA9\u5ECA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmzrlc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u6B63\u65E5\u4E34\u671D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20824
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5411\u5BA0\u8BD7\u96C6",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbssgsqdsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BD7\u96C6\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8BD7\u96C6\uFF1F",
		"id":20825
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E23\u7B5D\u91D1\u7C9F\u67F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczldtz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u7AEF\u300A\u542C\u7B5D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20826
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u884C\u4E07\u4E58\u51FA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljhchlcscqg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u6248\u4ECE\u8FD8\u6D1B\u5448\u4F8D\u4ECE\u7FA4\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20827
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C85\u6709\u82B7\u516E\u6FA7\u6709\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnstdsrlbddbzxlnjsbsczxln",
		"question":"\u300A\u884C\u8DEF\u96BE\u300B\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u884C\u8DEF\u96BE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20828
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A35\u4EBA\u5F52\u6B32\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywdjqjszds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u7684\u300A\u5BC4\u5168\u6912\u5C71\u4E2D\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20829
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC6\u9635",
		"indexes":"sbbfzybzzfxlnyxbsybzf",
		"question":"\u300A\u5B59\u8191\u5175\u6CD5\u300B\u4E2D\u6709\u516B\u79CD\u9635\u6CD5\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u9635\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":20830
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9526\u5E06\u5E94\u662F\u5230\u5929\u6DAF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywteszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20831
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u65E5\u843D\u6881\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczxhzq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u6D51\u300A\u65E9\u79CB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20832
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u85C9\u505A\u65E7",
		"indexes":"zggdwhbdjsqzhdgjdyjbhzqtyyscdhddgjzwsfrhdbcsdjdzccxxlnxsfbsyzwsf",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6587\u5316\u535A\u5927\u7CBE\u6DF1\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u5F88\u591A\u53E4\u7C4D\u90FD\u5DF2\u7EDD\u7248\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ED6\u539F\u56E0\u5931\u4F20\uFF0C\u4F46\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u53E4\u7C4D\u4F5C\u4F2A\u624B\u6CD5\u8BA9\u5F88\u591A\u4E0D\u4F20\u4E16\u7684\u7ECF\u5178\u518D\u6B21\u51FA\u73B0\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E9B\u624B\u6CD5\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F5C\u4F2A\u624B\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":20833
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57AB\u5E95",
		"indexes":"xlngtyycbsqyygd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u4F53\u80B2\u7528\u8BCD\u4E0D\u662F\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20834
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u4F2F\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lxqcjzlcsyzgmdsjzgmnymbbgszyqwxlnwbsbbgszy",
		"question":"\u300A\u5217\u4ED9\u5168\u4F20\u300B\u8BB0\u8F7D\u4E86\u8D22\u795E\u7237\u8D75\u516C\u660E\u7684\u4E8B\u8FF9\uFF0C\u8D75\u516C\u660E\u4E43\u5143\u660E\u516B\u90E8\u9B3C\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u516B\u90E8\u9B3C\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20835
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u71EE",
		"indexes":"gdcnycjrdrwcdhsqyzmdbcxlsbsybc",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u79F0\u80FD\u4EE5\u8D22\u6551\u4EBA\u7684\u4EBA\u4E3A\u53A8\uFF0C\u4E1C\u6C49\u65F6\u671F\u6709\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u516B\u53A8\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u516B\u53A8\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20836
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6B66",
		"indexes":"zhjcxyzgzqhzjdwcbzskcwzgwqnzzzyztsdwjzzjxlnwbszhj",
		"question":"\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\u6218\u56FD\u81F3\u79E6\u6C49\u4E4B\u9645\uFF0C\u591A\u4E3A\u7B56\u8FA9\u4E4B\u58EB\uFF0C\u53EF\u79F0\u4E3A\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E94\u5343\u5E74\u4E2D\u6700\u65E9\u4E5F\u6700\u7279\u6B8A\u7684\u5916\u4EA4\u653F\u6CBB\u5BB6\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20837
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65A9",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssysqdzyhddflzdzdxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u5143\u65F6\u671F\u5BF9\u4E2D\u539F\u6C49\u5730\u7684\u6CD5\u5F8B\u5236\u5EA6\u4E2D\u7684\u5211\u7F5A\uFF1F",
		"id":20838
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606D\u4EB2\u738B",
		"indexes":"qcfjdfsfwjgfhefxlnwtmzwsyef",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5C01\u7235\u7684\u65B9\u5F0F\u5206\u4E3A\u519B\u529F\u5C01\u548C\u6069\u5C01\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u94C1\u5E3D\u5B50\u738B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6069\u5C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20839
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u5C71\u671B\u4E0D\u7A77",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlrqcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5165\u79E6\u5DDD\u754C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20840
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u8F66\u672A\u53EF\u6500",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyzygzds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4E8E\u7D2B\u4E91\u89C2\u8D60\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20841
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E1A\u6210\u8270\u96BE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszxjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u5E78\u664B\u9633\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20842
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u5B8B\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u5C01\u7235\u738B\u56FD\u516C",
		"indexes":"xlgygrdjmbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u7235\u540D\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20843
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5BAB\u56DB\u5E8F\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzjcgqcyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u4E5D\u6210\u5BAB\u79CB\u521D\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20844
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB5\u77E5\u5357\u571F\u70ED",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstyfsqjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u591C\u53D1\u4E09\u6CC9\u5373\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20845
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9547\u629A\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlngjgbsydxwsxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u673A\u6784\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u4EE3\u5BA3\u6170\u53F8\u4E0B\u8F96\uFF1F",
		"id":20846
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77E5\u547D\u662F\u7537\u5B50\u516D\u5341\u5C81",
		"indexes":"gwzgynldcwcwds",
		"question":"\u53E4\u6587\u4E2D\u5173\u4E8E\u5E74\u9F84\u7684\u79F0\u8C13\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20847
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u4E71",
		"indexes":"xlngzsbsfszwjnbcsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6218\u4E8B\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u9B4F\u664B\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":20848
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u79FB\u8C6B\u5DDE\u6A84\u300B",
		"indexes":"jaqzdyzdyscmdzpyjbzpdswjaqzzjxlnbbszpgyjaqzdzp",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u7684\u539F\u8457\u90FD\u5DF2\u5931\u4F20\uFF0C\u660E\u4EE3\u5F20\u6EA5\u6709\u51E0\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u90FD\u662F\u4E3A\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u505A\u96C6\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u6EA5\u5173\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20849
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u65B0\u4E66\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsjyddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u8D3E\u8C0A\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":20850
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56FD\u98CE\u300B",
		"indexes":"twzszgzxlsjrjdsebjskxscsejxlnxbsysej",
		"question":"\u5510\u6587\u5B97\u65F6\u5728\u56FD\u5B50\u5B66\u7ACB\u77F3\u5C06\u5112\u5BB6\u7684\u5341\u4E8C\u90E8\u7ECF\u4E66\u523B\u4E0B\uFF0C\u53F2\u79F0\u201C\u5341\u4E8C\u7ECF\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u5341\u4E8C\u7ECF\u201D",
		"id":20851
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5B54\u96C0\u4E1C\u5357\u98DE\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u957F\u7BC7\u6C49\u8D4B",
		"indexes":"xlnxgywxzpdmsscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20852
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7F57\u5BC6\u6B27\u4E0E\u8331\u4E3D\u53F6\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlbsyssbydwdbjds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u7684\u4E94\u5927\u60B2\u5267\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20853
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6625\u6C5F\u82B1\u6708\u591C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzclfts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u81EA\u521B\u4E50\u5E9C\u4F53\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20854
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u97E9\u975E\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"zggdwhzrjszwzldwhxlnxbsrjjd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6587\u5316\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5112\u5BB6\u662F\u6700\u4E3A\u4E3B\u6D41\u7684\u6587\u5316\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u7ECF\u5178\uFF1F",
		"id":20855
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8001\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"qcdjstcjlwgrdmzpwlczsxlnxbslczs",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u91D1\u5723\u53F9\u66FE\u5C06\u516D\u4F4D\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u540D\u8457\u8BC4\u4E3A\u201C\u516D\u624D\u5B50\u4E66\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u516D\u624D\u5B50\u4E66\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20856
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u539F\u541B\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u7BC7\u5177\u6709\u81EA\u7531\u601D\u60F3\u7684\u653F\u8BBA\u6587",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20857
	},
	{
		"answer":"25\u5C4A",
		"indexes":"sjjyayhsnj",
		"question":"\u9996\u5C4A\u7981\u70DF\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u5C4A\uFF1F",
		"id":20858
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"qcjqmgbzxsnrmqtzdsqcgydsq",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5C06\u5168\u8499\u53E4\u90E8\u4F17\u6089\u6570\u7EB3\u5165\u76DF\u65D7\u4F53\u5236\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u6E05\u671D\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u65D7\uFF1F",
		"id":20859
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CE\u841D\u66F4\u8499\u906E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwhspzlsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6D63\u7EB1\u7BC7\u8D60\u9646\u4E0A\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20860
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C1\u58F0\u8FDC\u8FC7\u6F47\u6E58\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwtyysy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u7476\u745F\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20861
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E14\u5C06\u56E2\u6247\u5171\u5F98\u5F8A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclzxy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u957F\u4FE1\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20862
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F9D\u65E7\u70DF\u7B3C\u5341\u91CC\u5824",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwzjlt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u91D1\u9675\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20863
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u9ECE\u4E16",
		"indexes":"gjzlzbzn",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u603B\u90E8\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":20864
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u953A\u7E47",
		"indexes":"xlnwsgrwbsdwwjzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u4E1C\u5434\u4E94\u541B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":20865
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C61\u7B75\u6577\u5FF5\u8BDA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwyfhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6E38\u6CD5\u534E\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20866
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u82E5\u8BB7",
		"indexes":"ssmxxszdqzzmdnsmljzxlnwbssmljzzy",
		"question":"\u82CF\u8F7C\u95E8\u4E0B\u5B66\u751F\u4F17\u591A\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4E43\u201C\u82CF\u95E8\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u82CF\u95E8\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20867
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDB\u5BF9\u4E00\u8A00\u91CD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljdwsdyqctdsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u7AEF\u5348\u4E09\u6BBF\u5BB4\u7FA4\u81E3\u63A2\u5F97\u795E\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6064\u4EBA\u4E88\u662F\u8D44",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlssxzzjfhz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u9001\u5F90\u5DDE\u5F20\u5EFA\u5C01\u8FD8\u9547\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E34\u98CE\u6005\u6000\u6B64",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsjxzssmfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u996F\u8BB8\u5DDE\u5B8B\u53F8\u9A6C\u8D74\u4EFB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B51\u97A0",
		"indexes":"zggdjyzqydgdcwcjxlxxngbscjdbm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5C31\u6709\u8DB3\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF0C\u53E4\u4EE3\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u8E74\u97A0\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u9009\u9879\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u8E74\u97A0\u201D\u7684\u522B\u540D\uFF1F",
		"id":20871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u7AE0\u53F0\u591C\u601D\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":20872
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B4C\u5439\u5B9B\u72B9\u6628",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjtqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20873
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u7389\u73AF",
		"indexes":"xrmndczbyxhsszdjdzmlnmxhszs",
		"question":"\u5F62\u5BB9\u7F8E\u5973\u7684\u8BCD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u95ED\u6708\u7F9E\u82B1\u7B97\u662F\u6700\u9876\u7EA7\u7684\u8D5E\u7F8E\u4E86\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u7F9E\u82B1\u662F\u6307\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u4E09",
		"indexes":"hwdyyfwnjqgfwjgz",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D\u4E8E\u5143\u5C01\u4E94\u5E74\u5C06\u5168\u56FD\u5206\u4E3A\u51E0\u4E2A\u5DDE\uFF1F",
		"id":20875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D85\u55BB",
		"indexes":"yxnzbsybyxs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6BD4\u55BB\u5F62\u5F0F\uFF1F",
		"id":20876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF1\u6797\u4EBA\u4E0D\u77E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwzlg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u7AF9\u91CC\u9986\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u99A5\u9752\u6EAA\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbssfjyydzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u4E0A\u5DF3\u6D6E\u6C5F\u5BB4\u97F5\u5F97\u5740\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u65E5\u6CB3\u6881\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbysb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20879
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u975E",
		"indexes":"xlnywbszhjddbrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":20880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u987B\u6000\u62B1\u91CD\u51C4\u51C4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlysdwesdcymxc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u9001\u9093\u738B\u4E8C\u5341\u5F1F\u4ECE\u76CA\u7267\u5BA3\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B32\u7A77\u5343\u91CC\u76EE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwzhdgql",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u4E4B\u6DA3\u300A\u767B\u9E73\u96C0\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u9634\u5E26\u53F6\u660F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwsflhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9001\u8D39\u516D\u8FD8\u8700\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC2\u5BDE\u7A7A\u5EAD\u6625\u6B32\u665A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlfpcy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u65B9\u5E73\u300A\u6625\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6709\u53CC\u7AF9\u6797",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgzcjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u6625\u6C5F\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20885
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5021\u5987\u9AD8\u697C\u522B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20886
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u6DF1\u70DF\u96FE\u591A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjszzzsk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u90D1\u5DDE\u5468\u53F8\u7A7A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20887
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u8349\u5DF2\u4E91\u66AE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwtysrdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u9001\u4EBA\u4E1C\u6E38\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u897F",
		"indexes":"tdkclzgzqssdhfdjzttzbtxfwsdxmngbssdzy",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5F00\u521B\u4E86\u4E2D\u56FD\u653F\u533A\u53F2\u4E0A\u9053\u548C\u5E9C\u7684\u5EFA\u5236\uFF0C\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u628A\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u4E3A\u5341\u9053\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5341\u9053\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u5357\u4E94\u5E9C\u7ECF\u7565\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"tczqcyfzgjdjmgysgfzmgfzsyjdsxlnwbsyfzjds",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u957F\u671F\u5904\u4E8E\u85E9\u9547\u5272\u636E\u7684\u5C40\u9762\uFF0C\u5171\u6709\u5341\u4E2A\u85E9\u9547\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u85E9\u9547\u8BBE\u6709\u8282\u5EA6\u4F7F\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u85E9\u9547\u8282\u5EA6\u4F7F\uFF1F",
		"id":20890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8054",
		"indexes":"zcclgjzldgjbbkxlnggj",
		"question":"\u6700\u521D\u6210\u7ACB\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u672F",
		"indexes":"xlngxmbsayhbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9879\u76EE\u4E0D\u662F\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":20892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u672F",
		"indexes":"xlngxmbsayhbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9879\u76EE\u4E0D\u662F\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":20893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5206\u5272\u636E\u7EA1\u7B79\u7B56",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclzqjzzbxllbeyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u6C5F\u5DDE\u91CD\u522B\u859B\u516D\u67F3\u516B\u4E8C\u5458\u5916\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u660E\u9001\u5BA2\u695A\u5C71\u5B64",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclfrlsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u8299\u84C9\u697C\u9001\u8F9B\u6E10\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F1A\u8272",
		"indexes":"yxctddywzdjgysdwpcjgwsfychzdjbjgxlngbsyhzdjbjg",
		"question":"\u6BB7\u589F\u51FA\u571F\u7684\u5E26\u6709\u6587\u5B57\u7684\u7532\u9AA8\u6709\u5341\u591A\u4E07\u7247\uFF0C\u4ECE\u7532\u9AA8\u6587\u4E0A\u53CD\u5E94\u51FA\u6C49\u5B57\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u7ED3\u6784\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C49\u5B57\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u7ED3\u6784\uFF1F",
		"id":20896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F2B\u4FDF\u660E\u5E74\u6842",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzydgdmx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u300A\u53E4\u4E1C\u95E8\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u6258\u8247",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsjxyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6781\u9650\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":20898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"xlbshddqbzywqdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u7684\u9A91\u5175\u4E3B\u8981\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20899
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D35\u6E38\u884C",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsccdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5C91\u53C2\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":20900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64\u8BED\u8BB0\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsxblgyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u767D\u9E7F\u89C2\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20901
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A5\u5230\u5C71\u4E2D\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwhjlt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6C49\u6C5F\u4E34\u773A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20902
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u897F",
		"indexes":"ttzbqgfwsdxlnxbsysd",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u628A\u5168\u56FD\u5206\u4E3A\u5341\u9053\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5341\u9053\uFF1F",
		"id":20903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82D4\u6DF1\u4E0D\u8FA8\u94ED",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlwwjt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6587\u7FC1\u8BB2\u5802\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94A6\u5929",
		"indexes":"scdzzjgzsysjqzgyljgzqzqwxlngbsyljzy",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u673A\u6784\u4E2D\u8BBE\u6709\u5BFA\u76D1\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u5171\u6709\u516D\u76D1\uFF0C\u5404\u4E13\u5176\u804C\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516D\u76D1\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20905
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82D4\u5206\u4F3C\u5217\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwcsm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u51FA\u77F3\u95E8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20906
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3\u6709\u7075\u7280\u4E00\u70B9\u901A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsysg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u968B\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u5949\u5929\u4E66\u62DC\u7410\u95F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u8700\u76F8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20908
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E66\u9E49\u524D\u5934\u4E0D\u6562\u8A00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzqygc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6731\u5E86\u9980\u300A\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BC1\u5723",
		"indexes":"xlngnhbstcdnh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u5E74\u53F7\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":20910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9152\u5E03",
		"indexes":"tdsrdmdqjjncyktjsqlytlyhscsgjqfjqjsjddzpxlnxbsjqdbc",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u675C\u7267\u7684\u4E03\u7EDD\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u6625\u300B\uFF0C\u4E00\u5F00\u5934\u5C31\u662F\u201C\u5343\u91CC\u83BA\u557C\u7EFF\u6620\u7EA2\uFF0C\u6C34\u6751\u5C71\u90ED\u9152\u65D7\u98CE\u201D\u3002\u9152\u65D7\u5C31\u662F\u9152\u5E97\u7684\u62DB\u724C\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u9152\u65D7\u7684\u522B\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":20911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u91ED\u7130\u9752\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxywshg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u697C\u81EA\u7BA1\u5F26",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsjrxlhjby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u50E7\u768E\u7136\u300A\u5BFB\u9646\u9E3F\u6E10\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20913
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6625\u666F\u7269\u6ECB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsywctsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u671B\u6625\u4EAD\u4F8D\u6E38\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u7B3C\u5BD2\u6C34\u6708\u7B3C\u6C99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmbqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20915
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"gwzgybxdchcwds",
		"question":"\u53E4\u6587\u4E2D\u5173\u4E8E\u767E\u59D3\u7684\u79F0\u547C\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20916
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u4E34\u996E\u9A6C\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszccgxsqjdzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6B21\u6210\u768B\u5148\u5723\u64D2\u5EFA\u5FB7\u4E4B\u6240\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20917
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u7720\u4E0D\u89C9\u6653",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczmhrcx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u6625\u6653\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20918
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u987A\u8D77\u4E49",
		"indexes":"xlncqybsymssqdrmqy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u6B21\u8D77\u4E49\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u706D\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\uFF1F",
		"id":20919
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5401\u55DF\u9675\u8C37\u8FC1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxjybq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u53D9\u5BC4\u5458\u534A\u5343\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u7AA5\u9752\u6D77\u6E7E",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmjyzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u90CA\u300A\u6E38\u5B50\u541F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbscqsqdgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20922
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5929\u7965\u53F7\u6587\u5C71\u5C45\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xlgygdsrdbhbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u522B\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60AC\u5F27\u5C06\u76F8\u513F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcygtmwsbjts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5143\u5149\u300A\u592A\u6BCD\u9B4F\u6C0F\u534A\u5F84\u9898\u77F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20924
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9648\u60C5\u8868\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsypw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9A88\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":20925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u5728\u6728\u5170\u821F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsybql",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u5317\u9752\u841D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u9785",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyqcdcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u671D\u7684\u81E3\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":20927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u4E11",
		"indexes":"sgsdgycygwgzljdwmsjxlsbsgyszlj",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u4EE3\u5173\u7FBD\u66FE\u6709\u8FC7\u4E94\u5173\u65A9\u516D\u5C06\u7684\u95FB\u540D\u4E8B\u8FF9\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u6240\u65A9\u516D\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":20928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u7BA1\u6742\u98CE\u6D41",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsxlytgdqyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u68A8\u56ED\u4EAD\u89C2\u6253\u7403\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7707\u7136\u767B\u4E91\u8F66",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbhx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6000\u4ED9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbstcsqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5F02\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":20931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5B98\u6367\u65E5\u8F66",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszcclc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u521D\u51FA\u6D1B\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4F2F\u4F26",
		"indexes":"NBAqlbzddqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u62A2\u7BEE\u677F\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":20933
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5973\u4E8E\u7F51\u9AD82.4\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnxgypqydsjmscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6392\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u6570\u636E\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5355\u9A6C\u5C82\u9080\u529F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadzdccxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u4E1C\u5F81\u7B54\u671D\u81E3\u76F8\u9001\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20935
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78EC",
		"indexes":"xszdqtlqbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u590F\u5546\u5468\u7684\u9752\u94DC\u4E50\u5668\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20936
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606C\u8499",
		"indexes":"zgsqmjbcxlnywbszgmj",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u540D\u5C06\u8F88\u51FA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u540D\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":20937
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u697C\u5DF2\u534A\u66DB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u6C5F\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsytsbdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":20939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B",
		"indexes":"zgdgtdcsbknsxlnx",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u53E4\u5854\u7684\u5C42\u6570\u4E0D\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5E73\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"xlnygzybsfszhc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E00\u4E2A\u6218\u5F79\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6C49\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":20941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DD1\u6C14\u4F9D\u8FDF\u67F3\u8272\u9752",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhszcrxwcgyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6625\u65E5\u5E78\u671B\u6625\u5BAB\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7387\u6027\u5937\u8363\u8FB1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljhtfljjxmtj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u548C\u540C\u5E9C\u674E\u796D\u9152\u4F11\u6C90\u7530\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7D\u90FD\u65E0\u591A\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzkhx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u82E6\u5BD2\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5C71\u9E1F\u98DE\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzyjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u300A\u6C5F\u96EA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F2F\u5588\u8FC1\u585E\u5317",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbytzsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u9014\u4E2D\u8FF0\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u95F4\u96EA\u4F3C\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhzxhrygslt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u4EF2\u5BA3\u300A\u6666\u65E5\u5BB4\u9AD8\u6C0F\u6797\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20947
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9636\u79CB\u82D4\u85D3\u9EC4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxybjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F90\u5F66\u4F2F\u300A\u5A55\u59A4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CA9\u6249\u677E\u5F84\u957F\u5BC2\u5BE5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfwflszgcjjhmt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u97E6\u8BBD\u5F55\u4E8B\u5B85\u89C2\u66F9\u5C06\u519B\u753B\u9A6C\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u671D",
		"indexes":"lsszmdtdzcttzscszngcd",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u5C6F\u7530\u5236\u662F\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u4EE4\u5C81\u6708\u6613\u8E49\u8DCE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczchhhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62AB\u8863\u89C9\u9732\u6ECB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdsyhjllczcyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u548C\u664B\u9675\u8DEF\u4E1E\u65E9\u6625\u6E38\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E2\u6247\u79CB\u98CE\u8D77",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyqbm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u59BE\u8584\u547D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u6DF1\u4E91\u666F\u9C9C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwrykwdjls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u5165\u5D16\u53E3\u4E94\u6E21\u5BC4\u674E\u9069\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90ED\u5B50\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"xlnwbshzmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u65CF\u540D\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":20955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u548C\u7EFF\u91CE\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsycrhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u6000\u5F52\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u534A\u949F\u58F0\u5230\u5BA2\u8239",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjfqyb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u7EE7\u300A\u67AB\u6865\u591C\u6CCA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u821C\u4E50\u4E0B\u524D\u6EAA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyccrlycsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4F8D\u5BB4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u522B\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsfszsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":20959
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5915\u6000\u7A7A\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u9752\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83B2\u82B1\u5B9D\u76D6\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycysrqssyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u4E09\u65E5\u66F2\u6C34\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u70DF\u6563\u5165\u4E94\u4FAF\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhhhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u5BD2\u98DF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5185\u5927\u81E3",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsqcdcypwzjg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u4ECE\u4E00\u54C1\u6587\u804C\u4EAC\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":20963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A91",
		"indexes":"xlnzjybsyzhcszdly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u6280\u827A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u5F20\u8861\u4F20\u300B\u6240\u6307\u7684\u516D\u827A\uFF1F",
		"id":20964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u6708\u8FC7\u6B8B\u5792",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczljxqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u810A\u865A\u300A\u9619\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51C9\u666F\u5411\u79CB\u6F84",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwbljdsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u522B\u674E\u5CE4\u5F97\u80DC\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58EE\u5FD7\u9010\u5E74\u8870",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwznby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u7EC8\u5357\u522B\u4E1A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73ED\u9B13\u5411\u957F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzdfsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u65E9\u5EA6\u5206\u6C34\u5CAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u9645\u5927\u5956\u8D5B",
		"indexes":"ATPzynzwqxhdbszlbbkyxnx",
		"question":"ATP(\u804C\u4E1A\u7537\u5B50\u7F51\u7403\u534F\u4F1A)\u7684\u6BD4\u8D5B\u79CD\u7C7B\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":20969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u78D0\u9640",
		"indexes":"jsljzswkdyxwyhxrqzmjzsm",
		"question":"\u636E\u53F2\u6599\u8BB0\u8F7D\u5B59\u609F\u7A7A\u7684\u539F\u578B\u4E3A\u4E00\u7334\u5F62\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5176\u771F\u540D\u53EB\u505A\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":20970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u989C\u672A\u8001\u6069\u5148\u65AD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczbjyhgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u540E\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8DB3\u8D77\u7EA2\u5C18",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5218\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51A0\u7389\u4E3D\u79FE\u59FF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczywqfhtznftpgzcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u4E07\u9877\u300A\u5949\u548C\u592A\u5B50\u7EB3\u5983\u592A\u5E73\u516C\u4E3B\u51FA\u964D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u82B1\u65F6\u8282\u53C8\u9022\u541B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdfjnflgn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u9022\u674E\u9F9F\u5E74\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"tcddfgzzsylcxlnxbsylc",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u5B98\u5236\u4E2D\u8BBE\u6709\u516D\u66F9\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516D\u66F9\uFF1F",
		"id":20975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhcdxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5212\u8239\u7684\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":20976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5F0B\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbslld",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5362\u7EB6\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":20977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"gjcthzxcthldjxbcwjdkxdfzdxswglssdyccxgjcthzxcthldjxszngcd",
		"question":"\u5DE5\u5320\u4F20\u7EDF\u548C\u54F2\u5B66\u4F20\u7EDF\u5408\u6D41\u7684\u8FF9\u8C61\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u8FD1\u4EE3\u79D1\u5B66\u5927\u53D1\u5C55\u7684\u5148\u58F0\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u51FA\u73B0\u5DE5\u5320\u4F20\u7EDF\u548C\u54F2\u5B66\u4F20\u7EDF\u5408\u6D41\u7684\u8FF9\u8C61\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20978
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"lsszmdtdzcjtzscszngcd",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u5747\u7530\u5236\u662F\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":20979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA\u5904\u7591\u82B1\u6EE1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlmhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6885\u82B1\u843D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u4E0A\u7F8A\u5F52\u585E\u8349\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscxfgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u859B\u9022\u300A\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ECE\u660C\u697C",
		"indexes":"xlngbsbjbdlzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u516B\u5927\u697C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":20982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7F15\u6668\u9E21\u672A\u5B66\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhlcyyycyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u7ACB\u6625\u6E38\u82D1\u8FCE\u6625\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8282\u65C4\u96F6\u843D\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlyxq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u96E8\u96EA\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C",
		"indexes":"wjsqdhryybfsjfbyxlngmzbsyzl",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u664B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u80E1\u4EBA\u6709\u4E00\u90E8\u5206\u662F\u91D1\u53D1\u78A7\u773C\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8FD9\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":20985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F44",
		"indexes":"sdyyczdlqxlnxbssddlq",
		"question":"\u5546\u4EE3\u5DF2\u6709\u6210\u7EC4\u7684\u4E50\u5668\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5546\u4EE3\u7684\u4E50\u5668\uFF1F",
		"id":20986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A2A\u62CD\u76F4\u6253",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyppqdtgzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E52\u4E53\u7403\u7684\u63A8\u653B\u6218\u672F?",
		"id":20987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8DB3\u8DF5\u80E1\u5C18",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwcjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6101\u770B\u7389\u955C\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjmhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6885\u82B1\u843D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5149\u6597\u4E3A\u5DE6\u6BC5\u516C",
		"indexes":"xlgygrdshbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u8C25\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":20990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"ssjawxxjmdkcz",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u5EFA\u5B89\u6587\u5B66\u65B0\u5C40\u9762\u7684\u5F00\u521B\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":20991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"sgsqsrzsfldwrbcqzzzmdsjaqzxlnwbsyjaqz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u867D\u7136\u6218\u4E8B\u7EB7\u4E71\uFF0C\u4F46\u6587\u4EBA\u8F88\u51FA\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u662F\u201C\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":20992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7965\u7B26\u591C\u544A\u4E30",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyyhgm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u8C12\u6C49\u9AD8\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C89\u94A9\u6447\u5154\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzljzwy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6C5F\u4E2D\u671B\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20994
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"xlnyxbstsdjbxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u8BD7\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u5F62\u5F0F\uFF1F",
		"id":20995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u539F\u88AB\u82B1\u5B9E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstxjjcnrmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u6653\u6D4E\u80F6\u5DDD\u5357\u5165\u5BC6\u754C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u5E74\u591A\u75C5\u72EC\u767B\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfdl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u767B\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20997
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E45\u5BA2\u4E34\u6D77\u6709\u6000",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwjklhyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4E45\u5BA2\u4E34\u6D77\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u98CE\u5750\u76F8\u60A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczmhrdqdlsjzw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u79CB\u767B\u5170\u5C71\u5BC4\u5F20\u4E94\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":20999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u94B1\u8D60\u4E0B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5927\u917A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F52\u9A6C\u8BC6\u6B8B\u65D7",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsyfy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u98CE\u96E8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6708\u901A\u7985\u5BC2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczhhccyqyjsjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u916C\u7A0B\u5EF6\u79CB\u591C\u5373\u4E8B\u89C1\u8D60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21002
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6\u7B5D\u591C\u4E45\u6BB7\u52E4\u5F04",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwqyq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u5F53\u5171\u526A\u897F\u7A97\u70DB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyyyjb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u591C\u96E8\u5BC4\u5317\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u987A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsymdscz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u4EE3\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F5E\u56FD\u516C\u4FAF\u541B\u96C6",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsxhkggc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u6C49\u5F00\u56FD\u529F\u81E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BA1\u4E50\u6709\u624D\u539F\u4E0D\u5FDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u620F\u7F62\u66FE\u65E0\u7406\u66F2\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfajt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u54C0\u6C5F\u5934\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21008
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjzljozbjsjddcjzh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u5386\u5C4A\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u6210\u7EE9\u6700\u597D\uFF1F",
		"id":21009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjzljozbjsjddcjzh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u5386\u5C4A\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u6210\u7EE9\u6700\u597D\uFF1F",
		"id":21010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1F\u5251\u8BB8\u826F\u56FE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadhstzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u7B54\u97E9\u4F7F\u540C\u5728\u8FB9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECD\u6500\u742A\u6811\u8363",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjttsmxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5BC4\u5929\u53F0\u53F8\u9A6C\u5148\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5A01\u519B",
		"indexes":"tzdjjzbyljyfwlbxlnxbsybyljzl",
		"question":"\u592A\u5B97\u7684\u7981\u519B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5317\u8859\u516D\u519B\u53C8\u5206\u4E3A\u516D\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u8859\u516D\u519B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21013
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u516C\u660E",
		"indexes":"zggdshzxlnwsxbsms",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u795E\u4ED9\u4E0D\u662F\u95E8\u795E\uFF1F",
		"id":21014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BBF\u6614\u68A6\u89C1\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjtzgsjfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u996F\u5510\u5DDE\u9AD8\u4F7F\u541B\u8D74\u4EFB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8584\u66AE\u7A7A\u6F6D\u66F2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfcszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6625\u5BBF\u5DE6\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u591C\u8349\u866B\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxysyws",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5D69\u5CB3\u95FB\u7B19\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u79D1\u7279",
		"indexes":"NBAdsfqjlsyngqybcd",
		"question":"NBA\u7684\u4E09\u5206\u7403\u7EAA\u5F55\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4E2A\u7403\u5458\u4FDD\u6301\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u662D\u541B",
		"indexes":"xlnwmnbsysgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u7F8E\u5973\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CAD\u5916\u97F3\u4E66\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlpdhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9891\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21020
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606F\u541B\u60C5\u66F4\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwxfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u606F\u592B\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21021
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB6\u4F4F\u5C42\u57CE\u90BB\u6C49\u82D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscllwcez",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5362\u7EB6\u300A\u665A\u6B21\u9102\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21022
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u67F3\u5171\u98CE\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctbsdzcyyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5DF4\u5C71\u9053\u4E2D\u9664\u591C\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21023
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6069\u8363\u53D8\u82E6\u8F9B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysglzbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u9001\u9AD8\u90CE\u4E2D\u5317\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21024
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94BB\u9267\u6F6D\u4E1C\u5C0F\u4E18\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"xlnpyjbsylzydyzbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u7BC7\u6E38\u8BB0\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u6C38\u5DDE\u516B\u8BB0\uFF1F",
		"id":21025
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58F0\u9759\u591C\u76F8\u5B9C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlhchmyzytczz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u548C\u5D14\u9EC4\u95E8\u5BD3\u76F4\u591C\u542C\u8749\u4E4B\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EE7\u660C",
		"indexes":"hcdhnwlaybgymdmkxlnwbsybmkzy",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u6DEE\u5357\u738B\u5218\u5B89\u6709\u516B\u4E2A\u6709\u540D\u7684\u95E8\u5BA2\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u95E8\u5BA2\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D\u300A\u84BF\u91CC\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlgyjasrjqzpdcwmssnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u8BD7\u4EBA\u53CA\u5176\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u9519\u8BEF\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21028
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F73\u6C14\u6EE1\u65CC\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwyzxsyxsfcylwz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9B4F\u5143\u5FE0\u300A\u4FEE\u4E66\u9662\u5B66\u58EB\u5949\u6555\u5BB4\u6881\u738B\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21029
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u5927\u5510\u5BAB\u5EF7\u8336\u201D",
		"indexes":"cslydcjfyldtcyxlnxzcjzwjld",
		"question":"\u8336\u795E\u9646\u7FBD\u7684\u300A\u8336\u7ECF\u300B\u590D\u539F\u4E86\u201C\u5927\u5510\u8336\u97F5\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5728\u300A\u8336\u7ECF\u300B\u4E2D\u672A\u8BB0\u5F55\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u63FD\u8F94\u5F55\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsnssqsrdsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u8BD7\u96C6\uFF1F",
		"id":21031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56FD\u98CE\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbjdbssszdly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u7ECF\u5178\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u5E08\u8BF4\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u516D\u827A\uFF1F",
		"id":21032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxqsqdjdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u7ECF\u5178\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21033
	},
	{
		"answer":"m\u00F2",
		"indexes":"xcbjxjcxdmnmxdmzdyw",
		"question":"\u590F\u671D\u66B4\u541B\u590F\u6840\u5BA0\u5E78\u7684\u7F8E\u5973\u59B9\u559C\u7684\u59B9\u5B57\u8BFB\u97F3\u4E3A\uFF1F",
		"id":21034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5308\u5974",
		"indexes":"tcwlyxglyzslllddhfxlngbsdhf",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u4E3A\u4E86\u6709\u6548\u7BA1\u7406\u5F02\u65CF\uFF0C\u8BBE\u7ACB\u4E86\u516D\u5927\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":21035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A8\u606F\u5982\u6709\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbyf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u548F\u98CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u6CFD\u59D4\u662D\u5BA3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszslssrs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9001\u674E\u5C1A\u4E66\u5165\u8700\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u5C14\u00B7\u62C9\u8D5B\u5C14",
		"indexes":"NBAlssnwqxhddzgjjzzd",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u90A3\u4F4D\u7403\u661F\u83B7\u5F97\u7684\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6212\u6307\u6700\u591A\uFF1F",
		"id":21038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u661F\u5165\u5251\u7AEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwszsfrlgfxkycr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9001\u90D1\u5C11\u5E9C\u5165\u8FBD\u5171\u8D4B\u4FA0\u5BA2\u8FDC\u4ECE\u620E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21039
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u53F6\u866B\u4E66\u904D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzzxgzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u957F\u4FE1\u5BAB\u4E2D\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21040
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5916\u52A1\u90E8",
		"indexes":"qcsylbxlbsylbds",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u8BBE\u6709\u201C\u516D\u90E8\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516D\u90E8\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u6625\u5165\u65E7\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfcszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6625\u5BBF\u5DE6\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u4F1A\u591A\u6B22\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszyrcyqjtflysyqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u91CD\u9633\u65E5\u8D50\u5BB4\u66F2\u6C5F\u4EAD\uFF0C\u8D4B\u516D\u97F5\u8BD7\u7528\u6E05\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21043
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u601C\u65E0\u5B9A\u6CB3\u8FB9\u9AA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczctlxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u9676\u300A\u9647\u897F\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21044
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u62DC\u65E6",
		"indexes":"xdalpkcsrss",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4EE3\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21045
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u62DC\u65E6",
		"indexes":"alpkhqwhqdsjzs",
		"question":"\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u4F1A\u65D7-\u4E94\u73AF\u65D7\u7684\u8BBE\u8BA1\u8005\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21046
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlzphzzdyzqdxxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4F5C\u54C1\u548C\u4F5C\u8005\u5BF9\u5E94\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u9009\u9879\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60A0\u60A0\u8FDC\u5BA2\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqnxbd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u5357\u884C\u522B\u5F1F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21048
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7834\u6D95\u6682\u4E3A\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjszzzsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u6893\u5DDE\u5468\u53F8\u529F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u91D1\u94F8\u9A6C\u97AD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9AA2\u9A6C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u91CC\u5176\u5982\u4F55",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczyjdztsglbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u7ED3\u7684\u300A\u8D3C\u9000\u793A\u5B98\u540F\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676F\u63A5\u8FD1\u81E3\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyzngzdzyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21052
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6797\u7E41\u82B1\u7167\u773C\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsyhb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u97E9\u7891\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6298\u621F\u6C88\u6C99\u94C1\u672A\u9500",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmcb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u8D64\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u6765\u672A\u8457\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzqsbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E54\u300A\u4E66\u8FB9\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u65F7\u9E4A\u505C\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyfhqxsylydyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E03\u5915\u4F8D\u5BB4\u4E24\u4EEA\u6BBF\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D8\u8C03\u5982\u95FB\u6768\u67F3\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczcczmcxfsfdfcsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u300A\u8D70\u9A6C\u5DDD\u884C\u5949\u9001\u5C01\u5927\u592B\u51FA\u5E08\u897F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21057
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5408\u8D64\u7B26\u5148",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxyyhszm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u8C12\u6C49\u4E16\u7956\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u9CA4\u8FE2\u8FE2\u4E00\u7EB8\u7B14",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyjlhlz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u5BC4\u4EE4\u72D0\u90CE\u4E2D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21059
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u8499\u771F\u50E7\u987E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwycjsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u96E8\u4ECE\u7B95\u5C71\u6765\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u5FC3\u83AB\u5171\u82B1\u4E89\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsycby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u7B79\u7B14\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21061
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u602A\u7389\u5C71\u9893",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlxfszgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8F9B\u6CD5\u53F8\u5B85\u89C2\u5993\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u67F3\u6E21\u6C5F\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwcbgsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u6E7E\u300A\u6B21\u5317\u56FA\u5C71\u4E0B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21064
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64D2\u4FD8\u5E1D\u9053\u4EA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljxccgtjxsqjdzsmsgygef",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u884C\u6B21\u6210\u768B\u9014\u7ECF\u5148\u5723\u64D2\u5EFA\u5FB7\u4E4B\u6240\u7F05\u601D\u529F\u4E1A\u611F\u800C\u8D4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9694\u53F6\u9EC4\u9E42\u7A7A\u597D\u97F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfkz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BA2\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u5723\uFF1A\u4E1C\u664B\u738B\u732E\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xldwglslsdmscwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5BF9\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u516D\u5723\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u6301\u957F\u74E2\u5750\u5DF4\u4E18",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczbjyzhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u957F\u6068\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E1D\u5F97\u5723\u76F8\u76F8\u66F0\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfbcx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5175\u8F66\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u751F\u4E00\u5251\u77E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmdbsqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u705E\u4E0A\u79CB\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67B6\u6D77\u6CE2\u6F84\u955C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmgjzes",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u8FC7\u65E7\u5B85\u4E8C\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21071
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u7ED5\u5439\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysytsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5BBF\u7FBD\u4EAD\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679D\u4E9A\u679C\u65B0\u80A5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydwst",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u90FD\u5C09\u5C71\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E95\u7530",
		"indexes":"xlnxjcbswasbfdnr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E3E\u63AA\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":21074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u5229",
		"indexes":"ssnlzxdsjbgj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u5E74\u9F84\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u6708\u51B7\u76F8\u968F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsjrxlhjby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u50E7\u768E\u7136\u300A\u5BFB\u9646\u9E3F\u6E10\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65C5\u5BA2\u975E\u60A0\u60A0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadlyzr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u7B54\u6D1B\u9633\u4E3B\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u71B9",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsymcrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u671D\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690",
		"indexes":"xlngsrcswtsqddb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u8BD7\u4EBA\u624D\u662F\u665A\u5510\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\uFF1F",
		"id":21079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7096\u732A\u5934",
		"indexes":"ctszgrjjzzsyxsycqhbszsdqsbhzyzhctysgjddfxlnxbsswdbhzy",
		"question":"\u4F20\u7EDF\u4E0A\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u8BB2\u7A76\u5728\u6B63\u5F0F\u5BB4\u5E2D\u4E0A\u8981\u5403\u201C\u4E03\u8364\u516B\u7D20\u201D,\u8FD9\u662F\u5BF9\u201C\u4E03\u7D20\u3001\u516B\u8364\u201D\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E2D\u534E\u4F20\u7EDF\u996E\u98DF\u89C4\u77E9\u7684\u98A0\u8986\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6240\u8C13\u7684\u516B\u8364\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u8BBA\u6570\u7EFF\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjyss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6709\u6240\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5076\u7136\u503C\u6797\u53DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdffjyzsygsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5949\u6D4E\u9A7F\u91CD\u9001\u4E25\u516C\u56DB\u97F5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21082
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u66AE\u5BA2\u6101\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczmhrsjdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u5BBF\u5EFA\u5FB7\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u5439\u4F55\u5386\u5386",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxyqrtrytb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9898\u6C5D\u9633\u6F6D\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21084
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79F0\u540D\u5FC6\u65E7\u5BB9",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzqxnz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u65B0\u5E74\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u971C\u4E0B\u9707\u96F7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsylyan",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u65C5\u5BD3\u5B89\u5357\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21086
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u559C\u9E4A",
		"indexes":"qcwgcfsdbzdsydwwtaxlnzdwbscfbzsdta",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u6587\u5B98\u671D\u670D\u4E0A\u7684\u8865\u5B50\u90FD\u662F\u4EE5\u52A8\u7269\u4E3A\u56FE\u6848\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u671D\u670D\u8865\u5B50\u4E0A\u7684\u56FE\u6848\uFF1F",
		"id":21087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73E0\u623F\u6298\u6D77\u69B4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcstdwsc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5510\u90FD\u5C09\u5C71\u6C60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u4EBA\u591A\u5B66\u5439",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjftq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u51E4\u53F0\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21089
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6816\u6816\u4E00\u4EE3\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjlwyhy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u671B\u6708\u6000\u8FDC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u5439\u53C8\u751F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlyxjwdyyb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u76CA\u300A\u559C\u89C1\u5916\u5F1F\u53C8\u8A00\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21091
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u574E\u58C8\u5026\u6E38\u79E6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyhgyspsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u610F\u4E0A\u88F4\u4F8D\u90CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u4EF2\u8212\u732E\u5929\u4EBA\u4E09\u7B56",
		"indexes":"sgycmdbxxlnxbsybxzy",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6709\u51FA\u540D\u7684\u201C\u516B\u732E\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u732E\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u5439\u4FBF\u5750\u6851",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgztxywctzsryzzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u540C\u5F90\u5458\u5916\u9664\u592A\u5B50\u820D\u4EBA\u5BD3\u76F4\u4E4B\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4F2F\u4F26",
		"indexes":"dcdfzddqyss",
		"question":"\u5355\u573A\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21095
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F2\u6E86\u4E3D\u73E0\u5149",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbywsdhsjxy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u738B\u5E08\u6E21\u6C49\u6C34\u7ECF\u8944\u9633\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21096
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1F\u7FBD\u8FDC\u4ECE\u620E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzljksncx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u7ED3\u5BA2\u5C11\u5E74\u573A\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21097
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F27\u5708\u7403",
		"indexes":"xlnyxbszqsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u8DB3\u7403\u672F\u8BED?",
		"id":21098
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u5171\u6653\u5149\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxjss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u897F\u4EAC\u5B88\u5C81\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5C45\u4E91\u4F5C\u7F28",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycglycsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u6545\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDC\u6170\u98CE\u96E8\u5915",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjlgysszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u611F\u9047\u56DB\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21101
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64\u8BED\u8BB0\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsxblgyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u767D\u9E7F\u89C2\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21102
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E23\u7B33\u51FA\u671B\u82D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyfhcccyyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5949\u548C\u521D\u6625\u51FA\u6E38\u5E94\u4EE4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u4F5C\u969C\u6CE5\u534A\u4F5C\u5E06",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsysg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u968B\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21104
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DA9\u8DEF\u62E5\u5D29\u67E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwwqtj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u665A\u61A9\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C81\u65F6\u4F0F\u814A\u8D70\u6751\u7FC1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E94\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21106
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6F6E\u5E26\u96E8\u665A\u6765\u6025",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwywczxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u6EC1\u5DDE\u897F\u6DA7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21107
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u796D\u6C7E\u9634\u4E50\u7AE0",
		"indexes":"wwstcymdsrxlnbbswwdzp",
		"question":"\u738B\u7EF4\u662F\u5510\u671D\u6709\u540D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21108
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u6B66\u5927\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbshcddjjjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5927\u5C06\u519B\u519B\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":21110
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5915\u51C9\u98CE\u81F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwgxjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u8FC7\u9999\u79EF\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21111
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6EF4\u94DC\u9F99\u663C\u6F0F\u957F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscsqqgycbqqzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6C88\u5168\u671F\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u5448\u8865\u9619\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u56DB",
		"indexes":"qcdwyhywlcdwybyyesflhdddjqwqcdwyfljgdj",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u548C\u4EE5\u5F80\u5386\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u4E0D\u4E00\u6837\uFF0C\u800C\u662F\u5206\u4E86\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u5206\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF1F",
		"id":21113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u82B1\u8DF3\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlnxbstsyddzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u8DF3\u6C34\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u79CD\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":21114
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6289\u62E9",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqdlbjszdzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6E05\u4EE3\u516D\u90E8\u7ED9\u4E8B\u4E2D\u7684\u804C\u8D23\uFF1F",
		"id":21115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u964C\u8F69\u8F66\u522B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsslqwlzsdfdc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u9001\u6881\u537F\u738B\u90CE\u4E2D\u4F7F\u4E1C\u8543\u540A\u518C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u603B\u6301\u5BFA\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsmhrdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21117
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5D29\u4E91\u6D12\u82B3\u7252",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbcrylyyfydjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u5BB4\u4E50\u6E38\u56ED\u8D4B\u97F5\u5F97\u63A5\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21118
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E0\u98CE\u60F3\u7389\u73C2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhryzzdxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u4E0E\u8BF8\u5B50\u767B\u5C98\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D2A\u5408\u9C7C\u9F99\u6784\u5F3A\u540D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlybqtssb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u75C5\u8D77\u9898\u5C71\u820D\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u6B21",
		"indexes":"tcyalbrjdsygjcjf",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u4E0E\u963F\u62C9\u4F2F\u4EBA\uFF08\u5373\u5927\u98DF\uFF09\u6709\u8FC7\u51E0\u6B21\u4EA4\u950B\uFF1F",
		"id":21121
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC4\u97E6\u73E9",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbslyxd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"sjsdycsyzbhyxxyszwgngcd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4F7F\u7528\u7EB8\u5E01\u548C\u94F6\u884C\u4FE1\u7528\u662F\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sgsqdzygzdddqwwglssdddzdyync",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5468\u745C\u5B98\u81F3\u5927\u90FD\u7763\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u90FD\u7763\u5236\u5EA6\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":21124
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9488\u7EBF\u72B9\u5B58\u672A\u5FCD\u5F00",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscyzqbhsszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u4E01",
		"indexes":"sdmjfhsxlnwsdjwdqz",
		"question":"\u5546\u4EE3\u540D\u5C06\u5987\u597D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5546\u4EE3\u541B\u738B\u7684\u59BB\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21126
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6458\u82B3\u5171\u73CD\u8350",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzwsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u9AD8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96CD\u5E03\u62C9\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"xlngbszglssdhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7687\u5BAB\uFF1F",
		"id":21128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5B97",
		"indexes":"btfbdlkzadslssnwhd",
		"question":"\u88AB\u5410\u8543\u903C\u5F97\u79BB\u5F00\u957F\u5B89\u7684\u662F\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":21129
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80FD\u58F0\u5BC4\u4FAF\u4F2F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstjyzlsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u996F\u90E2\u5DDE\u674E\u4F7F\u541B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6577\u8BDA\u5F52\u4E0A\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzlrds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8D60\u674E\u8363\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21131
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u62F3",
		"indexes":"xlnxbswstlydddz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6B66\u672F\u5957\u8DEF\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u52A8\u4F5C?",
		"id":21132
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FA1\u53F2\u5927\u592B",
		"indexes":"xlnggzbsyqcdjqzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B98\u804C\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u671D\u7684\u4E5D\u537F\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u697C\u901A\u591C\u655E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczywqfhcrct",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u4E07\u9877\u300A\u5949\u548C\u6625\u65E5\u6C60\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA2\u5FC3\u60B2\u66AE\u5E8F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyychg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u90E2\u57CE\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u9762\u5E76\u5982\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgjsyyxxyt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9AD8\u747E\u300A\u4E0A\u5143\u591C\u6548\u5C0F\u5EBE\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21136
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u671D\u522B\u66AE\u8FD8\u89C1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqtdddhjsjjynfjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u542C\u8463\u5927\u5F39\u80E1\u7B33\u58F0\u517C\u5BC4\u8BED\u5F04\u623F\u7ED9\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21137
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83B2\u8863\u627F\u7389\u948F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycycln",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u91C7\u83B2\u5973\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21138
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FD7\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"zgdygtjsjgjss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u7530\u5F84\u4E16\u754C\u51A0\u519B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21139
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u591C\u519B\u884C\u6208\u76F8\u62E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczyjsyhszgbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u7ED3\u300A\u77F3\u9C7C\u6E56\u4E0A\u9189\u6B4C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5CE1\u661F\u6CB3\u5F71\u52A8\u6447",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"xlnggjmyhdgozbgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"xlnggjmyhdgozbgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u7591\u4F5C\u8D4B\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlxrqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u76F8\u5982\u7434\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u5F71\u6247\u4E2D\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyxzpxcmylxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u620F\u8D60\u6F58\u5F90\u57CE\u95E8\u8FCE\u4E24\u65B0\u5987\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u5B55\u5B9D\u7B26",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxrydzzgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u5FB7\u5DDE\u8D60\u9AD8\u56DB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6628\u591C\u88D9\u5E26\u89E3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqdyytt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6743\u5FB7\u8206\u300A\u7389\u53F0\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u98D8\u7D20\u5F71\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyhkwtzwyyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u548C\u5EB7\u4E94\u5EAD\u829D\u671B\u6708\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u68B5\u524D\u5C71\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwsyms",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u5BBF\u4E91\u95E8\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21149
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"yzdygsbayhdcssng",
		"question":"\u4E9A\u6D32\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u7533\u529E\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":21150
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EFF\u7AF9\u7F18\u6EAA\u6DA7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwzxyztzhsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u81EA\u6E58\u6E90\u81F3\u6F6D\u5DDE\u8861\u5C71\u53BF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A00\u5E08\u91C7\u836F\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjdxyzby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3E\u5C9B\u300A\u5BFB\u9690\u8005\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u77F6\u897F\u7554\u95EE\u6E14\u8239",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzxthx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u65ED\u300A\u6843\u82B1\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u821F\u4E8B\u6CBF\u8D8A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsdssyykwdjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u7B54\u5B8B\u5341\u4E00\u5D16\u53E3\u4E94\u6E21\u89C1\u8D60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u6B21\u4E50\u4E61\u53BF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczawclxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u665A\u6B21\u4E50\u4E61\u53BF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21155
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC8\u662F\u5723\u660E\u5929\u5B50\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczztmwp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90D1\u754B\u300A\u9A6C\u5D6C\u5761\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21156
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u4FE1\u82B3",
		"indexes":"zgessjysdmdhsxmdqwxlnwbsmdzy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E8C\u5341\u4E16\u7EAA\u6709\u201C\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u65E6\u201D\u548C\u201C\u56DB\u5C0F\u540D\u65E6\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u540D\u65E6\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B63\u5B59\uFF08\u4F2F\u989C\uFF09",
		"indexes":"kzdxszzzmddssezxlbsysez",
		"question":"\u5B54\u5B50\u7684\u5B66\u751F\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u5F53\u5C5E\u5341\u4E8C\u54F2\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5341\u4E8C\u54F2\uFF1F",
		"id":21158
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnbbswcldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u768E\u768E\u6620\u5C42\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljqswyclqc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u79CB\u5C71\u671B\u6708\u916C\u674E\u9A91\u66F9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u659C\u62D4\u7389\u9497\u706F\u5F71\u7554",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhznr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u8D60\u5185\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70E7\u5200\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnzjbsygdzgmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9152\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u540D\u9152\uFF1F",
		"id":21162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u60C5\u6076\u8870\u6B47",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczdfdwy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u7684\u300A\u671B\u5CB3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u754C\u8B66\u5BDF\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"xlngydhmjtrsxlrbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A\u6CA1\u5C06\u94C1\u4EBA\u4E09\u9879\u5217\u5165\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":21164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u5FC3\u5411\u6625\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczbjyfdgycsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u8D4B\u5F97\u53E4\u539F\u8349\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u6853",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbsyxndfc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u540D\u65CF\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5308\u5974\u7684\u8303\u7574\uFF1F",
		"id":21166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592B\u5B50\u4F55\u4E3A\u8005",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwbsdsfzrsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u9001\u675C\u5C11\u5E9C\u4E4B\u4EFB\u8700\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C79\u6251",
		"indexes":"xlngjdbszgsqdslwzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u519B\u961F\u4E0D\u662F\u8D1E\u89C2\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5341\u516D\u536B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u7B20\u5E26\u659C\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzqslc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u9001\u7075\u6F88\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21169
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u65E5\u751F\u6B8B\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbdjmsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E21\u8346\u95E8\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EA5\u5FB7\u7FCA\u98DE\u9F99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcygsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5143\u5149\u300A\u793A\u73E6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648",
		"indexes":"zgswglsshzydydlsqgzhghzysxlnggjbszgqxzy",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u5F88\u91CD\u8981\u7684\u4E00\u6BB5\u5386\u53F2\uFF0C\u4E03\u4E2A\u8BF8\u4FAF\u56FD\u6DF7\u6218\u4E00\u65F6\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u65E5\u82B1\u5F00\u53C8\u4E00\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnjbschhttxyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u540C\u9898\u4ED9\u6E38\u89C2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u540E\u7FBF",
		"indexes":"xlnygbsxcdhd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":21174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC7\u6E29\u6C64",
		"indexes":"ttzlsmclzgptxdbswhsygyxdsrxlnbbslsmdzp",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u9664\u4E86\u6CBB\u56FD\u5E73\u5929\u4E0B\u7684\u672C\u4E8B\u5916\uFF0C\u8FD8\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A\u4F18\u79C0\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F2\u8FBE\u7956",
		"indexes":"xlnwcrsyxypcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u5C5E\u4E8E\u95F2\u9038\u6D3E\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":21176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u6597\u59CB\u5F00\u7B3C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqhsyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u5BD2\u98DF\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66AE\u96E8\u76F8\u547C\u5931",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwsjqm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u5C71\u5C45\u79CB\u669D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793C\u81F4\u4E00\u7262\u7960",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszjkzjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u7ECF\u5B54\u5B50\u65E7\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u644A\u4E01\u5165\u4EA9",
		"indexes":"xlnxzmdtdzcbsczqcyq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E05\u671D\u4EE5\u524D\uFF1F",
		"id":21180
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u97EC\u7389\u300A\u8D2B\u5973\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswyjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u7EDD\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyzgxzdewbsm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u6C38\u8D1E\u9769\u65B0\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E8C\u738B\u516B\u53F8\u9A6C\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u66B9\u7C92\u201D",
		"indexes":"zlzpbmkmirwznbdggxlnxdybsdzlddy",
		"question":"\u771F\u814A\u5360\u5A46\u7891\u540Dkmir\uFF0C\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5357\u534A\u5C9B\u53E4\u56FD\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u8BFB\u97F3\u4E0D\u662F\u5BF9\u771F\u814A\u7684\u5BF9\u97F3\uFF1F",
		"id":21183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u7B49\u5E42\u7B49\u79EF\u201D",
		"indexes":"xlnxsxcjbsfszscsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u6570\u5B66\u6210\u5C31\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5B8B\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u897F\u5317\u6709\u9AD8\u697C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsycsfzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u66F9\u6C0F\u7236\u5B50\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5317\u9B4F\u5F8B\u8003\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbswmdjclkzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u300A\u4E5D\u671D\u5F8B\u8003\u300B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21186
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C5F\u8FB9\u522B\u300B",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbsydf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u675C\u752B\uFF1F",
		"id":21187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsylfjt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E50\u5E9C\u65E7\u9898\uFF1F",
		"id":21188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5415\u89C8\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C49\u8D4B\uFF1F",
		"id":21189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E0A\u6797\u8D4B\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyjawxdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u6587\u5B66\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6E58\u592B\u4EBA\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssjzdzj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u7AE0\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":21191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7B54\u5BA2\u96BE\u300B",
		"indexes":"yxsxhzmdfjxlnbzpbsyxddbz",
		"question":"\u6768\u96C4\u662F\u897F\u6C49\u8457\u540D\u7684\u8D4B\u5BB6\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u6768\u96C4\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":21192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyxss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53D9\u4E8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u5FD7\u5E73\u8BDD\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsmqdzhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u660E\u6E05\u7684\u7AE0\u56DE\u5C0F\u8BF4\uFF1F",
		"id":21194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56FD\u8BED\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u7F16\u5E74\u4F53\u53F2\u4E66",
		"indexes":"dxlwxzpjmsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u6587\u5B66\u4F5C\u54C1\u96C6\u63CF\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u897F\u585E\u5C71\u6000\u53E4\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqyjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E03\u8A00\u7EDD\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C34\u7ECF\u6CE8\u300B",
		"indexes":"zyzjsjdcyqzycwdcxlnxbsydczl",
		"question":"\u300A\u5468\u6613\u300B\u4E2D\u89E3\u91CA\u7ECF\u7684\u4F20\u6709\u4E03\u79CD\uFF0C\u4E5F\u79F0\u4E3A\u5927\u4F20\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u4F20\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u964C\u4E0A\u6851\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsytys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7530\u56ED\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21198
	},
	{
		"answer":"305",
		"indexes":"sjycwssbnmsjsldsggydsp",
		"question":"\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u53C8\u79F0\u4E3A\u300A\u8BD7\u4E09\u767E\u300B\u90A3\u4E48\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u6536\u5F55\u7684\u8BD7\u6B4C\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u7BC7\uFF1F",
		"id":21199
	},
	{
		"answer":"789",
		"indexes":"jgdldxyzxtzgydstw",
		"question":"\u91D1\u56FD\u7684\u5F8B\u5178\u300A\u54B8\u96CD\u91CD\u4FEE\u6761\u5236\u300B\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6761\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":21200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u4E89\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8",
		"indexes":"cjgjhjghyclyglzzdjlbbbkxlng",
		"question":"\u53C2\u52A0\u5171\u6D4E\u4F1A\u9152\u9986\u4F1A\u8BAE\u6210\u7ACB\u82F1\u683C\u5170\u8DB3\u603B\u7684\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":21201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u5A46",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsxzhjlx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u85CF\u9EC4\u6559\u9886\u8896\uFF1F",
		"id":21202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B50",
		"indexes":"jwswglsscxygzbxdxzdwdyzzdqwxlngjwzscsmyd",
		"question":"\u7235\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u51FA\u73B0\u4E0E\u5B98\u5236\u5E76\u884C\u7684\u8C61\u5F81\u5730\u4F4D\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u5236\u5EA6\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u7235\u4F4D\u5728\u5546\u671D\u662F\u6CA1\u6709\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngcsbsldgdzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u662F\u516D\u5927\u53E4\u90FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D",
		"indexes":"xabsxlncdgd",
		"question":"\u897F\u5B89\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u671D\u7684\u53E4\u90FD\uFF1F",
		"id":21205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u69DB\u5916\u957F\u6C5F\u7A7A\u81EA\u6D41",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbtwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6ED5\u738B\u9601\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AE1\u94B3\u4E3A\u53F0\u96B6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlysss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u548F\u53F2\u56DB\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80EF\u4E0B\u4E4B\u8FB1",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbsfszsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u914C\u996E\u56DB\u5EA7\u4EE5\u6563\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwlynex",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6D1B\u9633\u5973\u513F\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9752\u753B\u677E\u77F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwczyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u521D\u81F3\u5D16\u53E3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E7\u7ECF\u5907\u9619\u6587",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsfyhtcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u6C7E\u9634\u540E\u571F\u7960\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"ttzwlbzzjdcdglfessmdcwlygkgessgcxlnwbsyessgc",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u4E3A\u4E86\u8868\u5F70\u81EA\u5DF1\u5927\u81E3\u7684\u529F\u52B3\uFF0C\u5C01\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u540D\u5927\u81E3\u4E3A\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u5F00\u56FD\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1\u5E3D\u5B50\u738B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqcwydch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6E05\u671D\u738B\u7237\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u636E\u5C71\u6CB3\u636E\u5E73\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbjjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90ED\u6C5C",
		"indexes":"sgzdmjlbsxyzmdbwjjbcwbjjqzbsybjjzzds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u7684\u540D\u5C06\u201C\u5415\u5E03\u201D\u624B\u4E0B\u6709\u8457\u540D\u7684\u516B\u4F4D\u5C06\u519B\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u516B\u5065\u5C06\u201D\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u516B\u5065\u5C06\u201D\u4E4B\u4E2D\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B65\u51FA\u4E1C\u658B\u8BFB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwclssq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u671B\u4E0B\u7AE0\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadjmwc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u5EA6\u8346\u95E8\u671B\u695A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u7AEF\u5AC1\u5F97\u91D1\u9F9F\u5A7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsywy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u4E3A\u6709\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u5FB7\u5DDE\u8D60\u9AD8\u56DB",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsczadzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u897F\u4E4B\u5F79",
		"indexes":"qwxlnczybsfszzgsq",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u573A\u6218\u5F79\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF2\u4F3C\u957F\u6C99\u5085",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrlbwsyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u7559\u522B\u738B\u4F8D\u5FA1\u7EF4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC7\u664B\u9633\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u6CBB\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u9675",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslsmdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E94\u591C\u89C2\u706F",
		"indexes":"xlnbbszjldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60C5\u6E2D\u65E5\u8FB9\u4E34",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszcqyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6B21\u743C\u5CB3\u97F5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95F2\u56ED\u5373\u4E8B\u5BC4\u97E6\u4F8D\u90CE",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslbwdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9675",
		"indexes":"xlnwbssgrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EFA\u7B51\u5409\u7965",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzgbdjxwh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u516B\u5927\u5409\u7965\u6587\u5316\uFF1F",
		"id":21228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u987B\u81FE\u4E3A\u4E00\u6574\u5929",
		"indexes":"wcydzyhjysnmgysjdcwshs",
		"question":"\u6587\u5E38\u6709\u201C\u5F39\u6307\u4E00\u6325\u95F4\u201D\u4E00\u8BF4\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u5173\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u7684\u9519\u8BEF\u8BF4\u8BDD\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5411",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsqgsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u79E6\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6258\u5854\u5929\u738B\u674E\u9756",
		"indexes":"xlngbssgms",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0A\u53E4\u9B54\u795E\uFF1F",
		"id":21231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D4F\u4EAE\u5982\u7B19\u788E\u5728\u7F11",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyqy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u79CB\u83BA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C64",
		"indexes":"xlngbsxcdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u671D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u534E\u65E9\u8457\u540D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5BC4\u6768\u516C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u5BA1",
		"indexes":"mzsczszydmpsrzdjcdbxlsbsymzscz",
		"question":"\u95FD\u4E2D\u5341\u624D\u5B50\u662F\u6307\u5143\u4EE3\u95FD\u6D3E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E2D\u7684\u6770\u51FA\u4EE3\u8868\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u95FD\u4E2D\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u84DF\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsdfd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u675C\u752B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u59BE\u65AD\u80A0\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczydfdmlb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u675C\u752B\u7684\u300A\u68A6\u674E\u767D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u66AE\u4E61\u5173\u4F55\u5904\u662F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclqswwzj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u9001\u9B4F\u4E07\u4E4B\u4EAC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u6211\u72EC\u6C89\u4E45",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5B64\u96C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6E38\u66F2\u4E8C\u9996",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbslzyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u53F2\u90A3\u601D\u6469",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsycsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6148\u6EAA\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglsshnsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6CB3\u5357\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5E1D\u6218\u86A9\u5C24",
		"indexes":"xlbsysgsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u53E4\u795E\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":21243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5DDE\u4E91\u9F99\u5C71\u5E99\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"wljnsgmjyhdsgmshdxlnghdbssgmshd",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u7EAA\u5FF5\u4E09\u56FD\uFF0C\u6C11\u95F4\u6709\u5F88\u591A\u4E09\u56FD\u6C11\u4FD7\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D3B\u52A8\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6C11\u4FD7\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":21244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF1\u6069\u96E8\u9732\u5782",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqzzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u76F4\u4E2D\u4E66\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90FD\u62A4\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnggzbstcdwz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B98\u804C\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u6B66\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":21246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u866C\u987B\u864E\u7709\u4ECD\u5927\u98A1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqtawscblg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u542C\u5B89\u4E07\u5584\u5439\u7B5A\u7BE5\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91\u795E\u67AA",
		"indexes":"xlnwsbsczsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u201C\u795E\u201D\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u5188",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyhdgozbjsjdzjssdch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u6700\u4F73\u5C04\u624B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u5188",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyhdgozbjsjdzjssdch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u6700\u4F73\u5C04\u624B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u85CF\u9738",
		"indexes":"hgwdfesbwjjwytesbjxlnwbsytesbj",
		"question":"\u6C49\u5149\u6B66\u5E1D\u5C01\u4E8C\u5341\u516B\u4F4D\u5C06\u519B\u4E3A\u4E91\u53F0\u4E8C\u5341\u516B\u5C06\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E91\u53F0\u4E8C\u5341\u516B\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":21251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u4E91\u65E0\u5C3D\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdxsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u897F\u65BD\u548F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u864E\u8425",
		"indexes":"yfsnsmjkjyxyfqxjbrltbsqxzmdsbyxlnxbssbyss",
		"question":"\u5CB3\u98DE\u662F\u5357\u5B8B\u540D\u5C06\u6297\u91D1\u82F1\u96C4\uFF0C\u5CB3\u98DE\u65D7\u4E0B\u7CBE\u5175\u5982\u6797\uFF0C\u7279\u522B\u662F\u65D7\u4E0B\u8457\u540D\u7684\u5341\u516B\u8425\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5341\u516B\u8425\u6240\u5C5E\uFF1F",
		"id":21253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u9633\u65E0\u9650\u597D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsydlyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u767B\u4E50\u6E38\u539F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D60\u738B\u516B\u8862",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsdfdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u675C\u752B\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u590F",
		"indexes":"bsjlhzgbmytyznbhybsdgjzqxlngzqbsybssqdgjzq",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u5EFA\u7ACB\u540E\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u5E76\u6CA1\u6709\u7EDF\u4E00\uFF0C\u5728\u5357\u5317\u8FD8\u6709\u4E0D\u5C11\u7684\u5272\u636E\u653F\u6743\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u653F\u6743\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5272\u636E\u653F\u6743\uFF1F",
		"id":21256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341",
		"indexes":"hjjswgzzdybcjhjjgyjb",
		"question":"\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u8BCD\u96C6\uFF0C\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u90E8\uFF1F",
		"id":21257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u5386",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxldbc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u5386\u7684\u522B\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":21258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u5C3A\u9F99\u987B\u65B9\u9526\u8925",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhhyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u5DF2\u51C9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u7EB3\u5C14\u591A",
		"indexes":"sjbjqzdqyss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u8FDB\u7403\u6700\u591A\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DE1\u626B\u8346\u95E8\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwcldbsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u705E\u4E0A\u95F2\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6263\u6740",
		"indexes":"xlnxjsbsysqydybbdzxjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u6280\u672F\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u5FC5\u5907\u7684\u4E13\u9879\u6280\u672F\uFF1F",
		"id":21262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u8FDC\u5FA1\u6148\u7559",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsfhsjcgzsxfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21263
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6BD3\u7B60",
		"indexes":"byjfslprwbszxhqsxsegjjbywfpdsstbxlnwbssstb",
		"question":"\u5317\u6D0B\u519B\u9600\u5B9E\u529B\u6D3E\u4EBA\u7269\u201C\u8FAB\u5E05\u201D\u5F20\u52CB\u548C\u5176\u624B\u4E0B\u5341\u4E8C\u4E2A\u5065\u5C06\uFF0C\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u590D\u8F9F\u515A\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u8D24",
		"indexes":"tcddwzybsdsyscgfqwxlnwtcdhdbssr",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5E1D\u738B\u4E2D\u6709\u4E0D\u5C11\u90FD\u5584\u4E8E\u8BD7\u8BCD\u6B4C\u8D4B\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u4E0D\u662F\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":21265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE\u53F7\u9189\u4ED9",
		"indexes":"xlgygdsrdbhbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u522B\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FEF\u542C\u95FB\u60CA\u98CE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywdjqjszds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u7684\u300A\u5BC4\u5168\u6912\u5C71\u4E2D\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5C45\u79CB\u669D",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbslsyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u5546\u9690\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u8F89\u7389\u81C2\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwwcxjzpxcd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u8F8B\u5DDD\u95F2\u5C45\u8D60\u88F4\u79C0\u624D\u8FEA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u539F\u738B\u6FEC",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsnbcdcmsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5317\u671D\u7684\u51FA\u540D\u4E16\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":21270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5200\u4E07\u5250",
		"indexes":"xlnxxfbsymqsdkxzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5211\u7F5A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6EE1\u6E05\u5341\u5927\u9177\u5211\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u662D",
		"indexes":"xlnwbswjnbcsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u9B4F\u664B\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u4E18\u660E",
		"indexes":"ccsllyqywsjwsrdzpxlnwsrdzpwslzccz",
		"question":"\u300A\u695A\u8F9E\u300B\u6536\u5F55\u4E86\u4EE5\u5C48\u539F\u4E3A\u9996\u51E0\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\u672A\u6536\u5F55\u5728\u300A\u695A\u8F9E\u300B\u4E2D\uFF1F",
		"id":21273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90B9\u5143\u6807",
		"indexes":"mcwqddldsyjnsdfwzdzzjtqzzzmddsdlbczxlnwsydlbcz",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u665A\u671F\u7684\u4E1C\u6797\u515A\u662F\u4EE5\u6C5F\u5357\u58EB\u5927\u592B\u4E3A\u4E3B\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u96C6\u56E2\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u5F53\u5C5E\u201C\u4E1C\u6797\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E1C\u6797\u516B\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u9634\u9001\u665A\u96F7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyxrgzqsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u8FC7\u90D1\u4E03\u5C71\u658B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE",
		"indexes":"xlnwcrsyhfpcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8C6A\u653E\u6D3E\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":21276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u9002\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqygs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u53E4\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u6D32\u62E5\u5915\u6DA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwzjnzswzw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u5728\u6C5F\u5357\u8D60\u5B8B\u4E94\u4E4B\u95EE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03\u5B57\u5949\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlgysgrwxmbzcwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\u59D3\u540D\u8868\u5B57\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u6D6E\u4E91\u9634\u4E14\u6674",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhryglmsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u591C\u5F52\u9E7F\u95E8\u5C71\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6851\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnxydydmzbgjtclhhylmmjsdz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u88AB\u56FD\u9645\u4F53\u64CD\u8054\u5408\u4F1A\u7528\u6765\u547D\u540D\u6280\u672F\u52A8\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":21281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE0\u534E\u5373\u65E7\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydxyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u767B\u8944\u9633\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5965\u65AF\u5361\u00B7\u7F57\u4F2F\u900A",
		"indexes":"NBAdfzddhwss",
		"question":"NBA\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u591A\u7684\u540E\u536B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u4E34\u51FA\u4E16\u754C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdswclyj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u9690\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u66F2\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswygs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u53E4\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9880\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswylf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u4E50\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":21286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbszglssdfsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u9644\u5C5E\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":21287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5B59\u5F52\u4E0D\u5F52",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EF6\u9996\u665E\u4E91\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczrxghlgqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4EFB\u5E0C\u53E4\u300A\u548C\u674E\u516C\u4E03\u5915\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D1\u5323\u5148\u6765\u745E\u6709\u865E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhszlcp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9F99\u6C60\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52CB",
		"indexes":"xlngsxddjmdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u590F\u4EE3\u7684\u7235\u547D\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF1F",
		"id":21291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B65\u6B65\u6625\u82B3\u7EFF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxycs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u91C7\u6851\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E7\u597D\u9694\u826F\u7F18",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5B64\u96C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u557C\u65F6\u60CA\u59BE\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjcxcy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u91D1\u660C\u7EEA\u300A\u6625\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECE\u58C1\u4E0A\u89C2",
		"indexes":"xlngcybsczcqb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u9648\u60C5\u8868\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u6C10",
		"indexes":"whslgkclssmzrzzydxlzydwgmzbcwwhxlngmzbsywhzl",
		"question":"\u4E94\u80E1\u5341\u516D\u56FD\u5F00\u521B\u4E86\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF\u5165\u4E3B\u4E2D\u539F\u7684\u5148\u4F8B\uFF0C\u4E3B\u8981\u7684\u4E94\u4E2A\u540D\u65CF\u88AB\u6210\u4E3A\u4E94\u80E1\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u80E1\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u8001\u4E0E\u4EBA\u4E89\u5E2D\u7F62",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwwcgjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u916C\u90ED\u7ED9\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u4EBA\u591A\u4E0D\u5F39",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzqdq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u5F39\u7434\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6765\u6E90\u4E8E\u52C7\u51A0\u4E09\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsgjdchdly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u51A0\u519B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\u7684\u6765\u6E90\uFF1F",
		"id":21299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B32\u628A\u4E00\u9EBE\u6C5F\u6D77\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjfwxdlyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u5C06\u8D74\u5434\u5174\u767B\u4E50\u6E38\u539F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u5FF5\u5C71\u4E2D\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjldhkwlspbq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u6E56\u53E3\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03\u6CC9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u98DF",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbsgdzgdmz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u540D\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u6C11\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":21302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u8C0B\u6881\u56FD\u73CD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysyalgzmysyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5C81\u591C\u5B89\u4E50\u516C\u4E3B\u6EE1\u6708\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9AA8\u76F8\u6491\u59D4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjbszc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u5317\u4F7F\u957F\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7531\u6765\u5F81\u6218\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CA7\u6D77\u6708\u660E\u73E0\u6709\u6CEA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FA1\u6797\u519B",
		"indexes":"gzjswtyqbzwgcswcycjjycjjfwwgxtxlnxbsyycjjd",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u7956\u5C06\u4E09\u4E07\u592A\u539F\u4EB2\u5175\u4F5C\u4E3A\u5BAB\u57CE\u5BBF\u536B\uFF0C\u79F0\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u3002\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u5206\u4E3A\u4E94\u4E2A\u7CFB\u7EDF\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u81E3\u5C06\u738B\u547D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczqwqdcfryx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u7DA6\u6BCB\u6F5C\u7684\u300A\u6625\u6CDB\u82E5\u8036\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79BB\u79BB\u65E9\u9E3F\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbywdjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u665A\u6E21\u6C5F\u6D25\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65CB\u8F6C",
		"indexes":"xlnxdzbshbddznr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u52A8\u4F5C\u4E0D\u662F\u6ED1\u677F\u7684\u52A8\u4F5C\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":21310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEB",
		"indexes":"fjzszrsdjpbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u6559\u4E2D\u6240\u6307\u4EBA\u751F\u7684\u4E5D\u54C1\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5B66",
		"indexes":"gddetjyhtzkdfzcsjdyxdjzjxlxzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5BF9\u513F\u7AE5\u6559\u80B2\u548C\u7AE5\u5B50\u79D1\u7684\u53D1\u5C55\u4EA7\u751F\u8F83\u5927\u5F71\u54CD\u7684\u51E0\u79CD\u6559\u5B66\u7C7B\u578B\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FE5\u773A\u7A77\u539F\u6CFD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljfjzfjcgtzkh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u5949\u6559\u8FFD\u8D74\u4E5D\u6210\u5BAB\u9014\u4E2D\u53E3\u53F7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97",
		"indexes":"zgfjyxsyszyxdygzjgdyhddwxffjbgyfmhddchqwxlnwhdbsyqzzy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F5B\u6559\u5F71\u54CD\u6DF1\u8FDC\uFF0C\u751A\u81F3\u5F71\u54CD\u5230\u4E00\u56FD\u4E4B\u541B\uFF0C\u53E4\u4EE3\u6709\u5F88\u591A\u5E1D\u738B\u4FE1\u5949\u4F5B\u6559\uFF0C\u88AB\u51A0\u4EE5\u4F5B\u95E8\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5176\u4E2D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97F6\u5973\u5CF0",
		"indexes":"slszgwdgdlzysdzyjysxlngdmbsjysfjdjd",
		"question":"\u821C\u9675\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E94\u5927\u53E4\u5E1D\u9675\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u821C\u5E1D\u846C\u4E8E\u4E5D\u5DB7\u5C71\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u540D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E5D\u5DB7\u5C71\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u666F\u70B9\uFF1F",
		"id":21315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u5357\u9022\u674E\u9F9F\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnbbstczjldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"dsczlyxbjddjgdfqzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E1D\u7EF8\u4E4B\u8DEF\u5F71\u54CD\u6BD4\u8F83\u5927\u7684\u51E0\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u5176\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9971\u537F",
		"indexes":"scdzzjgzsysjgyjsgzqzqwxlngbsyjszy",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u673A\u6784\u4E2D\u8BBE\u6709\u5BFA\u76D1\uFF0C\u5171\u6709\u4E5D\u5BFA\uFF0C\u5404\u4E13\u5176\u804C\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u5BFA\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21318
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u9732\u5BFA",
		"indexes":"tczzysyjsxlngbmbsyjs",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u5728\u4E2D\u592E\u8BBE\u6709\u4E5D\u5BFA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u90E8\u95E8\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u5BFA\uFF1F",
		"id":21319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5C0F\u9999\u9970\u300A\u96C1\u95E8\u5173\u300B\u4E4B\u8427\u592A\u540E",
		"indexes":"gxnjhssrpycshztzgxsqdssmkqjjzmyydjzhxcsyhcwtgssjqwxlnwbstgssjzy",
		"question":"\u5149\u7EEA\u5E74\u95F4\uFF0C\u753B\u5E08\u6C88\u84C9\u5703\u4EE5\u5F69\u8272\u7ED8\u5236\u540C\u6CBB\u3001\u5149\u7EEA\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5341\u4E09\u540D\u6606\u66F2\u3001\u4EAC\u5267\u8457\u540D\u6F14\u5458\u7684\u5267\u88C5\u753B\u50CF\uFF0C\u4F20\u4E16\u4EE5\u540E\uFF0C\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u540C\u5149\u5341\u4E09\u7EDD\u201D\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u540C\u5149\u5341\u4E09\u7EDD\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u513F\u7AE5\u76F8\u89C1\u4E0D\u76F8\u8BC6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhzzhxos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3A\u77E5\u7AE0\u300A\u56DE\u4E61\u5076\u4E66\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F6\u9732\u6E7F\u7F57\u8966",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzxsfgf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u4E0B\u5C71\u9022\u6545\u592B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9690\u9690\u9999\u53F0\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlsjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u77F3\u955C\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u5F52\u9E7F\u95E8\u5C71\u6B4C",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbslsyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u5546\u9690\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u5F71\u65E0\u5982\u767D\u53D1\u4F55",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclzqzsgjyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u957F\u6C99\u8FC7\u8D3E\u8C0A\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672A\u8C19\u59D1\u98DF\u6027",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwjxjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u5EFA\u300A\u65B0\u5AC1\u5A18\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u53F3",
		"indexes":"tsbdjstssqbdswdbzjdhcxlnwsytsbdj",
		"question":"\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\u662F\u5510\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u516B\u5927\u6563\u6587\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\u5BB6\u7684\u5408\u79F0\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u6E38",
		"indexes":"fwsxlsdwh",
		"question":"\u201C\u653E\u7FC1\u201D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u7684\u665A\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21328
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EF2\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsscdgw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5546\u671D\u7684\u56FD\u738B\uFF1F",
		"id":21329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6742\u66F2\u6B4C\u8BCD",
		"indexes":"xlnzstbsyqts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u8BD7\u4F53\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5168\u5510\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u4E0B\u98DE\u5929\u955C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6708\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u536B\u57CE8\u5EA7",
		"indexes":"xlnxgyhbqhdjnzcdtjscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6CB3\u5317\u79E6\u7687\u5C9B\u5883\u5185\u957F\u57CE\u7684\u7EDF\u8BA1\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5C09",
		"indexes":"hcsxsgjqzxlnxbsyjq",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u5B9E\u884C\u4E09\u516C\u4E5D\u537F\u5236\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u537F\uFF1F",
		"id":21333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5343\u592A\u4E59\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u51FA\u585E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21334
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u62D2\u590D\u897F\u654C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u585E\u57A3\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u597D\u7A7A\u6240\u60DC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczsthdzbcryss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u548C\u675C\u4E3B\u7C3F\u6625\u65E5\u6709\u6240\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8776\u604B\u82B1\uFF08\u82B1\u892A\u6B8B\u7EA2\u9752\u674F\u5C0F\uFF09",
		"indexes":"xlnscbsscncrlqzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BCD\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u5973\u8BCD\u4EBA\u674E\u6E05\u7167\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC8\u5357\u9634\u5CAD\u79C0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzyznwyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u7956\u548F\u300A\u7EC8\u5357\u671B\u9980\u96EA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u5356\u81EA\u5938",
		"indexes":"xlnjxhyhsgwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\u548C\u4E09\u56FD\u65E0\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":21339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5343\u9A91",
		"indexes":"tzdjjzbyqyyfwqbxlnxbsybyqyzl",
		"question":"\u592A\u5B97\u7684\u7981\u519B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5317\u8859\u4E03\u8425\u53C8\u5206\u4E3A\u4E03\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u8859\u4E03\u8425\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u51C0\u6563\u4EBA\u90DD\u5927\u901A",
		"indexes":"jywxzzmdqzqzsyxszjcdbqzwyxxlnwsybqz",
		"question":"\u91D1\u5EB8\u6B66\u4FA0\u4E2D\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u5168\u771F\u4E03\u5B50\u201D\u662F\u4EE5\u73B0\u5B9E\u4E2D\u91D1\u671D\u7684\u201C\u5317\u4E03\u771F\u4E3A\u539F\u578B\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u4E03\u771F\uFF1F",
		"id":21341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u6572\u521D\u591C\u78EC",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjmfgr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u7C4D\u300A\u6CA1\u8543\u6545\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u5B66\u6E38\u4FA0\u513F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmjlnc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u90CA\u300A\u70C8\u5973\u64CD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D8A\u91CE\u8F66",
		"indexes":"xdwxzdbsxlnx",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4EE3\u4E94\u9879\u6307\u5F97\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5CE1\u697C\u53F0\u6DF9\u65E5\u6708",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwsze",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C18\u8D77\u6D1B\u9633\u98CE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrjldscwl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u996F\u9646\u9053\u58EB\u9648\u6587\u6797\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u5927\u4EFB",
		"indexes":"qjqnjdbwczbsrcwjqbczxlsbsbczzl",
		"question":"\u6E05\u5609\u5E86\u5E74\u95F4\u7684\u516B\u4F4D\u624D\u5B50\u88AB\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5609\u5E86\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6CC9\u6EE1\u6E05\u542C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzydcycsydsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u300A\u6668\u8BE3\u8D85\u5E08\u9662\u8BFB\u7985\u7ECF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u5CA9",
		"indexes":"yzbgzdsqwxthfxsdyprxlnwbsyyzbgzy",
		"question":"\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\u503C\u5F97\u662F\u8DA3\u5473\u76F8\u6295\u753B\u98CE\u76F8\u4F3C\u7684\u4E00\u6279\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u7FFB\u5317\u6F6D\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbstyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u5C71\u4EAD\u591C\u5BB4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B1B",
		"indexes":"xlnzlqbsygsqdlq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u4E50\u5668\u4E0D\u662F\u8FDC\u53E4\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E50\u5668\uFF1F",
		"id":21351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhsdjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u540E\u4E16\u7684\u9152\u793C\uFF1F",
		"id":21352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F30\u5BA2\u663C\u7720\u77E5\u6D6A\u9759",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscyzqbhsszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u7ACB",
		"indexes":"lssddyfzqsfmdwljsclclzqsserjsslddmdywzqzbbkxlnxwz",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFD\u8DB3\u7403\u201C\u9996\u53D1\u540D\u5355\u201D\u300A\u6B66\u6797\u65E7\u4E8B\u300B\u66FE\u5217\u51FA\u4E86\u201C\u7B51\u7403\u4E09\u5341\u4E8C\u4EBA\u201D\u7ADE\u8D5B\u65F6\u4E24\u961F\u7684\u540D\u5355\u4E0E\u4F4D\u7F6E,\u5176\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4F4D\u7F6E?",
		"id":21354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u4E8E\u7956\u9F99\u7559\u9762\u76EE",
		"indexes":"lytjlzhyxlnj",
		"question":"\u674E\u715C\u300A\u9898\u91D1\u697C\u5B50\u540E\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5143\u66F4\u5E9F\u5174",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczagysssbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u611F\u9047\u8BD7\u4E09\u5341\u516B\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u56DE\u767E\u5DDD\u6F8D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwjlsncch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u666F\u9F99\u56DB\u5E74\u6625\u7960\u6D77\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6668\u98D9\u65AD\u66D9\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzxjhdwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5B5D\u656C\u7687\u5E1D\u633D\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7317\u6B24\u6B64\u63A8\u62E9",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljczzcsytzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u8D50\u8BF8\u5DDE\u523A\u53F2\u4EE5\u9898\u5EA7\u53F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6000\u541B\u5C5E\u79CB\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwywqyjqyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u5BC4\u90B1\u5458\u5916\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A35\u4EBA\u5F52\u6B32\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbzyssgcg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5B50\u591C\u56DB\u65F6\u6B4C\uFF1A\u6625\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u65E9\u6458\u8299\u8556",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxsyzngzdz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5BAA\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u5E74\u4E00\u89C9\u626C\u5DDE\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u9063\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21363
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9633\u548C\u4E0D\u6563\u7A77\u9014\u6068",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwywjldyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u5BC4\u674E\u510B\u5143\u9521\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CBE\u88F3\u5373\u6B64\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlwsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u9AD8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21365
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u671F\u59CB\u9057\u8204",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczczadbdchg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u7684\u300A\u767D\u5E1D\u57CE\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F52\u671B\u9010\u6625\u6765",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzwzssssfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90D1\u60DF\u5FE0\u300A\u9001\u82CF\u5C1A\u4E66\u8D74\u76CA\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u9999\u6697\u8BC6\u83B2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycydj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u591C\u6E21\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u6C34\u5343\u5BFB\u7011",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjgxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5E7F\u6EAA\u5CE1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D\u6709\u5C01\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbdjmsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E21\u8346\u95E8\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D6E\u76D6\u4E0B\u5954\u6D9B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbydhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7F15\u6668\u9E21\u672A\u5B66\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhlcyyycyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u7ACB\u6625\u6E38\u82D1\u8FCE\u6625\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624D\u5B50\u80FD\u6B4C\u591C\u672A\u592E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryyyalgzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u591C\u5BB4\u5B89\u4E50\u516C\u4E3B\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21373
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676F\u63A5\u8FD1\u81E3\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyzngzdzyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5947\u6BDB\u81EA\u5076\u9E9F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxysynyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u5709\u5E08\u300A\u548F\u725B\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u72EC\u5F02\u4E61\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlyxsxzm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u8700\u5148\u4E3B\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6628\u591C\u4E0A\u7687\u65B0\u6388\u25A1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhjlteszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u96C6\u7075\u53F0\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u4E38\u591C\u8BED\u98DE\u7535\u5149",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrdsyssfdddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u4E1A\u5E08\u5C71\u623F\u5F85\u4E01\u5927\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6570\u4E1B\u6C99\u8349\u7FA4\u9E25\u6563",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwtyswm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u82CF\u6B66\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F81\u6218\u4E8C\u5EAD\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzngzcza",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u62DF\u53E4\u8D60\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FA\u4E2D\u5C11\u5987\u4E0D\u77E5\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u95FA\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u518D\u987E\u7ED9\u4E8B\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycysctzkhyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u4F8D\u4ECE\u9014\u4E2D\u53E3\u53F7\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"mhqglxhcdjwdxkzjscznwsrzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u540D\u82B1\u503E\u56FD\u4E24\u76F8\u6B22\uFF0C\u5E38\u5F97\u541B\u738B\u5E26\u7B11\u770B\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BD7\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21383
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u79CD\u7BF1\u8FB9\u83CA",
		"indexes":"mdcjhgmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u695A\u6C5F\u6000\u53E4\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsywtwdsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u665A\u5510\u4E94\u4EE3\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21385
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u6108",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyhjcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u82B1\u95F4\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":21386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u521D\u95FB\u6D95\u6CEA\u6EE1\u8863\u88F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u767B\u9AD8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5E1D\u7EAA",
		"indexes":"xlnznpwzbsczsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u54EA\u7BC7\u6587\u7AE0\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u7EEE\u53CC\u9E33\u9E2F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbqyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u957F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21389
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u70DF\u671B\u4E94\u6D25",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbwzyycbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u5728\u72F1\u548F\u8749\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21390
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9080\u4EBA\u5085\u7C89\u7C89",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdwctj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u6E2D\u5DDD\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21391
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u5341\u91CC\u626C\u5DDE\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmzbeszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u8D60\u522B\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21392
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65F6\u96E8\u4F94\u6614\u8D24",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljszztskzyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u9001\u5FE0\u5DDE\u592A\u5B88\u5EB7\u662D\u8FDC\u7B49\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21393
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E8B\u5B81\u6020\u9051",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljfszsflzcleez",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u5949\u4F7F\u7B51\u6714\u65B9\u516D\u5DDE\u57CE\u7387\u5C14\u800C\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u611F\u65F6\u5FC3\u7EEA\u6773\u96BE\u5E73",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyjysros",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u5341\u65E5\u5076\u4E66\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21395
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u852C\u5145\u81B3\u7518\u957F\u85FF",
		"indexes":"yzqbhsszemyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21396
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5782\u6761\u62C2\u9AFB\u9B1F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcszyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u73E0\u5728\u9493\u77F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstkmcyzdwbbxsyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u6606\u660E\u6C60\u664F\u5750\u7B54\u738B\u5175\u90E8\u73E3\u4E09\u97F5\u89C1\u793A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u7269\u51C4\u51C4\u5BBF\u96E8\u6536",
		"indexes":"hfrcsmyxlnj",
		"question":"\u7687\u752B\u5189\u300A\u6625\u601D\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21399
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u95E8\u9635",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsscdcpm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u8BCD\u7684\u8BCD\u724C\u540D\uFF1F",
		"id":21400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73AF\u4F69\u7A7A\u5F52\u6708\u4E0B\u9B42",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u56DB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21401
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u659C\u697C\u4E0A\u4E94\u66F4\u949F",
		"indexes":"lsywteszemyxlnj",
		"question":"\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21402
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u541B\u5BB6\u4F55\u5904\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczchzgxeszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u957F\u5E72\u884C\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21403
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u6BDB\u5E26\u96EA\u6C57\u6C14\u84B8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfjhjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BC4\u97E9\u8C0F\u8BAE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E24\u5CB8\u733F\u58F0\u557C\u4E0D\u4F4F",
		"indexes":"lbxjlyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u4E0B\u6C5F\u9675\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21405
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u61A9\u738B\u5C11\u5E9C\u4E1C\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsyzqdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u989C\u771F\u537F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21406
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529F\u7591\u590D\u590F\u521D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjcxhhdwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3E\u66FE\u300A\u5B5D\u548C\u7687\u5E1D\u633D\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21407
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u548C\u897F\u8543\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyshxfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u9001\u548C\u897F\u8543\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21408
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60ED\u975E\u718F\u98CE\u5531",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszhjryblcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E2D\u548C\u8282\u65E5\u5BB4\u767E\u50DA\u8D50\u8BD7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21409
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u5EAD\u6C99\u6B63\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u662D\u541B\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21410
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u751F\u79EF\u77F3\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhsjcgzsxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21411
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u76F8\u9A70\u9010",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsdmx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5927\u6F20\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u5C4F\u8F9E\u91D1\u6BBF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzfhbyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5949\u548C\u522B\u8D8A\u738B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21413
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9675\u5E78\u65E7\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmzxwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u91CD\u5E78\u6B66\u529F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C34\u8C03\u6B4C\u5934\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyqzdqp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u66F2\u4E2D\u7684\u66F2\u724C\uFF1F",
		"id":21415
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u77F3\u58D5\u540F\u300B",
		"indexes":"dfpbzhnhbjnszlhdsydzpxlnbbszyqjdzp",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u6F02\u6CCA\u5728\u6E56\u5357\u6E56\u5317\u5883\u5185\u65F6\uFF0C\u4F5C\u4E86\u5F88\u591A\u5931\u610F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u8FD9\u4E00\u671F\u95F4\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21416
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u767B\u697C\u8D4B\u300B",
		"indexes":"smxrshcddwrbcwfsxlnbzpbsfsdbz",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5927\u6587\u4EBA\uFF0C\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u8D4B\u5723\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u8D4B\u5723\u201D\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":21417
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E66\u738B\u77E5\u8F7D\u6710\u5C71\u6742\u548F\u540E\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsytyspsrdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7530\u56ED\u8BD7\u6D3E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u900D\u9065\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsxqzzsw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u8BF8\u5B50\u6563\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":21419
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u548F\u6000\u4E94\u767E\u5B57\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsywyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E94\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21420
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u5F85\u65E0\u82B1\u7A7A\u6298\u679D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdqnjly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u79CB\u5A18\u300A\u91D1\u7F15\u8863\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5C0F\u77F3\u6F6D\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlspbjytwyytsdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8BD7\u7BC7\u4E0D\u5177\u6709\u6258\u7269\u5BD3\u610F\u7279\u8272\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u4E45\u4FB5\u7F57\u889C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u7389\u9636\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u5F80\u5C82\u6B8A\u8C03",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbwdyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u7684\u300A\u548F\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21424
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB5\u56DE\u9053\u6797\u8F99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwjnsxyzjsbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u89C1\u5357\u5C71\u5915\u9633\u53EC\u76D1\u5E08\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21425
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u5C71\u9AD8\u6E10\u51FA",
		"indexes":"lbydyxgcyszlmmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u767B\u53F6\u53BF\u6545\u57CE\u8C12\u6C88\u8BF8\u6881\u5E99\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FE7\u4ECE\u671B\u91CC\u5BBD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwwxxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u671B\u4E61\u5915\u6CDB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u5357\u4EAD\u6000\u8F9B\u5927\u300B",
		"indexes":"hfsxqzldqxcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u8377\u98CE\u9001\u9999\u6C14\uFF0C\u7AF9\u9732\u6EF4\u6E05\u54CD\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u6566\u671D\u91CE\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsjysbcblzsyssh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u5341\u516B\u8D50\u767E\u50DA\u8FFD\u8D4F\u56E0\u4E66\u6240\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u79CB\u4E50\u672A\u592E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlslddybl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u9E9F\u5FB7\u6BBF\u5BB4\u767E\u50DA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21430
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7CB2",
		"indexes":"jaqzzwxcjzgdss",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u4E2D\u6587\u5B66\u6210\u5C31\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21431
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u591A\u6742\u9F13\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u677E\u58F0\u665A\u7A97\u91CC",
		"indexes":"wcldtcdnzwyysycsfmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u540C\u4ECE\u5F1F\u5357\u658B\u73A9\u6708\u5FC6\u5C71\u9634\u5D14\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u6237\u58F0\u660E\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzfhtznftpgzcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u5949\u548C\u592A\u5B50\u7EB3\u5983\u592A\u5E73\u516C\u4E3B\u51FA\u964D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u6D3D\u671D\u91CE\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszhjcbgyjyssh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E2D\u548C\u8282\u8D50\u767E\u5B98\u71D5\u96C6\u56E0\u793A\u6240\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21435
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u6D66\u6E05\u6C5F\u4E07\u91CC\u6865",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfwgjshnhb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u95FB\u5B98\u519B\u6536\u6CB3\u5357\u6CB3\u5317\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BFE\u6210\u5E94\u7B2C\u4E00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljslyzrht",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u9001\u674E\u9095\u4E4B\u4EFB\u6ED1\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8868\u745E\u826F\u5728\u5179",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljwtdx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u6E29\u6C64\u5BF9\u96EA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3\u9A70\u660E\u6708\u5173",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u9500\u65E5\u51FA\u4E0D\u89C1\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczgsygxbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9AD8\u9002\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21440
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3E\u5934\u671B\u660E\u6708",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u591C\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u89C1\u964C\u5934\u6768\u67F3\u8272",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclyjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u7389\u9636\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21442
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F3\u845B\u4F3C\u6500\u6A1B",
		"indexes":"lbwzfsyxlnj",
		"question":"\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u81F3\u5206\u9655\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u4F3C\u6D1E\u5EAD\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlhynbcsykjdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6000\u8FDC\u300A\u51DD\u78A7\u6C60\u4F8D\u5BB4\u770B\u7ADE\u6E21\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u9E1F\u6816\u521D\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczccdygsxjdcesft",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u7684\u300A\u4E0E\u9AD8\u9002\u859B\u636E\u767B\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u6D6E\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21445
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u613F\u541B\u591A\u91C7\u64B7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u76F8\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u56FD\u4E09\u5343\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhhmz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u4F55\u6EE1\u5B50\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DEB\u5C71\u8FDE\u695A\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbjnn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u5F04\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u8D60\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300B",
		"indexes":"zypzsmhbsjcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u9189\u6708\u9891\u4E2D\u5723\uFF0C\u8FF7\u82B1\u4E0D\u4E8B\u541B\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B7B\u751F\u957F\u522B\u79BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmdcjhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u695A\u6C5F\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21450
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u620F\u51EB\u5206\u65AD\u5CB8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlhjzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8FD8\u4EAC\u8D60\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8854\u6CE5\u529B\u5C1A\u5FAE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzzyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u9DDF\u300A\u548F\u71D5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u4E18\u5931\u660E",
		"indexes":"xmngqjbsxybjdzyqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u60C5\u8282\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u9879\u7FBD\u672C\u7EAA\u300B\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u60C5\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":21453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u53F2",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyesssdfc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53F2\u201D\u7684\u8303\u7574\uFF1F",
		"id":21454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u6708\u601C\u7B5D\u67F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxybfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F90\u5F66\u4F2F\u300A\u82B3\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21455
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6301\u6B64\u8C22\u9AD8\u9E1F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbgsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5173\u5C71\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u5149\u8349\u9732\u56E2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycqywy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u671B\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u65E5\u9001\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbsrhd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u4EFB\u534E\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21458
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8427\u6761\u5F02\u4EE3\u4E0D\u540C\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u524D\u65CC\u9619\u585E\u901A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhsztcszz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9014\u6B21\u9655\u5DDE\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u95E8\u62AB\u7389\u9986",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxdlsgdym",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u767B\u9A8A\u5C71\u9AD8\u9876\u5BD3\u76EE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6307\u9EBE\u516B\u8352\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmxwgqsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u5E78\u6B66\u529F\u5E86\u5584\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F6C\u6218\u5165\u768B\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzlm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u7D2B\u9A9D\u9A6C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u5986\u66F2\u672A\u7EC8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydzsysmr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u4EE3\u5F20\u4F8D\u5FA1\u4F24\u7F8E\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE2\u8367\u5FC3\u6B32\u65E0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwdth",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6D1E\u5EAD\u6E56\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u5CF0\u7ED5\u745E\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyplsdsyfcyznsyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u84EC\u83B1\u4E09\u6BBF\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5949\u6555\u548F\u7EC8\u5357\u5C71\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u751F",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyzjzdzyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u6742\u5267\u4E2D\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u89D2\u8272\uFF1F",
		"id":21467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u65E5\u534E\u7EC4\u7EC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljxlycxfdxltjyysqg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u6821\u730E\u4E49\u6210\u559C\u9022\u5927\u96EA\u7387\u9898\u4E5D\u97F5\u4EE5\u793A\u7FA4\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5173\u671B\u6E10\u8D4A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjsfcwsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u4E30\u57CE\u738B\u5C11\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21469
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u97E9\u7891\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqylf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u4E50\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":21470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6234\u590D\u53E4",
		"indexes":"nscxlygspjhpxlnwdjhpdyxzd",
		"question":"\u5357\u5B8B\u51FA\u73B0\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BD7\u6D3E\u201C\u6C5F\u6E56\u6D3E\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5BF9\u6C5F\u6E56\u6D3E\u7684\u5F71\u54CD\u6700\u5927\uFF1F",
		"id":21471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u5B97\u9053",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsymdhqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u4EE3\u540E\u4E03\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21472
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F9D\u7136\u8E51\u4E91\u80CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbhmyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u5FFD\u68A6\u6E38\u4ED9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B0\u25A1\u5DF2\u9542\u6D25",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u5B88\u5C81\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9601\u9053\u9042\u6210\u589F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxxqshl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u5E78\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u9675\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21475
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u8BCF\u8D4B\u97F5\u5F97\u524D\u5B57",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21476
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9880\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlgysrjqzpdjscwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u53CA\u5176\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u4ECB\u7ECD\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21477
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BE5\u5ED3\u70DF\u4E91\u8868",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzydces",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u8C12\u5927\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21478
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u7827\u6363\u6587\u7EC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21479
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u6865\u660E\u6708\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjyzhcpg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u5BC4\u626C\u5DDE\u97E9\u7EF0\u5224\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21480
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F6D\u6CFD\u83CA\u521D\u6536",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxjyjrxlwtdgdqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u663E\u300A\u4E5D\u6708\u4E5D\u65E5\u5E78\u4E34\u6E2D\u4EAD\u767B\u9AD8\u5F97\u79CB\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52FF\u4EE5\u6076\u5C0F\u800C\u4E3A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczyxqsw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u5148\u79E6\u6563\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":21482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590D\u503C\u63A5\u8206\u9189",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlcqslzcghyby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E38\u537F\u300A\u9001\u674E\u4E2D\u4E1E\u5F52\u6C49\u9633\u522B\u4E1A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B50\u9EC4\u91D1\u52D2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlsyqsydzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u4E09\u6708\u66F2\u6C34\u5BB4\u5F97\u5C0A\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsyhmsp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u97E9\u5B5F\u8BD7\u6D3E\uFF1F",
		"id":21485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90A3\u582A\u7384\u9B13\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczszwtdylby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u9898\u5927\u5EBE\u5CAD\u5317\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u5C71\u843D\u65E5\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrshsddz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9001\u4FAF\u56DB\u5F97\u5F39\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C4F\u6B32\u9664\u5962\u653F\u8FD4\u6DF3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzxhdyjczqblt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6CBB\u300A\u54B8\u4EA8\u6BBF\u5BB4\u8FD1\u81E3\u8BF8\u4EB2\u67CF\u6881\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u6B4C\u601D\u6740\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxygs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5F52\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u82B1\u6405\u72EC\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyfdqbm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u8D4B\u5F97\u59BE\u8584\u547D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6765\u82B1\u9E1F\u82E5\u4E3A\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryjtyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u996F\u5510\u6C38\u660C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u4EE5\u9677\u90BB\u5883",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrdsyssfdddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u4E1A\u5E08\u5C71\u623F\u5F85\u4E01\u5927\u4E0D\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6CC9\u6EE1\u6E05\u542C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwdwctj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u6E2D\u5DDD\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u82B1\u72B9\u4F3C\u5760\u697C\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u91D1\u8C37\u56ED\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D8B\u8D8B\u516E\u8DC4\u8DC4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycyywmep",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u9E66\u9E49\u732B\u513F\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21495
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F59\u5F97\u5949\u620E\u65C3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczaxhzsgdqbqzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u897F\u8FD8\u81F3\u6563\u5173\u7B54\u4E54\u8865\u9619\u77E5\u4E4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u79CD\u7BF1\u8FB9\u83CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwzztys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u7AE0\u53F0\u591C\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21497
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u4E0A\u76F8\u9022\u65E0\u7EB8\u7B14",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczccfrjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5C91\u53C2\u300A\u9022\u5165\u4EAC\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F6E\u843D\u591C\u6C5F\u659C\u6708\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhtjld",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u9898\u91D1\u9675\u6E21\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u5BB4\u9F7F\u7C2A\u7F28",
		"indexes":"lbyfhzrlcyzmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5949\u548C\u6B63\u65E5\u4E34\u671D\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21500
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u89C1\u6709\u4EBA\u8FD8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbzgx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u957F\u5E72\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8\u7591\u5F85\u4F5B\u5F00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcscesjryz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u4E5D\u65E5\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21502
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9075\u6E1A\u672A\u6765\u9E3F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyyyhjztb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u6708\u591C\u6709\u6000\u7B80\u8BF8\u540C\u75C5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73E0\u7B94\u98D8\u706F\u72EC\u81EA\u5F52",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwtylznd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u5229\u6D32\u5357\u6E21\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u9EC4\u6CB3\u7ED5\u9ED1\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzyzry",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u4E2D\u5EB8\u300A\u5F81\u4EBA\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u591C\u504F\u77E5\u6625\u6C14\u6696",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlfpyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u65B9\u5E73\u300A\u6708\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u582A\u95F2\u5750\u7EC6\u601D\u91CF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlydzjwscqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u6E21\u4E2D\u6C5F\u671B\u77F3\u57CE\u6CE3\u4E0B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u524D\u4E8B\u4E0D\u5FD8\uFF0C\u540E\u4E8B\u4E4B\u5E08",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968F\u610F\u6625\u82B3\u6B47",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhryzzdxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u4E0E\u8BF8\u5B50\u767B\u5C98\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5F81\u9A6C\u4E0D\u80A5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1A\u590D\u4E94\u94E2\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrqmrymdsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u65E5\u5BB4\u6885\u9053\u58EB\u623F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u4F3C\u6D1E\u5EAD\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlhynbcsykjdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u6000\u8FDC\u300A\u51DD\u78A7\u6C60\u4F8D\u5BB4\u770B\u7ADE\u6E21\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u751F\u6B32\u95EE\u5929",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjfhsypyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E0A\u5143\u917A\u5BB4\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679D\u4ECE\u70B9\u7F00\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjljc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u526A\u5F69\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u71D5\u516C\u5CB3\u5DDE\u5C71\u57CE",
		"indexes":"xlnbbshzzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u8D3A\u77E5\u7AE0\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u9633\u7834\u4E1C\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwcdlhsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u521D\u5230\u9646\u6D51\u5C71\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21516
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u62C2\u69DB\u9732\u534E\u6D53",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbqpdsszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E05\u5E73\u8C03\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21517
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706F\u524D\u9976\u770B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczxsyyxxyt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u77E5\u8D24\u300A\u4E0A\u5143\u591C\u6548\u5C0F\u5EBE\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E3F\u96C1\u4E0D\u582A\u6101\u91CC\u542C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscchxjhy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u884C\u7ECF\u534E\u9634\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u522B\u6765\u6CA7\u6D77\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywhsxhlcgr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u6DEE\u4E0A\u559C\u4F1A\u6881\u5DDD\u6545\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB9\u8272\u671D\u671D\u843D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlfs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u82B3\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E88\u5367\u5357\u5C71\u963F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwbzwhdsltsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u522B\u4E4B\u671B\u540E\u72EC\u5BBF\u84DD\u7530\u5C71\u5E84\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C0\u547D\u8FD4\u7A77\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F6\u843D\u4ECE\u6B64\u59CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxygsp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5B64\u677E\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u601C\u591C\u534A\u865A\u524D\u5E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u8D3E\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6545\u5792\u8427\u8427\u82A6\u837B\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscqqzqxpsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u94B1\u8D77\u300A\u8D60\u9619\u4E0B\u88F4\u820D\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F59\u6C1B\u5411\u65E5\u9555",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxtzhcygpcks",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u5929\u6B63\u300A\u548C\u9648\u5143\u5149\u5E73\u6F6E\u5BC7\u8BD7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79BB\u9B42\u6697\u9A6C\u60CA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcscdltcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u916C\u675C\u9E9F\u53F0\u6625\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D35\u621A\u6743\u95E8\u5F97\u7B14\u8FF9",
		"indexes":"hyssmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u97E9\u6108\u300A\u5C71\u77F3\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u884C\u5230\u4E2D\u5EAD\u6570\u82B1\u6735",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyxcc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u300A\u6625\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u843D\u5F81\u9014\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyqwdgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u79CB\u665A\u767B\u53E4\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72B9\u4E3A\u79BB\u4EBA\u7167\u843D\u82B1",
		"indexes":"zmjryxlnyj",
		"question":"\u5F20\u6CCC\u300A\u5BC4\u4EBA\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5C71\u5BC7\u76D7\u83AB\u76F8\u4FB5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfsf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BBF\u5E9C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u832B\u832B\u6C5F\u6C49\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsksxwdlljs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u53F8\u7A7A\u66D9\u300A\u559C\u5916\u5F1F\u5362\u7EB6\u89C1\u5BBF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u7A7A\u7EFF\u91CE\u95F2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjbcw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5180\u5317\u6625\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u58F0\u5CE1\u5916\u957F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjws",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u8FDC\u5FA1\u6148\u7559",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsfhsjcgzsxfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u949F\u9F13\u9707\u5CA9\u5ECA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmzrlc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u6B63\u65E5\u4E34\u671D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5411\u5BA0\u8BD7\u96C6",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbssgsqdsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BD7\u96C6\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8BD7\u96C6\uFF1F",
		"id":21539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E23\u7B5D\u91D1\u7C9F\u67F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczldtz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u7AEF\u300A\u542C\u7B5D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u884C\u4E07\u4E58\u51FA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljhchlcscqg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u6248\u4ECE\u8FD8\u6D1B\u5448\u4F8D\u4ECE\u7FA4\u5B98\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C85\u6709\u82B7\u516E\u6FA7\u6709\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnstdsrlbddbzxlnjsbsczxln",
		"question":"\u300A\u884C\u8DEF\u96BE\u300B\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u884C\u8DEF\u96BE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A35\u4EBA\u5F52\u6B32\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywdjqjszds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u7684\u300A\u5BC4\u5168\u6912\u5C71\u4E2D\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9526\u5E06\u5E94\u662F\u5230\u5929\u6DAF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywteszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u4E8C\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u65E5\u843D\u6881\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczxhzq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8BB8\u6D51\u300A\u65E9\u79CB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CD\u5C71\u671B\u4E0D\u7A77",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlrqcj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u5165\u79E6\u5DDD\u754C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u8F66\u672A\u53EF\u6500",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyzygzds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4E8E\u7D2B\u4E91\u89C2\u8D60\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E1A\u6210\u8270\u96BE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszxjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u5E78\u664B\u9633\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5BAB\u56DB\u5E8F\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyzjcgqcyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u794E\u4E4B\u300A\u4E5D\u6210\u5BAB\u79CB\u521D\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB5\u77E5\u5357\u571F\u70ED",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstyfsqjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u591C\u53D1\u4E09\u6CC9\u5373\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u8F6E\u6CD5\u738B",
		"indexes":"mczxzffdsdfwhwddfzwtcxzbwxlnwbsybwzl",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u5728\u897F\u85CF\u5206\u5C01\u7684\u4E09\u5927\u6CD5\u738B\u548C\u4E94\u5927\u5730\u65B9\u4E4B\u738B\uFF0C\u7EDF\u79F0\u897F\u85CF\u516B\u738B\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21551
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"qmshtzdrwgydswnx",
		"question":"\u300A\u6E05\u660E\u4E0A\u6CB3\u56FE\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4F4D\u5973\u6027\uFF1F",
		"id":21552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u514B\u00B7\u7EA6\u7FF0\u900A",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsysjqtdcqrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E16\u754C\u62F3\u575B\u7684\u4F20\u5947\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u9999\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlngftbszjcdzcft",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4F5B\u5802\u4E0D\u662F\u7D2B\u7981\u57CE\u7684\u85CF\u4F20\u4F5B\u5802\uFF1F",
		"id":21554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u9E21\u8D77\u821E",
		"indexes":"xlngcsjdddg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u624D\u662F\u664B\u4EE3\u7684\u5178\u6545\uFF1F",
		"id":21555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB3\u738B\u5251",
		"indexes":"xlnbjbsyzggdmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u628A\u5251\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u540D\u5251\uFF1F",
		"id":21556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D2A\u5DDE\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglssfjsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u798F\u5EFA\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21557
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4EBF",
		"indexes":"xlnwcsxtsgzyzj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u624D\u662F\u897F\u25A1\u4F53\u8BD7\u6B4C\u4E3B\u8981\u4F5C\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u653F\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsytdymdsbxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u4EE3\u6709\u540D\u7684\u5341\u516B\u5B66\u58EB\uFF1F",
		"id":21559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u79B9\u9521",
		"indexes":"srcbjydjrwxsjlqwxlnwbsyjlzl",
		"question":"\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u7B49\u4E5D\u4EBA\u4E3A\u201C\u9999\u5C71\u4E5D\u8001\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u8001\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF7\u4EBA\u5403\u996D",
		"indexes":"cjszgzzydctjrznlxnzjtzgrdhyyxjhxlnxbszgrgndjh",
		"question":"\u6625\u8282\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u91CD\u8981\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5\uFF0C\u5728\u519C\u5386\u65B0\u5E74\u8FD9\u51E0\u5929\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u90FD\u4F1A\u6709\u4E00\u4E9B\u5FCC\u8BB3\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u8FC7\u5E74\u7684\u5FCC\u8BB3\uFF1F",
		"id":21561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u796D\u7940",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsydyljddzdhly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u79B9\u9675\u796D\u5178\u7684\u5236\u5EA6\u548C\u793C\u4EEA\uFF1F",
		"id":21562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88F4\u91CC\u5339\u5E95\u65AF",
		"indexes":"mlsspswjnsesld",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u62C9\u677E\u8D5B\u8DD1\u662F\u4E3A\u7EAA\u5FF5\u8C01\u800C\u8BBE\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718F\u5236",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsztqdctgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5236\u9676\u5668\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u5DE5\u827A\uFF1F",
		"id":21564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u571F\u9CD6",
		"indexes":"zggdzmdjddybbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4E5D\u5927\u6BD2\u836F\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u7CB1\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnzjbsgdjrqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9152\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u8282\u65E5\u5E86\u9152\uFF1F",
		"id":21566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4E3D\u840D",
		"indexes":"xlnwsjydymydpsjjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C04\u7BAD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u6CA1\u6709\u6253\u7834\u4E16\u754C\u7EAA\u5F55\uFF1F",
		"id":21567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u519B\u971E",
		"indexes":"dyghowsjdzgrss",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u83B7\u6B27\u6587\u65AF\u5956\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u5BAA",
		"indexes":"sgmjmcdfqnhmxltsxlnwbsxlrw",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u540D\u5C06\u9A6C\u8D85\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u4E43\u6C49\u672B\u897F\u51C9\u592A\u5B88\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u51C9\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"xlsswhjhy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u662F\u4E94\u864E\u5C06\u540E\u88D4\uFF1F",
		"id":21570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8499\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyqgdcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u56FD\u7684\u81E3\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21571
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA6\u7FF0.\u65AF\u6258\u514B\u987F",
		"indexes":"NBApjzgzddqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u5E73\u5747\u52A9\u653B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21572
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u59C6\u65AF\u7279\u6717",
		"indexes":"hdzgjzddhfzxcxsss",
		"question":"\u83B7\u5F97\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u73AF\u6CD5\u81EA\u884C\u8F66\u9009\u624B\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":21573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5E38\u76D1",
		"indexes":"xlnxbcsgzmc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u624D\u662F\u5B98\u804C\u540D\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":21574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F58\u5CB3",
		"indexes":"xjdsfhsgwmysqzddbwessyxlnwbsyessy",
		"question":"\u897F\u664B\u7684\u58EB\u98CE\u548C\u8BD7\u6B4C\u95FB\u540D\u4E8E\u4E16\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4E3A\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53CB\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53CB\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51EF\u5C14\u7279\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"NBAlsshdgjzddqds",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u83B7\u5F97\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u961F\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6881\u9F0E\u82AC",
		"indexes":"xlnwbcwlnjdsjzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5CAD\u5357\u8FD1\u4EE3\u56DB\u5BB6\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u622C",
		"indexes":"xlnywbsybsycmzzdlz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u5B8B\u6709\u81ED\u540D\u662D\u8457\u7684\u201C\u516D\u8D3C\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u83F2\u56FE\u65AF",
		"indexes":"gdayhcsrss",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"zglscyjzzcxmnxbsjzzl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u66FE\u6709\u201C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\u4E4B\u79F0\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u4E5D\u5DDE\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BC6\u9635",
		"indexes":"sbbfzybzzfxlnyxbsybzf",
		"question":"\u300A\u5B59\u8191\u5175\u6CD5\u300B\u4E2D\u6709\u516B\u79CD\u9635\u6CD5\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u9635\u6CD5\uFF1F",
		"id":21581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57AB\u5E95",
		"indexes":"xlngtyycbsqyygd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u4F53\u80B2\u7528\u8BCD\u4E0D\u662F\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u4F2F\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lxqcjzlcsyzgmdsjzgmnymbbgszyqwxlnwbsbbgszy",
		"question":"\u300A\u5217\u4ED9\u5168\u4F20\u300B\u8BB0\u8F7D\u4E86\u8D22\u795E\u7237\u8D75\u516C\u660E\u7684\u4E8B\u8FF9\uFF0C\u8D75\u516C\u660E\u4E43\u5143\u660E\u516B\u90E8\u9B3C\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u516B\u90E8\u9B3C\u5E05\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u71EE",
		"indexes":"xlnwsmgljzzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6C11\u56FD\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6B66",
		"indexes":"xlnwbszgsqdzhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70AE\u70D9",
		"indexes":"xlnxsscflzdzdxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u662F\u5546\u671D\u6CD5\u5F8B\u5236\u5EA6\u4E2D\u7684\u5211\u7F5A\uFF1F",
		"id":21586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606D\u4EB2\u738B",
		"indexes":"qcfjdfsfwjgfhefxlnwtmzwsyef",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5C01\u7235\u7684\u65B9\u5F0F\u5206\u4E3A\u519B\u529F\u5C01\u548C\u6069\u5C01\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u94C1\u5E3D\u5B50\u738B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6069\u5C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u5B8B\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u5C01\u7235\u738B\u56FD\u516C",
		"indexes":"xlgygrdjmbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u7235\u540D\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9547\u629A\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlngzwsnscqccxd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u52A1\u662F\u5357\u5B8B\u521D\u671F\u624D\u51FA\u73B0\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77E5\u547D\u662F\u7537\u5B50\u516D\u5341\u5C81",
		"indexes":"gwzgynldcwcwds",
		"question":"\u53E4\u6587\u4E2D\u5173\u4E8E\u5E74\u9F84\u7684\u79F0\u8C13\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21590
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u4E71",
		"indexes":"xlngzsbsfszwjnbcsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6218\u4E8B\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u9B4F\u664B\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u79FB\u8C6B\u5DDE\u6A84\u300B",
		"indexes":"jaqzdyzdyscmdzpyjbzpdswjaqzzjxlnbbszpgyjaqzdzp",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u7684\u539F\u8457\u90FD\u5DF2\u5931\u4F20\uFF0C\u660E\u4EE3\u5F20\u6EA5\u6709\u51E0\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u90FD\u662F\u4E3A\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u505A\u96C6\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u6EA5\u5173\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u65B0\u4E66\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsjyddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u8D3E\u8C0A\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":21593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56FD\u98CE\u300B",
		"indexes":"twzszgzxlsjrjdsebjskxscsejxlnxbsysej",
		"question":"\u5510\u6587\u5B97\u65F6\u5728\u56FD\u5B50\u5B66\u7ACB\u77F3\u5C06\u5112\u5BB6\u7684\u5341\u4E8C\u90E8\u7ECF\u4E66\u523B\u4E0B\uFF0C\u53F2\u79F0\u201C\u5341\u4E8C\u7ECF\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u5341\u4E8C\u7ECF\u201D",
		"id":21594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6625\u6C5F\u82B1\u6708\u591C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzclfts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u81EA\u521B\u4E50\u5E9C\u4F53\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u97E9\u975E\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"zggdwhzrjszwzldwhxlnxbsrjjd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6587\u5316\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5112\u5BB6\u662F\u6700\u4E3A\u4E3B\u6D41\u7684\u6587\u5316\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5112\u5BB6\u7ECF\u5178\uFF1F",
		"id":21596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8001\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"qcdjstcjlwgrdmzpwlczsxlnxbslczs",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u91D1\u5723\u53F9\u66FE\u5C06\u516D\u4F4D\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u540D\u8457\u8BC4\u4E3A\u201C\u516D\u624D\u5B50\u4E66\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u516D\u624D\u5B50\u4E66\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21597
	},
	{
		"answer":"25\u5C4A",
		"indexes":"sjjyayhsnj",
		"question":"\u9996\u5C4A\u7981\u70DF\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u5C4A\uFF1F",
		"id":21598
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"qcjqmgbzxsnrmqtzdsqcgydsq",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5C06\u5168\u8499\u53E4\u90E8\u4F17\u6089\u6570\u7EB3\u5165\u76DF\u65D7\u4F53\u5236\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u6E05\u671D\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u65D7\uFF1F",
		"id":21599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CE\u841D\u66F4\u8499\u906E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwhspzlsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6D63\u7EB1\u7BC7\u8D60\u9646\u4E0A\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21600
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C1\u58F0\u8FDC\u8FC7\u6F47\u6E58\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwtyysy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u7476\u745F\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E14\u5C06\u56E2\u6247\u5171\u5F98\u5F8A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclzxy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u957F\u4FE1\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F9D\u65E7\u70DF\u7B3C\u5341\u91CC\u5824",
		"indexes":"wzjltyxlnj",
		"question":"\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u91D1\u9675\u56FE\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u9ECE\u4E16",
		"indexes":"gjzlzbzn",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u603B\u90E8\u5728\u54EA\uFF1F",
		"id":21604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u953A\u7E47",
		"indexes":"xlnwssgswsfj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u9B4F\u4E66\u6CD5\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C61\u7B75\u6577\u5FF5\u8BDA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwyfhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u6E38\u6CD5\u534E\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u82E5\u8BB7",
		"indexes":"ssmxxszdqzzmdnsmljzxlnwbssmljzzy",
		"question":"\u82CF\u8F7C\u95E8\u4E0B\u5B66\u751F\u4F17\u591A\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4E43\u201C\u82CF\u95E8\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u82CF\u95E8\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDB\u5BF9\u4E00\u8A00\u91CD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljdwsdyqctdsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u7AEF\u5348\u4E09\u6BBF\u5BB4\u7FA4\u81E3\u63A2\u5F97\u795E\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6064\u4EBA\u4E88\u662F\u8D44",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlssxzzjfhz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u9001\u5F90\u5DDE\u5F20\u5EFA\u5C01\u8FD8\u9547\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E34\u98CE\u6005\u6000\u6B64",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsjxzssmfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u996F\u8BB8\u5DDE\u5B8B\u53F8\u9A6C\u8D74\u4EFB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B51\u97A0",
		"indexes":"zggdjyzqydxlxxngbszqdgc",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5C31\u6709\u8DB3\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u9009\u9879\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u8DB3\u7403\u7684\u53E4\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":21611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E6\u5E84\u300A\u7AE0\u53F0\u591C\u601D\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbsqyls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E03\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B4C\u5439\u5B9B\u72B9\u6628",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjtqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u7389\u73AF",
		"indexes":"xrmndczbyxhsszdjdzmlnmxhszs",
		"question":"\u5F62\u5BB9\u7F8E\u5973\u7684\u8BCD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u95ED\u6708\u7F9E\u82B1\u7B97\u662F\u6700\u9876\u7EA7\u7684\u8D5E\u7F8E\u4E86\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u7F9E\u82B1\u662F\u6307\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u4E09",
		"indexes":"hwdyyfwnjqgfwjgz",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D\u4E8E\u5143\u5C01\u4E94\u5E74\u5C06\u5168\u56FD\u5206\u4E3A\u51E0\u4E2A\u5DDE\uFF1F",
		"id":21615
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D85\u55BB",
		"indexes":"yxnzbsybyxs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6BD4\u55BB\u5F62\u5F0F\uFF1F",
		"id":21616
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF1\u6797\u4EBA\u4E0D\u77E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwzlg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u7AF9\u91CC\u9986\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21617
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u99A5\u9752\u6EAA\u91CC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbssfjyydzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u4E0A\u5DF3\u6D6E\u6C5F\u5BB4\u97F5\u5F97\u5740\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u65E5\u6CB3\u6881\u4E0A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbysb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u975E",
		"indexes":"xlnywsfjddbrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6CD5\u5BB6\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u987B\u6000\u62B1\u91CD\u51C4\u51C4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlysdwesdcymxc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u9001\u9093\u738B\u4E8C\u5341\u5F1F\u4ECE\u76CA\u7267\u5BA3\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u4E9A\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nssqcmnstmhyxecldzmjbwxttxlnwsnsddbrw",
		"question":"\u5357\u793E\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u672B\u5E74\u53D7\u540C\u76DF\u4F1A\u5F71\u54CD\u800C\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\u8457\u540D\u8FDB\u6B65\u6587\u5B66\u56E2\u4F53\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u5357\u793E\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B32\u7A77\u5343\u91CC\u76EE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwzhdgql",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u4E4B\u6DA3\u300A\u767B\u9E73\u96C0\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u9634\u5E26\u53F6\u660F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwsflhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9001\u8D39\u516D\u8FD8\u8700\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6709\u53CC\u7AF9\u6797",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgzcjq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u6625\u6C5F\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u6DF1\u70DF\u96FE\u591A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjszzzsk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u90D1\u5DDE\u5468\u53F8\u7A7A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u8349\u5DF2\u4E91\u66AE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwtysrdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E29\u5EAD\u7B60\u300A\u9001\u4EBA\u4E1C\u6E38\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u897F",
		"indexes":"tdkclzgzqssdhfdjzxmnxbsytcsdzy",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5F00\u521B\u4E86\u4E2D\u56FD\u653F\u533A\u53F2\u4E0A\u9053\u548C\u5E9C\u7684\u5EFA\u5236\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u671D\u5341\u9053\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u5357\u4E94\u5E9C\u7ECF\u7565\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"tczqcyfzgjdjmgysgfzmgfzsyjdsxlnwbsyfzjds",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u957F\u671F\u5904\u4E8E\u85E9\u9547\u5272\u636E\u7684\u5C40\u9762\uFF0C\u5171\u6709\u5341\u4E2A\u85E9\u9547\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u85E9\u9547\u8BBE\u6709\u8282\u5EA6\u4F7F\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u85E9\u9547\u8282\u5EA6\u4F7F\uFF1F",
		"id":21629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8054",
		"indexes":"zcclgjzldgjbbkxlnggj",
		"question":"\u6700\u521D\u6210\u7ACB\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u672F",
		"indexes":"xlngxmbsayhbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9879\u76EE\u4E0D\u662F\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":21631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u672F",
		"indexes":"xlngxmbsayhbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9879\u76EE\u4E0D\u662F\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":21632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5206\u5272\u636E\u7EA1\u7B79\u7B56",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclzqjzzbxllbeyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u6C5F\u5DDE\u91CD\u522B\u859B\u516D\u67F3\u516B\u4E8C\u5458\u5916\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u660E\u9001\u5BA2\u695A\u5C71\u5B64",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwclfrlsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u8299\u84C9\u697C\u9001\u8F9B\u6E10\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F2B\u4FDF\u660E\u5E74\u6842",
		"indexes":"lzydgdmxmyxlnj",
		"question":"\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u300A\u53E4\u4E1C\u95E8\u884C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u6258\u8247",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsjxyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6781\u9650\u8FD0\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":21636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"xlbshddqbzywqdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u7684\u9A91\u5175\u4E3B\u8981\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21637
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D35\u6E38\u884C",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsccdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5C91\u53C2\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64\u8BED\u8BB0\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsxblgyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u767D\u9E7F\u89C2\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A5\u5230\u5C71\u4E2D\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwhjlt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6C49\u6C5F\u4E34\u773A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u897F",
		"indexes":"ttzbqgfwsdxlnxbsysd",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u628A\u5168\u56FD\u5206\u4E3A\u5341\u9053\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5341\u9053\uFF1F",
		"id":21641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82D4\u6DF1\u4E0D\u8FA8\u94ED",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlwwjt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6587\u7FC1\u8BB2\u5802\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94A6\u5929",
		"indexes":"qwxlngbsyscdzzjgzdljzy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u673A\u6784\u4E2D\u7684\u516D\u76D1\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21643
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82D4\u5206\u4F3C\u5217\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwcsm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u51FA\u77F3\u95E8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3\u6709\u7075\u7280\u4E00\u70B9\u901A",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsysg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u968B\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21645
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u5949\u5929\u4E66\u62DC\u7410\u95F1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u8700\u76F8\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E66\u9E49\u524D\u5934\u4E0D\u6562\u8A00",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzqygc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6731\u5E86\u9980\u300A\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BC1\u5723",
		"indexes":"xlngnhbstcdnh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u5E74\u53F7\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5E74\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u91ED\u7130\u9752\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxywshg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u697C\u81EA\u7BA1\u5F26",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsjrxlhjby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u50E7\u768E\u7136\u300A\u5BFB\u9646\u9E3F\u6E10\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6625\u666F\u7269\u6ECB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsywctsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u671B\u6625\u4EAD\u4F8D\u6E38\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u7B3C\u5BD2\u6C34\u6708\u7B3C\u6C99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmbqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB6\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"gwzgybxdchcwds",
		"question":"\u53E4\u6587\u4E2D\u5173\u4E8E\u767E\u59D3\u7684\u79F0\u547C\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u4E34\u996E\u9A6C\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszccgxsqjdzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6B21\u6210\u768B\u5148\u5723\u64D2\u5EFA\u5FB7\u4E4B\u6240\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u7720\u4E0D\u89C9\u6653",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczmhrcx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u6625\u6653\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u987A\u8D77\u4E49",
		"indexes":"xlncqysscsqdrmqy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u6B21\u8D77\u4E49\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\uFF1F",
		"id":21656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5401\u55DF\u9675\u8C37\u8FC1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxjybq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u53D9\u5BC4\u5458\u534A\u5343\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u7AA5\u9752\u6D77\u6E7E",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmjyzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u90CA\u300A\u6E38\u5B50\u541F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u8299\u84C9\u697C\u9001\u8F9B\u6E10\u300B",
		"indexes":"hyljyrwpmskcsgcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5BD2\u96E8\u8FDE\u6C5F\u591C\u5165\u5434\uFF0C\u5E73\u660E\u9001\u5BA2\u695A\u5C71\u5B64\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbscqsqdgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u5929\u7965\u53F7\u6587\u5C71\u5C45\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xlgygdcrdbhbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BCD\u4EBA\u7684\u522B\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60AC\u5F27\u5C06\u76F8\u513F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcygtmwsbjts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5143\u5149\u300A\u592A\u6BCD\u9B4F\u6C0F\u534A\u5F84\u9898\u77F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9648\u60C5\u8868\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsypw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9A88\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":21663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u5728\u6728\u5170\u821F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsybql",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u5317\u9752\u841D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u9785",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyqcdcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u671D\u7684\u81E3\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u4E11",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsgygwgzsdwj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u8FC7\u4E94\u5173\u65A9\u6740\u7684\u6B66\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":21666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u7BA1\u6742\u98CE\u6D41",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsxlytgdqyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u68A8\u56ED\u4EAD\u89C2\u6253\u7403\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7707\u7136\u767B\u4E91\u8F66",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbhx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6000\u4ED9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbstcsqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5F02\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":21669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5B98\u6367\u65E5\u8F66",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszcclc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u521D\u51FA\u6D1B\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4F2F\u4F26",
		"indexes":"NBAqlbzddqyss",
		"question":"NBA\u62A2\u7BEE\u677F\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21671
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5973\u4E8E\u7F51\u9AD82.4\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnxgypqydsjmscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u6392\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u6570\u636E\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5355\u9A6C\u5C82\u9080\u529F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadzdccxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u4E1C\u5F81\u7B54\u671D\u81E3\u76F8\u9001\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21673
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78EC",
		"indexes":"xszdqtlqbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u590F\u5546\u5468\u7684\u9752\u94DC\u4E50\u5668\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606C\u8499",
		"indexes":"zgsqmjbcxlnywbszgmj",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u540D\u5C06\u8F88\u51FA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u540D\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":21675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u697C\u5DF2\u534A\u66DB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u6C5F\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsytsbdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B",
		"indexes":"zgdgtdcsbknsxlnx",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u53E4\u5854\u7684\u5C42\u6570\u4E0D\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5E73\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"xlnygzybsfszhc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E00\u4E2A\u6218\u5F79\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6C49\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":21679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DD1\u6C14\u4F9D\u8FDF\u67F3\u8272\u9752",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhszcrxwcgyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6625\u65E5\u5E78\u671B\u6625\u5BAB\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5D\u9633\u738B",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyxjsqbwzlzdbwzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u897F\u664B\u65F6\u671F\u201C\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7387\u6027\u5937\u8363\u8FB1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljhtfljjxmtj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u548C\u540C\u5E9C\u674E\u796D\u9152\u4F11\u6C90\u7530\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7D\u90FD\u65E0\u591A\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzkhx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u82E6\u5BD2\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5C71\u9E1F\u98DE\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzyjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u300A\u6C5F\u96EA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F2F\u5588\u8FC1\u585E\u5317",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbytzsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u9014\u4E2D\u8FF0\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21685
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u95F4\u96EA\u4F3C\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhzxhrygslt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u4EF2\u5BA3\u300A\u6666\u65E5\u5BB4\u9AD8\u6C0F\u6797\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9636\u79CB\u82D4\u85D3\u9EC4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczxybjy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F90\u5F66\u4F2F\u300A\u5A55\u59A4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u53F6\u6EE1\u7A7A\u5C71",
		"indexes":"lbdcsmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u7684\u300A\u6625\u601D\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CA9\u6249\u677E\u5F84\u957F\u5BC2\u5BE5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfwflszgcjjhmt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u97E6\u8BBD\u5F55\u4E8B\u5B85\u89C2\u66F9\u5C06\u519B\u753B\u9A6C\u56FE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u671D",
		"indexes":"lsszmdtdzcttzscszngcd",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u5C6F\u7530\u5236\u662F\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A7A\u4EE4\u5C81\u6708\u6613\u8E49\u8DCE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczchhhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u98A2\u300A\u9EC4\u9E64\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62AB\u8863\u89C9\u9732\u6ECB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdsyhjllczcyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u548C\u664B\u9675\u8DEF\u4E1E\u65E9\u6625\u6E38\u671B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E2\u6247\u79CB\u98CE\u8D77",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyqbm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u59BE\u8584\u547D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u6DF1\u4E91\u666F\u9C9C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwrykwdjls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u5165\u5D16\u53E3\u4E94\u6E21\u5BC4\u674E\u9069\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90ED\u5B50\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"xlnwbshcmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u540D\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":21695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u548C\u7EFF\u91CE\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsycrhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u6000\u5F52\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u534A\u949F\u58F0\u5230\u5BA2\u8239",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjfqyb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u7EE7\u300A\u67AB\u6865\u591C\u6CCA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u821C\u4E50\u4E0B\u524D\u6EAA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyccrlycsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4F8D\u5BB4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u522B\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsfszsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5915\u6000\u7A7A\u610F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u9752\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83B2\u82B1\u5B9D\u76D6\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycysrqssyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u4E09\u65E5\u66F2\u6C34\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21701
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u70DF\u6563\u5165\u4E94\u4FAF\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhhhs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u5BD2\u98DF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5185\u5927\u81E3",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsqcdcypwzjg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u4ECE\u4E00\u54C1\u6587\u804C\u4EAC\u5B98\uFF1F",
		"id":21703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A91",
		"indexes":"xlnzjybsyzhcszdly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u6280\u827A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u300A\u5F20\u8861\u4F20\u300B\u6240\u6307\u7684\u516D\u827A\uFF1F",
		"id":21704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u6708\u8FC7\u6B8B\u5792",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczljxqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u810A\u865A\u300A\u9619\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51C9\u666F\u5411\u79CB\u6F84",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwbljdsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u522B\u674E\u5CE4\u5F97\u80DC\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21706
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58EE\u5FD7\u9010\u5E74\u8870",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwznby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u7EC8\u5357\u522B\u4E1A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73ED\u9B13\u5411\u957F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzdfsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u65E9\u5EA6\u5206\u6C34\u5CAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u9645\u5927\u5956\u8D5B",
		"indexes":"ATPzynzwqxhdbszlbbkyxnx",
		"question":"ATP(\u804C\u4E1A\u7537\u5B50\u7F51\u7403\u534F\u4F1A)\u7684\u6BD4\u8D5B\u79CD\u7C7B\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u989C\u672A\u8001\u6069\u5148\u65AD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczbjyhgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u540E\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8DB3\u8D77\u7EA2\u5C18",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u5218\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u843D\u82B1\u65F6\u8282\u53C8\u9022\u541B",
		"indexes":"dfjnflgnyxlnj",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6C5F\u5357\u9022\u674E\u9F9F\u5E74\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsytcddfgzzdlc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u5B98\u5236\u4E2D\u7684\u516D\u66F9\uFF1F",
		"id":21713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhcdxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5212\u8239\u7684\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":21714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5F0B\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbslld",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5362\u7EB6\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u671D",
		"indexes":"lsszmdtdzcjtzscszngcd",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u5747\u7530\u5236\u662F\u4EA7\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"gjcthzxcthldjxbcwjdkxdfzdxswglssdyccxgjcthzxcthldjxszngcd",
		"question":"\u5DE5\u5320\u4F20\u7EDF\u548C\u54F2\u5B66\u4F20\u7EDF\u5408\u6D41\u7684\u8FF9\u8C61\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u8FD1\u4EE3\u79D1\u5B66\u5927\u53D1\u5C55\u7684\u5148\u58F0\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u51FA\u73B0\u5DE5\u5320\u4F20\u7EDF\u548C\u54F2\u5B66\u4F20\u7EDF\u5408\u6D41\u7684\u8FF9\u8C61\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA\u5904\u7591\u82B1\u6EE1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlmhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6885\u82B1\u843D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u4E0A\u7F8A\u5F52\u585E\u8349\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscxfgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u859B\u9022\u300A\u5BAB\u8BCD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ECE\u660C\u697C",
		"indexes":"xlngbsbjbdlzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u516B\u5927\u697C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u7F15\u6668\u9E21\u672A\u5B66\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhlcyyycyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u7ACB\u6625\u6E38\u82D1\u8FCE\u6625\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8282\u65C4\u96F6\u843D\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlyxq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u96E8\u96EA\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C9C\u5351",
		"indexes":"clcysxtsqllgsytccymmfccdjnymsdxlngmzdcj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6555\u52D2\u5DDD\uFF0C\u9634\u5C71\u4E0B\uFF0C\u5929\u4F3C\u7A79\u5E90\uFF0C\u7B3C\u76D6\u56DB\u91CE\u3002\u5929\u82CD\u82CD\uFF0C\u91CE\u832B\u832B\uFF0C\u98CE\u5439\u8349\u4F4E\u89C1\u725B\u7F8A\u3002\u201D\u63CF\u8FF0\u7684\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u573A\u666F\uFF1F",
		"id":21723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C",
		"indexes":"wjsqdhryybfsjfbyxlngmzbsyzl",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u664B\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u80E1\u4EBA\u6709\u4E00\u90E8\u5206\u662F\u91D1\u53D1\u78A7\u773C\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8FD9\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":21724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F44",
		"indexes":"sdyyczdlqxlnxbssddlq",
		"question":"\u5546\u4EE3\u5DF2\u6709\u6210\u7EC4\u7684\u4E50\u5668\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5546\u4EE3\u7684\u4E50\u5668\uFF1F",
		"id":21725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DD1\u5792",
		"indexes":"bqdjbfsjsbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u68D2\u7403\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u9632\u5B88\u6280\u672F\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A2A\u62CD\u76F4\u6253",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyppqdtgzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E52\u4E53\u7403\u7684\u63A8\u653B\u6218\u672F?",
		"id":21727
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8DB3\u8DF5\u80E1\u5C18",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwcjx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6101\u770B\u7389\u955C\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjmhl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6885\u82B1\u843D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5149\u6597\u4E3A\u5DE6\u6BC5\u516C",
		"indexes":"xlgygrdshbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EBA\u7684\u8C25\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"ssjawxxjmdkcz",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u5EFA\u5B89\u6587\u5B66\u65B0\u5C40\u9762\u7684\u5F00\u521B\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":21731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"sgsqsrzsfldwrbcqzzzmdsjaqzxlnwbsyjaqz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u867D\u7136\u6218\u4E8B\u7EB7\u4E71\uFF0C\u4F46\u6587\u4EBA\u8F88\u51FA\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u662F\u201C\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u201C\u5EFA\u5B89\u4E03\u5B50\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7965\u7B26\u591C\u544A\u4E30",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyyhgm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u8C12\u6C49\u9AD8\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C89\u94A9\u6447\u5154\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzljzwy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u6C5F\u4E2D\u671B\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u8A00\u5F8B\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"xlnyxbstsdjbxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u8BD7\u7684\u57FA\u672C\u5F62\u5F0F\uFF1F",
		"id":21735
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u539F\u88AB\u82B1\u5B9E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstxjjcnrmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u6653\u6D4E\u80F6\u5DDD\u5357\u5165\u5BC6\u754C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u5E74\u591A\u75C5\u72EC\u767B\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfdl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u767B\u697C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E45\u5BA2\u4E34\u6D77\u6709\u6000",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwjklhyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u4E45\u5BA2\u4E34\u6D77\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95FB\u98CE\u5750\u76F8\u60A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczmhrdqdlsjzw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u300A\u79CB\u767B\u5170\u5C71\u5BC4\u5F20\u4E94\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u94B1\u8D60\u4E0B\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5927\u917A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6708\u901A\u7985\u5BC2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczhhccyqyjsjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u916C\u7A0B\u5EF6\u79CB\u591C\u5373\u4E8B\u89C1\u8D60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6\u7B5D\u591C\u4E45\u6BB7\u52E4\u5F04",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwqyq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u79CB\u591C\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u5F53\u5171\u526A\u897F\u7A97\u70DB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyyyjb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u591C\u96E8\u5BC4\u5317\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u987A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnwsrbsymdscz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u4EE3\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21744
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F5E\u56FD\u516C\u4FAF\u541B\u96C6",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsxhkggc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u6C49\u5F00\u56FD\u529F\u81E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21745
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BA1\u4E50\u6709\u624D\u539F\u4E0D\u5FDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u620F\u7F62\u66FE\u65E0\u7406\u66F2\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfajt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u54C0\u6C5F\u5934\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjzljozbjsjddcjzh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u5386\u5C4A\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u6210\u7EE9\u6700\u597D\uFF1F",
		"id":21748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjzljozbjsjddcjzh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5728\u5386\u5C4A\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u6210\u7EE9\u6700\u597D\uFF1F",
		"id":21749
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1F\u5251\u8BB8\u826F\u56FE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadhstzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u7B54\u97E9\u4F7F\u540C\u5728\u8FB9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECD\u6500\u742A\u6811\u8363",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjttsmxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5BC4\u5929\u53F0\u53F8\u9A6C\u5148\u751F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5A01\u519B",
		"indexes":"tzdjjzbyljyfwlbxlnxbsybyljzl",
		"question":"\u592A\u5B97\u7684\u7981\u519B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5317\u8859\u516D\u519B\u53C8\u5206\u4E3A\u516D\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u8859\u516D\u519B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u516C\u660E",
		"indexes":"zggdshzxlnwsxscs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u795E\u8BDD\u4E2D\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u795E\u4ED9\u662F\u8D22\u795E\uFF1F",
		"id":21753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BBF\u6614\u68A6\u89C1\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsjtzgsjfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u996F\u5510\u5DDE\u9AD8\u4F7F\u541B\u8D74\u4EFB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8584\u66AE\u7A7A\u6F6D\u66F2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfcszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6625\u5BBF\u5DE6\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u591C\u8349\u866B\u9E23",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxysyws",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u5D69\u5CB3\u95FB\u7B19\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u79D1\u7279",
		"indexes":"NBAdsfqjlsyngqybcd",
		"question":"NBA\u7684\u4E09\u5206\u7403\u7EAA\u5F55\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u4E2A\u7403\u5458\u4FDD\u6301\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u662D\u541B",
		"indexes":"xlnwsyhcsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CAD\u5916\u97F3\u4E66\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlpdhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9891\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21759
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u606F\u541B\u60C5\u66F4\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwxfr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u606F\u592B\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BB6\u4F4F\u5C42\u57CE\u90BB\u6C49\u82D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscllwcez",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5362\u7EB6\u300A\u665A\u6B21\u9102\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u67F3\u5171\u98CE\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctbsdzcyyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5DF4\u5C71\u9053\u4E2D\u9664\u591C\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6069\u8363\u53D8\u82E6\u8F9B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysglzbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u9001\u9AD8\u90CE\u4E2D\u5317\u4F7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94BB\u9267\u6F6D\u4E1C\u5C0F\u4E18\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"xlnpyjbsylzydyzbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u7BC7\u6E38\u8BB0\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u6C38\u5DDE\u516B\u8BB0\uFF1F",
		"id":21764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58F0\u9759\u591C\u76F8\u5B9C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlhchmyzytczz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u548C\u5D14\u9EC4\u95E8\u5BD3\u76F4\u591C\u542C\u8749\u4E4B\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EE7\u660C",
		"indexes":"hcdhnwlaybgymdmkxlnwbsybmkzy",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u6DEE\u5357\u738B\u5218\u5B89\u6709\u516B\u4E2A\u6709\u540D\u7684\u95E8\u5BA2\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u95E8\u5BA2\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21766
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D\u300A\u84BF\u91CC\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlgyjasrjqzpdcwmssnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u8BD7\u4EBA\u53CA\u5176\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u9519\u8BEF\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21767
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u8012",
		"indexes":"xlnwssmsxszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u82CF\u95E8\u56DB\u5B66\u58EB\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F73\u6C14\u6EE1\u65CC\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwyzxsyxsfcylwz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9B4F\u5143\u5FE0\u300A\u4FEE\u4E66\u9662\u5B66\u58EB\u5949\u6555\u5BB4\u6881\u738B\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u63FD\u8F94\u5F55\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsnssqsrdsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u8BD7\u96C6\uFF1F",
		"id":21770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56FD\u98CE\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbjdbssszdly",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u7ECF\u5178\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u5E08\u8BF4\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u516D\u827A\uFF1F",
		"id":21771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxqsqdjdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5148\u79E6\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u7ECF\u5178\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5308\u5974",
		"indexes":"tcwlyxglyzslllddhfxlngbsdhf",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u4E3A\u4E86\u6709\u6548\u7BA1\u7406\u5F02\u65CF\uFF0C\u8BBE\u7ACB\u4E86\u516D\u5927\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":21773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A8\u606F\u5982\u6709\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbyf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u548F\u98CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u6CFD\u59D4\u662D\u5BA3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszslssrs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9001\u674E\u5C1A\u4E66\u5165\u8700\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD4\u5C14\u00B7\u62C9\u8D5B\u5C14",
		"indexes":"NBAlssnwqxhddzgjjzzd",
		"question":"NBA\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u90A3\u4F4D\u7403\u661F\u83B7\u5F97\u7684\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6212\u6307\u6700\u591A\uFF1F",
		"id":21776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u661F\u5165\u5251\u7AEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwszsfrlgfxkycr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u9001\u90D1\u5C11\u5E9C\u5165\u8FBD\u5171\u8D4B\u4FA0\u5BA2\u8FDC\u4ECE\u620E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u53F6\u866B\u4E66\u904D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzzxgzs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u957F\u4FE1\u5BAB\u4E2D\u6811\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21778
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5916\u52A1\u90E8",
		"indexes":"qcsylbxlbsylbds",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u8BBE\u6709\u201C\u516D\u90E8\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516D\u90E8\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u6625\u5165\u65E7\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfcszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6625\u5BBF\u5DE6\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u4F1A\u591A\u6B22\u58F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszyrcyqjtflysyqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u91CD\u9633\u65E5\u8D50\u5BB4\u66F2\u6C5F\u4EAD\uFF0C\u8D4B\u516D\u97F5\u8BD7\u7528\u6E05\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u601C\u65E0\u5B9A\u6CB3\u8FB9\u9AA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczctlxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u9676\u300A\u9647\u897F\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21782
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u62DC\u65E6",
		"indexes":"xdalpkcsrss",
		"question":"\u73B0\u4EE3\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u62DC\u65E6",
		"indexes":"alpkhqwhqdsjzs",
		"question":"\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514B\u4F1A\u65D7-\u4E94\u73AF\u65D7\u7684\u8BBE\u8BA1\u8005\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD\u300A\u71D5\u6B4C\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlzphzzdyzqdxxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4F5C\u54C1\u548C\u4F5C\u8005\u5BF9\u5E94\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u9009\u9879\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60A0\u60A0\u8FDC\u5BA2\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqnxbd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u5357\u884C\u522B\u5F1F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7834\u6D95\u6682\u4E3A\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjszzzsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9001\u6893\u5DDE\u5468\u53F8\u529F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52A8\u5DE5",
		"indexes":"xlbsyhlzsydsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9EC4\u5386\u4E2D\u672F\u8BED\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u91D1\u94F8\u9A6C\u97AD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u9AA2\u9A6C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u91CC\u5176\u5982\u4F55",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczyjdztsglbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u7ED3\u7684\u300A\u8D3C\u9000\u793A\u5B98\u540F\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676F\u63A5\u8FD1\u81E3\u6B22",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyzngzdzyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u4F8D\u5BB4\u957F\u5B81\u516C\u4E3B\u4E1C\u5E84\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6797\u7E41\u82B1\u7167\u773C\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlsyhb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u97E9\u7891\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6298\u621F\u6C88\u6C99\u94C1\u672A\u9500",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmcb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u8D64\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u6765\u672A\u8457\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzqsbs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E54\u300A\u4E66\u8FB9\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u65F7\u9E4A\u505C\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyfhqxsylydyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E03\u5915\u4F8D\u5BB4\u4E24\u4EEA\u6BBF\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D8\u8C03\u5982\u95FB\u6768\u67F3\u6625",
		"indexes":"cczmcxfsfdfcsxmyxlnj",
		"question":"\u5C91\u53C2\u300A\u8D70\u9A6C\u5DDD\u884C\u5949\u9001\u5C01\u5927\u592B\u51FA\u5E08\u897F\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5408\u8D64\u7B26\u5148",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxyyhszm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u8C12\u6C49\u4E16\u7956\u5E99\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21797
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u9CA4\u8FE2\u8FE2\u4E00\u7EB8\u7B14",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsyjlhlz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u5BC4\u4EE4\u72D0\u90CE\u4E2D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9C\u6237",
		"indexes":"bwmnbflzdqydldzzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u5317\u9B4F\u672B\u5E74\u5317\u65B9\u516D\u9547\u5927\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u516D\u5927\u91CD\u9547\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u8499\u771F\u50E7\u987E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwycjsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u96E8\u4ECE\u7B95\u5C71\u6765\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21800
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u5FC3\u83AB\u5171\u82B1\u4E89\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsycby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u7B79\u7B14\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u602A\u7389\u5C71\u9893",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlxfszgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8F9B\u6CD5\u53F8\u5B85\u89C2\u5993\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21802
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u9707\u6625",
		"indexes":"jjssxyysstbxlnwbsjjssstb",
		"question":"\u848B\u4ECB\u77F3\u624B\u4E0B\u4E5F\u6709\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u848B\u4ECB\u77F3\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21803
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6885\u67F3\u6E21\u6C5F\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwcbgsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u6E7E\u300A\u6B21\u5317\u56FA\u5C71\u4E0B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21804
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64D2\u4FD8\u5E1D\u9053\u4EA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlljxccgtjxsqjdzsmsgygef",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u300A\u884C\u6B21\u6210\u768B\u9014\u7ECF\u5148\u5723\u64D2\u5EFA\u5FB7\u4E4B\u6240\u7F05\u601D\u529F\u4E1A\u611F\u800C\u8D4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5012\u6C64",
		"indexes":"tjcqpccxfdxlbsyqzzyds",
		"question":"\u5510\u541B\u81E3\u6E05\u5E73\u8336\u7A0B\u5E8F\u7E41\u591A\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5176\u4E2D\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21806
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9694\u53F6\u9EC4\u9E42\u7A7A\u597D\u97F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfkz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5BA2\u81F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21807
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u5723\uFF1A\u4E1C\u664B\u738B\u732E\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"wglssdlsbbkxls",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u516D\u5723\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21808
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u6301\u957F\u74E2\u5750\u5DF4\u4E18",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczbjyzhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u957F\u6068\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E1D\u5F97\u5723\u76F8\u76F8\u66F0\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfbcx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5175\u8F66\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u751F\u4E00\u5251\u77E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmdbsqj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A6C\u6234\u300A\u705E\u4E0A\u79CB\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67B6\u6D77\u6CE2\u6F84\u955C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsmgjzes",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u300A\u8FC7\u65E7\u5B85\u4E8C\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21812
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u7ED5\u5439\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysytsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5BBF\u7FBD\u4EAD\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679D\u4E9A\u679C\u65B0\u80A5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydwst",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u90FD\u5C09\u5C71\u4EAD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E95\u7530",
		"indexes":"wasbfdnrzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u5229",
		"indexes":"ssnlzxdsjbgj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u5E74\u9F84\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6458\u82B3\u5171\u73CD\u8350",
		"indexes":"qzzwsgyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u5DEB\u5C71\u9AD8\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u6708\u51B7\u76F8\u968F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczsjrxlhjby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u50E7\u768E\u7136\u300A\u5BFB\u9646\u9E3F\u6E10\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65C5\u5BA2\u975E\u60A0\u60A0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadlyzr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u7B54\u6D1B\u9633\u4E3B\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u71B9",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsymcrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u660E\u671D\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21820
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5546\u9690",
		"indexes":"xlngsrcswtsqddb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u8BD7\u4EBA\u624D\u662F\u665A\u5510\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\uFF1F",
		"id":21821
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u8BBA\u6570\u7EFF\u94B1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjyss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u6709\u6240\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21822
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5076\u7136\u503C\u6797\u53DF",
		"indexes":"dffjyzsygsymyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u5949\u6D4E\u9A7F\u91CD\u9001\u4E25\u516C\u56DB\u97F5\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21823
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u66AE\u5BA2\u6101\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczmhrsjdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u5BBF\u5EFA\u5FB7\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21824
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u5439\u4F55\u5386\u5386",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxyqrtrytb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u9898\u6C5D\u9633\u6F6D\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21825
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79F0\u540D\u5FC6\u65E7\u5BB9",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlzqxnz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u65B0\u5E74\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21826
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u971C\u4E0B\u9707\u96F7",
		"indexes":"dsylyanyxlnj",
		"question":"\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u65C5\u5BD3\u5B89\u5357\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21827
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u559C\u9E4A",
		"indexes":"qcwgcfsdbzdsydwwtaxlnzdwbscfbzsdta",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u6587\u5B98\u671D\u670D\u4E0A\u7684\u8865\u5B50\u90FD\u662F\u4EE5\u52A8\u7269\u4E3A\u56FE\u6848\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u671D\u670D\u8865\u5B50\u4E0A\u7684\u56FE\u6848\uFF1F",
		"id":21828
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73E0\u623F\u6298\u6D77\u69B4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcstdwsc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5510\u90FD\u5C09\u5C71\u6C60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21829
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u4EBA\u591A\u5B66\u5439",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjftq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u51E4\u53F0\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21830
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6816\u6816\u4E00\u4EE3\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjlwyhy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u671B\u6708\u6000\u8FDC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21831
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u5439\u53C8\u751F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlyxjwdyyb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u76CA\u300A\u559C\u89C1\u5916\u5F1F\u53C8\u8A00\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21832
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u574E\u58C8\u5026\u6E38\u79E6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwyhgyspsl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u610F\u4E0A\u88F4\u4F8D\u90CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21833
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u4EF2\u8212\u732E\u5929\u4EBA\u4E09\u7B56",
		"indexes":"sgycmdbxxlnxbsybxzy",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6709\u51FA\u540D\u7684\u201C\u516B\u732E\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u732E\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21834
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u5439\u4FBF\u5750\u6851",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgztxywctzsryzzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90ED\u9707\u300A\u540C\u5F90\u5458\u5916\u9664\u592A\u5B50\u820D\u4EBA\u5BD3\u76F4\u4E4B\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21835
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4F2F\u4F26",
		"indexes":"dcdfzddqyss",
		"question":"\u5355\u573A\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u591A\u7684\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21836
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F2\u6E86\u4E3D\u73E0\u5149",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbywsdhsjxy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u738B\u5E08\u6E21\u6C49\u6C34\u7ECF\u8944\u9633\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21837
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1F\u7FBD\u8FDC\u4ECE\u620E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzljksncx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u7ED3\u5BA2\u5C11\u5E74\u573A\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21838
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F27\u5708\u7403",
		"indexes":"xlnyxbszqsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u8DB3\u7403\u672F\u8BED?",
		"id":21839
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u5171\u6653\u5149\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxjss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u897F\u4EAC\u5B88\u5C81\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21840
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5C45\u4E91\u4F5C\u7F28",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycglycsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u59DA\u5D07\u300A\u6545\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21841
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDC\u6170\u98CE\u96E8\u5915",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjlgysszs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u611F\u9047\u56DB\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21842
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E64\u8BED\u8BB0\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"csxblgyzyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5E78\u767D\u9E7F\u89C2\u5E94\u5236\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21843
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E23\u7B33\u51FA\u671B\u82D1",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyfhcccyyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5949\u548C\u521D\u6625\u51FA\u6E38\u5E94\u4EE4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21844
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u4F5C\u969C\u6CE5\u534A\u4F5C\u5E06",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsysg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u968B\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21845
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DA9\u8DEF\u62E5\u5D29\u67E5",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwwqtj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u665A\u61A9\u7530\u5BB6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21846
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C81\u65F6\u4F0F\u814A\u8D70\u6751\u7FC1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E94\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21847
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6F6E\u5E26\u96E8\u665A\u6765\u6025",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwywczxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u300A\u6EC1\u5DDE\u897F\u6DA7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21848
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u796D\u6C7E\u9634\u4E50\u7AE0",
		"indexes":"wwstcymdsrxlnbbswwdzp",
		"question":"\u738B\u7EF4\u662F\u5510\u671D\u6709\u540D\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21849
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u6B66\u5927\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbshcddjjjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5927\u5C06\u519B\u519B\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":21850
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5915\u51C9\u98CE\u81F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwgxjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u8FC7\u9999\u79EF\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21851
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u9762\u5E76\u5982\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczgjsyyxxyt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9AD8\u747E\u300A\u4E0A\u5143\u591C\u6548\u5C0F\u5EBE\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21852
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u6EF4\u94DC\u9F99\u663C\u6F0F\u957F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscsqqgycbqqzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u6C88\u5168\u671F\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u5448\u8865\u9619\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21853
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u56DB",
		"indexes":"qcdwyhywlcdwybyyesflhdddjqwqcdwyfljgdj",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u548C\u4EE5\u5F80\u5386\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u4E0D\u4E00\u6837\uFF0C\u800C\u662F\u5206\u4E86\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u738B\u7237\u5206\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u7B49\u7EA7\uFF1F",
		"id":21854
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70DF\u82B1\u8DF3\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlnxbstsyddzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u8DF3\u6C34\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u79CD\u7C7B\uFF1F",
		"id":21855
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u964C\u8F69\u8F66\u522B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsslqwlzsdfdc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u9001\u6881\u537F\u738B\u90CE\u4E2D\u4F7F\u4E1C\u8543\u540A\u518C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21856
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u603B\u6301\u5BFA\u9601",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsmhrdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21857
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5D29\u4E91\u6D12\u82B3\u7252",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbcrylyyfydjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6625\u65E5\u5BB4\u4E50\u6E38\u56ED\u8D4B\u97F5\u5F97\u63A5\u5B57\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21858
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56E0\u98CE\u60F3\u7389\u73C2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhryzzdxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u4E0E\u8BF8\u5B50\u767B\u5C98\u5C71\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21859
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D2A\u5408\u9C7C\u9F99\u6784\u5F3A\u540D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlybqtssb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u75C5\u8D77\u9898\u5C71\u820D\u58C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21860
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CF0\u683C\u00B7\u4F0D\u5179",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsslkzmxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u65AF\u6D1B\u514B\u8457\u540D\u9009\u624B\uFF1F",
		"id":21861
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u6B21",
		"indexes":"tcyalbrjdsygjcjf",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u4E0E\u963F\u62C9\u4F2F\u4EBA\uFF08\u5373\u5927\u98DF\uFF09\u6709\u8FC7\u51E0\u6B21\u4EA4\u950B\uFF1F",
		"id":21862
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"sjsdycsyzbhyxxyszwgngcd",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4F7F\u7528\u7EB8\u5E01\u548C\u94F6\u884C\u4FE1\u7528\u662F\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":21863
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sgsqdzygzdddqwwglssdddzdyync",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5468\u745C\u5B98\u81F3\u5927\u90FD\u7763\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u90FD\u7763\u5236\u5EA6\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":21864
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9488\u7EBF\u72B9\u5B58\u672A\u5FCD\u5F00",
		"indexes":"yzqbhsszsmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E09\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21865
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u4E01",
		"indexes":"sdmjfhsxlnwsdjwdqz",
		"question":"\u5546\u4EE3\u540D\u5C06\u5987\u597D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5546\u4EE3\u541B\u738B\u7684\u59BB\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21866
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96CD\u5E03\u62C9\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"xlngbszglssdhg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7687\u5BAB\uFF1F",
		"id":21867
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5B97",
		"indexes":"lssnwhdbtfbdlkza",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u88AB\u5410\u8543\u903C\u5F97\u79BB\u5F00\u957F\u5B89\uFF1F",
		"id":21868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80FD\u58F0\u5BC4\u4FAF\u4F2F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczstjyzlsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u996F\u90E2\u5DDE\u674E\u4F7F\u541B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6577\u8BDA\u5F52\u4E0A\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlzlrds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u8D60\u674E\u8363\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u62F3",
		"indexes":"xlnxbswstlydddz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6B66\u672F\u5957\u8DEF\u8FD0\u52A8\u7684\u52A8\u4F5C?",
		"id":21871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FA1\u53F2\u5927\u592B",
		"indexes":"xlnggzbsyqcdjqzl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B98\u804C\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u79E6\u671D\u7684\u4E5D\u537F\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21872
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u697C\u901A\u591C\u655E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczywqfhcrct",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u4E07\u9877\u300A\u5949\u548C\u6625\u65E5\u6C60\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21873
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BA2\u5FC3\u60B2\u66AE\u5E8F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyychg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u90E2\u57CE\u6000\u53E4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83B2\u8863\u627F\u7389\u948F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczycycln",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u960E\u671D\u9690\u300A\u91C7\u83B2\u5973\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FD7\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"zgdygtjsjgjss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u7530\u5F84\u4E16\u754C\u51A0\u519B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u592B\u56DB\u547D",
		"indexes":"qdffwjmxlnxbsyjmds",
		"question":"\u537F\u5927\u592B\u5206\u4E3A\u201C\u4E5D\u547D\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u547D\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u591C\u519B\u884C\u6208\u76F8\u62E8",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczyjsyhszgbx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5143\u7ED3\u300A\u77F3\u9C7C\u6E56\u4E0A\u9189\u6B4C\u5E76\u5E8F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5CE1\u661F\u6CB3\u5F71\u52A8\u6447",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21879
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEE\u9634\u4FAF\u97E9\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyxhsbh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u897F\u6C49\u5341\u516B\u4FAF\uFF1F",
		"id":21880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"xlnggjmyhdgozbgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404\u7259",
		"indexes":"xlnggjmyhdgozbgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":21882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u7591\u4F5C\u8D4B\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlxrqt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u76F8\u5982\u7434\u53F0\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u5F71\u6247\u4E2D\u65B0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyxzpxcmylxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u620F\u8D60\u6F58\u5F90\u57CE\u95E8\u8FCE\u4E24\u65B0\u5987\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u5B55\u5B9D\u7B26",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwxrydzzgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u5FB7\u5DDE\u8D60\u9AD8\u56DB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21885
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6628\u591C\u88D9\u5E26\u89E3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqdyytt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6743\u5FB7\u8206\u300A\u7389\u53F0\u4F53\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21886
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u98D8\u7D20\u5F71\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyhkwtzwyyh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u548C\u5EB7\u4E94\u5EAD\u829D\u671B\u6708\u6709\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21887
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u68B5\u524D\u5C71\u7A7A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwsyms",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u5BBF\u4E91\u95E8\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"yzdygsbayhdcssng",
		"question":"\u4E9A\u6D32\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u7533\u529E\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u7684\u57CE\u5E02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":21889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EFF\u7AF9\u7F18\u6EAA\u6DA7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwzxyztzhsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u81EA\u6E58\u6E90\u81F3\u6F6D\u5DDE\u8861\u5C71\u53BF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A00\u5E08\u91C7\u836F\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjdxyzby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3E\u5C9B\u300A\u5BFB\u9690\u8005\u4E0D\u9047\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E25\u756F",
		"indexes":"xlsbszlqxzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u7AF9\u6797\u4E03\u8D24\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u77F6\u897F\u7554\u95EE\u6E14\u8239",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzxthx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u65ED\u300A\u6843\u82B1\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B64\u821F\u4E8B\u6CBF\u8D8A",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsdssyykwdjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u7B54\u5B8B\u5341\u4E00\u5D16\u53E3\u4E94\u6E21\u89C1\u8D60\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u6B21\u4E50\u4E61\u53BF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczawclxx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u665A\u6B21\u4E50\u4E61\u53BF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC8\u662F\u5723\u660E\u5929\u5B50\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczztmwp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u90D1\u754B\u300A\u9A6C\u5D6C\u5761\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u4FE1\u82B3",
		"indexes":"zgessjysdmdhsxmdqwxlnwbsmdzy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E8C\u5341\u4E16\u7EAA\u6709\u201C\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u65E6\u201D\u548C\u201C\u56DB\u5C0F\u540D\u65E6\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u540D\u65E6\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u671D\u522B\u66AE\u8FD8\u89C1",
		"indexes":"lqtdddhjsjjynfjsmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u9880\u300A\u542C\u8463\u5927\u5F39\u80E1\u7B33\u58F0\u517C\u5BC4\u8BED\u5F04\u623F\u7ED9\u4E8B\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B63\u5B59\uFF08\u4F2F\u989C\uFF09",
		"indexes":"kzdxszzzmddssezxlbsysez",
		"question":"\u5B54\u5B50\u7684\u5B66\u751F\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u5F53\u5C5E\u5341\u4E8C\u54F2\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5341\u4E8C\u54F2\uFF1F",
		"id":21899
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6653\u53D1",
		"indexes":"xlnbbswcldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u768E\u768E\u6620\u5C42\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljqswyclqc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u79CB\u5C71\u671B\u6708\u916C\u674E\u9A91\u66F9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21901
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u659C\u62D4\u7389\u9497\u706F\u5F71\u7554",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzhznr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u795C\u300A\u8D60\u5185\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21902
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70E7\u5200\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnzjbsygdzgmj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u9152\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u540D\u9152\uFF1F",
		"id":21903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u60C5\u6076\u8870\u6B47",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczdfdwy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u7684\u300A\u671B\u5CB3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u754C\u8B66\u5BDF\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"xlngydhmjtrsxlrbsxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u8FD0\u52A8\u4F1A\u6CA1\u5C06\u94C1\u4EBA\u4E09\u9879\u5217\u5165\u6BD4\u8D5B\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":21905
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u5FC3\u5411\u6625\u5C3D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczbjyfdgycsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u300A\u8D4B\u5F97\u53E4\u539F\u8349\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21906
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592B\u5B50\u4F55\u4E3A\u8005",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwbsdsfzrsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u9001\u675C\u5C11\u5E9C\u4E4B\u4EFB\u8700\u5DDE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C79\u6251",
		"indexes":"xlngjdbszgsqdslwzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u519B\u961F\u4E0D\u662F\u8D1E\u89C2\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5341\u516D\u536B\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21908
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u7B20\u5E26\u659C\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzqslc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u9001\u7075\u6F88\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u65E5\u751F\u6B8B\u591C",
		"indexes":"lbdjmsbmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u6E21\u8346\u95E8\u9001\u522B\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EA5\u5FB7\u7FCA\u98DE\u9F99",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcygsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5143\u5149\u300A\u793A\u73E6\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648",
		"indexes":"zgqxbbkxlnggj",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":21912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u65E5\u82B1\u5F00\u53C8\u4E00\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnjbschhttxyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u540C\u9898\u4ED9\u6E38\u89C2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21913
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u540E\u7FBF",
		"indexes":"xlnwrwbsxcdhd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":21914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC7\u6E29\u6C64",
		"indexes":"ttzlsmclzgptxdbswhsygyxdsrxlnbbslsmdzp",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u9664\u4E86\u6CBB\u56FD\u5E73\u5929\u4E0B\u7684\u672C\u4E8B\u5916\uFF0C\u8FD8\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A\u4F18\u79C0\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21915
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F2\u8FBE\u7956",
		"indexes":"mxcsxlnwcrdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u6885\u6EAA\u8BCD\u300B\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21916
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u6597\u59CB\u5F00\u7B3C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqhsyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u5BD2\u98DF\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21917
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66AE\u96E8\u76F8\u547C\u5931",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwsjqm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u5C71\u5C45\u79CB\u669D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21918
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u793C\u81F4\u4E00\u7262\u7960",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszjkzjz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u7ECF\u5B54\u5B50\u65E7\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21919
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u644A\u4E01\u5165\u4EA9",
		"indexes":"xlnxzmdtdzcbsczqcyq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u8457\u540D\u7684\u571F\u5730\u653F\u7B56\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6E05\u671D\u4EE5\u524D\uFF1F",
		"id":21920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsyzgxzdewbsm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u201C\u6C38\u8D1E\u9769\u65B0\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E8C\u738B\u516B\u53F8\u9A6C\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":21921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u7B49\u5E42\u7B49\u79EF\u201D",
		"indexes":"bssqzkxfmdfzyzhhdcjxlnxsxcjbsfszscsq",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u65F6\u671F\u5728\u79D1\u5B66\u65B9\u9762\u7684\u53D1\u5C55\u6709\u7740\u8F89\u714C\u7684\u6210\u5C31\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u6570\u5B66\u6210\u5C31\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5B8B\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21922
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u897F\u5317\u6709\u9AD8\u697C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsycsfzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u66F9\u6C0F\u7236\u5B50\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5317\u9B4F\u5F8B\u8003\u300B",
		"indexes":"wmdjclkbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u300A\u4E5D\u671D\u5F8B\u8003\u300B\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":21924
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C5F\u8FB9\u522B\u300B",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbsydf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u675C\u752B\uFF1F",
		"id":21925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4ECE\u519B\u884C\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsylfjt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E50\u5E9C\u65E7\u9898\uFF1F",
		"id":21926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5415\u89C8\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C49\u8D4B\uFF1F",
		"id":21927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E0A\u6797\u8D4B\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlngbsyjawxdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5EFA\u5B89\u6587\u5B66\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6E58\u592B\u4EBA\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssjzdzj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u7AE0\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":21929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7B54\u5BA2\u96BE\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsxhzmdfjyxddbz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u6C49\u8457\u540D\u7684\u8D4B\u5BB6\u6768\u96C4\u7684\u4EE3\u8868\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":21930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyxss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53D9\u4E8B\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u5FD7\u5E73\u8BDD\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsmqdzhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u660E\u6E05\u7684\u7AE0\u56DE\u5C0F\u8BF4\uFF1F",
		"id":21932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u897F\u585E\u5C71\u6000\u53E4\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqyjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E03\u8A00\u7EDD\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":21933
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6C34\u7ECF\u6CE8\u300B",
		"indexes":"zyzjsjdcyqzycwdcxlnxbsydczl",
		"question":"\u300A\u5468\u6613\u300B\u4E2D\u89E3\u91CA\u7ECF\u7684\u4F20\u6709\u4E03\u79CD\uFF0C\u4E5F\u79F0\u4E3A\u5927\u4F20\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u4F20\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":21934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u964C\u4E0A\u6851\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsytys",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7530\u56ED\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":21935
	},
	{
		"answer":"305",
		"indexes":"sjycwssbnmsjsldsggydsp",
		"question":"\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u53C8\u79F0\u4E3A\u300A\u8BD7\u4E09\u767E\u300B\u90A3\u4E48\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B\u6536\u5F55\u7684\u8BD7\u6B4C\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u7BC7\uFF1F",
		"id":21936
	},
	{
		"answer":"789",
		"indexes":"jgdldxyzxtzgydstw",
		"question":"\u91D1\u56FD\u7684\u5F8B\u5178\u300A\u54B8\u96CD\u91CD\u4FEE\u6761\u5236\u300B\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6761\u6587\uFF1F",
		"id":21937
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u4E89\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8",
		"indexes":"cjgjhjghyclyglzzdjlbbbkxlng",
		"question":"\u53C2\u52A0\u5171\u6D4E\u4F1A\u9152\u9986\u4F1A\u8BAE\u6210\u7ACB\u82F1\u683C\u5170\u8DB3\u603B\u7684\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":21938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u5A46",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsxzhjlx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u897F\u85CF\u9EC4\u6559\u9886\u8896\uFF1F",
		"id":21939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngcsbsldgdzy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u662F\u516D\u5927\u53E4\u90FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":21940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1\u5E3D\u5B50\u738B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyqcwydch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6E05\u671D\u738B\u7237\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u69DB\u5916\u957F\u6C5F\u7A7A\u81EA\u6D41",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbtwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u6ED5\u738B\u9601\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AE1\u94B3\u4E3A\u53F0\u96B6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlysss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u548F\u53F2\u56DB\u9996\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80EF\u4E0B\u4E4B\u8FB1",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbsfszsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":21944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u914C\u996E\u56DB\u5EA7\u4EE5\u6563\u6101",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwlynex",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6D1B\u9633\u5973\u513F\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9752\u753B\u677E\u77F3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczszwczyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u521D\u81F3\u5D16\u53E3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E7\u7ECF\u5907\u9619\u6587",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsfyhtcz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9069\u300A\u6C7E\u9634\u540E\u571F\u7960\u4F5C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21947
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsytclygessgc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u671D\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u636E\u5C71\u6CB3\u636E\u5E73\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbjjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B65\u51FA\u4E1C\u658B\u8BFB",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwclssq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u671B\u4E0B\u7AE0\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczczadjmwc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u300A\u5EA6\u8346\u95E8\u671B\u695A\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u7AEF\u5AC1\u5F97\u91D1\u9F9F\u5A7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsywy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u4E3A\u6709\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u65E5\u6E38\u5FB7\u5DDE\u8D60\u9AD8\u56DB",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsczadzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u9648\u5B50\u6602\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF2\u4F3C\u957F\u6C99\u5085",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmhrlbwsyw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u7559\u522B\u738B\u4F8D\u5FA1\u7EF4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC7\u664B\u9633\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u6CBB\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u79E6\u59CB\u7687\u9675",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslsmdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E94\u591C\u89C2\u706F",
		"indexes":"xlnbbszjldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60C5\u6E2D\u65E5\u8FB9\u4E34",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszcqyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u6B21\u743C\u5CB3\u97F5\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95F2\u56ED\u5373\u4E8B\u5BC4\u97E6\u4F8D\u90CE",
		"indexes":"xlnbbslbwdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21959
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9675",
		"indexes":"xlnwshcrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlngdfsyhcsqdwhzd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E4C\u6052\u9A7B\u5730\uFF1F",
		"id":21961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EFA\u7B51\u5409\u7965",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzgbdjxwh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u516B\u5927\u5409\u7965\u6587\u5316\uFF1F",
		"id":21962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u987B\u81FE\u4E3A\u4E00\u6574\u5929",
		"indexes":"wcydzyhjysnmgysjdcwshs",
		"question":"\u6587\u5E38\u6709\u201C\u5F39\u6307\u4E00\u6325\u95F4\u201D\u4E00\u8BF4\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u5173\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u7684\u9519\u8BEF\u8BF4\u8BDD\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":21963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F88\u591A",
		"indexes":"yzbgygyjgr",
		"question":"\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\u4E00\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":21964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5411",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsqgsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u79E6\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6258\u5854\u5929\u738B\u674E\u9756",
		"indexes":"xlngbssgms",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0A\u53E4\u9B54\u795E\uFF1F",
		"id":21966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D4F\u4EAE\u5982\u7B19\u788E\u5728\u7F11",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlyqy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u715C\u300A\u79CB\u83BA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C64",
		"indexes":"xlngbsxcdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u671D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u534E\u65E9\u8457\u540D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbyjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u5BC4\u6768\u516C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u5BA1",
		"indexes":"mzsczszydmpsrzdjcdbxlsbsymzscz",
		"question":"\u95FD\u4E2D\u5341\u624D\u5B50\u662F\u6307\u5143\u4EE3\u95FD\u6D3E\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E2D\u7684\u6770\u51FA\u4EE3\u8868\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u95FD\u4E2D\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":21970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u84DF\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbsdfd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u675C\u752B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u59BE\u65AD\u80A0\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczydfdmlb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u675C\u752B\u7684\u300A\u68A6\u674E\u767D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u66AE\u4E61\u5173\u4F55\u5904\u662F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclqswwzj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u9001\u9B4F\u4E07\u4E4B\u4EAC\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u6211\u72EC\u6C89\u4E45",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5B64\u96C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6E38\u66F2\u4E8C\u9996",
		"indexes":"xmnbzpbslzyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u53F2\u90A3\u601D\u6469",
		"indexes":"xlnwstcsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":21976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6148\u6EAA\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglsshnsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6CB3\u5357\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":21977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5E1D\u6218\u86A9\u5C24",
		"indexes":"xlbsysgsh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u53E4\u795E\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":21978
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5DDE\u4E91\u9F99\u5C71\u5E99\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"wljnsgmjyhdsgmshdxlnghdbssgmshd",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4E86\u7EAA\u5FF5\u4E09\u56FD\uFF0C\u6C11\u95F4\u6709\u5F88\u591A\u4E09\u56FD\u6C11\u4FD7\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6D3B\u52A8\u4E0D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6C11\u4FD7\u6D3B\u52A8\uFF1F",
		"id":21979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF1\u6069\u96E8\u9732\u5782",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwcqzzss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u627F\u5E86\u300A\u76F4\u4E2D\u4E66\u7701\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90FD\u62A4\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"xlnggzbstcdwz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B98\u804C\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u7684\u6B66\u804C\uFF1F",
		"id":21981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u866C\u987B\u864E\u7709\u4ECD\u5927\u98A1",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqtawscblg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u542C\u5B89\u4E07\u5584\u5439\u7B5A\u7BE5\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91\u795E\u67AA",
		"indexes":"xlnxdysgsqdsmscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5BF9\u4E8E\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u201C\u795E\u201D\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":21983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u5188",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyhdgozbjsjdzjssdch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u6700\u4F73\u5C04\u624B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u5188",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyhdgozbjsjdzjssdch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u6700\u4F73\u5C04\u624B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":21985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u85CF\u9738",
		"indexes":"xlnwbshgwdsfytesbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u5149\u6B66\u5E1D\u6240\u5C01\u4E91\u53F0\u4E8C\u5341\u516B\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":21986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u4E91\u65E0\u5C3D\u65F6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdxsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u897F\u65BD\u548F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u864E\u8425",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyfkjsbyss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5CB3\u98DE\u6297\u91D1\u5341\u516B\u8425\u6240\u5C5E\uFF1F",
		"id":21988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5915\u9633\u65E0\u9650\u597D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlsydlyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u767B\u4E50\u6E38\u539F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D60\u738B\u516B\u8862",
		"indexes":"xlnbbsdfdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u675C\u752B\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":21990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u590F",
		"indexes":"xlngzqbsyhbsbcdgjzq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u653F\u6743\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u548C\u5317\u5B8B\u5E76\u5B58\u7684\u5272\u636E\u653F\u6743\uFF1F",
		"id":21991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341",
		"indexes":"hjjswgzzdybcjhjjgyjb",
		"question":"\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u8BCD\u96C6\uFF0C\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u90E8\uFF1F",
		"id":21992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u5386",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxldbc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u590F\u5386\u7684\u522B\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":21993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67B8\u675E",
		"indexes":"swccsjnjzclacz",
		"question":"\u6240\u8C13\u201C\u5403\u8336\u201D\u662F\u5C06\u54EA\u51E0\u79CD\u6750\u6599\u71AC\u6210\u7CA5\uFF1F",
		"id":21994
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u5C3A\u9F99\u987B\u65B9\u9526\u8925",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhhyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u5DF2\u51C9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u7EB3\u5C14\u591A",
		"indexes":"sjbjqzdqyss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u8FDB\u7403\u6700\u591A\u7403\u5458\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":21996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DE1\u626B\u8346\u95E8\u70DF",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwcldbsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u705E\u4E0A\u95F2\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21997
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6263\u6740",
		"indexes":"xlnxjsbsysqydybbdzxjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u6280\u672F\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u7403\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u5FC5\u5907\u7684\u4E13\u9879\u6280\u672F\uFF1F",
		"id":21998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u8FDC\u5FA1\u6148\u7559",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcsfhsjcgzsxfyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u5949\u548C\u9001\u91D1\u57CE\u516C\u4E3B\u9002\u897F\u8543\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":21999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u8D24",
		"indexes":"tcddwzybsdsyscgfqwxlnwtcdhdbssr",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u7684\u5E1D\u738B\u4E2D\u6709\u4E0D\u5C11\u90FD\u5584\u4E8E\u8BD7\u8BCD\u6B4C\u8D4B\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5510\u671D\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u4E0D\u662F\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":22000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE\u53F7\u9189\u4ED9",
		"indexes":"xlgygdsrdbhbscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u53E4\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u522B\u53F7\u8868\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":22001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FEF\u542C\u95FB\u60CA\u98CE",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwywdjqjszds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u97E6\u5E94\u7269\u7684\u300A\u5BC4\u5168\u6912\u5C71\u4E2D\u9053\u58EB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22002
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5C45\u79CB\u669D",
		"indexes":"xlnbzpbslsyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1\u4E0D\u662F\u674E\u5546\u9690\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u8F89\u7389\u81C2\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczwwwcxjzpxcd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u8F8B\u5DDD\u95F2\u5C45\u8D60\u88F4\u79C0\u624D\u8FEA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u539F\u738B\u6FEC",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsnbcdcmsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5317\u671D\u7684\u51FA\u540D\u4E16\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":22005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u5200\u4E07\u5250",
		"indexes":"mqsdkxbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u6EE1\u6E05\u5341\u5927\u9177\u5211\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u662D",
		"indexes":"xlnwbswjnbcsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u9B4F\u664B\u5357\u5317\u671D\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":22007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u4E18\u660E",
		"indexes":"ccsllyqywsjwsrdzpxlnwsrdzpwslzccz",
		"question":"\u300A\u695A\u8F9E\u300B\u6536\u5F55\u4E86\u4EE5\u5C48\u539F\u4E3A\u9996\u51E0\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\u672A\u6536\u5F55\u5728\u300A\u695A\u8F9E\u300B\u4E2D\uFF1F",
		"id":22008
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90B9\u5143\u6807",
		"indexes":"mcwqddldsyjnsdfwzdzzjtqzzzmddsdlbczxlnwsydlbcz",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u665A\u671F\u7684\u4E1C\u6797\u515A\u662F\u4EE5\u6C5F\u5357\u58EB\u5927\u592B\u4E3A\u4E3B\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u96C6\u56E2\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u8457\u540D\u7684\u5F53\u5C5E\u201C\u4E1C\u6797\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E1C\u6797\u516B\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":22009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u9634\u9001\u665A\u96F7",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsyxrgzqsz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u590F\u65E5\u8FC7\u90D1\u4E03\u5C71\u658B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE",
		"indexes":"xlnwcrsyhfpcr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8C6A\u653E\u6D3E\u8BCD\u4EBA\uFF1F",
		"id":22011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u6D32\u62E5\u5915\u6DA8",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwzjnzswzw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u5728\u6C5F\u5357\u8D60\u5B8B\u4E94\u4E4B\u95EE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03\u5B57\u5949\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlgysgrwxmbzcwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\u59D3\u540D\u8868\u5B57\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22013
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u91CC\u6D6E\u4E91\u9634\u4E14\u6674",
		"indexes":"mhryglmsgmyxlnj",
		"question":"\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u300A\u591C\u5F52\u9E7F\u95E8\u5C71\u6B4C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":22014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6851\u5170",
		"indexes":"xlnxydydmzbgjtclhhylmmjsdz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u88AB\u56FD\u9645\u4F53\u64CD\u8054\u5408\u4F1A\u7528\u6765\u547D\u540D\u6280\u672F\u52A8\u4F5C\uFF1F",
		"id":22015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE0\u534E\u5373\u65E7\u53F0",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsydxyc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u767B\u8944\u9633\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5965\u65AF\u5361\u00B7\u7F57\u4F2F\u900A",
		"indexes":"NBAdfzddhwss",
		"question":"NBA\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u591A\u7684\u540E\u536B\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":22017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u4E34\u51FA\u4E16\u754C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsbsczwwdswclyj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u7684\u300A\u5BBF\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u9690\u5C45\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u660C\u9F84\u300A\u585E\u4E0A\u66F2\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswygs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u53E4\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":22019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9880\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnssbswylf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u8A00\u4E50\u5E9C\uFF1F",
		"id":22020
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbszglssdfsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u9644\u5C5E\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":22021
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5B59\u5F52\u4E0D\u5F52",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwsb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u9001\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22022
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EF6\u9996\u665E\u4E91\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczrxghlgqx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4EFB\u5E0C\u53E4\u300A\u548C\u674E\u516C\u4E03\u5915\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22023
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D1\u5323\u5148\u6765\u745E\u6709\u865E",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhszlcp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u9F99\u6C60\u7BC7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22024
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B65\u6B65\u6625\u82B3\u7EFF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxycs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5E0C\u5937\u300A\u91C7\u6851\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22025
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E7\u597D\u9694\u826F\u7F18",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczctgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6D82\u300A\u5B64\u96C1\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u557C\u65F6\u60CA\u59BE\u68A6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczjcxcy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u91D1\u660C\u7EEA\u300A\u6625\u6028\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECE\u58C1\u4E0A\u89C2",
		"indexes":"xlngcybsczcqb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u9648\u60C5\u8868\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22028
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CE\u8001\u4E0E\u4EBA\u4E89\u5E2D\u7F62",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscwwcgjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u916C\u90ED\u7ED9\u4E8B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22029
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ECA\u4EBA\u591A\u4E0D\u5F39",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzqdq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u5F39\u7434\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B32\u628A\u4E00\u9EBE\u6C5F\u6D77\u53BB",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdmjfwxdlyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u7267\u300A\u5C06\u8D74\u5434\u5174\u767B\u4E50\u6E38\u539F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u5FF5\u5C71\u4E2D\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjldhkwlspbq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u300A\u6E56\u53E3\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03\u6CC9\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u98DF",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbsgdzgdmz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u540D\u65CF\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u6C11\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":22033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u8C0B\u6881\u56FD\u73CD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsysyalgzmysyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u5C81\u591C\u5B89\u4E50\u516C\u4E3B\u6EE1\u6708\u4F8D\u5BB4\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9AA8\u76F8\u6491\u59D4",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwjbszc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u65E0\u7ADE\u300A\u5317\u4F7F\u957F\u57CE\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7531\u6765\u5F81\u6218\u5730",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CA7\u6D77\u6708\u660E\u73E0\u6709\u6CEA",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsywt",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u65E0\u9898\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FA1\u6797\u519B",
		"indexes":"gzjswtyqbzwgcswcycjjycjjfwwgxtxlnxbsyycjjd",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u7956\u5C06\u4E09\u4E07\u592A\u539F\u4EB2\u5175\u4F5C\u4E3A\u5BAB\u57CE\u5BBF\u536B\uFF0C\u79F0\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u3002\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u5206\u4E3A\u4E94\u4E2A\u7CFB\u7EDF\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5143\u4ECE\u7981\u519B\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F7F\u81E3\u5C06\u738B\u547D",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczqwqdcfryx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u7DA6\u6BCB\u6F5C\u7684\u300A\u6625\u6CDB\u82E5\u8036\u6EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22039
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79BB\u79BB\u65E9\u9E3F\u5EA6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbywdjj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767E\u836F\u300A\u665A\u6E21\u6C5F\u6D25\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22040
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65CB\u8F6C",
		"indexes":"xlnxdzbshbddznr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u52A8\u4F5C\u4E0D\u662F\u6ED1\u677F\u7684\u52A8\u4F5C\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":22041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DEB",
		"indexes":"fjzszrsdjpbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u6559\u4E2D\u6240\u6307\u4EBA\u751F\u7684\u4E5D\u54C1\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u5B66",
		"indexes":"gddetjyhtzkdfzcsjdyxdjzjxlxzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u5BF9\u513F\u7AE5\u6559\u80B2\u548C\u7AE5\u5B50\u79D1\u7684\u53D1\u5C55\u4EA7\u751F\u8F83\u5927\u5F71\u54CD\u7684\u51E0\u79CD\u6559\u5B66\u7C7B\u578B\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22043
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FE5\u773A\u7A77\u539F\u6CFD",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczljfjzfjcgtzkh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u5CE4\u300A\u5949\u6559\u8FFD\u8D74\u4E5D\u6210\u5BAB\u9014\u4E2D\u53E3\u53F7\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22044
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97",
		"indexes":"gdyhddwxfdjqwxlnwhdxd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u6709\u5F88\u591A\u5E1D\u738B\u4FE1\u5949\u9053\u6559\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u4FE1\u9053\uFF1F",
		"id":22045
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97F6\u5973\u5CF0",
		"indexes":"slszgwdgdlzysdzyjysxlngdmbsjysfjdjd",
		"question":"\u821C\u9675\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E94\u5927\u53E4\u5E1D\u9675\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF0C\u821C\u5E1D\u846C\u4E8E\u4E5D\u5DB7\u5C71\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u540D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E5D\u5DB7\u5C71\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u666F\u70B9\uFF1F",
		"id":22046
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u5357\u9022\u674E\u9F9F\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnbbstczjldzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u90E8\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u671D\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":22047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"dsczlyxbjddjgdfqzbbkxlnx",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E1D\u7EF8\u4E4B\u8DEF\u5F71\u54CD\u6BD4\u8F83\u5927\u7684\u51E0\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u5176\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22048
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9971\u537F",
		"indexes":"qwxlngbsyscdzzjgzdjszy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u653F\u6CBB\u673A\u6784\u4E2D\u7684\u4E5D\u5BFA\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":22049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u9732\u5BFA",
		"indexes":"xlngbmbsytcdzyswjgjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u90E8\u95E8\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5510\u671D\u7684\u4E2D\u592E\u4E8B\u52A1\u673A\u5173\u4E5D\u5BFA\uFF1F",
		"id":22050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u513F\u7AE5\u76F8\u89C1\u4E0D\u76F8\u8BC6",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczhzzhxos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u8D3A\u77E5\u7AE0\u300A\u56DE\u4E61\u5076\u4E66\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F6\u9732\u6E7F\u7F57\u8966",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczqzzxsfgf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E54\u77E5\u4E4B\u300A\u4E0B\u5C71\u9022\u6545\u592B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22052
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9690\u9690\u9999\u53F0\u591C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlzlsjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5362\u7167\u90BB\u300A\u77F3\u955C\u5BFA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u5F71\u65E0\u5982\u767D\u53D1\u4F55",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclzqzsgjyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5218\u957F\u537F\u300A\u957F\u6C99\u8FC7\u8D3E\u8C0A\u5B85\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672A\u8C19\u59D1\u98DF\u6027",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwjxjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u5EFA\u300A\u65B0\u5AC1\u5A18\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u53F3",
		"indexes":"xlnwzghlybx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u505A\u8FC7\u7FF0\u6797\u9662\u7F16\u4FEE\uFF1F",
		"id":22056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u6E38",
		"indexes":"fwsxlsdwh",
		"question":"\u201C\u653E\u7FC1\u201D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u7684\u665A\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":22057
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u91CD\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlnwsybsyjysqdbqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u91D1\u5143\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u201C\u5317\u4E03\u771F\uFF1F",
		"id":22058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EF2\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsscdgw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5546\u671D\u7684\u56FD\u738B\uFF1F",
		"id":22059
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A2A\u626B\u516D\u5408",
		"indexes":"xlbsyzgsqdsssnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u53F2\u4E8B\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6742\u66F2\u6B4C\u8BCD",
		"indexes":"xlnzstbsyqts",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u8BD7\u4F53\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5168\u5510\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":22061
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u4E0B\u98DE\u5929\u955C",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6708\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u6D77\u87FE",
		"indexes":"xlnwsybsyjysqdnqz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u91D1\u5143\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u201C\u5357\u4E03\u771F\uFF1F",
		"id":22063
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5C09",
		"indexes":"hcsxsgjqzxlnxbsyjq",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u5B9E\u884C\u4E09\u516C\u4E5D\u537F\u5236\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u537F\uFF1F",
		"id":22064
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5343\u592A\u4E59\u519B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczyjcs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u6768\u70AF\u300A\u51FA\u585E\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u62D2\u590D\u897F\u654C",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcssyx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u6E5C\u300A\u585E\u57A3\u884C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u597D\u7A7A\u6240\u60DC",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczsthdzbcryss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u82CF\u988B\u300A\u548C\u675C\u4E3B\u7C3F\u6625\u65E5\u6709\u6240\u601D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8776\u604B\u82B1\uFF08\u82B1\u892A\u6B8B\u7EA2\u9752\u674F\u5C0F\uFF09",
		"indexes":"xlnscbsscncrlqzdzp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9996\u8BCD\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u5973\u8BCD\u4EBA\u674E\u6E05\u7167\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":22068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EC8\u5357\u9634\u5CAD\u79C0",
		"indexes":"zyznwyxyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u7956\u548F\u300A\u7EC8\u5357\u671B\u9980\u96EA\u300B\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":22069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA1\u7F8A\u8865\u7262",
		"indexes":"xlngcybsczyxybj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u300A\u9879\u7FBD\u672C\u7EAA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u5356\u81EA\u5938",
		"indexes":"xlnjxhyhsgwg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\u548C\u4E09\u56FD\u65E0\u5173\uFF1F",
		"id":22071
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5343\u9A91",
		"indexes":"tzdjjzbyqyyfwqbxlnxbsybyqyzl",
		"question":"\u592A\u5B97\u7684\u7981\u519B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5317\u8859\u4E03\u8425\u53C8\u5206\u4E3A\u4E03\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u8859\u4E03\u8425\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":22072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u6572\u521D\u591C\u78EC",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczzjmfgr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u7C4D\u300A\u6CA1\u8543\u6545\u4EBA\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u5B66\u6E38\u4FA0\u513F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczmjlnc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B5F\u90CA\u300A\u70C8\u5973\u64CD\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5CE1\u697C\u53F0\u6DF9\u65E5\u6708",
		"indexes":"dfyhgjwszemyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E8C\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":22075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C18\u8D77\u6D1B\u9633\u98CE",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwqrjldscwl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u79CB\u65E5\u996F\u9646\u9053\u58EB\u9648\u6587\u6797\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u5927\u4EFB",
		"indexes":"qjqnjdbwczbsrcwjqbczxlsbsbczzl",
		"question":"\u6E05\u5609\u5E86\u5E74\u95F4\u7684\u516B\u4F4D\u624D\u5B50\u88AB\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5609\u5E86\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u516B\u624D\u5B50\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":22077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6CC9\u6EE1\u6E05\u542C",
		"indexes":"lzydcycsydsjmyxlnyj",
		"question":"\u67F3\u5B97\u5143\u7684\u300A\u6668\u8BE3\u8D85\u5E08\u9662\u8BFB\u7985\u7ECF\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\uFF1F",
		"id":22078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u7FFB\u5317\u6F6D\u5F71",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwbstyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u52C3\u300A\u5C71\u4EAD\u591C\u5BB4\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u4FC4\u5C3C\u5E03\u695A\u6761\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"xlngtysqcdyzhqddty",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6761\u7EA6\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u6253\u8D62\u4ED7\u540E\u7B7E\u8BA2\u7684\u6761\u7EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":22080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B1B",
		"indexes":"ygsqdlqzmyxlnx",
		"question":"\u8FDC\u53E4\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E50\u5668\u4E2D\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u5BA2",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyhsdjl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u540E\u4E16\u7684\u9152\u793C\uFF1F",
		"id":22082
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F30\u5BA2\u663C\u7720\u77E5\u6D6A\u9759",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscyzqbhsszy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u5143\u7A39\u300A\u9063\u60B2\u6000\u4E09\u9996\u4E4B\u4E00\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":22083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u7ACB",
		"indexes":"lssddyfzqsfmdwljsclclzqsserjsslddmdywzqzbbkxlnxwz",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFD\u8DB3\u7403\u201C\u9996\u53D1\u540D\u5355\u201D\u300A\u6B66\u6797\u65E7\u4E8B\u300B\u66FE\u5217\u51FA\u4E86\u201C\u7B51\u7403\u4E09\u5341\u4E8C\u4EBA\u201D\u7ADE\u8D5B\u65F6\u4E24\u961F\u7684\u540D\u5355\u4E0E\u4F4D\u7F6E,\u5176\u4E2D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4F4D\u7F6E?",
		"id":22084
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"cccjfswhsth",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u66FE\u7ECF\u5C01\u8C01\u4E3A\u6C49\u5BFF\u4EAD\u5019?",
		"id":22085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"sgzbywbjjdbwjjssdsx",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u201C\u516B\u5065\u5C06\u201D\u7684\u516B\u4F4D\u5C06\u519B\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u624B\u4E0B\uFF1F",
		"id":22086
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u767B\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qwxlnczybsfszhcsq",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u573A\u6218\u5F79\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":22087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4E30\u7A91",
		"indexes":"xlngcswglssjxsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u624D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":22088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u53F2",
		"indexes":"essszpfzzdsnb",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u53F2\u4E2D\u7BC7\u5E45\u6700\u957F\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u90E8\uFF1F",
		"id":22089
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u53C9",
		"indexes":"xlngmzbsyzggdmz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u6C11\u65CF\uFF1F",
		"id":22090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u4E91\u793E",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssczmylzz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u671D\u8457\u540D\u5A31\u4E50\u7EC4\u7EC7\uFF1F",
		"id":22091
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8981\u585E3\u5EA7",
		"indexes":"xlgyhbqhdjnzcdtjznxscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u6CB3\u5317\u79E6\u7687\u5C9B\u5883\u5185\u957F\u57CE\u7684\u7EDF\u8BA1\u4E2D\u54EA\u9879\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u5510",
		"indexes":"xabsxlncdgd",
		"question":"\u897F\u5B89\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u671D\u7684\u53E4\u90FD\uFF1F",
		"id":22093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u7231\u73B2",
		"indexes":"xlnwbsjshsdmy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u65E7\u4E0A\u6D77\u5341\u5927\u540D\u5A9B\uFF1F",
		"id":22094
	},
	{
		"answer":"1994\u5E74\u7F8E\u56FD\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u4E3B\u9898\u66F2\uFF0D\uFF1A\u201C\u8F89\u714C\u4E4B\u5730\u201D",
		"indexes":"xlgyljsjbztqdmszqdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u5386\u5C4A\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u4E3B\u9898\u66F2\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22095
	},
	{
		"answer":"1000\u7C73\u957F\u8DD1",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxdtyzdqxqnzdxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u73B0\u4EE3\u4F53\u80B2\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E03\u9879\u5168\u80FD\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":22096
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5F77\u5FA8\u300B\u6536\u51651925\u5E74\u7684\u300A\u795D\u798F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnxgylxdmsscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u9C81\u8FC5\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22097
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u745F-\u5FB7\u9C81\u5229\u5FB7\u56FD1955-1961",
		"indexes":"xlgyljgjzlzxdmscwds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u5386\u5C4A\u56FD\u9645\u8DB3\u8054\u4E3B\u5E2D\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22098
	},
	{
		"answer":"1988\u5E74\u5728\u97E9\u56FD\u4E3E\u529E\u7684\u7B2C\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A",
		"indexes":"qjwzgmzddayhsnyj",
		"question":"\u8FC4\u4ECA\u4E3A\u6B62\u89C4\u6A21\u6700\u5927\u7684\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5C4A\uFF1F",
		"id":22099
	},
	{
		"answer":"1952\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wxhqdyczaycskggpysnyn",
		"question":"\u4E94\u661F\u7EA2\u65D7\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5728\u5965\u8FD0\u6751\u4E0A\u7A7A\u9AD8\u9AD8\u98D8\u626C\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":22100
	},
	{
		"answer":"1894",
		"indexes":"gjawhsnyncld",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22101
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"sjlddlsqyzlsssyjzddsqsx108hhssfsjjzsjdsxzydswhh",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u6C5F\u9886\u5BFC\u7684\u6881\u5C71\u8D77\u4E49\u5728\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u662F\u6709\u8BB0\u8F7D\u7684\uFF0C\u4F46\u662F\u5176\u624B\u4E0B108\u597D\u6C49\u6240\u8FF0\u975E\u5B9E\uFF0C\u636E\u8BB0\u8F7D\u5B8B\u6C5F\u7684\u624B\u4E0B\u53EA\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4F4D\u597D\u6C49\uFF1F",
		"id":22102
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5207\u5C14\u897F",
		"indexes":"1998nozgdlshmjlbwqzozlUEFAgyozgjlsggzytnzblsblsemmzklhyycmwG14dxzzdsxlngjlbbsG14cy",
		"question":"1998\u5E74\u6B27\u6D32\u5404\u5927\u8054\u8D5B\u8C6A\u95E8\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E3A\u7275\u5236\u6B27\u8DB3\u8054\uFF08UEFA\uFF09\u5173\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32\u51A0\u519B\u8054\u8D5B\u6539\u9769\u5236\uFF0C\u4E8E\u540C\u5E74\u5728\u6BD4\u5229\u65F6\u5E03\u9C81\u585E\u5C14\u79D8\u5BC6\u53EC\u5F00\u4E86\u4F1A\u8BAE\uFF01\u7531\u6B64\u540D\u4E3A\u300CG14\u300D\u7684\u65B0\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8BDE\u751F\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\u4E0D\u662FG14\u6210\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":22103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8212\u9A6C\u8D6B",
		"indexes":"hdzgjzddF1xsss",
		"question":"\u83B7\u5F97\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684F1\u9009\u624B\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22104
	},
	{
		"answer":"1957\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgzqjjlssynyn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u7532\u7EA7\u8054\u8D5B\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74?",
		"id":22105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsF1djszd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662FF1\u5927\u5956\u8D5B\u7AD9\u70B9?",
		"id":22106
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65A9",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssysqdzyhddflzdzdxf",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u5143\u65F6\u671F\u5BF9\u4E2D\u539F\u6C49\u5730\u7684\u6CD5\u5F8B\u5236\u5EA6\u4E2D\u7684\u5211\u7F5A\uFF1F",
		"id":22107
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5D\u9633\u738B",
		"indexes":"zgxjstzjtnbls16n291306zjdzlscbwzlxlnwbsybwzl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u897F\u664B\u65F6\u7EDF\u6CBB\u96C6\u56E2\u5185\u90E8\u5386\u65F616\u5E74\uFF08291\uFF5E306\uFF09\u4E4B\u4E45\u7684\u6218\u4E71\uFF0C\u53F2\u79F0\u201C\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":22108
	},
	{
		"answer":"186",
		"indexes":"NBAdcbsdfzgdsdsf",
		"question":"NBA\u5355\u573A\u6BD4\u8D5B\u5F97\u5206\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u662F\u591A\u5C11\u5206\uFF1F",
		"id":22109
	},
	{
		"answer":"1986\u58A8\u897F\u54E5",
		"indexes":"xlgydgsjmszqds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u593A\u51A0\u65F6\u95F4\u63CF\u8FF0\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":22110
	},
	{
		"answer":"1980\u5E74\u7B2C\u516B\u5C4A\u4E16\u754C\u9526\u6807\u8D5B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzgnpdwlgsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u5973\u6392\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u8FDE\u51A0\u201D\u6B8A\u8363\uFF1F",
		"id":22111
	},
	{
		"answer":"1980\u5E74\u7B2C\u516B\u5C4A\u4E16\u754C\u9526\u6807\u8D5B",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsyzgnpdwlgsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u5973\u6392\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u8FDE\u51A0\u201D\u6B8A\u8363\uFF1F",
		"id":22112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u970D\u5C14\u5C91\u8D1D",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyrx1974nsjbzjzr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u5165\u90091974\u5E74\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u6700\u4F73\u9635\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":22113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D2\u7FC5\u864E\u6731\u4EDD",
		"indexes":"xldsh108jdmscwdsnx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5BF9\u6C34\u6D52108\u5C06\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u9879\uFF1F",
		"id":22114
	},
	{
		"answer":"110\u7C73\u680F\u51A0\u519B\uFF08\u5218\u7FD4\uFF09",
		"indexes":"xlnxd27jayhsqddgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u7B2C27\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E0A\u53D6\u5F97\u7684\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":22115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"dlsczstdzdlnj10wsrsdbdygsglpxlnwbsydlscz",
		"question":"\u5927\u5386\u5341\u624D\u5B50\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u5B97\u5927\u5386\u5E74\u95F410\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u6240\u4EE3\u8868\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BD7\u6B4C\u6D41\u6D3E\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u5386\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":22116
	},
	{
		"answer":"1894",
		"indexes":"gjawhsnyncld",
		"question":"\u56FD\u9645\u5965\u59D4\u4F1A\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u6210\u7ACB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":22117
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"sjlddlsqyzlsssyjzddsqsx108hhssfsjjzsjdsxzydswhh",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u6C5F\u9886\u5BFC\u7684\u6881\u5C71\u8D77\u4E49\u5728\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u662F\u6709\u8BB0\u8F7D\u7684\uFF0C\u4F46\u662F\u5176\u624B\u4E0B108\u597D\u6C49\u6240\u8FF0\u975E\u5B9E\uFF0C\u636E\u8BB0\u8F7D\u5B8B\u6C5F\u7684\u624B\u4E0B\u53EA\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4F4D\u597D\u6C49\uFF1F",
		"id":22118
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5207\u5C14\u897F",
		"indexes":"1998nozgdlshmjlbwqzozlUEFAgyozgjlsggzytnzblsblsemmzklhyycmwG14dxzzdsxlngjlbbsG14cy",
		"question":"1998\u5E74\u6B27\u6D32\u5404\u5927\u8054\u8D5B\u8C6A\u95E8\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\uFF0C\u4E3A\u7275\u5236\u6B27\u8DB3\u8054\uFF08UEFA\uFF09\u5173\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32\u51A0\u519B\u8054\u8D5B\u6539\u9769\u5236\uFF0C\u4E8E\u540C\u5E74\u5728\u6BD4\u5229\u65F6\u5E03\u9C81\u585E\u5C14\u79D8\u5BC6\u53EC\u5F00\u4E86\u4F1A\u8BAE\uFF01\u7531\u6B64\u540D\u4E3A\u300CG14\u300D\u7684\u65B0\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8BDE\u751F\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4FF1\u4E50\u90E8\u4E0D\u662FG14\u6210\u5458\uFF1F",
		"id":22119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8212\u9A6C\u8D6B",
		"indexes":"hdzgjzddF1xsss",
		"question":"\u83B7\u5F97\u603B\u51A0\u519B\u6700\u591A\u7684F1\u9009\u624B\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22120
	},
	{
		"answer":"1957\u5E74",
		"indexes":"wgzqjjlssynyn",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u7532\u7EA7\u8054\u8D5B\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74?",
		"id":22121
	},
	{
		"answer":"1000\u7C73\u957F\u8DD1",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxdtyzdqxqnzdxm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u73B0\u4EE3\u4F53\u80B2\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E03\u9879\u5168\u80FD\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u9879\u76EE\uFF1F",
		"id":22122
	},
	{
		"answer":"1986\u58A8\u897F\u54E5",
		"indexes":"xlgydgsjmszqds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5173\u4E8E\u593A\u51A0\u65F6\u95F4\u63CF\u8FF0\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":22123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u970D\u5C14\u5C91\u8D1D",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyrx1974nsjbzjzr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u5165\u90091974\u5E74\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u6700\u4F73\u9635\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":22124
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u517B\u7531\u57FA\u5E9E\u4E07\u6625",
		"indexes":"xlnxbssh108j",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u6C34\u6D52108\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":22125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u7981\u533A\u957F18\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnxgyzqcdsjscwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u5173\u4E8E\u8DB3\u7403\u573A\u7684\u6570\u636E\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684?",
		"id":22126
	},
	{
		"answer":"110\u7C73\u680F\u51A0\u519B\uFF08\u5218\u7FD4\uFF09",
		"indexes":"xlnxd27jayhsqddgj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u7B2C27\u5C4A\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E0A\u53D6\u5F97\u7684\u51A0\u519B\uFF1F",
		"id":22127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"dlsczstdzdlnj10wsrsdbdygsglpxlnwbsydlscz",
		"question":"\u5927\u5386\u5341\u624D\u5B50\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u5B97\u5927\u5386\u5E74\u95F410\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u6240\u4EE3\u8868\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u8BD7\u6B4C\u6D41\u6D3E\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5927\u5386\u5341\u624D\u5B50\uFF1F",
		"id":22128
	},
	{
		"answer":"H",
		"indexes":"xlnygsqdhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6C22\u7684\u5316\u5B66\u5F0F?",
		"id":22129
	},
	{
		"answer":"P",
		"indexes":"xlnygsldhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u78F7\u7684\u5316\u5B66\u5F0F?",
		"id":22130
	},
	{
		"answer":"Ca",
		"indexes":"xlnygsgdhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u9499\u7684\u5316\u5B66\u5F0F?",
		"id":22131
	},
	{
		"answer":"Na",
		"indexes":"xlnygsndhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u94A0\u7684\u5316\u5B66\u5F0F?",
		"id":22132
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1",
		"indexes":"yxsyjsds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u91D1\u5C5E\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u94DC",
		"indexes":"yxsyjsds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u91D1\u5C5E\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FDD\u65F6\u6377",
		"indexes":"yxsyqcppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C7D\u8F66\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672C\u7530",
		"indexes":"yxsyqcppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C7D\u8F66\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22136
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u67EF\u8FBE",
		"indexes":"yxsyqcppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C7D\u8F66\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22137
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E30\u7530",
		"indexes":"yxsyqcppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C7D\u8F66\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22138
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F9\u679C",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22139
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u7C73",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BFA\u57FA\u4E9A",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u661F",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u6258\u7F57\u62C9",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9524\u5B50",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u597D",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54DF",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxhzsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22149
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6563",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22150
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0A",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70E6",
		"indexes":"yxhzsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5728",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D8",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9760",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22155
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F66",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22156
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F:",
		"id":22158
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u667A\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"xmsbssgyyzdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u6893\u5C90",
		"indexes":"xmsbssgyyzdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u8FC1",
		"indexes":"xmsbssgyyzdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8303\u5FD7\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"sszgddyccjsjbjsjddqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u7403\u5458",
		"id":22162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u660E\u5B87",
		"indexes":"sszgddyccjsjbjsjddqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u7403\u5458",
		"id":22163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90B5\u4F73\u4E00",
		"indexes":"sszgddyccjsjbjsjddqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u7403\u5458",
		"id":22164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90DD\u6D77\u4E1C",
		"indexes":"sszgddyccjsjbjsjddqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u7403\u5458",
		"id":22165
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E18\u6210\u6850",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u666F\u6DA6",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u6B65\u9752",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u7701\u8EAB",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22169
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6218\u56FD\u7B56",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u79CB",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C01\u795E\u699C",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u5BB6\u5C06",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u57FA\u7763\u5C71\u4F2F\u7235\u6069\u4EC7\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u59C6\u96F7\u7279",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5C14\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u514B\u767D",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269?",
		"id":22178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbsydecsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22179
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbsydecsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22180
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbsydecsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FB7\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjsydycsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22182
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5965\u65AF\u66FC\u571F\u8033\u5176\u5E1D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjsydycsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5965\u5308\u5E1D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjsydycsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbsydycsjdztmg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u540C\u76DF\u56FD?",
		"id":22185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62C9\u683C\u6717\u65E5",
		"indexes":"xlnygssxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22186
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u970D\u91D1",
		"indexes":"xlnygskxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94B1\u5B66\u68EE",
		"indexes":"xlnygskxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9093\u7A3C\u5148",
		"indexes":"xlnygskxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u514B\u65AF\u97E6",
		"indexes":"xlnygskxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u57FA\u7C73\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"xlnygssxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD5\u52A0\u7D22",
		"indexes":"xlnygshj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u5948",
		"indexes":"xlnygshj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u60B2\u9E3F",
		"indexes":"xlnygshj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u5BE8\u6C9F",
		"indexes":"xmnygjdbzbjsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u70B9\u4E0D\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u5E02\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xmnygjdbzbjsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u70B9\u4E0D\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u5E02\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xmnygcsbztwsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5728\u53F0\u6E7E\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xmnyzsztwsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u5C71\u5728\u53F0\u6E7E\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u7AF9",
		"indexes":"xmnygcsztwsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u53F0\u6E7E\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22199
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"xmnygcszjssjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u6C5F\u82CF\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FBD\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xmnygcsbzjssjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5728\u6C5F\u82CF\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u57D4\u6E2F",
		"indexes":"xmnyggkzgdsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6E2F\u53E3\u5728\u5E7F\u4E1C\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xmnygcszgdsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u5E7F\u4E1C\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u5E86",
		"indexes":"xmnygcszhljsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u9ED1\u9F99\u6C5F\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1\u5CAD",
		"indexes":"xmnygcsbzhljsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5728\u9ED1\u9F99\u6C5F\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u829D",
		"indexes":"xmnygcsbzxjwwezzqjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5728\u65B0\u7586\u7EF4\u543E\u5C14\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u78A3\u77F3",
		"indexes":"xmnygbsyxyggds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u897F\u57DF\u53E4\u56FD\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71D5\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykyfdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u98DE\u7684\u9E1F?",
		"id":22208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyscdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u98DF\u8349\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":22209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CB8\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"xlnygsybrdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":22210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732B",
		"indexes":"xlnygsybrdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":22211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u70B3",
		"indexes":"xlnygsylj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6?",
		"id":22212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC",
		"indexes":"xlnygsylj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6?",
		"id":22213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83AB\u624E\u7279",
		"indexes":"xlnygsylj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6?",
		"id":22214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65AF\u7279\u52B3\u65AF",
		"indexes":"xlnygsymdyljz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6709\u540D\u7684\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6\u65CF?",
		"id":22215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"xmnywstddsr",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u5927\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":22216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u6B65\u9752",
		"indexes":"xmnywbssddwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5B8B\u4EE3\u5927\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73\u82BE",
		"indexes":"xmnywbstsbdj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6?",
		"id":22218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167",
		"indexes":"xmnywbstddwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u5927\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5B88\u4EC1",
		"indexes":"xmnywbstddwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5510\u4EE3\u5927\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982",
		"indexes":"xmnywshdwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u96C4",
		"indexes":"xmnywshdwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"xmnywssgsqwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"xmnywssgsqwxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B59\u74D2",
		"indexes":"ymsjhxmnywwg",
		"question":"\u8F95\u95E8\u5C04\u621F\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"ccjjhxmnywwg",
		"question":"\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"szqrhxmnywwg",
		"question":"\u820C\u6218\u7FA4\u5112\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"sgmlhxmnywwg",
		"question":"\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"tysjyhxmnywwg",
		"question":"\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u548C\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E29\u5EA6\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"smdxtqyrtpdyg",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E1C\u897F\u5929\u6C14\u8D8A\u70ED,\u5B83\u722C\u7684\u8D8A\u9AD8?",
		"id":22230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u868A\u5B50",
		"indexes":"smdwndsltqllndx",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u52A8\u7269,\u4F60\u6253\u6B7B\u4E86\u5B83\u5374\u6D41\u4E86\u4F60\u7684\u8840?",
		"id":22231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u533B\u751F",
		"indexes":"sttqkb",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5929\u5929\u53BB\u770B\u75C5?",
		"id":22232
	},
	{
		"answer":"X\u5149\u7247",
		"indexes":"smzpkbczdss",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u7167\u7247\u770B\u4E0D\u51FA\u7167\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u6708",
		"indexes":"wlttztddbxktyygyshzssnygy",
		"question":"\u738B\u8001\u592A\u592A\u6574\u5929\u558B\u558B\u4E0D\u4F11,\u53EF\u5979\u6709\u4E00\u4E2A\u6708\u8BF4\u8BDD\u6700\u5C11,\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6708?",
		"id":22234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7011\u5E03",
		"indexes":"smbjbd",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E03\u526A\u4E0D\u65AD?",
		"id":22235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95E8\u662F\u63A8\u7684",
		"indexes":"xzbgzyjbmyssdfjlkstsccndlqybnbmlkzszmhs",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u5F20\u88AB\u5173\u5728\u4E00\u95F4\u5E76\u6CA1\u6709\u4E0A\u9501\u7684\u623F\u95F4\u91CC,\u53EF\u662F\u4ED6\u4F7F\u51FA\u5403\u5976\u7684\u529B\u6C14\u4E5F\u4E0D\u80FD\u628A\u95E8\u62C9\u5F00,\u8FD9\u662F\u600E\u4E48\u56DE\u4E8B?",
		"id":22236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA4\u767D\u5377",
		"indexes":"zyckszydtzjlymyydkjdlsrwtmkdmyzbzswsm",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E00\u6B21\u8003\u8BD5\u4E2D,\u4E00\u5BF9\u540C\u684C\u4EA4\u4E86\u4E00\u6A21\u4E00\u6837\u7684\u8003\u5377,\u4F46\u8001\u5E08\u8BA4\u4E3A\u4ED6\u4EEC\u80AF\u5B9A\u6CA1\u6709\u505A\u5F0A,\u8FD9\u662F\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E21\u86CB",
		"indexes":"jrhngddxssm",
		"question":"\u52A0\u70ED\u4F1A\u51DD\u56FA\u7684\u4E1C\u897F\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u517D\u533B\u9662",
		"indexes":"wsmyjyycbjrkb",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u5BB6\u533B\u9662\u4ECE\u4E0D\u7ED9\u4EBA\u770B\u75C5?",
		"id":22239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A5\u7EB8",
		"indexes":"zzyqyyxyqstytdcpssm",
		"question":"\u5236\u9020\u66F0\u671F\u4E0E\u6709\u6548\u66F0\u671F\u662F\u540C\u4E00\u5929\u7684\u4EA7\u54C1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934",
		"indexes":"yyzhxgdtnygbjt",
		"question":"\u7528\u6930\u5B50\u548C\u897F\u74DC\u6253\u5934\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6BD4\u8F83\u75DB?",
		"id":22241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5047\u7259",
		"indexes":"xwybsyybyxdczkstszmzdd",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u738B\u4E00\u8FB9\u5237\u7259,\u4E00\u8FB9\u60A0\u95F2\u7684\u5439\u7740\u53E3\u54E8,\u4ED6\u662F\u600E\u4E48\u505A\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":22242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F66\u4E0A\u6709\u7A7A\u4F4D",
		"indexes":"yywlttslgcwsmmrrz",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E00\u4F4D\u8001\u592A\u592A\u4E0A\u4E86\u516C\u8F66,\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6CA1\u4EBA\u8BA9\u5EA7?",
		"id":22243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C31\u662F\u6211",
		"indexes":"yygrtsnfmsddtqbsndxdjmtss",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EBA,\u4ED6\u662F\u4F60\u7236\u6BCD\u751F\u7684,\u4F46\u4ED6\u5374\u4E0D\u662F\u4F60\u7684\u5144\u5F1F\u59D0\u59B9,\u4ED6\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79D8\u4E66",
		"indexes":"sdmbddsssms",
		"question":"\u4E66\u5E97\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230\u7684\u4E66\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E66?",
		"id":22245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u5728\u7784\u51C6",
		"indexes":"xwsymyxsbyttzzgzqsmmkdydrqqxtmglwsmtqzyzybyzy",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u738B\u662F\u4E00\u540D\u4F18\u79C0\u58EB\u5175,\u4E00\u5929\u4ED6\u5728\u7AD9\u5C97\u503C\u52E4\u65F6,\u660E\u660E\u770B\u5230\u6709\u654C\u4EBA\u6084\u6084\u5411\u4ED6\u6478\u8FC7\u6765,\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u4ED6\u5374\u7741\u4E00\u53EA\u773C\u95ED\u4E00\u53EA\u773C?",
		"id":22246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7403\u95E8",
		"indexes":"smmyygbs",
		"question":"\u4EC0\u4E48\u95E8\u6C38\u8FDC\u5173\u4E0D\u4E0A?",
		"id":22247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u778C\u7761",
		"indexes":"dsmdxhbfl",
		"question":"\u6253\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E1C\u897F\u6BEB\u4E0D\u8D39\u529B?",
		"id":22248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DF9\u4E0D\u4E86",
		"indexes":"cbgzrtlhm2mhsmxsszbmjgxshsnymrt",
		"question":"\u8239\u8FB9\u6302\u7740\u8F6F\u68AF,\u79BB\u6D77\u97622\u7C73,\u6D77\u6C34\u6BCF\u5C0F\u65F6\u4E0A\u6DA8\u534A\u7C73,\u51E0\u4E2A\u5C0F\u65F6\u6D77\u6C34\u80FD\u6DF9\u6CA1\u8F6F\u68AF?",
		"id":22249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5411\u65E5\u8475",
		"indexes":"ykydhjkylmcyhm",
		"question":"\u8FDC\u770B\u4E00\u6735\u82B1,\u8FD1\u770B\u4E00\u8138\u9EBB(\u731C\u4E00\u82B1\u540D)",
		"id":22250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5706\u89C4",
		"indexes":"ygjhzxxyjdwbkyyjbtzqqcywj",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E2A\u5BB6\u4F19\u771F\u65B0\u9C9C,\u4E00\u811A\u5B9A\u4F4D\u4E0D\u80AF\u79FB,\u4E00\u811A\u4E0D\u505C\u8F6C\u5708\u5708(\u731C\u4E00\u6587\u5177)",
		"id":22251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F05\u7538",
		"indexes":"byddgjcygjm",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u7528\u7535\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6(\u731C\u4E00\u56FD\u5BB6\u540D)",
		"id":22252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B3C\u8BDD\u8FDE\u7BC7",
		"indexes":"ntmmzltcycy",
		"question":"\u725B\u5934\u9A6C\u9762\u5728\u804A\u5929(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672A",
		"indexes":"yzqtcyz",
		"question":"\u4E00\u67F1\u64CE\u5929(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8461\u8404",
		"indexes":"ycycgssxdzmzykyzyhzplcysg",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E32\u4E00\u4E32\u6302\u6811\u4E0A,\u5144\u5F1F\u59CA\u59B9\u4F4F\u4E00\u5757,\u6709\u7D2B\u6709\u7EA2\u771F\u6F02\u4EAE(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u679C)",
		"id":22255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u9053",
		"indexes":"hsdldcyyzxx",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u8272\u7684\u8DEF\u9053(\u731C\u4E00\u5B87\u5B99\u73B0\u8C61)",
		"id":22256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"kqspcyrm",
		"question":"\u5B54\u96C0\u6536\u5C4F(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u8D3C",
		"indexes":"wbbrxdlythclbtqystszcyszsw",
		"question":"\u5916\u8868\u767D\u5982\u96EA,\u809A\u91CC\u4E00\u56E2\u9ED1,\u4ECE\u6765\u4E0D\u5077\u7A83,\u786C\u8BF4\u4ED6\u662F\u8D3C(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u4E2D\u751F\u7269)",
		"id":22258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E39\u9EA6",
		"indexes":"zmlkbwscygjm",
		"question":"\u53EA\u5356\u6765\u5BA2\u4E0D\u5916\u9001(\u731C\u4E00\u56FD\u5BB6\u540D)",
		"id":22259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u542B\u82DE\u5F85\u653E",
		"indexes":"yzbzdmtcycy",
		"question":"\u54AC\u7740\u5305\u5B50\u8E72\u9A6C\u6876(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6770",
		"indexes":"4grbgmtcyz",
		"question":"4\u4E2A\u4EBA\u642C\u4E2A\u6728\u5934(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5947\u5F02\u679C",
		"indexes":"tyxzmrrlsgrzedcysg",
		"question":"\u692D\u5706\u5F62\u72B6,\u6BDB\u8338\u8338,\u7EFF\u8272\u679C\u8089,\u5B50\u513F\u591A(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u679C)",
		"id":22262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5168\u98DF",
		"indexes":"ct24xsyycyyzxx",
		"question":"\u9910\u538524\u5C0F\u65F6\u8425\u4E1A(\u731C\u4E00\u5B87\u5B99\u73B0\u8C61)",
		"id":22263
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B14",
		"indexes":"ywzbjzltcxbcrjlntxhcywjyp",
		"question":"\u4E00\u7269\u5634\u5DF4\u5C16,\u8D70\u8DEF\u5934\u671D\u4E0B.\u4E0D\u5403\u4EBA\u95F4\u7CAE\u80FD*\u5929\u4E0B\u6D3B(\u731C\u4E00\u6587\u5177\u7528\u54C1)",
		"id":22264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u660E\u78CA\u843D",
		"indexes":"tglskdstctjcycy",
		"question":"\u5929\u521A\u4EAE,\u4E09\u5757\u5927\u77F3\u5934\u4ECE\u5929\u964D(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706B\u8F66",
		"indexes":"jkspxfwykxtdzlxqfbbmljxlshllcyjtgj",
		"question":"\u8FD1\u770B\u662F\u6392\u5C0F\u623F\u5C4B,\u8FDC\u770B\u50CF\u6761\u5927\u957F\u9F99,\u5411\u524D\u98DE\u5954\u4E0D\u8FF7\u8DEF,\u811A\u4E0B\u96F7\u58F0\u8F70\u9686\u9686(\u731C\u4E00\u4EA4\u901A\u5DE5\u5177)",
		"id":22266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u660E",
		"indexes":"wbjgcyrm",
		"question":"\u6316\u58C1\u501F\u5149(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u53C2",
		"indexes":"bpwwdxzssllsgxydylysgzbstbjkcyzw",
		"question":"\u767D\u80D6\u5A03\u5A03\u5730\u4E0B\u85CF,\u6DF1\u5C71\u8001\u6797\u662F\u6545\u4E61,\u8D8A\u5927\u8D8A\u8001\u8D8A\u662F\u8D35,\u6ECB\u8865\u8EAB\u4F53\u4FDD\u5065\u5EB7(\u731C\u4E00\u690D\u7269)",
		"id":22268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"zzfccygjm",
		"question":"\u5FD7\u5728\u53D1\u8D22(\u731C\u4E00\u56FD\u5BB6\u540D)",
		"id":22269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8354\u679D",
		"indexes":"hggblbhzfsjycysg",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u5173\u516C,\u767D\u5218\u5907,\u9ED1\u5F20\u98DE,\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u679C)",
		"id":22270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u53EF",
		"indexes":"gafjbcysp",
		"question":"\u54E5\u554A!\u5206\u5BB6\u5427!(\u731C\u4E00\u98DF\u54C1)",
		"id":22271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D7",
		"indexes":"wxzacyz",
		"question":"\u65E0\u5FC3\u4E4B\u7231(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"gwdxmzcyz",
		"question":"\u56FD\u738B\u5E26\u5C0F\u5E3D\u5B50(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u83F2",
		"indexes":"gwzxfjcyrm",
		"question":"\u56FD\u738B\u5750\u5C0F\u98DE\u673A(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80A5\u6599",
		"indexes":"zftxycywp",
		"question":"\u589E\u80A5\u7279\u6548\u836F(\u731C\u4E00\u7269\u54C1)",
		"id":22275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A81",
		"indexes":"yzxgszdkcyz",
		"question":"\u4E00\u53EA\u5C0F\u72D7\u5B88\u5728\u6D1E\u53E3(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22276
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u7B5D",
		"indexes":"ggfstqkfythdmqkxcywp",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u9AD8\u98DE\u4E0A\u5929,\u5168\u9760\u98CE,\u8981\u5B83\u56DE\u5730\u9762,\u5168\u9760\u7EBF(\u731C\u4E00\u7269\u54C1)",
		"id":22277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA6\u7FF0\u5C48\u4F0F\u5854",
		"indexes":"bsxtdlsqfcyrm",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u8428\u659C\u5854\u5012\u4E86\u8C01\u53BB\u6276(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u8517",
		"indexes":"tlqsjycjdkdbtlzcwxdchqbgtmddcysg",
		"question":"\u8131\u843D\u9752\u6749\u5C31\u8981\u6101,\u5C16\u5200\u5FEB\u5F97\u4E0D\u505C\u7559,\u69A8\u51FA\u6211\u8840\u5F53\u8336\u559D,\u5374\u628A\u9AA8\u5934\u6EE1\u5730\u4E22(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u679C)",
		"id":22279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u86CB",
		"indexes":"szghbnzlnxscyhybcysp",
		"question":"\u8EAB\u5B50\u5149\u6ED1,\u4E0D\u80FD\u7AD9\u7ACB,\u5185\u5FC3\u6DF1\u5904,\u6709\u9EC4\u6709\u767D(\u731C\u4E00\u98DF\u54C1)",
		"id":22280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u857E",
		"indexes":"rmdyshckcyz",
		"question":"\u5982\u82D7\u5F97\u96E8,\u4F3C\u82B1\u521D\u5F00(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72D7",
		"indexes":"zztmhjqcxhwdcydw",
		"question":"\u7CBD\u5B50\u5934,\u6885\u82B1\u811A,\u524D\u5531\u620F,\u540E\u821E\u5200(\u731C\u4E00\u52A8\u7269)",
		"id":22283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8",
		"indexes":"ytxejtdydqbdjdjbdldblycyzrxx",
		"question":"\u4E00\u6761\u7EBF\u513F\u63A5\u7530\u5730,\u7528\u5200\u5207\u4E0D\u65AD,\u526A\u5200\u526A\u4E0D\u65AD,\u843D\u5730\u53D8\u4E86\u6837(\u731C\u4E00\u81EA\u7136\u73B0\u8C61)",
		"id":22284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F5B\u95E8\u4E2D\u4EBA\u53BB\u4E16",
		"indexes":"fjscyjsz",
		"question":"\u4F5B\u6559\u6240\u79F0\u201C\u5706\u5BC2\u201D\u662F\u6307:",
		"id":22285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC",
		"indexes":"jtlgypdzyyls",
		"question":"\u201C\u666F\u6CF0\u84DD\u201D\u5DE5\u827A\u54C1\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u6599\u662F:",
		"id":22286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519C\u5386\u4E5D\u6708\u521D\u4E5D",
		"indexes":"zgmjdzyjszdnyt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u95F4\u7684\u201C\u91CD\u9633\u8282\u201D\u662F\u6307\u7684\u54EA\u4E00\u5929:",
		"id":22287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80A5\u6599",
		"indexes":"zftxycywp",
		"question":"\u589E\u80A5\u7279\u6548\u836F(\u731C\u4E00\u7269\u54C1)",
		"id":22288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B67\u8DEF\u4EA1\u7F8A",
		"indexes":"yzymllcycy",
		"question":"\u4E00\u53EA\u7F8A\u8FF7\u8DEF\u4E86(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u76EE\u76F8\u4EA4",
		"indexes":"xjysgcbcycy",
		"question":"\u9999\u8549\u6709\u56DB\u4E2A\u7FC5\u8180(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DF3\u86A4",
		"indexes":"jsxrcykc",
		"question":"\u50F5\u5C38\u5BFB\u4EBA(\u731C\u4E00\u6606\u866B)",
		"id":22291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u65E5\u5343\u91CC",
		"indexes":"86400m500000mcycy",
		"question":"86400\u79D2500000\u7C73(\u731C\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9488",
		"indexes":"hllgllyjzzpgscywp",
		"question":"\u6ED1\u6E9C\u6E9C,\u5149\u4EAE\u4EAE,\u773C\u775B\u957F\u5728\u5C41\u80A1\u4E0A(\u731C\u4E00\u7269\u54C1)",
		"id":22293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u8272\u5217",
		"indexes":"xmdhcygjm",
		"question":"\u9009\u7F8E\u5927\u4F1A(\u731C\u4E00\u56FD\u5BB6\u540D)",
		"id":22294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"jlscyrm",
		"question":"\u964D\u843D\u4F1E(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A81",
		"indexes":"yzxgszdkcyz",
		"question":"\u4E00\u53EA\u5C0F\u72D7\u5B88\u5728\u6D1E\u53E3(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u7B5D",
		"indexes":"ggfstqkfythdmqkxcywp",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u9AD8\u98DE\u4E0A\u5929,\u5168\u9760\u98CE,\u8981\u5B83\u56DE\u5730\u9762,\u5168\u9760\u7EBF(\u731C\u4E00\u7269\u54C1)",
		"id":22297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA6\u7FF0\u5C48\u4F0F\u5854",
		"indexes":"bsxtdlsqfcyrm",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u8428\u659C\u5854\u5012\u4E86\u8C01\u53BB\u6276(\u731C\u4E00\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u8517",
		"indexes":"tlqsjycjdkdbtlzcwxdchqbgtmddcysg",
		"question":"\u8131\u843D\u9752\u6749\u5C31\u8981\u6101,\u5C16\u5200\u5FEB\u5F97\u4E0D\u505C\u7559,\u69A8\u51FA\u6211\u8840\u5F53\u8336\u559D,\u5374\u628A\u9AA8\u5934\u6EE1\u5730\u4E22(\u731C\u4E00\u6C34\u679C)",
		"id":22299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u86CB",
		"indexes":"szghbnzlnxscyhybcysp",
		"question":"\u8EAB\u5B50\u5149\u6ED1,\u4E0D\u80FD\u7AD9\u7ACB,\u5185\u5FC3\u6DF1\u5904,\u6709\u9EC4\u6709\u767D(\u731C\u4E00\u98DF\u54C1)",
		"id":22300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u548C\u4E09",
		"indexes":"twds1qsbs1cyz",
		"question":"\u5934\u5C3E\u90FD\u662F1,\u5176\u5B9E\u4E0D\u662F1(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u857E",
		"indexes":"rmdyshckcyz",
		"question":"\u5982\u82D7\u5F97\u96E8,\u4F3C\u82B1\u521D\u5F00(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96E8",
		"indexes":"ytxejtdydqbdjdjbdldblycyzrxx",
		"question":"\u4E00\u6761\u7EBF\u513F\u63A5\u7530\u5730,\u7528\u5200\u5207\u4E0D\u65AD,\u526A\u5200\u526A\u4E0D\u65AD,\u843D\u5730\u53D8\u4E86\u6837(\u731C\u4E00\u81EA\u7136\u73B0\u8C61)",
		"id":22303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FDD",
		"indexes":"bccyz",
		"question":"\u767D\u75F4(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6",
		"indexes":"bbcqcyz",
		"question":"\u534A\u90E8\u6625\u79CB(\u731C\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E45",
		"indexes":"tdhmzscbpzzlbjzshsbzcdw",
		"question":"\u5934\u6234\u7EA2\u5E3D\u5B50,\u8EAB\u7A7F\u767D\u888D\u5B50,\u8D70\u8DEF\u6446\u67B6\u5B50,\u8BF4\u8BDD\u4F38\u8116\u5B50(\u731C\u52A8\u7269)",
		"id":22306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9664\u5915",
		"indexes":"hsyyqcswgldsjscy",
		"question":"\u5BD2\u968F\u4E00\u591C\u53BB,\u6625\u968F\u4E94\u66F4\u6765\u3002(\u6253\u65F6\u8282\u4FD7\u79F0\u4E00)",
		"id":22307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C1C",
		"indexes":"mxdrsldyz",
		"question":"\u8FF7\u4FE1\u7684\u4EBA\u5C11\u4E86\u3002(\u6253\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71",
		"indexes":"jscxdyz",
		"question":"\u4ECA\u5C81\u9664\u5915(\u6253\u4E00\u5B57)",
		"id":22309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F9E\u65E7\u8FCE\u65B0",
		"indexes":"cxyssdyxhy",
		"question":"\u9664\u5915\u591C\u5B88\u5C81(\u6253\u4E00\u6B47\u540E\u8BED)",
		"id":22310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E74\u4E09\u5341",
		"indexes":"eldsjscy",
		"question":"\u800C\u7ACB\u3002(\u6253\u65F6\u8282\u4FD7\u79F0\u4E00)",
		"id":22311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D3A\u656C\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"bndzjmy",
		"question":"\u62DC\u5E74\u3002(\u6253\u4F5C\u5BB6\u540D\u4E00)",
		"id":22312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F69\u6392",
		"indexes":"cchlqlzdyysmc",
		"question":"\u8D64\u6A59\u9EC4\u7EFF\u9752\u84DD\u7D2B(\u6253\u4E00\u827A\u672F\u540D\u8BCD)",
		"id":22313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u5E73\u9759\u7684\u591C",
		"indexes":"nyxdysmy",
		"question":"\u95F9\u5143\u5BB5(\u6253\u5F71\u89C6\u540D\u4E00)",
		"id":22314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u900A",
		"indexes":"zsqrsgrm",
		"question":"\u518D\u4E09\u8C26\u8BA9(\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5168\u7AEF",
		"indexes":"hptcsgrm",
		"question":"\u548C\u76D8\u6258\u51FA(\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u8499",
		"indexes":"sdprsgrm",
		"question":"\u6570\u5EA6\u9A97\u4EBA(\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u540D)",
		"id":22317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u8D1D\u8BA1\u5212",
		"indexes":"dsmnsxhdydy",
		"question":"\u6253\u7B97\u660E\u5E74\u751F\u5C0F\u5B69(\u6253\u4E00\u7535\u5F71)",
		"id":22318
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u670B\u6EE1\u5EA7",
		"indexes":"wdlsqyqhydycy",
		"question":"\u6B66\u5927\u90CE\u76DB\u60C5\u5BB4\u8BF7\u597D\u53CB(\u6253\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u60F3\u957F\u5927",
		"indexes":"qysybzyeydygm",
		"question":"\u60C5\u613F\u4E0A\u4E00\u8F88\u5B50\u5E7C\u513F\u56ED(\u6253\u4E00\u6B4C\u540D)",
		"id":22320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u4E1D\u4E0D\u6302",
		"indexes":"lddzzdycy",
		"question":"\u61D2\u60F0\u7684\u8718\u86DB(\u6253\u4E00\u6210\u8BED)",
		"id":22321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u6DA6\u53D1",
		"indexes":"ywmtdztsdymx",
		"question":"\u4E00\u7897\u7C73\u6C64\u5012\u5728\u5934\u4E0A(\u6253\u4E00\u660E\u661F)",
		"id":22322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u8C5A",
		"indexes":"yxngdwsbrdw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":22323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A8\u5B50",
		"indexes":"yxngsysg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u679C",
		"id":22324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7261\u4E39",
		"indexes":"xmnzhhztcbsrtc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u79CD\u82B1\u5349\u5728\u5510\u671D\u88AB\u4E16\u4EBA\u63A8\u5D07?",
		"id":22325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u83B2",
		"indexes":"xmnzhhdgjso",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u79CD\u82B1\u5349\u7684\u6839\u830E\u662F\u85D5?",
		"id":22326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C34\u4E95\u574A",
		"indexes":"yxngjcdzsc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9152\u4EA7\u5730\u5728\u56DB\u5DDD?",
		"id":22329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsshcs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u662F\u7701\u4F1A\u57CE\u5E02",
		"id":22330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE2\u6E56",
		"indexes":"yxngswgddsh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u6DE1\u6C34\u6E56",
		"id":22331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C7E\u9152",
		"indexes":"yxngjcdzsx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9152\u4EA7\u5730\u5728\u5C71\u897F?",
		"id":22332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u51E4\u9152",
		"indexes":"yxngjcdzsx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9152\u4EA7\u5730\u5728\u9655\u897F?",
		"id":22333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94A2\u7434",
		"indexes":"yxnzbsyzhmzlq",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u534E\u6C11\u65CF\u4E50\u5668?",
		"id":22335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A",
		"indexes":"yxngdwsjc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u5BB6\u755C?",
		"id":22336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u9632\u79D1\u6280\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzbzbj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u4E0D\u5728\u5317\u4EAC?",
		"id":22337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u5357\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzbzsh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u4E0D\u5728\u4E0A\u6D77?",
		"id":22338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u5357\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzzzs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u5728\u957F\u6C99?",
		"id":22339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5916\u4EA4\u5B66\u9662",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzzbj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u5728\u5317\u4EAC?",
		"id":22340
	},
	{
		"answer":"0",
		"indexes":"yxngzwzzrtjxzdtkh",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u690D\u7269\u5728\u81EA\u7136\u6761\u4EF6\u4E0B\u5728\u51AC\u5929\u5F00\u82B1?",
		"id":22341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u519C\u4E1A\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsyyxzdwdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u94F6\u884C\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u5927\u884C\u201D?",
		"id":22342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA4\u901A\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsyyxzdwdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u94F6\u884C\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u5927\u884C\u201D?",
		"id":22343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u519C\u4E1A\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsyyxzdwdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u94F6\u884C\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u5927\u884C\u201D?",
		"id":22344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsyyxzdwdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u94F6\u884C\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u5927\u884C\u201D?",
		"id":22345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u771F\u8BDA",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52C7\u6562",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5584\u826F",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u865A\u4F2A",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u6D6E",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9CB8\u9C7C",
		"indexes":"yxngbsdsy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6DE1\u6C34\u9C7C?",
		"id":22351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F4\u53EF\u592B\u65AF\u57FA",
		"indexes":"yxszqjds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u662F\u4F5C\u66F2\u5BB6\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u5927\u5343",
		"indexes":"zgjxdzmhjs",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD1\u73B0\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u753B\u5BB6\u662F",
		"id":22353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xmnwssgyyzdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06",
		"id":22354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A\u8089\u6CE1\u998D",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjyxbfw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C0F\u5403\u5177\u6709\u897F\u5317\u98CE\u5473?",
		"id":22355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80A0\u7C89",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjygdfw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C0F\u5403\u5177\u6709\u5E7F\u4E1C\u98CE\u5473?",
		"id":22356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u7C73",
		"indexes":"yxngbshzppp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5316\u5986\u54C1\u54C1\u724C?",
		"id":22357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6",
		"indexes":"yxngsgjs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D35\u91D1\u5C5E?",
		"id":22358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u67A3",
		"indexes":"yxngstwsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u751C\u5473\u98DF\u7269?",
		"id":22359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u897F",
		"indexes":"hhljyxngsf",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u6CB3\u6D41\u7ECF\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u4EFD?",
		"id":22360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u6E05",
		"indexes":"yxngpjbsgypp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5564\u9152\u4E0D\u662F\u56FD\u6709\u54C1\u724C?",
		"id":22361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72AC\u591C\u53C9",
		"indexes":"yxngsdmrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u52A8\u6F2B\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjcwlscddgx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u59D3\u66FE\u7ECF\u6210\u4E3A\u5386\u53F2\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u56FD\u59D3?",
		"id":22363
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u5170\u5DF4\u6258",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsyzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD?",
		"id":22364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6D77",
		"indexes":"ngcscjbsgdhdddc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u66FE\u7ECF\u4E0D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u90FD\u57CE?",
		"id":22365
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u628A\u5200",
		"indexes":"dynxnwmyqzgdnhddys",
		"question":"\u7535\u5F71\u300A\u90A3\u4E9B\u5E74,\u6211\u4EEC\u4E00\u8D77\u8FFD\u8FC7\u7684\u5973\u5B69\u300B\u7684\u5BFC\u6F14\u662F?",
		"id":22366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"lsfdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u6D1B\u795E\u8D4B\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F?",
		"id":22367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"qbsdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E03\u6B65\u8BD7\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F?",
		"id":22368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"tqtfdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0\u8D4B\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F?",
		"id":22369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"sxmnwjlzzbqhddj",
		"question":"\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886\u5728\u957F\u677F\u6865\u559D\u65AD\u654C\u519B?",
		"id":22370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"gwgzljsxmnwjjdszsw",
		"question":"\u201C\u8FC7\u4E94\u5173,\u65A9\u516D\u5C06\u201D\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u519B\u7684\u6240\u4F5C\u6240\u4E3A?",
		"id":22371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DBF\u53BF",
		"indexes":"lbgyzfsrzcznxy",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u3001\u5173\u7FBD\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u4E09\u4EBA\u6700\u521D\u5728\u54EA\u76F8\u9047?",
		"id":22372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96CC\u96C4\u53CC\u80A1\u5251",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzlbsydssmwq",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u5218\u5907\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22373
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u9F99\u5043\u6708\u5200",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzgysydssmwq",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u5173\u7FBD\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E08\u516B\u86C7\u77DB",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzzfsydssmwq",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8D75\u98DE\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u5929\u753B\u621F",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzlbsydssmwq",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u5415\u5E03\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u98DE\u5148\u751F",
		"indexes":"ptbsrcz",
		"question":"\u5E9E\u7EDF\u88AB\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u4F5C?",
		"id":22377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"xzmzsxjzzwggzbhlcddszcybblcydszs",
		"question":"\u73B0\u5728\u5E99\u4E2D\u795E\u50CF,\u5C45\u4E2D\u8005\u4E3A\u5173\u516C,\u5DE6\u8FB9\u9ED1\u8138\u6301\u5200\u7684\u662F\u5468\u4ED3,\u53F3\u8FB9\u767D\u8138\u6301\u5370\u7684\u662F\u5219\u662F?",
		"id":22378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u4FCA\u6770",
		"indexes":"lxylccsnwgsczd",
		"question":"\u6D41\u884C\u97F3\u4E50\u300A\u66F9\u64CD\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u6B4C\u624B\u521B\u4F5C\u7684?",
		"id":22379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u4FCA\u6770",
		"indexes":"lxylzcbsnwgsczd",
		"question":"\u6D41\u884C\u97F3\u4E50\u300A\u9189\u8D64\u58C1\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u6B4C\u624B\u521B\u4F5C\u7684?",
		"id":22380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5937\u9675\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"zslbfwsbdgjzys",
		"question":"\u81F4\u4F7F\u5218\u5907\u4F10\u5434\u5931\u8D25\u7684\u5173\u952E\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":22381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"zsccnxsbdgjzys",
		"question":"\u81F4\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u5357\u4E0B\u5931\u8D25\u7684\u5173\u952E\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":22382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u91ED\u5251",
		"indexes":"zyzzbplhdwqs",
		"question":"\u8D75\u4E91\u5728\u957F\u5742\u5761\u63B3\u83B7\u7684\u6B66\u5668\u662F?",
		"id":22383
	},
	{
		"answer":"208",
		"indexes":"cbzzjsyxyjn",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u7ED3\u675F\u4E8E\u897F\u5143\u51E0\u5E74?",
		"id":22384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7684\u5362",
		"indexes":"lbdzqjsmmz",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u7684\u5750\u9A91\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":22385
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u9042",
		"indexes":"cymcxlkcdxldjs",
		"question":"\u66FE\u4E0E\u9A6C\u8D85\u534F\u529B\u6297\u66F9\u7684\u897F\u51C9\u5927\u5C06\u662F?",
		"id":22386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzjsyhslczsrzk",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u65E2\u751F\u745C,\u4F55\u751F\u4EAE\u201D\u51FA\u4E4B\u8C01\u4EBA\u4E4B\u53E3?",
		"id":22387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u5723",
		"indexes":"gybhszcw",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u88AB\u540E\u4E16\u5C0A\u79F0\u4E3A?",
		"id":22388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5141",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzdcyssjdbn",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8C82\u8749\u539F\u662F\u8C01\u5BB6\u7684\u5A62\u5973?",
		"id":22389
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzsswjzhx",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u662F\u8C01\u201C\u6E29\u9152\u65A9\u534E\u96C4\u201D?",
		"id":22390
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzsslxlwmzkddg",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u662F\u8C01\u7559\u4E0B\u4E86\u201C\u671B\u6885\u6B62\u6E34\u201D\u7684\u5178\u6545?",
		"id":22391
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"xqjjl",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u4E54\u5AC1\u7ED9\u4E86?",
		"id":22392
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u85E4\u7532\u5175",
		"indexes":"wpdnzdqdmhplzbkmhgspdbzs",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u5E73\u5B9A\u5357\u4E2D\u5730\u533A\u7684\u5B5F\u83B7\u53DB\u4E71\u4E2D,\u88AB\u5B54\u660E\u706B\u653B\u6240\u7834\u7684\u5175\u79CD\u662F?",
		"id":22393
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662D\u70C8\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"lbshdshs",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u6B7B\u540E\u7684\u8C25\u53F7\u662F?",
		"id":22394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u8499",
		"indexes":"xmnwbsgydsxbj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u624B\u4E0B\u8D25\u5C06?",
		"id":22395
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzcbszddghswg",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u8D64\u818A\u4E0A\u9635\u201D\u7684\u5178\u6545\u548C\u8C01\u65E0\u5173?",
		"id":22396
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u6C64",
		"indexes":"fqhzsybzshdnwjlssd",
		"question":"\u201C\u72AF\u5F3A\u6C49\u8005,\u867D\u8FDC\u5FC5\u8BDB\u201D\u662F\u6C49\u4EE3\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886\u6240\u8BF4\u7684?",
		"id":22397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzjnmjddghsyg",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u7CBE\u56CA\u5999\u8BA1\u201D\u7684\u5178\u6545\u548C\u8C01\u6709\u5173?",
		"id":22398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u8C0C",
		"indexes":"lstjcwzstdnwezyssj",
		"question":"\u5218\u7985\u6295\u964D\u66F9\u9B4F\u4E4B\u65F6,\u4ED6\u7684\u54EA\u4F4D\u513F\u5B50\u4EE5\u8EAB\u6B7B\u8282?",
		"id":22399
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzszcyxzhddgzdss",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u8EAB\u5728\u66F9\u8425\u5FC3\u5728\u6C49\u201D\u7684\u5178\u6545\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzkcjsyzs",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u201D\u4F7F\u7528\u8005\u662F?",
		"id":22401
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"whsjzsszgj",
		"question":"\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u4E2D\u8C01\u64C5\u957F\u5F13\u7BAD?",
		"id":22402
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzqmzjlyxdcyzscchs",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u9752\u6885\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\u201D\u7684\u53C2\u4E0E\u8005\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8C01?",
		"id":22403
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzsbcwxbw",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8C01\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5C0F\u9738\u738B\u201D?",
		"id":22404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u5F29",
		"indexes":"zglfmdzzwqjz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u53D1\u660E\u7684\u4F5C\u6218\u6B66\u5668\u53EB\u4F5C?",
		"id":22405
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u5B81",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzzjrjdqybsjyddds",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u5728\u52A0\u5165\u519B\u961F\u524D\u539F\u672C\u662F\u6C5F\u6D0B\u5927\u76D7\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22406
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u8FBD",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzszwy",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8C01\u5B57\u6587\u8FDC?",
		"id":22407
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u900D\u9065\u6D25\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"wyztdsfsznczyzh",
		"question":"\u201C\u6587\u8FDC\u6B62\u557C\u201D\u7684\u8BF4\u6CD5\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u573A\u6218\u5F79\u4E4B\u540E?",
		"id":22408
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BDB\u73A0",
		"indexes":"zcssxccjyftzylbc",
		"question":"\u6700\u521D\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u5EFA\u8BAE\u201C\u5949\u5929\u5B50\u4EE5\u4EE4\u4E0D\u81E3\u201D?",
		"id":22409
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9A6C\u4E49\u4ECE",
		"indexes":"gszzzdbdbcz",
		"question":"\u516C\u5B59\u74D2\u7EC4\u7EC7\u7684\u90E8\u961F\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C?",
		"id":22410
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u89D2",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzbcwtgjjds",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5929\u516C\u5C06\u519B\u201D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22411
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u5B9D",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzbcwdgjjds",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5730\u516C\u5C06\u519B\u201D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u6881",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzbcwrgjjds",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4EBA\u516C\u5C06\u519B\u201D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22413
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u8FBD",
		"indexes":"cwzyzsszfhfdnezswbj",
		"question":"\u66F9\u9B4F\u9635\u8425\u4E2D,\u662F\u8C01\u9A7B\u9632\u5408\u80A5\u591A\u5E74\u627C\u5236\u5B59\u5434\u5317\u8FDB?",
		"id":22414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"xmjlbzwzljzlds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C06\u9886\u4E0D\u5728\u201C\u4E94\u5B50\u826F\u5C06\u201D\u4E4B\u5217\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22415
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u53F2\u6148",
		"indexes":"xmjlbzwzljzlds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C06\u9886\u4E0D\u5728\u201C\u4E94\u5B50\u826F\u5C06\u201D\u4E4B\u5217\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22416
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"xmjlbzwzljzlds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C06\u9886\u4E0D\u5728\u201C\u4E94\u5B50\u826F\u5C06\u201D\u4E4B\u5217\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22417
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"xmjlbzwzljzlds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u5C06\u9886\u4E0D\u5728\u201C\u4E94\u5B50\u826F\u5C06\u201D\u4E4B\u5217\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4E15",
		"indexes":"ccshdjcrs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6B7B\u540E\u7684\u7EE7\u627F\u4EBA\u662F?",
		"id":22419
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"qwljflzzqlssdsj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u201C\u8001\u9AA5\u4F0F\u67A5,\u5FD7\u5728\u5343\u91CC?\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5?",
		"id":22420
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"qwfdbwymzfnjwyzyssdmj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u201C\u975E\u6DE1\u6CCA\u65E0\u4EE5\u660E\u5FD7,\u975E\u5B81\u9759\u65E0\u4EE5\u81F4\u8FDC\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u660E\u53E5?",
		"id":22421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8083",
		"indexes":"jzycrswdddds",
		"question":"\u7EE7\u5468\u745C\u51FA\u4EFB\u5B59\u5434\u5927\u90FD\u7763\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u6708\u82F1",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzzgldfrs",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u592B\u4EBA\u662F?",
		"id":22423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzbsdjzdsnwjl",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u201C\u62D4\u77E2\u5556\u775B\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":22424
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"zsgyyzssxlbtjdzgl",
		"question":"\u5728\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u5218\u5907\u63A8\u8350\u7684\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE?",
		"id":22425
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u6E0A",
		"indexes":"djszydwjnwdjbz",
		"question":"\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u6218\u5F79\u7684\u9B4F\u519B\u54EA\u4F4D\u5927\u5C06\u88AB\u65A9?",
		"id":22426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"jmcssdmcdpj",
		"question":"\u201C\u9526\u9A6C\u8D85\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u5BF9\u9A6C\u8D85\u7684\u8BC4\u4EF7?",
		"id":22427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"shsxbbk",
		"question":"\u201C\u8700\u6C49\u56DB\u76F8\u201D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC?",
		"id":22428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u6743",
		"indexes":"shsxbbk",
		"question":"\u201C\u8700\u6C49\u56DB\u76F8\u201D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC?",
		"id":22429
	},
	{
		"answer":"5050",
		"indexes":"12349899100",
		"question":"1+2+3+4+\u2026+98+99+100=?",
		"id":22430
	},
	{
		"answer":"18",
		"indexes":"711",
		"question":"7+11=?",
		"id":22431
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"55",
		"question":"5+5=?",
		"id":22432
	},
	{
		"answer":"96",
		"indexes":"888",
		"question":"8+88+?",
		"id":22433
	},
	{
		"answer":"84",
		"indexes":"777",
		"question":"7+77=?",
		"id":22434
	},
	{
		"answer":"50",
		"indexes":"2525",
		"question":"25+25=?",
		"id":22435
	},
	{
		"answer":"32",
		"indexes":"2012",
		"question":"20+12=?",
		"id":22436
	},
	{
		"answer":"24",
		"indexes":"1410",
		"question":"14+10=?",
		"id":22437
	},
	{
		"answer":"85",
		"indexes":"6322",
		"question":"63+22=?",
		"id":22438
	},
	{
		"answer":"124",
		"indexes":"5173",
		"question":"51+73=?",
		"id":22439
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"11",
		"question":"1+1=?",
		"id":22440
	},
	{
		"answer":"2i",
		"indexes":"ii",
		"question":"i+i=?",
		"id":22441
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"2X13X",
		"question":"2X+1=3,X=?",
		"id":22442
	},
	{
		"answer":"5cm",
		"indexes":"yzzjsjxltzjbfbw3cmh4cmnxbzw",
		"question":"\u5DF2\u77E5\u76F4\u89D2\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\u4E24\u6761\u76F4\u89D2\u8FB9\u5206\u522B\u4E3A3cm\u548C4cm,\u90A3\u659C\u8FB9\u957F\u4E3A?",
		"id":22443
	},
	{
		"answer":"4cm",
		"indexes":"yzzjsjxytzjbw3cmqxbw5cmnlytzjbzw",
		"question":"\u5DF2\u77E5\u76F4\u89D2\u4E09\u89D2\u5F62\u4E00\u6761\u76F4\u89D2\u8FB9\u4E3A3cm,\u4E14\u659C\u8FB9\u4E3A5cm,\u90A3\u53E6\u4E00\u6761\u76F4\u89D2\u8FB9\u957F\u4E3A?",
		"id":22444
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"xy3qyx1zx",
		"question":"x+y=3,\u4E14y-x=1,\u5219x=?",
		"id":22445
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"84",
		"question":"8+4=?",
		"id":22446
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"65",
		"question":"6+5=?",
		"id":22447
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"110",
		"question":"1+10=?",
		"id":22448
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"141",
		"question":"14+1=?",
		"id":22449
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"29",
		"question":"2+9=?",
		"id":22450
	},
	{
		"answer":"18",
		"indexes":"99",
		"question":"9+9=?",
		"id":22451
	},
	{
		"answer":"54",
		"indexes":"945",
		"question":"9+45=?",
		"id":22452
	},
	{
		"answer":"51",
		"indexes":"456",
		"question":"45+6=?",
		"id":22453
	},
	{
		"answer":"57",
		"indexes":"1245",
		"question":"12+45=?",
		"id":22454
	},
	{
		"answer":"990",
		"indexes":"9855",
		"question":"985+5=?",
		"id":22455
	},
	{
		"answer":"100",
		"indexes":"955",
		"question":"95+5=?",
		"id":22456
	},
	{
		"answer":"112",
		"indexes":"5656",
		"question":"56+56=?",
		"id":22457
	},
	{
		"answer":"100",
		"indexes":"3070",
		"question":"30+70=?",
		"id":22458
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"43",
		"question":"4+3=?",
		"id":22459
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"48",
		"question":"4+8=?",
		"id":22460
	},
	{
		"answer":"113",
		"indexes":"2192",
		"question":"21+92=?",
		"id":22461
	},
	{
		"answer":"45",
		"indexes":"423",
		"question":"42+3=?",
		"id":22462
	},
	{
		"answer":"60",
		"indexes":"564",
		"question":"56+4=?",
		"id":22463
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"25",
		"question":"2+5=?",
		"id":22464
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"228",
		"question":"22+8=?",
		"id":22465
	},
	{
		"answer":"49",
		"indexes":"454",
		"question":"45+4=?",
		"id":22466
	},
	{
		"answer":"9",
		"indexes":"18",
		"question":"1+8=?",
		"id":22467
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"37",
		"question":"3+7=?",
		"id":22468
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"22",
		"question":"2+2=?",
		"id":22469
	},
	{
		"answer":"64",
		"indexes":"568",
		"question":"56+8=?",
		"id":22470
	},
	{
		"answer":"17",
		"indexes":"125",
		"question":"12+5=?",
		"id":22471
	},
	{
		"answer":"89",
		"indexes":"287",
		"question":"2+87=?",
		"id":22472
	},
	{
		"answer":"100",
		"indexes":"991",
		"question":"99+1=?",
		"id":22473
	},
	{
		"answer":"45",
		"indexes":"450",
		"question":"45+0=?",
		"id":22474
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"57",
		"question":"5+7=?",
		"id":22475
	},
	{
		"answer":"54",
		"indexes":"459",
		"question":"45+9=?",
		"id":22476
	},
	{
		"answer":"111",
		"indexes":"2289",
		"question":"22+89=?",
		"id":22477
	},
	{
		"answer":"14",
		"indexes":"68",
		"question":"6+8=?",
		"id":22478
	},
	{
		"answer":"16",
		"indexes":"97",
		"question":"9+7=?",
		"id":22479
	},
	{
		"answer":"13",
		"indexes":"67",
		"question":"6+7=?",
		"id":22480
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"128",
		"question":"12+8=?",
		"id":22481
	},
	{
		"answer":"128",
		"indexes":"5078",
		"question":"50+78=?",
		"id":22482
	},
	{
		"answer":"41",
		"indexes":"329",
		"question":"32+9=?",
		"id":22483
	},
	{
		"answer":"34",
		"indexes":"727",
		"question":"7+27=?",
		"id":22484
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"17",
		"question":"1+7=?",
		"id":22485
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"75",
		"question":"7+5=?",
		"id":22486
	},
	{
		"answer":"246",
		"indexes":"123123",
		"question":"123+123=?",
		"id":22487
	},
	{
		"answer":"68",
		"indexes":"5612",
		"question":"56+12=?",
		"id":22488
	},
	{
		"answer":"14",
		"indexes":"59",
		"question":"5+9=?",
		"id":22489
	},
	{
		"answer":"59",
		"indexes":"1445",
		"question":"14+45=?",
		"id":22490
	},
	{
		"answer":"31",
		"indexes":"247",
		"question":"24+7=?",
		"id":22491
	},
	{
		"answer":"48",
		"indexes":"435",
		"question":"43+5=?",
		"id":22492
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"17",
		"question":"1+7=?",
		"id":22493
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"37",
		"question":"3+7=?",
		"id":22494
	},
	{
		"answer":"14",
		"indexes":"122",
		"question":"12+2=?",
		"id":22495
	},
	{
		"answer":"28",
		"indexes":"217",
		"question":"21+7=?",
		"id":22496
	},
	{
		"answer":"23",
		"indexes":"149",
		"question":"14+9=?",
		"id":22497
	},
	{
		"answer":"79",
		"indexes":"4534",
		"question":"45+34=?",
		"id":22498
	},
	{
		"answer":"16",
		"indexes":"151",
		"question":"15+1=?",
		"id":22499
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"34",
		"question":"3+4=?",
		"id":22500
	},
	{
		"answer":"155",
		"indexes":"1541",
		"question":"154+1=?",
		"id":22501
	},
	{
		"answer":"123",
		"indexes":"7845",
		"question":"78+45=?",
		"id":22502
	},
	{
		"answer":"70",
		"indexes":"763",
		"question":"7+63=?",
		"id":22503
	},
	{
		"answer":"57",
		"indexes":"1245",
		"question":"12+45=?",
		"id":22504
	},
	{
		"answer":"140",
		"indexes":"6278",
		"question":"62+78=?",
		"id":22505
	},
	{
		"answer":"102",
		"indexes":"8319",
		"question":"83+19=?",
		"id":22506
	},
	{
		"answer":"73",
		"indexes":"3439",
		"question":"34+39=?",
		"id":22507
	},
	{
		"answer":"100",
		"indexes":"8713",
		"question":"87+13=?",
		"id":22508
	},
	{
		"answer":"55",
		"indexes":"4510",
		"question":"45+10=?",
		"id":22509
	},
	{
		"answer":"59",
		"indexes":"4910",
		"question":"49+10=?",
		"id":22510
	},
	{
		"answer":"146",
		"indexes":"5987",
		"question":"59+87=?",
		"id":22511
	},
	{
		"answer":"119",
		"indexes":"4871",
		"question":"48+71=?",
		"id":22512
	},
	{
		"answer":"113",
		"indexes":"9815",
		"question":"98+15=?",
		"id":22513
	},
	{
		"answer":"109",
		"indexes":"1990",
		"question":"19+90=?",
		"id":22514
	},
	{
		"answer":"112",
		"indexes":"1498",
		"question":"14+98=?",
		"id":22515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8305\u53F0",
		"indexes":"yxngjcdzgz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9152\u4EA7\u5730\u5728\u8D35\u5DDE?",
		"id":22516
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngsyzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E9A\u6D32\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22517
	},
	{
		"answer":"0",
		"indexes":"xmnggjdgqbsyhblsszcd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u56FD\u65D7\u4E0D\u662F\u7531\u7EA2\u767D\u84DD\u4E09\u8272\u7EC4\u6210\u7684?",
		"id":22518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u79D1",
		"indexes":"xmngbsITgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662FIT\u516C\u53F8?",
		"id":22519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u77F3\u6CB9",
		"indexes":"xmngbsITgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662FIT\u516C\u53F8?",
		"id":22520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FCF\u6C5F\u5357",
		"indexes":"ngsbskcd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E0D\u662F\u5FEB\u9910\u5E97?",
		"id":22521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u662F\u6211\u7684OK\u7EF7",
		"indexes":"yxnsgbyzjlyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u9996\u6B4C\u4E0D\u7531\u5468\u6770\u4F26\u6F14\u5531?",
		"id":22522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u662F\u6211\u7684OK\u7EF7",
		"indexes":"yxnsgbyljjyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u9996\u6B4C\u4E0D\u7531\u6797\u4FCA\u6770\u6F14\u5531?",
		"id":22523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6DDE\u6CAA\u4F1A\u6218",
		"indexes":"yxncbsdecsjdzzdzmzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u6B21\u4E0D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":22524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5F97\u5170\u6D77\u6218",
		"indexes":"yxncbsdecsjdzzdzmzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u6B21\u4E0D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":22525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6ED1\u94C1\u5362\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"yxncbsdecsjdzzdzmzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u6B21\u4E0D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":22526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u79CB\u8282",
		"indexes":"ngszgdctjr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5?",
		"id":22528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94C1\u62D0\u674E",
		"indexes":"bxghzdbxynyg",
		"question":"\u516B\u4ED9\u8FC7\u6D77\u4E2D\u7684\u516B\u4ED9\u6709\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":22529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767B\u9AD8",
		"indexes":"zyjsrmhjxnxhd",
		"question":"\u91CD\u9633\u8282\u65F6\u4EBA\u4EEC\u4F1A\u8FDB\u884C\u54EA\u9879\u6D3B\u52A8?",
		"id":22530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":22531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":22532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":22533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8861\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxngsswyzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C71\u662F\u4E94\u5CB3\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6B27\u5E73\u539F",
		"indexes":"yxngpybwyzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5E73\u539F\u4E0D\u4F4D\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD?",
		"id":22535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7CA4",
		"indexes":"ngszgsqjczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7701\u533A\u7B80\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"ngslcgdzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u516D\u671D\u53E4\u90FD\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FC4\u7F57\u65AF",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":22538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lhgcrlsgsng",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":22539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6052\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxngsswyzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C71\u662F\u4E94\u5CB3\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u534E\u9C9F",
		"indexes":"nzyshzdsl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6DE1\u6C34\u91CC?",
		"id":22541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F01\u9E45",
		"indexes":"nznbhf",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9E1F\u4E0D\u4F1A\u98DE?",
		"id":22542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u71D5",
		"indexes":"nzsyhn",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6D77\u9E1F?",
		"id":22543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72C2\u5984\u81EA\u5927",
		"indexes":"yxngsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u9510",
		"indexes":"yxnwswxljzzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u201C\u620A\u620C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E66\u5251\u6069\u4EC7\u5F55",
		"indexes":"ngbslxdzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795E\u96D5\u4FA0\u4FA3",
		"indexes":"ngsjydxs",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u91D1\u5EB8\u7684\u5C0F\u8BF4?",
		"id":22547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5217\u5B81",
		"indexes":"ngbszgdsxj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6?",
		"id":22548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u514B",
		"indexes":"ngbszgdsxj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6?",
		"id":22549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u664B",
		"indexes":"ngszgsqjczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7701\u533A\u7B80\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F6D\u52A0\u6728",
		"indexes":"xlnygsywgdkxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u79D1\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22551
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E9\u53D1\u767D\u5E1D\u57CE",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u5B5F\u6D69\u7136\u4E4B\u5E7F\u9675",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u6C5F\u95E8\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u5750\u656C\u4EAD\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22557
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"nygsdhdsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E1C\u6C49\u7684\u9996\u90FD?",
		"id":22558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"nygsxhdsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u897F\u6C49\u7684\u9996\u90FD?",
		"id":22559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51A5\u738B\u661F",
		"indexes":"ngbsybdxx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u516B\u5927\u884C\u661F?",
		"id":22560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77F3\u5BB6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlngshbsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CB3\u5317\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u547C\u548C\u6D69\u7279",
		"indexes":"xlngsnmgzzqddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5185\u8499\u53E4\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD0\u57CE",
		"indexes":"xlngssxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C71\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngsjssddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6C5F\u82CF\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"xlngszjsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6D59\u6C5F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666F\u5FB7\u9547",
		"indexes":"xlngsjxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C9B",
		"indexes":"xlngssdsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C71\u4E1C\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22567
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u6797",
		"indexes":"xlngsgxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E7F\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"xlngshnsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CB3\u5357\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6210\u90FD",
		"indexes":"xlngsscsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56DB\u5DDD\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u7406",
		"indexes":"xlngsynsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E91\u5357\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22571
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"xlngssxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9655\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u6C34",
		"indexes":"xlngsgssddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7518\u8083\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94F6\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"xlngsnxhzzzqddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5B81\u590F\u56DE\u65CF\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u96C4",
		"indexes":"xlngstwddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53F0\u6E7E\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":22576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67CF\u6797",
		"indexes":"xmngcszdg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u5FB7\u56FD?",
		"id":22577
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5948\u826F",
		"indexes":"xmngcszrb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5728\u65E5\u672C?",
		"id":22578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u7FB2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"yxnwsltjxdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u5170\u4EAD\u96C6\u5E8F\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90D1\u548C",
		"indexes":"yxnwqxxy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E03\u4E0B\u897F\u6D0B?",
		"id":22580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u6743",
		"indexes":"nwlsskrzzzxsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u70C8\u58EB\u662F\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u727A\u7272\u7684?",
		"id":22581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5B58\u745E",
		"indexes":"nwlssjfzzzxsd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u70C8\u58EB\u662F\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u727A\u7272\u7684?",
		"id":22582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u5B89\u95E8",
		"indexes":"ngsghdnr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5FBD\u7684\u5185\u5BB9?",
		"id":22583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F7F\u8F6E",
		"indexes":"ngsghdnr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5FBD\u7684\u5185\u5BB9?",
		"id":22584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A3B\u7A57",
		"indexes":"ngsghdnr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5FBD\u7684\u5185\u5BB9?",
		"id":22585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u9510",
		"indexes":"nwswxljzzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u620A\u620C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC\u6761\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"ngsqzftqlzqddbpdty",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u540C\u4FB5\u7565\u8005\u7B7E\u8BA2\u7684\u4E0D\u5E73\u7B49\u6761\u7EA6?",
		"id":22587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6392\u6BD4",
		"indexes":"ngsxcff",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4FEE\u8F9E\u65B9\u6CD5?",
		"id":22588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5584\u826F",
		"indexes":"ngsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u908B\u9062",
		"indexes":"ngsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD?",
		"id":22590
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u6865\u548C\u5E0C",
		"indexes":"yxngsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgscdwxj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":22592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5F7B",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswghcdlsrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u6C49\u671D\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgsgsqdlsrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswgjfzzsqdgcdjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5171\u4EA7\u515A\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":22595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygshjzzsqsjgddf",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u7EA2\u519B\u957F\u5F81\u65F6\u671F\u6240\u7ECF\u8FC7\u7684\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96C1\u5357\u98DE",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywstymydxszdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F<<\u5929\u6DAF\u660E\u6708\u5200>>\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnygsqlwgdbgljdgj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4FB5\u7565\u6211\u56FD\u7684\u300A\u516B\u56FD\u8054\u519B\u300B\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6?",
		"id":22598
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u501A\u5929\u5C60\u9F99\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"qzcjyzpdsnyg",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u91D1\u5EB8\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":22599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D41\u661F\u00B7\u8774\u8776\u00B7\u5251",
		"indexes":"qzcnygbslysdzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6881\u7FBD\u751F\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"sgzlxyjhslyjbls",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u9646\u900A\u7528\u8BA1\u706B\u70E7\u8FDE\u8425\u51FB\u8D25\u4E86\u8C01?",
		"id":22602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u4F57",
		"indexes":"ssjgyggld",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u7ED9\u5173\u7FBD\u522E\u9AA8\u7597\u6BD2?",
		"id":22603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"bbldwpwky",
		"question":"\u80CC\u5305\u91CC\u7684\u7269\u54C1,\u6211\u53EF\u4EE5:",
		"id":22604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6309M\u952E\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zyxlkykdsjdtm",
		"question":"\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u91CC\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u5230\u4E16\u754C\u5730\u56FE\u5417?",
		"id":22605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxlddjyjz",
		"question":"\u6E38\u620F\u91CC\u7684\u9053\u5177\u6709\u51E0\u79CD?",
		"id":22606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxzddjlyy",
		"question":"\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7684\u9053\u5177\u6765\u6E90\u6709:",
		"id":22607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"gycldmsnxszqd",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u8349\u6599\u7684\u63CF\u8FF0,\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u6B63\u786E\u7684:",
		"id":22608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"QQsgsyksmtcdyx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u662F\u4E00\u6B3E\u4EC0\u4E48\u9898\u6750\u7684\u6E38\u620F?",
		"id":22609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"zglsnggjd",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684?",
		"id":22610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":22611
	},
	{
		"answer":"QQ\u53F7\u7801",
		"indexes":"ysmzhjkyzjdlQQsg",
		"question":"\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E10\u53F7\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u76F4\u63A5\u767B\u9646QQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":22612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72B6\u6001\u754C\u9762",
		"indexes":"F1ssmjmdkjj",
		"question":"F1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u754C\u9762\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E?",
		"id":22613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5546\u57CE",
		"indexes":"F9ssmjmdkjj",
		"question":"F9\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u754C\u9762\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E?",
		"id":22614
	},
	{
		"answer":"F9",
		"indexes":"scdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5546\u57CE\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22615
	},
	{
		"answer":"G",
		"indexes":"yzjdNPCdhdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u4E0E\u6700\u8FD1\u7684NPC\u5BF9\u8BDD\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22616
	},
	{
		"answer":"C",
		"indexes":"sqlzdsddjdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u62FE\u53D6\u843D\u5728\u5730\u4E0A\u7684\u9053\u5177\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22617
	},
	{
		"answer":"Tab",
		"indexes":"ksdxsbgwdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5FEB\u901F\u70B9\u9009\u8EAB\u8FB9\u602A\u7269\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22619
	},
	{
		"answer":"M",
		"indexes":"dkdtdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u6253\u5F00\u5730\u56FE\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8F66\u592B",
		"indexes":"xksddlwdccygzngNPC",
		"question":"\u60F3\u5FEB\u901F\u5230\u8FBE\u53E6\u5916\u7684\u57CE\u6C60,\u5E94\u8BE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC?",
		"id":22622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7269\u54C1\u754C\u9762",
		"indexes":"xzyxzbgtwygtgngjmcz",
		"question":"\u60F3\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u6446\u4E2A\u644A\u4F4D,\u5E94\u8BE5\u901A\u8FC7\u54EA\u4E2A\u754C\u9762\u64CD\u4F5C?",
		"id":22624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":22625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":22626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":22627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":22628
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A91\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxngzysbsyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":22629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"QQsgdrwzgyjljbsx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u603B\u5171\u6709\u51E0\u7C7B\u57FA\u672C\u5C5E\u6027?",
		"id":22630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u5747\u578B",
		"indexes":"jsssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u5251\u4F8D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":22631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u9632\u578B",
		"indexes":"hjssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u8C6A\u6770\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":22632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u653B\u578B",
		"indexes":"yysssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":22633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6062\u590D\u578B",
		"indexes":"xssssmlxdzy",
		"question":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":22634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"jszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u5251\u4F8D\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65A7\u5934",
		"indexes":"hjzbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u8C6A\u6770\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6756",
		"indexes":"yyszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22637
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6247\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xsszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":22638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"mgzytsjyyjlxf",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u5929\u751F\u5C31\u62E5\u6709\u51E0\u7C7B\u5FC3\u6CD5?",
		"id":22639
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"1QbngdhdsQd",
		"question":"1Q\u5E01\u80FD\u591F\u5151\u6362\u591A\u5C11Q\u70B9?",
		"id":22640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"hjjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6A2A\u5251\u51FB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22641
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxjwsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u996E\u8840\u5251\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"hfflsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u56DE\u98CE\u62C2\u67F3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22643
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jrsxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u5203\u566C\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"fgzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5206\u5149\u65A9\u5F71\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22645
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"klqxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u96F7\u4E03\u661F\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"shyssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6151\u9B42\u4E00\u5F0F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jdbhsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u8361\u516B\u8352\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"cysxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6B8B\u5F71\u8680\u5FC3\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"adcqsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u50B2\u65AD\u82CD\u7A79\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jhhjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u9E3F\u5E7B\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"cyhxjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u51FA\u4E91\u5E7B\u661F\u5251\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jqcjxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5251\u6C14\u51B2\u4E5D\u9704\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bwfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u9738\u738B\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"qxfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6CE3\u8840\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jxlhfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u796D\u8840\u8FDE\u73AF\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"nhktsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6012\u6D77\u72C2\u6D9B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"sggfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u5DE5\u9B3C\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"lzqjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u529B\u65A9\u5343\u94A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jlldsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u96F7\u88C2\u5730\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"slthsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u9F99\u63A2\u6D77\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jzfldsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E5D\u5DDE\u98CE\u96F7\u52A8\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"kfcxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u65A7\u51B2\u9704\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"ksbzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u6C99\u767E\u6218\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"sxptsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u55DC\u8840\u7834\u5929\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"tnrysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5929\u6012\u4EBA\u6028\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cyxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70BD\u708E\u88AD\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22668
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"kyysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u708E\u6D8C\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cyzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6B8B\u9633\u7099\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xhzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u661F\u706B\u5760\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22671
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yhfxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E1A\u706B\u711A\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hjlhsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5E7B\u5251\u79BB\u706B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22673
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jskwsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u91D1\u86C7\u72C2\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xjmysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5378\u7532\u51A5\u7130\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yhlysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u91CE\u706B\u71CE\u539F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"aydcxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6697\u708E\u51CB\u6B8B\u661F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"lyymzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70BC\u72F1\u9634\u9B54\u5492\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xllhzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u70AB\u7075\u6D41\u706B\u5492\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jsfhxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6C5F\u5C71\u70FD\u706B\u5578\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"spsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6C34\u7011\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hcssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u56DE\u6625\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xbhdsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7384\u51B0\u62A4\u76FE\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22683
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"yxssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u71D5\u884C\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22685
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hbcsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5BD2\u51B0\u523A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"nsjxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u51DD\u795E\u9759\u5FC3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xmjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7EED\u547D\u8BC0\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"tjqlssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u592A\u6781\u6E05\u7075\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"ylgxssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5143\u7075\u5F52\u5FC3\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"chncsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6CA7\u6D77\u6012\u6F6E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"cfftsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6625\u98CE\u62C2\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jfssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u75BE\u98CE\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"bhcssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u78A7\u6D77\u6F6E\u751F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22694
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"lhcsssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u83B2\u534E\u51FA\u6C34\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jtcyssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u6D9B\u7A7F\u4E91\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"qlssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u8F7B\u7075\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"jjjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6FC0\u5C06\u8BA1\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"ysjfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7389\u77F3\u4FF1\u711A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22699
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bmjssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u706D\u91D1\u8EAB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22700
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"bbzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u78C5\u7934\u6218\u610F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22701
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"txsfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6311\u8845\u56DB\u65B9\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"ksfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5F00\u5C71\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":22703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzygQQhxmsyjsdcksgydm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u4E00\u4E2AQQ\u53F7\u4E0B\u9762\u6240\u6709\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u662F\u5171\u7528\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":22704
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzjjkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u51E0\u7EA7\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":22705
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzydsgfzy",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":22706
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"zxscdngNPCkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u7684\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":22707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u80FD\u505A\u84DD\u836F\u4E5F\u80FD\u505A\u7EA2\u836F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzfzypddzyssm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u5E96\u4E01\u7684\u4F5C\u7528\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DE\u4F53\u529B\u7684\u84DD\u836F",
		"indexes":"nehss",
		"question":"\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u662F\u5565?",
		"id":22709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u56DE\u590D\u751F\u547D\u7684",
		"indexes":"clhhrysy",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u7EA2\u7EA2\u8089\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":22710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D500\u751F\u547D",
		"indexes":"cljzhhfssmsq",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u997A\u5B50\u540E\u4F1A\u53D1\u751F\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E8B\u60C5?",
		"id":22711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D200\u4F53\u529B",
		"indexes":"hlmrwjhfssmsq",
		"question":"\u559D\u4E86\u7F8E\u9AEF\u6E29\u9152\u4F1A\u53D1\u751F\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E8B\u60C5?",
		"id":22712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E78\u8FD0\u5408\u6210\u6216\u8005\u4F7F\u7528\u521D\u7EA7\u9505",
		"indexes":"y5gjdkyscc10gzjdm",
		"question":"\u75285\u4E2A\u9E21\u86CB\u53EF\u4EE5\u751F\u4EA7\u51FA10\u4E2A\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u5417?",
		"id":22713
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5373\u65F6\u56DE\u590D300\u751F\u547D",
		"indexes":"clzjddhgs",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u7684\u540E\u679C\u662F?",
		"id":22714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7259\u7B7E\u6ED1\u9C7C\u548C\u95EA\u907F\u4E4B\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhhzjhb",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u4F1A\u589E\u52A0\u56DE\u907F?",
		"id":22715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjntgtldhfsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F53\u529B\u7684\u6062\u590D\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":22716
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjntgsmdhfsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u63D0\u9AD8\u751F\u547D\u7684\u6062\u590D\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":22717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4E50\u9E21\u7FC5\u548C\u4E00\u98DE\u51B2\u5929",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjnzjyddsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u589E\u52A0\u79FB\u52A8\u7684\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":22718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u521B\u836F\u548C\u53CC\u9EC4\u86CB\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"yxffnzkykshfsm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u54EA\u79CD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u56DE\u590D\u751F\u547D?",
		"id":22719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u5FC3\u9732\u548C\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"yxffnzkykshftl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u54EA\u79CD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u56DE\u590D\u4F53\u529B?",
		"id":22720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ED920\u7EA7\u4EE5\u524D\u7684\u88C5\u5907\u6253\u5B54\u7684",
		"indexes":"ejqqzs",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u7EA7\u5D4C\u5668\u4E4B\u77F3",
		"id":22721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u6700\u5927\u751F\u547D\u7684",
		"indexes":"zjxqzyysy",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u7EA7\u8840\u6C14\u4E4B\u7389\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":22722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F31\u6548\u5316\u4F24\u4E3A\u4F53\u7389",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkyjsddshzhwtl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u5C06\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\u8F6C\u5316\u4E3A\u4F53\u529B?",
		"id":22723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8346\u68D8\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkyjsddshfdjgjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u5C06\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\u53CD\u5F39\u7ED9\u653B\u51FB\u8005?",
		"id":22724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F85\u52A9\u6279\u91CF\u751F\u4EA7\u7537\u513F\u9ED1\u7684",
		"indexes":"cjjhysy",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9152\u58F6\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":22725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkytghbl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u4F9B\u56DE\u907F\u7387?",
		"id":22726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B21\u7EA7\u8840\u6C14\u4E4B\u7389",
		"indexes":"yxsmwpkyyjtgndsmzdz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u6C38\u4E45\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F60\u7684\u751F\u547D\u6700\u5927\u503C?",
		"id":22728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u529B\u6C34\u6676",
		"indexes":"yxsmwpkyyjtgndtlzdz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u6C38\u4E45\u63D0\u9AD8\u4F60\u7684\u4F53\u529B\u6700\u5927\u503C?",
		"id":22729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FEE\u590D\u6C34\u6676\u548C\u4FEE\u590D\u77F3\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"rhxlshddj",
		"question":"\u5982\u4F55\u4FEE\u7406\u635F\u574F\u7684\u9053\u5177?",
		"id":22730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C060~3\u7EA7\u522B\u88C5\u5907\u5F3A\u5316",
		"indexes":"xpqhsysy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u54C1\u5F3A\u5316\u77F3\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":22731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F85\u52A9\u6279\u91CF\u751F\u4EA7\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u7684",
		"indexes":"cjgysy",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9505\u6709\u5565\u7528?",
		"id":22732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u884C\u77F3",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzrgxzxqsyxngstydsdhkyx",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u5982\u679C\u978B\u5B50\u9576\u5D4C\u4E0A\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u77F3\u5934,\u79FB\u52A8\u901F\u5EA6\u4F1A\u5FEB\u4E00\u4E9B?",
		"id":22733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkytgydsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u9AD8\u79FB\u52A8\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":22734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"cjxlbssngfzyscd",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u4FEE\u7406\u5B9D\u77F3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7684?",
		"id":22735
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zbqhysmxg",
		"question":"\u88C5\u5907\u5F3A\u5316\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u6548\u679C?",
		"id":22736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"cjgsngfzyscd",
		"question":"\u521D\u7EA7\u9505\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u751F\u4EA7\u7684?",
		"id":22737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"hjfbtgngNPCkyj",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u901A\u8FC7\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u8FDB?",
		"id":22738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u66FC",
		"indexes":"hjfbdygdBOSSjsmz",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u7B2C\u4E00\u5173\u7684BOSS\u53EB\u5565\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":22739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"nqhjfbswls",
		"question":"\u4F60\u53BB\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u5565?",
		"id":22740
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"hjfbdsjyskyj",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u4EE5\u4E0A\u53EF\u4EE5\u8FDB?",
		"id":22741
	},
	{
		"answer":"20",
		"indexes":"dsjbyskystd",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u4EE5\u4E0A\u53EF\u4EE5\u6536\u5F92\u5F1F?",
		"id":22742
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"dsjbyxcnbs",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u624D\u80FD\u62DC\u5E08?",
		"id":22743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"styqzdljyshc",
		"question":"\u5E08\u5F92\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7,\u6709\u5565\u597D\u5904?",
		"id":22744
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"tddsjbcs",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u51FA\u5E08?",
		"id":22745
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"tdcshhsfyqzdljyhcm",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u51FA\u5E08\u540E,\u548C\u5E08\u5085\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7\u6709\u597D\u5904\u5417?",
		"id":22746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"tdmcshsfyqzdljyxnxsdd",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u6CA1\u51FA\u5E08,\u548C\u5E08\u5085\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7,\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u5BF9\u7684?",
		"id":22747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6740\u795E\u548C\u5982\u610F\u90FD\u80FD\u6362\u5230",
		"indexes":"xszdzysmy",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u7528?",
		"id":22748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E08\u7F18\u9690\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xszdzszxscnldhwp",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u4E66\u5728\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u54EA\u91CC\u5151\u6362\u7269\u54C1?",
		"id":22749
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"ygdwlzdkyydsr",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u961F\u4F0D\u91CC\u6700\u591A\u53EF\u4EE5\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA?",
		"id":22750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zdhdzkygbm",
		"question":"\u7EC4\u961F\u540E\u961F\u957F\u53EF\u4EE5\u6539\u53D8\u5417?",
		"id":22751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F8\u540C\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u83B7\u5F97\u66F4\u591A\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u503C",
		"indexes":"rgdjdbtljbcbddrzdyqljysmhc",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u5927\u5BB6\u90FD\u4E0D\u5077\u61D2,\u7EA7\u522B\u5DEE\u4E0D\u591A\u7684\u4EBA\u7EC4\u961F\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC3\u7EA7\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u597D\u5904?",
		"id":22752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"zddrsfztyzdtcnfxjy",
		"question":"\u7EC4\u961F\u7684\u4EBA\u662F\u5426\u5728\u540C\u4E00\u5F20\u5730\u56FE\u624D\u80FD\u5206\u4EAB\u7ECF\u9A8C?",
		"id":22753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"kytsjdgrwm",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u540C\u65F6\u63A5\u591A\u4E2A\u4EFB\u52A1\u5417?",
		"id":22754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"gjrwkydczfzm",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u53EF\u4EE5\u591A\u6B21\u91CD\u590D\u505A\u5417?",
		"id":22755
	},
	{
		"answer":"BOSS\u6765\u7684,\u5237\u65B0\u65F6\u95F4\u6709\u70B9\u957F",
		"indexes":"sgxscpbdgwxmzwsmjczbd",
		"question":"\u8700\u56FD\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u602A\u7269\u5C0F\u86EE\u732A\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u7ECF\u5E38\u627E\u4E0D\u5230?",
		"id":22756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u94B1\u548C\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u6750\u6599",
		"indexes":"zgjrwknhddsmjl",
		"question":"\u505A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u53EF\u80FD\u4F1A\u5F97\u5230\u4EC0\u4E48\u5956\u52B1?",
		"id":22757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u4E66\u4E1E",
		"indexes":"dnljgjrw",
		"question":"\u5230\u54EA\u91CC\u63A5\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":22758
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"gjrwybydsb",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u4E00\u822C\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6B65?",
		"id":22759
	},
	{
		"answer":"20\u5206\u949F",
		"indexes":"xscpbdxBOSSdzsjsxyc",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u5C0FBOSS\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\u5237\u65B0\u4E00\u6B21?",
		"id":22760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zdgjdgwhbdgjdgwysbt",
		"question":"\u4E3B\u52A8\u653B\u51FB\u7684\u602A\u7269\u548C\u88AB\u52A8\u653B\u51FB\u7684\u602A\u7269\u6709\u5565\u4E0D\u540C?",
		"id":22761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BF9",
		"indexes":"bmxdjmjxjsrddbchbnmjqtNPCdhddm",
		"question":"\u628A\u67D0\u4E9B\u9053\u5177\u5356\u7ED9\u884C\u811A\u5546\u4EBA,\u5F97\u5230\u62A5\u916C\u4F1A\u6BD4\u4F60\u5356\u7ED9\u5176\u5B83NPC\u591A\u5F88\u591A,\u5BF9\u5417?",
		"id":22762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u6BD4\u5B83\u9AD8",
		"indexes":"rggwdmzslsdsmnhtddj",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u602A\u7269\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\u7EFF\u8272\u7684,\u8BF4\u660E\u4F60\u548C\u4ED6\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7",
		"id":22763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934\u4E0A\u6709\u9EC4\u8272\u7684\u611F\u53F9\u53F7\u5728\u95EA\u70C1\u7684",
		"indexes":"znxNPCkyjxrw",
		"question":"\u627E\u54EA\u4E9BNPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u65B0\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":22764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u6709\u4EFB\u52A1\u6CA1\u505A\u5B8C,\u9700\u8981\u548C\u4ED6\u5BF9\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"NPCdtsdzygwhssysy",
		"question":"NPC\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A\u95EE\u53F7\u662F\u5565\u610F\u601D\u5440?",
		"id":22765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u518D\u5347\u7EA7\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u65B0\u4EFB\u52A1\u4E86",
		"indexes":"NPCdtsdzyghsdgthssysy",
		"question":"NPC\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A\u7070\u8272\u7684\u611F\u53F9\u53F7\u662F\u5565\u610F\u601D\u5440?",
		"id":22766
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"dsjbkycjjt",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u53EF\u4EE5\u521B\u5EFA\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":22767
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"dsjbkyjrjt",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u53EF\u4EE5\u52A0\u5165\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":22768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u519B\u56E2\u7BA1\u7406\u4E13\u5458",
		"indexes":"zngNPCkycjjt",
		"question":"\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u521B\u5EFA\u519B\u56E2?",
		"id":22769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u6837\u5427",
		"indexes":"jtcyzddgdddjyhbfjtcydgdddjydm",
		"question":"\u519B\u56E2\u6210\u5458\u7EC4\u961F\u6253\u602A\u5F97\u5230\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4F1A\u6BD4\u975E\u519B\u56E2\u6210\u5458\u6253\u602A\u5F97\u5230\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u591A\u5417?",
		"id":22770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"rgnjrlygjtjyy",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u52A0\u5165\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u519B\u56E2,\u5C06\u62E5\u6709:",
		"id":22771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u5E38\u5728\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u8BF4\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzyggsxfdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u704C\u6C34\u5148\u950B'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":22772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u7ECF\u5E38\u751F\u4EA7\u8865\u84DD\/\u7EA2\u7684\u836F",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzhssdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u4E2D\u534E\u98DF\u795E'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":22773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320\u505A\u591A\u4E86",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzzdsdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u94F8\u9020\u5927\u5E08'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":22774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9576\u5D4C\u505A\u591A\u4E86",
		"indexes":"yxrdtsdzygzqdsdchzmldy",
		"question":"\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u5934\u4E0A\u9876\u7740\u4E00\u4E2A'\u5236\u5668\u5927\u5E08'\u7684\u79F0\u53F7,\u600E\u4E48\u6765\u7684\u5440?",
		"id":22775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zyhNPCdh",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u548CNPC\u5BF9\u8BDD?",
		"id":22776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u6750\u6599\u548C\u9AD8\u7EA7\u5408\u6210\u4E66",
		"indexes":"xtbdshhdsmwp",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u5077\u88AB\u6253\u6B7B\u540E,\u4F1A\u6389\u4EC0\u4E48\u7269\u54C1?",
		"id":22777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u9675\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u5C0F\u5077",
		"indexes":"zykndzjgjsdgws",
		"question":"\u6700\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u6389\u4E2D\u7EA7\u5DE5\u5320\u4E66\u7684\u602A\u7269\u662F?",
		"id":22778
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C5F\u9675\u9644\u8FD1\u7684\u5C0F\u5077",
		"indexes":"zykndzjxgsdgws",
		"question":"\u6700\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u6389\u4E2D\u7EA7\u9576\u5DE5\u4E66\u7684\u602A\u7269\u662F?",
		"id":22779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"wsmyxfzydszgssrnlmbd",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u4E9B\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u4E66\u5728\u53E4\u4E66\u5546\u4EBA\u90A3\u91CC\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230?",
		"id":22780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79C1\u804A",
		"indexes":"yxnzfskysxnhlygwjydydlt",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5B9E\u73B0\u4F60\u548C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u73A9\u5BB6\u4E00\u5BF9\u4E00\u5730\u804A\u5929?",
		"id":22781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zwgsygjpdshwgkykjm",
		"question":"\u5728\u9B4F\u56FD\u4F7F\u7528\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u8BF4\u8BDD,\u5434\u56FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u89C1\u5417?",
		"id":22783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u5587\u53ED",
		"indexes":"nsdhrgxyqfwqdsggjdntdygsy",
		"question":"\u4F60\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD\u5982\u679C\u60F3\u8981\u5168\u670D\u52A1\u5668\u7684\u4E09\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u90FD\u80FD\u542C\u5230,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4F7F\u7528?",
		"id":22784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zmhlygwjsl",
		"question":"\u600E\u4E48\u548C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u73A9\u5BB6\u79C1\u804A?",
		"id":22785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"cwhyhysmhc",
		"question":"\u6210\u4E3A\u597D\u53CB\u540E\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u597D\u5904?",
		"id":22786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66",
		"indexes":"rgycygcsdlygcszkdffs",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u8981\u4ECE\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u5230\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02,\u6700\u5FEB\u7684\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F?",
		"id":22787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u627E\u57CE\u5E02\u91CC\u7684\u9A7F\u7AD9\u9A6C\u592B\u548C\u4ED6\u5BF9\u8BDD",
		"indexes":"zmzmcy",
		"question":"\u600E\u4E48\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66\u5440?",
		"id":22788
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"hmdrkyzmcm",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u540D\u7684\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66\u5417?",
		"id":22789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"zxhdzjdygcsyxffkx",
		"question":"\u5728\u60F3\u56DE\u5230\u6700\u8FD1\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02,\u4EE5\u4E0B\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u884C?",
		"id":22790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51CF\u5C11QQ\u53F7\u88AB\u76D7\u540E\u4F60\u7684\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u635F\u5931",
		"indexes":"cjjsdshszmmsgmyd",
		"question":"\u521B\u5EFA\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u65F6\u5019\u8BBE\u7F6E\u5BC6\u7801\u662F\u5E72\u561B\u7528\u7684?",
		"id":22791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zyjzjdydwpdjmcqzq",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u5C06\u81EA\u5DF1\u591A\u4F59\u7684\u7269\u54C1\u9053\u5177\u5356\u51FA\u53BB\u8D5A\u94B1?",
		"id":22792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u53BB\u6253\u602A",
		"indexes":"btdrky",
		"question":"\u6446\u644A\u7684\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5:",
		"id":22793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"btdtwydsg",
		"question":"\u6446\u644A\u7684\u644A\u4F4D\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u683C?",
		"id":22794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u4ED6\u7B54\u6848\u90FD\u662F",
		"indexes":"rgnzydzkssjsbdzjhcxsmxx",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u5728\u79FB\u52A8\u4E2D\u5FEB\u901F\u53CC\u51FB\u9F20\u6807\u7684\u5DE6\u952E,\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u4EC0\u4E48\u73B0\u8C61?",
		"id":22795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51FA\u73B0\u547D\u4EE4\u9009\u5355",
		"indexes":"rgzwjtxsdjsbyjhcxsmxx",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u5728\u73A9\u5BB6\u5934\u50CF\u4E0A\u70B9\u51FB\u9F20\u6807\u53F3\u952E,\u4F1A\u51FA\u73B0\u4EC0\u4E48\u73B0\u8C61?",
		"id":22796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BF9",
		"indexes":"zycwndhyncnfxjjtdm",
		"question":"\u53EA\u6709\u6210\u4E3A\u4F60\u7684\u597D\u53CB,\u4F60\u624D\u80FD\u53D1\u4FE1\u4EF6\u7ED9\u4ED6,\u5BF9\u5417?",
		"id":22797
	},
	{
		"answer":"50",
		"indexes":"ygjsdyxzdnrndsfyj",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u90AE\u7BB1\u6700\u591A\u80FD\u5BB9\u7EB3\u591A\u5C11\u5C01\u90AE\u4EF6?",
		"id":22798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u4F7F\u7528\u4E86\u79C1\u4EBA\u4ED3\u5E93\u9053\u5177",
		"indexes":"wsmyxrdckbwdrld",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u6BD4\u6211\u7684\u5BB9\u91CF\u5927?",
		"id":22799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"btcyxkyhdtyqdlytxm",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u9000\u51FA\u6E38\u620F,\u53EF\u4EE5\u6362\u5230\u540C\u4E00\u533A\u7684\u53E6\u4E00\u6761\u7EBF\u5417?",
		"id":22800
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"rgwyjAjszwqtdjngjkym",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u6211\u8981\u5C06A\u952E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u4E3A\u5176\u5B83\u7684\u6280\u80FD\u653B\u51FB,\u53EF\u4EE5\u5417?",
		"id":22801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u5728\u7CFB\u7EDF\u8BBE\u7F6E\u4E86\u81EA\u52A8\u653B\u51FB",
		"indexes":"wsmyshwdgdyxhwbajpwdkyjxdzgg",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u65F6\u5019\u6211\u6253\u602A\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E0B\u540E\u6211\u4E0D\u6309\u952E\u76D8\u6211\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u7EE7\u7EED\u6253\u8FD9\u4E2A\u602A?",
		"id":22802
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E1F\u5C71\u660E",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22803
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624B\u51A2\u6CBB\u866B",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22804
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BAB\u5D0E\u9A8F",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22805
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D8A\u7530\u54F2\u5F18",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22806
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB8\u672C\u9F50\u53F2",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22807
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C3E\u7530\u8363\u4E00\u90CE",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22808
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6761\u82F1\u673A",
		"indexes":"yxsyrbezjjzfds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65E5\u672C\u4E8C\u6218\u7532\u7EA7\u6218\u72AF\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22809
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6A31\u6728\u82B1\u9053",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhglgszdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u704C\u7BEE\u9AD8\u624B\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22810
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D41\u5DDD\u67AB",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhglgszdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u704C\u7BEE\u9AD8\u624B\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22811
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E1F\u5C71\u660E",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhlzdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u9F99\u73E0\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22812
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u85E4\u5B50F\u4E0D\u4E8C\u96C4",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhdlAmdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u54C6\u5566A\u68A6\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22813
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624B\u51A2\u6CBB\u866B",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhtbatmdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u94C1\u81C2\u963F\u7AE5\u6728\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22814
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB8\u672C\u9F50\u53F2",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhhyrzdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u706B\u5F71\u5FCD\u8005\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22815
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C71\u521A\u660C",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhmztkndzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u300A\u540D\u4FA6\u63A2\u67EF\u5357\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22816
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"yxnwssgyydzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22817
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65BD\u8010\u5EB5",
		"indexes":"yxnwsshcdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u6C34\u6D52\u4F20\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22818
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u96EA\u82B9",
		"indexes":"yxnwshlmdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22819
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434\u627F\u6069",
		"indexes":"yxnwsxyjdzz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u300A\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005?",
		"id":22820
	},
	{
		"answer":"58",
		"indexes":"562",
		"question":"56+2=?",
		"id":22821
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"14",
		"question":"1+4=?",
		"id":22822
	},
	{
		"answer":"40",
		"indexes":"346",
		"question":"34+6=?",
		"id":22823
	},
	{
		"answer":"21",
		"indexes":"174",
		"question":"17+4=?",
		"id":22824
	},
	{
		"answer":"23",
		"indexes":"176",
		"question":"17+6=?",
		"id":22825
	},
	{
		"answer":"110",
		"indexes":"4565",
		"question":"45+65=?",
		"id":22826
	},
	{
		"answer":"119",
		"indexes":"9623",
		"question":"96+23=?",
		"id":22827
	},
	{
		"answer":"124",
		"indexes":"6262",
		"question":"62+62=?",
		"id":22828
	},
	{
		"answer":"118",
		"indexes":"5959",
		"question":"59+59=?",
		"id":22829
	},
	{
		"answer":"198",
		"indexes":"9999",
		"question":"99+99=?",
		"id":22830
	},
	{
		"answer":"111",
		"indexes":"5259",
		"question":"52+59=?",
		"id":22831
	},
	{
		"answer":"121",
		"indexes":"6259",
		"question":"62+59=?",
		"id":22832
	},
	{
		"answer":"161",
		"indexes":"6299",
		"question":"62+99=?",
		"id":22833
	},
	{
		"answer":"158",
		"indexes":"5999",
		"question":"59+99=?",
		"id":22834
	},
	{
		"answer":"81",
		"indexes":"6219",
		"question":"62+19=?",
		"id":22835
	},
	{
		"answer":"115",
		"indexes":"9916",
		"question":"99+16=?",
		"id":22836
	},
	{
		"answer":"75",
		"indexes":"5916",
		"question":"59+16=?",
		"id":22837
	},
	{
		"answer":"77",
		"indexes":"3443",
		"question":"34+43=?",
		"id":22838
	},
	{
		"answer":"27",
		"indexes":"252",
		"question":"25+2=?",
		"id":22839
	},
	{
		"answer":"92",
		"indexes":"6725",
		"question":"67+25=?",
		"id":22840
	},
	{
		"answer":"69",
		"indexes":"672",
		"question":"67+2=?",
		"id":22841
	},
	{
		"answer":"90",
		"indexes":"6228",
		"question":"62+28=?",
		"id":22842
	},
	{
		"answer":"95",
		"indexes":"6728",
		"question":"67+28=?",
		"id":22843
	},
	{
		"answer":"97",
		"indexes":"6730",
		"question":"67+30=?",
		"id":22844
	},
	{
		"answer":"398",
		"indexes":"215183",
		"question":"215+183=?",
		"id":22845
	},
	{
		"answer":"53",
		"indexes":"2528",
		"question":"25+28=?",
		"id":22846
	},
	{
		"answer":"30",
		"indexes":"228",
		"question":"2+28=?",
		"id":22847
	},
	{
		"answer":"32",
		"indexes":"230",
		"question":"2+30=?",
		"id":22848
	},
	{
		"answer":"61",
		"indexes":"3031",
		"question":"30+31=?",
		"id":22849
	},
	{
		"answer":"53",
		"indexes":"2528",
		"question":"25+28=?",
		"id":22850
	},
	{
		"answer":"55",
		"indexes":"2530",
		"question":"25+30=?",
		"id":22851
	},
	{
		"answer":"54",
		"indexes":"2430",
		"question":"24+30=?",
		"id":22852
	},
	{
		"answer":"56",
		"indexes":"2531",
		"question":"25+31=?",
		"id":22853
	},
	{
		"answer":"217",
		"indexes":"2152",
		"question":"215+2=?",
		"id":22854
	},
	{
		"answer":"519",
		"indexes":"215304",
		"question":"215+304=?",
		"id":22855
	},
	{
		"answer":"36",
		"indexes":"342",
		"question":"34+2=?",
		"id":22856
	},
	{
		"answer":"41",
		"indexes":"347",
		"question":"34+7=?",
		"id":22857
	},
	{
		"answer":"42",
		"indexes":"348",
		"question":"34+8=?",
		"id":22858
	},
	{
		"answer":"39",
		"indexes":"345",
		"question":"34+5=?",
		"id":22859
	},
	{
		"answer":"119",
		"indexes":"3485",
		"question":"34+85=?",
		"id":22860
	},
	{
		"answer":"98",
		"indexes":"8513",
		"question":"85+13=?",
		"id":22861
	},
	{
		"answer":"86",
		"indexes":"851",
		"question":"85+1=?",
		"id":22862
	},
	{
		"answer":"87",
		"indexes":"852",
		"question":"85+2=?",
		"id":22863
	},
	{
		"answer":"88",
		"indexes":"853",
		"question":"85+3=?",
		"id":22864
	},
	{
		"answer":"89",
		"indexes":"863",
		"question":"86+3=?",
		"id":22865
	},
	{
		"answer":"88",
		"indexes":"4939",
		"question":"49+39=?",
		"id":22866
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"29",
		"question":"2+9=?",
		"id":22867
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u6276\u6797",
		"indexes":"87bdsjhlmddys",
		"question":"87\u7248\u7535\u89C6\u5267\u300A\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u300B\u7684\u5BFC\u6F14\u662F?",
		"id":22868
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u6276\u6797",
		"indexes":"94bdsjsgyyddys",
		"question":"94\u7248\u7535\u89C6\u5267\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u7684\u5BFC\u6F14\u662F?",
		"id":22869
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"xslsmjsdsygfsznggjdgs",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u7F57\u751F\u95E8\u300B\u8BB2\u8FF0\u7684\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u6545\u4E8B?",
		"id":22870
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u8FC7",
		"indexes":"xssdxldnzjss",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u795E\u96D5\u4FA0\u4FA3\u300B\u7684\u7537\u4E3B\u89D2\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":22871
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5143\u76DB\u4E16",
		"indexes":"yxnglssjbsfszhd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6C49\u4EE3?",
		"id":22872
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E26\u7247\u6218\u4E89",
		"indexes":"yxnglssjbsfsztd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5510\u4EE3?",
		"id":22873
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u53F2\u4E4B\u4E71",
		"indexes":"yxnglssjsfsztd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u5510\u4EE3?",
		"id":22874
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D1B\u9633",
		"indexes":"xjdddzngcs",
		"question":"\u897F\u664B\u7684\u5B9A\u90FD\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":22875
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EFA\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"djdddzngcs",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u664B\u7684\u5B9A\u90FD\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":22876
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F01\u9E45",
		"indexes":"nzdwshznj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u5357\u6781?",
		"id":22877
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"nwslshh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6881\u5C71\u597D\u6C49?",
		"id":22878
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F58\u592A\u541B",
		"indexes":"nwsyjjzdrw",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6768\u5BB6\u5C06\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22879
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8336\u9986",
		"indexes":"nbxsslsdmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u90E8\u5C0F\u8BF4\u662F\u8001\u820D\u7684\u540D\u8457?",
		"id":22880
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u660E\u8282",
		"indexes":"ngjrszgctjr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u8282\u65E5\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u65E5?",
		"id":22881
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u610F\u5927\u5229",
		"indexes":"nggjcyoz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u6B27\u6D32?",
		"id":22882
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"nggjcyyz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u4E9A\u6D32?",
		"id":22883
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u6839\u5EF7",
		"indexes":"nggjcynmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u5357\u7F8E\u6D32?",
		"id":22884
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58A8\u897F\u54E5",
		"indexes":"nggjcybmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u4E8E\u5317\u7F8E\u6D32?",
		"id":22885
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5580\u9EA6\u9686",
		"indexes":"nggjcfz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u5904\u975E\u6D32?",
		"id":22886
	},
	{
		"answer":"7\u5143",
		"indexes":"rmbdmzmynyx",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u7684\u9762\u503C\u6CA1\u6709\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":22887
	},
	{
		"answer":"200\u5143",
		"indexes":"rmbdmzmynyx",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u7684\u9762\u503C\u6CA1\u6709\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":22888
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68B5\u8482\u5188",
		"indexes":"sjszxdgjs",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u662F?",
		"id":22889
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u575B",
		"indexes":"ngsbjgjz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5317\u4EAC\u53E4\u5EFA\u7B51?",
		"id":22890
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6F58\u5E15\u65AF\u9AD8\u539F",
		"indexes":"nggywynmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u9AD8\u539F\u4F4D\u4E8E\u5357\u7F8E\u6D32?",
		"id":22891
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u975E\u9AD8\u539F",
		"indexes":"nggywyfz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u9AD8\u539F\u4F4D\u4E8E\u975E\u6D32?",
		"id":22892
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5185\u8499\u53E4",
		"indexes":"ngsszgzzqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u81EA\u6CBB\u533A\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":22893
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95EA\u7C73\u7279\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22894
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u5C14\u66FC",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22895
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76CE\u683C\u9C81-\u6492\u514B\u900A\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22896
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51EF\u5C14\u7279\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22897
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22898
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u9053\u6218",
		"indexes":"nybsygkrzzdrwgshyp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6709\u5173\u6297\u65E5\u6218\u4E89\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\u6545\u4E8B\u6216\u5F71\u7247?",
		"id":22899
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EA5\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"yxnwsqchd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6E05\u671D\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":22900
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u7531\u68C0",
		"indexes":"xlnwsmchd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u660E\u671D\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":22901
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u672C",
		"indexes":"xlnggjcjgbgljhsymy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u53C2\u52A0\u8FC7\u516B\u56FD\u8054\u519B,\u706B\u70E7\u5706\u660E\u56ED?",
		"id":22902
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F17",
		"indexes":"ngzsypzxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u54C1\u5B57\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22903
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u838E",
		"indexes":"ngzsysxxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22904
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60EB",
		"indexes":"ngzsyszxxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E2D\u4E0B\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22905
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73AF",
		"indexes":"ngzsyzyxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22906
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FA9",
		"indexes":"ngzsyzzyxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u4E2D\u53F3\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22907
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngzsyqbwxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5168\u5305\u56F4\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22908
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81E3",
		"indexes":"ngzsybbwxjgd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B57\u5C5E\u4E8E\u534A\u5305\u56F4\u5F62\u7ED3\u6784\u7684?",
		"id":22909
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51B2",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssbd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u51AB\u7684?",
		"id":22910
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E38",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbsssd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u6C35\u7684?",
		"id":22911
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BE0",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssyd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u8BA0\u7684?",
		"id":22912
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u948A",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssdd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5202\u7684?",
		"id":22913
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E42",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssmd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5196\u7684?",
		"id":22914
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssm",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5B80?",
		"id":22915
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u7389\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22916
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5CA9\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22917
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"zzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E2D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22918
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"xzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5B66\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22919
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"qzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E03\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22920
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FAF",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssrd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u4EBB\u7684?",
		"id":22921
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"zzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u6731\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22922
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"lzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E3D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22923
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u838E\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22924
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"yzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u7531\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22925
	},
	{
		"answer":"11",
		"indexes":"jzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u68C0\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":22926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u667A\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"yxngbssgyyzcxgdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u51FA\u73B0\u8FC7\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22927
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u677E",
		"indexes":"yxngbssgyyzcxgdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u51FA\u73B0\u8FC7\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22928
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5DE2",
		"indexes":"yxngbssgyyzcxgdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u51FA\u73B0\u8FC7\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A0B\u98A2",
		"indexes":"yxngbssgyyzcxgdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u51FA\u73B0\u8FC7\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":22930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u97F3\u653E\u9001",
		"indexes":"yxngsfszdecsjdzzdsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":22931
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BFA\u66FC\u5E95\u767B\u9646",
		"indexes":"yxngsfszdecsjdzzdsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":22932
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u6C38",
		"indexes":"yxngbshchd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":22934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u71B9",
		"indexes":"yxngbsmchd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u660E\u671D\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":22935
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u4E2D\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yxnwtdlzgzcjjgmdfz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u63A8\u52A8\u4E86\u4E2D\u56FD\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u7684\u53D1\u5C55?",
		"id":22936
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u5143\u57F9",
		"indexes":"yxnwtcljrbbddxjysx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u63D0\u51FA\u4E86\u201C\u517C\u5BB9\u5E76\u5305\u201D\u7684\u5927\u5B66\u6559\u80B2\u601D\u60F3?",
		"id":22937
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u56FD\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"rjchsxmnwdsdzp",
		"question":"\u300A\u4EBA\u95F4\u8BCD\u8BDD\u300B\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5927\u5E08\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22938
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u6D77",
		"indexes":"qhhzwgngsjn",
		"question":"\u9752\u6D77\u6E56\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E56\u5317",
		"indexes":"qhzssdwgngsdbc",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u6E56\u4E4B\u7701\u201D\u662F\u5BF9\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u7684\u522B\u79F0?",
		"id":22940
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"scsjdccpdkthzs",
		"question":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u7701\u673A\u52A8\u8F66\u8F66\u724C\u7684\u5F00\u5934\u6C49\u5B57\u662F?",
		"id":22941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9102",
		"indexes":"hbsjdccpdkthzs",
		"question":"\u6E56\u5317\u7701\u673A\u52A8\u8F66\u8F66\u724C\u7684\u5F00\u5934\u6C49\u5B57\u662F?",
		"id":22942
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81",
		"indexes":"sdsjdccpdkthzs",
		"question":"\u5C71\u4E1C\u7701\u673A\u52A8\u8F66\u8F66\u724C\u7684\u5F00\u5934\u6C49\u5B57\u662F?",
		"id":22943
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E1D\u8F9B",
		"indexes":"yxnwbszcdjw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5468\u671D\u7684\u541B\u738B?",
		"id":22944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u536B\u5E84\u516C",
		"indexes":"yzsjyxnwjzbscqwb",
		"question":"\u4F9D\u7167\u300A\u53F2\u8BB0\u300B,\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u541B\u4E3B\u4E0D\u662F\u6625\u79CB\u4E94\u9738?",
		"id":22945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u536B",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbszgqx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4?",
		"id":22946
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbszgqx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4?",
		"id":22947
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5434",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbszgqx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u6218\u56FD\u4E03\u96C4?",
		"id":22948
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5FF5\u5974\u5A07\u00B7\u8D64\u58C1\u6000\u53E4\u300B",
		"indexes":"djdqltjqgflrwsczyxngzpldmj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u6C5F\u4E1C\u53BB,\u6D6A\u6DD8\u5C3D,\u5343\u53E4\u98CE\u6D41\u4EBA\u7269\u201D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4F5C\u54C1\u91CC\u7684\u540D\u53E5?",
		"id":22949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8F7C",
		"indexes":"djdqltjqgflrwsczyxnwwhbx",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u6C5F\u4E1C\u53BB,\u6D6A\u6DD8\u5C3D,\u5343\u53E4\u98CE\u6D41\u4EBA\u7269\u201D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u6587\u8C6A\u7B14\u4E0B?",
		"id":22950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8D64\u58C1\u300B",
		"indexes":"zjcstwxczyxyxngzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u6298\u621F\u6C89\u6C99\u94C1\u672A\u9500\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":22951
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u7267",
		"indexes":"zjcstwxczyxyxnwwhdzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u6298\u621F\u6C89\u6C99\u94C1\u672A\u9500\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u6587\u8C6A\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1??",
		"id":22952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5411\u524D",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywsxzgsqdsdys",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u65B0\u4E2D\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5341\u5927\u5143\u5E05?",
		"id":22953
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5937\u9675\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnycswggddzy",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u573A\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":22954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73\u82BE",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddhj",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u753B\u5BB6?",
		"id":22955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddsr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":22956
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D3E\u8C0A",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywswggddwc",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u7684\u6587\u81E3?",
		"id":22957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672D\u5E4C",
		"indexes":"qzcxmnyzsrbdcs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u65E5\u672C\u7684\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":22958
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u76DB\u987F\u54E5\u4F26\u6BD4\u4E9A\u7279\u533A",
		"indexes":"qzcyxngsmgsd",
		"question":"\u6E05\u6307\u51FA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7F8E\u56FD\u9996\u90FD?",
		"id":22959
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66FC\u8C37",
		"indexes":"qzcyxngstgcs",
		"question":"\u6E05\u6307\u51FA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CF0\u56FD\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":22960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u8FC8",
		"indexes":"qzcyxngstgcs",
		"question":"\u6E05\u6307\u51FA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6CF0\u56FD\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":22961
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49",
		"indexes":"ytyhjsjyzhjyxslgsxmnggdxszddyh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5BB4\u6843\u56ED\u8C6A\u6770\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49,\u65A9\u9EC4\u5DFE\u82F1\u96C4\u9996\u7ACB\u529F\u201D\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u53E4\u5178\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u56DE?",
		"id":22962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DA\u660E",
		"indexes":"yxnwzgydycxlmgzylmzdxsdhjd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E2D\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u66FE\u6548\u529B\u7F8E\u56FD\u804C\u4E1A\u8054\u76DF\u4E2D\u7684\u4F11\u65AF\u987F\u706B\u7BAD\u961F?",
		"id":22963
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8E\u7981",
		"indexes":"xmnwzsyqjdgszbgyfh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5728\u201C\u6C34\u6DF9\u4E03\u519B\u201D\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u4E2D\u88AB\u5173\u7FBD\u4FD8\u83B7?",
		"id":22964
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"yryhsjdssyxysdzdgs",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u6768\u4FEE\u4E0E\u8C01\u6597\u667A\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":22965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u664B",
		"indexes":"sgsdjshswglssdngcd",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u4EE3\u7ED3\u675F\u540E\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3?",
		"id":22966
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"csbssszjlsd",
		"question":"\u300A\u51FA\u5E08\u8868\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u4E0A\u594F\u7ED9\u5218\u7985\u7684?",
		"id":22967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"csbsszglszjsd",
		"question":"\u300A\u51FA\u5E08\u8868\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0A\u594F\u7ED9\u8C01\u7684?",
		"id":22968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"lbwldcsls",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u4E3A\u4E86\u8C82\u8749\u6740\u4E86\u8C01?",
		"id":22969
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u614E",
		"indexes":"sgyypscssxd",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u7BC7\u9996\u8BCD\u662F\u8C01\u5199\u7684?",
		"id":22970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B",
		"indexes":"sjcswjsxszsyxlmjcznwsrbx",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u53E5\u201C\u51FA\u5E08\u672A\u6377\u8EAB\u5148\u6B7B,\u957F\u4F7F\u82F1\u96C4\u6CEA\u6EE1\u895F\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u7B14\u4E0B?",
		"id":22971
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B",
		"indexes":"sgbztczyxnwsrzs",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u6B4C\u300A\u516B\u9635\u56FE\u300B\u51FA\u81EA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u4E4B\u624B?",
		"id":22972
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u5904\u671B\u795E\u5DDE,\u6EE1\u773C\u98CE\u5149\u5317\u56FA\u697C?",
		"indexes":"xqjnxzdjkbgtyhsqdyjs",
		"question":"\u8F9B\u5F03\u75BE\u300A\u5357\u4E61\u5B50\u00B7\u767B\u4EAC\u53E3\u5317\u56FA\u4EAD\u6709\u6000\u300B\u4E0A\u9619\u7B2C\u4E00\u53E5\u662F?",
		"id":22973
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u826F",
		"indexes":"mjwcbmzlzbmzds",
		"question":"\u201C\u9A6C\u5BB6\u4E94\u5E38,\u767D\u7709\u6700\u826F\u201D\u4E2D\u201C\u767D\u6BDB\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":22974
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8857\u4EAD",
		"indexes":"zgldycbfzmssslnzcczssjbdbthsz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u5317\u4F10\u4E2D\u9A6C\u8C21\u5931\u5B88\u4E86\u90A3\u5EA7\u57CE\u6C60\u81F4\u4F7F\u8700\u519B\u4E0D\u5F97\u4E0D\u9000\u56DE\u8700\u4E2D?",
		"id":22975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"dqssdlp",
		"question":"\u5927\u4E54\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8001\u5A46?",
		"id":22976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"xqssdlp",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u4E54\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8001\u5A46?",
		"id":22977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7FD4",
		"indexes":"xmnwydyddlyzrzayhsddymdpjp",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u593A\u5F97\u4E86\u4E9A\u6D32\u4EBA\u5728\u5965\u8FD0\u4F1A\u4E0A\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u77ED\u8DD1\u91D1\u724C?",
		"id":22978
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA8\u5229",
		"indexes":"xmnwfgydybzgqmcwdd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CD5\u56FD\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u88AB\u4E2D\u56FD\u7403\u8FF7\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5927\u5E1D\u201D?",
		"id":22979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u963F\u68EE\u7EB3",
		"indexes":"xmnzqddyyfywaxn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u652F\u7403\u961F\u7684\u7CA4\u8BED\u7FFB\u8BD1\u4E3A\u201C\u963F\u4ED9\u5974\u201D?",
		"id":22980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5207\u5C14\u897F",
		"indexes":"xmnzqddyyfywcls",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u652F\u7403\u961F\u7684\u7CA4\u8BED\u7FFB\u8BD1\u4E3A\u201C\u8F66\u8DEF\u58EB\u201D?",
		"id":22981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u957F",
		"indexes":"hdjlrgyzsm",
		"question":"\u6CB3\u4E1C\u89E3\u826F\u4EBA,\u5173\u7FBD\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22982
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FFC\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"yzzjrzfzsm",
		"question":"\u5E7D\u5DDE\u6DBF\u90E1\u4EBA,\u5F20\u98DE\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u8FDC",
		"indexes":"ymmyrzlzsm",
		"question":"\u96C1\u95E8\u9A6C\u9091\u4EBA,\u5F20\u8FBD\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":22984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B59\u74D2",
		"indexes":"lbsscysgtqxylz",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5C11\u65F6\u66FE\u4E0E\u8C01\u5171\u540C\u6C42\u5B66\u4E8E\u5362\u690D?",
		"id":22985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u676D\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"sgsqdhjjbkyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4F1A\u7A3D\u90E1\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"sgsqdwjbkyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5434\u90E1\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u6C49",
		"indexes":"sgsqdjzbkyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8346\u5DDE\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u90E1",
		"indexes":"sgsqdjzbkyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u8346\u5DDE\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6210\u90FD\u5E9C",
		"indexes":"sgsqdyzbkyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u76CA\u5DDE\u5305\u62EC\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F0\u6E7E",
		"indexes":"sgsqdyzzdsyxngdf",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u5937\u6D32\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":22991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u5357",
		"indexes":"zmlyjddcszwgngsjn",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u65C5\u6E38\u666F\u70B9\u6EC7\u6C60\u662F\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u897F",
		"indexes":"glszwgngsjn",
		"question":"\u6842\u6797\u5E02\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u5883\u5185?",
		"id":22993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C9C\u5351\u65CF",
		"indexes":"whlhbkxmngssmz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22994
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7FAF\u65CF",
		"indexes":"whlhbkxmngssmz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8C\u65CF",
		"indexes":"whlhbkxmngssmz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5308\u5974\u65CF",
		"indexes":"whlhbkxmngssmz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22997
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C10\u65CF",
		"indexes":"whlhbkxmngssmz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":22998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C38\u5609\u81F3\u4E71",
		"indexes":"yxngswhlhdbc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u201C\u4E94\u80E1\u4E71\u534E\u201D\u7684\u522B\u79F0?",
		"id":22999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u7984\u5C71",
		"indexes":"aszlzdazds",
		"question":"\u201C\u5B89\u53F2\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u5B89\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u6210\u516C\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"xzbdlgsszgbwyqnwgzxjd",
		"question":"\u897F\u85CF\u5E03\u8FBE\u62C9\u5BAB\u662F\u677E\u8D5E\u5E72\u5E03\u4E3A\u8FCE\u5A36\u54EA\u4F4D\u516C\u4E3B\u4FEE\u5EFA\u7684?",
		"id":23001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u798F\u5EFA",
		"indexes":"tgycycywgngsf",
		"question":"\u201C\u94C1\u89C2\u97F3\u201D\u8336\u539F\u4EA7\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701\u4EFD?",
		"id":23002
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u4E00\u5927\u6B65",
		"indexes":"mgamstldyhsdgrdyxbdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u963F\u59C6\u65AF\u7279\u6717\u767B\u6708\u540E\u8BF4\u7684\u201C\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7684\u4E00\u5C0F\u6B65\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u91CD\u9633",
		"indexes":"xssdyxcdychsljdslzss",
		"question":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u5C04\u96D5\u82F1\u96C4\u4F20\u300B\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u534E\u5C71\u8BBA\u5251\u7684\u80DC\u5229\u8005\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62FF\u7834\u4ED1",
		"indexes":"fgblkxmswljnsejd",
		"question":"\u6CD5\u56FD\u5DF4\u9ECE\u51EF\u65CB\u95E8\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u7EAA\u5FF5\u8C01\u800C\u5EFA\u7684?",
		"id":23005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9999\u6E2F",
		"indexes":"gcdfzzwdarzddfzzzdsngcs",
		"question":"\u6B4C\u8BCD\u201C\u4E1C\u65B9\u4E4B\u73E0,\u6211\u7684\u7231\u4EBA\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E1C\u65B9\u4E4B\u73E0\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":23006
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FBD\u6C88\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"jfzzzdsdzydygdxdzys",
		"question":"\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E09\u5927\u6218\u5F79\u201D\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u6253\u54CD\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":23007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D2B\u8346\u82B1",
		"indexes":"xgtbxzqdqhssm",
		"question":"\u9999\u6E2F\u7279\u522B\u884C\u653F\u533A\u7684\u533A\u82B1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23008
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672A\u592E\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xmnyzshcgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u5BAB\u6BBF?",
		"id":23009
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u4E50\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xmnyzshcgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u5BAB\u6BBF?",
		"id":23010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EFA\u7AE0\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xmnyzshcgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u5BAB\u6BBF?",
		"id":23011
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4F69\u73CA",
		"indexes":"83bsdxlssbydhr",
		"question":"83\u7248\u300A\u795E\u96D5\u4FA0\u4FA3\u300B\u662F\u8C01\u626E\u6F14\u7684\u9EC4\u84C9?",
		"id":23012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u6C27\u5316\u78B3",
		"indexes":"gbsnzwtdgtczxs",
		"question":"\u201C\u5E72\u51B0\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u7269\u4F53\u7684\u56FA\u6001\u5B58\u5728\u5F62\u5F0F?",
		"id":23013
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xmnwzjzdyjxgnzwdszhdydjbcwlymzyscs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u4F5C\u5BB6\u5728\u7B2C\u4E00\u5C4A\u300A\u65B0\u6982\u5FF5\u300B\u4F5C\u6587\u5927\u8D5B\u4E2D\u83B7\u5F97\u4E00\u7B49\u5956,\u5E76\u6210\u4E3A\u4E86\u4E00\u540D\u804C\u4E1A\u8D5B\u8F66\u624B?",
		"id":23014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5A01\u9707\u5929",
		"indexes":"dybxjgzyqtzzddfpsljsm",
		"question":"\u7535\u5F71\u300A\u53D8\u5F62\u91D1\u521A\u300B\u4E2D,\u4E0E\u64CE\u5929\u67F1\u4F5C\u5BF9\u7684\u53CD\u6D3E\u9996\u9886\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23015
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EBD\u4F26\u5821",
		"indexes":"ezghspfxsddgftznygcs",
		"question":"\u4E8C\u6218\u8FC7\u540E,\u5BA1\u5224\u6CD5\u897F\u65AF\u7684\u5FB7\u56FD\u6CD5\u5EAD\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":23016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C64\u59C6\u00B7\u6C49\u514B\u65AF",
		"indexes":"mgaskjlsszyyrlxljhdzjnyyjzgrss",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u5965\u65AF\u5361\u5956\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u53EA\u6709\u4E00\u4EBA\u8FDE\u7EED\u4E24\u5C4A\u83B7\u5F97\u6700\u4F73\u7537\u6F14\u5458\u5956,\u8FD9\u4E2A\u4EBA\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5362\u6D6E\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"szyyhmnlsdzgzpdfgbwgsnyz",
		"question":"\u6536\u85CF\u6709\u6CB9\u753B\u300A\u8499\u5A1C\u4E3D\u838E\u300B\u7B49\u73CD\u8D35\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u6CD5\u56FD\u535A\u7269\u9986\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7?",
		"id":23018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90D1\u677F\u6865",
		"indexes":"qcbcwyzbgdbgrzyhzzwmdsnyw",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u626C\u5DDE\u516B\u602A\u201D\u7684\u516B\u4E2A\u4EBA\u4E2D\u4EE5\u753B\u7AF9\u5B50\u95FB\u540D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D?",
		"id":23019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"yksswgngzmfjqdbzxjd",
		"question":"\u8FCE\u5BA2\u677E\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u90A3\u4E2A\u8457\u540D\u98CE\u666F\u533A\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u6027\u666F\u70B9?",
		"id":23020
	},
	{
		"answer":"P-40",
		"indexes":"yxnzezzdjcdgmzbmj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u6218\u6597\u673A\u66FE\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u88C5\u5907\u7F8E\u519B?",
		"id":23021
	},
	{
		"answer":"Me-262",
		"indexes":"yxnzezzdjcdgmzbdj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u6218\u6597\u673A\u66FE\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u88C5\u5907\u5FB7\u519B?",
		"id":23022
	},
	{
		"answer":"T34",
		"indexes":"yxnzeztkcdgmzbsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u5766\u514B\u66FE\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u88C5\u5907\u82CF\u519B?",
		"id":23023
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u201C\u864E\u201D\u5F0F",
		"indexes":"yxnzeztkccjzzbdj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u5766\u514B\u66FE\u6210\u5EFA\u5236\u88C5\u5907\u5FB7\u519B?",
		"id":23024
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C22\u5C14\u66FCM\u7CFB\u5766\u514B",
		"indexes":"yxnzeztkcdgmzbmj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u5766\u514B\u66FE\u5927\u89C4\u6A21\u88C5\u5907\u7F8E\u519B?",
		"id":23025
	},
	{
		"answer":"KV-1",
		"indexes":"yxnzeztkccjzzbsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u4E8C\u6218\u5766\u514B\u66FE\u6210\u5EFA\u5236\u88C5\u5907\u82CF\u519B?",
		"id":23026
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D0\u6C34",
		"indexes":"cbldshrmybhysmspyheljsmmctg",
		"question":"\u5403\u83E0\u841D\u7684\u65F6\u5019\u4EBA\u4EEC\u4E00\u822C\u4F1A\u7528\u4EC0\u4E48\u6C34\u6CE1\u4E00\u4F1A\u513F\u6765\u51CF\u5C11\u9EBB\u6728\u523A\u75DB\u611F?",
		"id":23027
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E7F\u5BD2\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"zgshdzcezylszdxgjsm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u795E\u8BDD\u5F53\u4E2D,\u5AE6\u5A25\u5728\u6708\u4EAE\u4E0A\u4F4F\u7684\u884C\u5BAB\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23028
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u80DC",
		"indexes":"lbzcshzsjwzhnxhdyrzsjws",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u81EA\u79F0\u662F\u6C49\u4E2D\u5C71\u9756\u738B\u4E4B\u540E,\u90A3\u897F\u6C49\u7B2C\u4E00\u4EFB\u4E2D\u5C71\u9756\u738B\u662F?",
		"id":23029
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D41\u6C99\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"wcexsxyjdztsznthslshsztd",
		"question":"\u5434\u627F\u6069\u5C0F\u8BF4\u300A\u897F\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u5F53\u4E2D,\u5510\u50E7\u5728\u54EA\u6761\u6CB3\u6536\u4E86\u6C99\u548C\u5C1A\u505A\u5F92\u5F1F?",
		"id":23030
	},
	{
		"answer":"207\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lbsgmlqdzgljrdclzddzlfzdgszgydsn",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u8BF7\u5F97\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u52A0\u5165,\u5F97\u51FA\u9686\u4E2D\u5BF9\u7684\u6218\u7565\u65B9\u9488,\u5927\u6982\u662F\u5728\u516C\u5143\u591A\u5C11\u5E74",
		"id":23031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90CE\u5E73",
		"indexes":"ytltycdqzgpqnydyss",
		"question":"\u6709\u201C\u94C1\u6994\u5934\u201D\u4E00\u79F0\u7684\u524D\u4E2D\u56FD\u6392\u7403\u5973\u8FD0\u52A8\u5458\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5B59\u5EB7",
		"indexes":"jdsrjsccrysyshptzsywzl",
		"question":"\u501F\u5200\u6740\u4EBA\u8BA1\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u8BA9\u8881\u6C0F\u4E0E\u8C01\u706B\u62FC,\u4ED6\u5750\u6536\u6E14\u7FC1\u4E4B\u5229",
		"id":23033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u5929\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"indexes":"yyglrzzgdnhbhlygqsnsgdgc",
		"question":"\u201C\u6709\u4E00\u4E2A\u8001\u4EBA\u5728\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5357\u6D77\u8FB9\u753B\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u5708\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u9996\u6B4C\u7684\u6B4C\u8BCD?",
		"id":23034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"mkblszngcdldzgd",
		"question":"\u9A6C\u53EF\u6CE2\u7F57\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u6765\u5230\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":23035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u4F57",
		"indexes":"cswgygglsdsnywmy",
		"question":"\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E3A\u5173\u7FBD\u201C\u522E\u9AA8\u7597\u4F24\u201D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u540D\u533B?",
		"id":23036
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8096\u90A6",
		"indexes":"sjsygqsrzcdblgqjsnyw",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6709\u201C\u94A2\u7434\u8BD7\u4EBA\u201D\u4E4B\u79F0\u7684\u6CE2\u6F9C\u94A2\u7434\u5BB6\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D?",
		"id":23037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"msqsnywgjdgg",
		"question":"\u300A\u9A6C\u8D5B\u66F2\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u56FD\u6B4C?",
		"id":23038
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7236\u4EB2",
		"indexes":"gdhzdldszpthzdnzcw",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u4E1C\u8BDD\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u8001\u8C46\u201D\u662F\u6307\u666E\u901A\u8BDD\u4E2D\u7684\u54EA\u79CD\u79F0\u8C13?",
		"id":23039
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u74DC",
		"indexes":"glthhgnzhgncjwhsszdcsynzzwbcd",
		"question":"\u683C\u6797\u7AE5\u8BDD\u300A\u7070\u59D1\u5A18\u300B\u4E2D,\u7070\u59D1\u5A18\u53C2\u52A0\u821E\u4F1A\u65F6\u6240\u505A\u7684\u8F66\u662F\u7531\u54EA\u79CD\u690D\u7269\u53D8\u6210\u7684?",
		"id":23040
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u9633\u8282",
		"indexes":"yzxddgcbczysyrmsdssmjr",
		"question":"\u201C\u9065\u77E5\u5144\u5F1F\u767B\u9AD8\u5904,\u904D\u63D2\u8331\u8438\u5C11\u4E00\u4EBA\u201D,\u63CF\u8FF0\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u8282\u65E5?",
		"id":23041
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u9ECE",
		"indexes":"zmdafettsngcsdbzxjd",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u57C3\u83F2\u5C14\u94C1\u5854\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u7684\u6807\u5FD7\u6027\u666F\u70B9?",
		"id":23042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9E\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"yxnwsgrwsycwzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E09\u56FD\u4EBA\u7269\u5C5E\u4E8E\u66F9\u9B4F\u9635\u8425?",
		"id":23043
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u56FD",
		"indexes":"dsndzbsznggj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8FEA\u65AF\u5C3C\u201D\u7684\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6?",
		"id":23044
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u739B\u4E3D\u83B2\u68A6\u9732",
		"indexes":"50ndybfcqqzwbzhbsjdmgxgnsss",
		"question":"50\u5E74\u4EE3\u4EE5\u88AB\u98CE\u5439\u8D77\u88D9\u5B50\u4E3A\u6807\u5FD7,\u7EA2\u904D\u4E16\u754C\u7684\u7F8E\u56FD\u6027\u611F\u5973\u795E\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23045
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u9EA6",
		"indexes":"nzpjdzyylssmls",
		"question":"\u917F\u9020\u5564\u9152\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u539F\u6599\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u7CAE\u98DF?",
		"id":23046
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D77\u4F26",
		"indexes":"zmdtlyzzcsqyssfwlzdygmnqwzwmnjsm",
		"question":"\u8457\u540D\u7684\u201C\u7279\u6D1B\u4F0A\u4E4B\u6218\u201D\u4F20\u8BF4\u8D77\u56E0\u662F\u53CC\u65B9\u4E3A\u4E86\u4E89\u593A\u4E00\u4E2A\u7F8E\u5973,\u8BF7\u95EE\u8FD9\u4F4D\u7F8E\u5973\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u6867",
		"indexes":"ymxyzmdhlmjyfdjcss",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u201C\u83AB\u987B\u6709\u201D\u7F6A\u540D\u6BD2\u5BB3\u4E86\u540D\u5C06\u5CB3\u98DE\u7684\u5978\u81E3\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23048
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5973\u5A32",
		"indexes":"zgshcszsnwsywsstbdt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u795E\u8BDD\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u795E\u7528\u4E94\u8272\u77F3\u5934\u8865\u7684\u5929?",
		"id":23049
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6606\u660E",
		"indexes":"ywsjrcebcwccdswgngcs",
		"question":"\u56E0\u4E3A\u56DB\u5B63\u5982\u6625\u800C\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u6625\u57CE\u201D\u7684\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":23050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u65AD\u80CC\u5C71\u300B",
		"indexes":"xmnbdysyladyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u90A3\u90E8\u7535\u5F71\u662F\u7531\u674E\u5B89\u5BFC\u6F14\u7684?",
		"id":23051
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"wmcsdydpjszdsppj",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u5E38\u8BF4\u7684\u201C\u4E00\u6253\u201D\u5564\u9152\u662F\u6307\u591A\u5C11\u74F6\u5564\u9152?",
		"id":23052
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"wgdyzwqyzgzxsjhsgdzjdqjyngcs",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u5EA7\u5B8C\u5168\u7531\u4E2D\u56FD\u81EA\u884C\u8BBE\u8BA1\u548C\u65BD\u5DE5\u7684\u957F\u6C5F\u5927\u6865\u5EFA\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02?",
		"id":23053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E91\u541E",
		"indexes":"gdrjctxchtcwsm",
		"question":"\u5E7F\u4E1C\u4EBA\u5C06\u4F20\u7EDF\u5C0F\u5403\u201C\u9984\u9968\u201D\u79F0\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23054
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8001\u9F20",
		"indexes":"zsesxzplsxdydssmdw",
		"question":"\u5728\u5341\u4E8C\u751F\u8096\u4E2D\u6392\u5217\u987A\u5E8F\u7B2C\u4E00\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":23055
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u82F1\u96C4\u513F\u5973\u300B",
		"indexes":"jdtcxwkpczzgnybldy",
		"question":"\u7ECF\u5178\u53F0\u8BCD\u201C\u5411\u6211\u5F00\u70AE!\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u8001\u7535\u5F71?",
		"id":23056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C82\u8749",
		"indexes":"xcsdzlbfmccdgdmnss",
		"question":"\u76F8\u4F20\u4F7F\u8463\u5353\u3001\u5415\u5E03\u53CD\u76EE\u6210\u4EC7\u7684\u53E4\u4EE3\u7F8E\u5973\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23057
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8700\u6C49",
		"indexes":"sgsqycdwzxjldzqssmzq",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F,\u4EE5\u6210\u90FD\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5FC3\u5EFA\u7ACB\u7684\u653F\u6743\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u653F\u6743?",
		"id":23058
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6797\u5219\u5F90",
		"indexes":"qcdgnjzhmxjypdmzyxss",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u9053\u5149\u5E74\u95F4,\u5728\u864E\u95E8\u9500\u7981\u9E26\u7247\u7684\u6C11\u65CF\u82F1\u96C4\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23059
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ED1\u9F99\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"rmcsdbshszdhsszdbdntjh",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u5E38\u8BF4\u7684\u201C\u767D\u5C71\u9ED1\u6C34\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u9ED1\u6C34\u201D\u662F\u6307\u4E1C\u5317\u7684\u54EA\u6761\u6C5F\u6CB3?",
		"id":23060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u767D\u5C71",
		"indexes":"rmcsdbshszdbsszdbdntsm",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u5E38\u8BF4\u7684\u201C\u767D\u5C71\u9ED1\u6C34\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u767D\u5C71\u201D\u662F\u6307\u4E1C\u5317\u7684\u54EA\u6761\u5C71\u8109?",
		"id":23061
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6492\u54C8\u62C9\u6C99\u6F20",
		"indexes":"sjszddsmjsmmz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6C99\u6F20\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":23062
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u5B50",
		"indexes":"jsbywsyrszgnwsrtcd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5DF1\u6240\u4E0D\u6B32\u52FF\u65BD\u4E8E\u4EBA\u201D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u54EA\u4F4D\u5723\u4EBA\u63D0\u51FA\u7684?",
		"id":23063
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u81EA\u6210",
		"indexes":"lcwszmmnwnmqylx",
		"question":"\u674E\u95EF\u738B\u662F\u6307\u660E\u672B\u54EA\u4F4D\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49\u9886\u8896?",
		"id":23064
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9756",
		"indexes":"fsyyznzdfqttltwmjsm",
		"question":"\u300A\u5C01\u795E\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D,\u54EA\u5412\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u6258\u5854\u674E\u5929\u738B\u540D\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"lygessgcbbkxmnw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D?",
		"id":23066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"lygessgcbbkxmnw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D?",
		"id":23067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"lygessgcbbkxmnw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D?",
		"id":23068
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"lygessgcbbkxmnw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D?",
		"id":23069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u5CF0\u5854",
		"indexes":"dsjxbnzcqzbszbyzsmtz",
		"question":"\u7535\u89C6\u5267\u300A\u65B0\u767D\u5A18\u5B50\u4F20\u5947\u300B\u4E2D,\u767D\u7D20\u8D1E\u88AB\u538B\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5854\u4E2D?",
		"id":23070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8428\u5C14\u6D52\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"mmldgszsyydyzs",
		"question":"\u660E\u672B\u8FBD\u4E1C\u653B\u5B88\u4E4B\u52BF\u5F02\u4E5F\u7684\u4E00\u6218\u662F?",
		"id":23071
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1\u5EB8",
		"indexes":"fxltsblxssxybysnwzjd14bzzjc",
		"question":"\u201C\u98DE\u96EA\u8FDE\u5929\u5C04\u767D\u9E7F,\u7B11\u4E66\u795E\u4FA0\u501A\u78A7\u9E33\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u4F5C\u5BB6\u768414\u90E8\u8457\u4F5C\u7B80\u79F0?",
		"id":23072
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8A\u57CE",
		"indexes":"yxngsgzdbc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5E7F\u5DDE\u7684\u201C\u522B\u79F0\u201D?",
		"id":23073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F99\u57CE",
		"indexes":"yxngstydbc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u592A\u539F\u7684\u201C\u522B\u79F0\u201D?",
		"id":23074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84C9\u57CE",
		"indexes":"yxngscddbc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6210\u90FD\u7684\u201C\u522B\u79F0\u201D?",
		"id":23075
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E4F\u57CE",
		"indexes":"yxngsszdbc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6DF1\u5733\u7684\u201C\u522B\u79F0\u201D?",
		"id":23076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u5854\u9547\u6CB3\u5996",
		"indexes":"zqwhszjdtctwgdhxyjs",
		"question":"\u300A\u667A\u53D6\u5A01\u864E\u5C71\u300B\u4E2D\u7ECF\u5178\u53F0\u8BCD\u201D\u5929\u738B\u76D6\u5730\u864E\u201C\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F?",
		"id":23077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u8EAB\u96BE\u4FDD",
		"indexes":"xhynpsghdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\u201D\u6CE5\u83E9\u8428\u8FC7\u6CB3\u201C\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23078
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u816E",
		"indexes":"kdksmhx",
		"question":"\u874C\u86AA\u9760\u4EC0\u4E48\u547C\u5438?",
		"id":23079
	},
	{
		"answer":"IQ",
		"indexes":"tcyEQbsqsnmzssynlgywzmbs",
		"question":"\u901A\u5E38\u7528EQ\u8868\u793A\u60C5\u5546,\u90A3\u4E48\u667A\u5546\u662F\u7528\u54EA\u4FE9\u4E2A\u82F1\u6587\u5B57\u6BCD\u8868\u793A?",
		"id":23080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD",
		"indexes":"gqkdqgzdkdzngs",
		"question":"\u6B4C\u66F2\u300A\u5EB7\u5B9A\u60C5\u6B4C\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u5EB7\u5B9A\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u7701?",
		"id":23081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u8BED",
		"indexes":"wmcsdtfkssdnzyyjxdcs",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u5E38\u8BF4\u7684\u6258\u798F\u8003\u8BD5\u662F\u5BF9\u54EA\u79CD\u8BED\u8A00\u8FDB\u884C\u7684\u6D4B\u8BD5",
		"id":23082
	},
	{
		"answer":"1",
		"indexes":"wlltzsfsdbdjghtdr",
		"question":"\u7F51\u7EDC\u8BBA\u575B\u4E2D,\u2018\u6C99\u53D1\u2019\u662F\u4EE3\u8868\u7B2C\u51E0\u4E2A\u56DE\u5E16\u7684\u4EBA",
		"id":23083
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60",
		"indexes":"nzshhlmbssm",
		"question":"\u2018\u4FAC\u2019\u5728\u4E0A\u6D77\u8BDD\u91CC\u9762\u8868\u793A\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23084
	},
	{
		"answer":"DJ",
		"indexes":"wmtcynlgywzmbsdtzcr",
		"question":"\u6211\u4EEC\u901A\u5E38\u7528\u54EA\u4FE9\u4E2A\u82F1\u6587\u5B57\u6BCD\u8868\u793A\u7535\u53F0\u4E3B\u6301\u4EBA",
		"id":23085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E16\u8D38\u5927\u53A6",
		"indexes":"mgzs911kbxjdsztjsm",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u906D\u53D7911\u6050\u6016\u88AD\u51FB\u7684\u53CC\u5B50\u5854\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23086
	},
	{
		"answer":"2B\u94C5\u7B14",
		"indexes":"gkyqksymdsdshtmdtkdsmqb",
		"question":"\u9AD8\u8003\u8981\u6C42\u8003\u751F\u7528\u58A8\u7684\u6DF1\u5EA6\u9002\u5408\u6D82\u62B9\u7B54\u9898\u5361\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u94C5\u7B14",
		"id":23087
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73E0\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"bywgzdmqhysgzzddhljsm",
		"question":"\u88AB\u8A89\u4E3A\u5E7F\u5DDE\u7684\u6BCD\u4EB2\u6CB3,\u4E5F\u662F\u5E7F\u5DDE\u6700\u5927\u7684\u6CB3\u6D41\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u68CD\u8282",
		"indexes":"mn11y11rdsnnhgdygylxjmjsmj",
		"question":"\u6BCF\u5E7411\u670811\u65E5,\u5355\u8EAB\u7537\u5973\u4F1A\u8FC7\u7684\u4E00\u4E2A\u5A31\u4E50\u6027\u8282\u76EE\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\u8282",
		"id":23089
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"sjbzqbsjnyc",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u8DB3\u7403\u6BD4\u8D5B\u51E0\u5E74\u4E00\u6B21",
		"id":23090
	},
	{
		"answer":"10",
		"indexes":"yz20yrmbpsl2fz1dyxkydhddsq",
		"question":"\u4E00\u5F2020\u5143\u4EBA\u6C11\u5E01\u7834\u635F\u4E862\u5206\u4E4B1,\u5230\u94F6\u884C\u53EF\u4EE5\u5151\u6362\u5230\u591A\u5C11\u94B1",
		"id":23091
	},
	{
		"answer":"GDP",
		"indexes":"bsgnsczzdywjcs",
		"question":"\u8868\u793A\u56FD\u5185\u751F\u4EA7\u603B\u503C\u7684\u82F1\u6587\u7B80\u79F0\u662F",
		"id":23092
	},
	{
		"answer":"CEO",
		"indexes":"sxzxgdzwywjcs",
		"question":"\u9996\u5E2D\u6267\u884C\u5B98\u7684\u804C\u52A1\u82F1\u6587\u7B80\u79F0\u662F?",
		"id":23093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EFB\u5929\u5802",
		"indexes":"zzdhbjyxcjmlyrbnjzmyxzzgscp",
		"question":"\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u7EA2\u767D\u673A\u6E38\u620F\u8D85\u7EA7\u739B\u4E3D\u7531\u65E5\u672C\u54EA\u5BB6\u77E5\u540D\u6E38\u620F\u5236\u4F5C\u516C\u53F8\u51FA\u54C1?",
		"id":23094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zqhtsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u771F\u6C14\u62A4\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23095
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hfftsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u706B\u51E4\u9644\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23096
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"wstxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5A01\u6151\u5929\u4E0B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23097
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zmssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u667A\u8C0B\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23098
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"njzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5B81\u9759\u81F4\u8FDC\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hbzjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7F13\u5175\u4E4B\u8BA1\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":23100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u594B\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"xtgzjdwlgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":23101
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5996\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"xtgzjdmfgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u9B54\u6CD5\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":23102
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7981\u536B",
		"indexes":"xjszjsddwlgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u51CF\u5C11\u81EA\u5DF1\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":23103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"xjszjsddmfgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u51CF\u5C11\u81EA\u5DF1\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u9B54\u6CD5\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":23104
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u9A8C",
		"indexes":"yxnyxnzxlzswfgbd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u9879,\u4F60\u5728'\u4FEE\u70BC'\u4E2D\u662F\u65E0\u6CD5\u6539\u53D8\u7684?",
		"id":23105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u672C\u56FD\u4E66\u4E1E",
		"indexes":"xyyzhdjqrwkyzngNPCjsrw",
		"question":"\u60F3\u8981\u4E00\u76F4\u83B7\u5F97\u91D1\u94B1\u4EFB\u52A1,\u53EF\u4EE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u63A5\u53D7\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":23106
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"yxnlfzsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u7C7B\u526F\u804C\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":23108
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E96\u4E01",
		"indexes":"kyschftlhsmdfzs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u751F\u4EA7\u56DE\u590D\u4F53\u529B\u548C\u751F\u547D\u7684\u526F\u804C\u662F?",
		"id":23109
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE5\u5320",
		"indexes":"zzzssngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"\u91CD\u94F8\u4E4B\u4E66\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":23110
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E96\u4E01",
		"indexes":"jrwjsngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"\u9152\u8089\u65E0\u5FCC\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":23111
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9576\u5DE5",
		"indexes":"wszzfsngfzsydhcsj",
		"question":"\u6B66\u795E\u4E4B\u795D\u798F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u526F\u804C\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u5408\u6210\u4E66\u7C4D?",
		"id":23112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"hcdzngNPCckygmd",
		"question":"\u56DE\u6625\u4E39\u5728\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u5904\u53EF\u4EE5\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230?",
		"id":23113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"yxngdjzqhscsgmbdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u5728\u5343\u8D27\u5546\u5904\u662F\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":23114
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"yxngdjskyzscngmdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u662F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u5546\u57CE\u5185\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":23115
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"fzsxydclybdkyznlgmd",
		"question":"\u526F\u804C\u6240\u9700\u8981\u7684\u6750\u6599,\u4E00\u822C\u90FD\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230?",
		"id":23116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795E\u884C\u4E4B\u5377",
		"indexes":"kysjtgzjdydhtyddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u77AC\u95F4\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u79FB\u52A8\u548C\u8DF3\u8DC3\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":23117
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D3B\u529B\u4E38",
		"indexes":"kysjtgzjydhlddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u77AC\u95F4\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u4E00\u5B9A\u6D3B\u529B\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":23119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4E38",
		"indexes":"kyszjhdsbjyddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u4F7F\u81EA\u5DF1\u83B7\u5F97\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":23120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9",
		"indexes":"zbyxngdjjkyzdjzjjx",
		"question":"\u88C5\u5907\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5\u81EA\u52A8\u7ED9\u81EA\u5DF1\u52A0\u8840?",
		"id":23122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88C5\u5907'\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9'\u540E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u9ED8\u8BA4\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u836F\u7269",
		"indexes":"gmlzdbjrhcnzdjzjdjsbj",
		"question":"\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E86'\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9'\u5982\u4F55\u624D\u80FD\u81EA\u52A8\u7ED9\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u89D2\u8272\u8865\u7ED9?",
		"id":23123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u5587\u53ED",
		"indexes":"syyxngdjkyrsydrdkjnsdh",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u53EF\u4EE5\u8BA9\u6240\u6709\u7684\u4EBA\u90FD\u770B\u89C1\u4F60\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD?",
		"id":23124
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u968F\u7B49\u7EA7\u6B21\u6570\u6539\u53D8",
		"indexes":"sygjpdfyxydssgb",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053\u53D1\u8A00,\u9700\u8981\u591A\u5C11\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01?",
		"id":23125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u9505\u5934",
		"indexes":"yxngdjsQQsgnd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177\u662FQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u5185\u7684?",
		"id":23126
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D29\u5356\u5546\u57CE\u9053\u5177",
		"indexes":"yxnzfsbnhdsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u4E0D\u80FD\u83B7\u5F97\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9?",
		"id":23127
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7269\u653B",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxdbwqdwlgjl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4EE3\u8868\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u529B?",
		"id":23128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7075\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxyxjsdhbnl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u5F71\u54CD\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u56DE\u907F\u80FD\u529B?",
		"id":23129
	},
	{
		"answer":"F1",
		"indexes":"xszzjdgxqmygsyngkjjhjztjm",
		"question":"\u60F3\u8BBE\u7F6E\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u4E2A\u6027\u7B7E\u540D,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4F7F\u7528\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u547C\u53EB\u72B6\u6001\u754C\u9762?",
		"id":23130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u4E8C\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"yzjbznsydsgsbjyw",
		"question":"\u4E00\u5468\u57FA\u672C\u53EA\u80FD\u4F7F\u7528\u591A\u5C11\u4E2A'\u53CC\u500D\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4E38'?",
		"id":23131
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7070\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjrhddgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u5F31\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":23132
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7EFF\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjsrdgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u7A0D\u5F31\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":23133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u9EC4\u8272",
		"indexes":"hwjcbddgw",
		"question":"\u548C\u73A9\u5BB6\u5DEE\u4E0D\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":23134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u6A59\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjsqdgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u7A0D\u5F3A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":23135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u602A\u7269\u540D\u4E3A\u7EA2\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjqhddgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u5F3A\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":23136
	},
	{
		"answer":"sg.qq.com",
		"indexes":"QQsggfwzdwzs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u5B98\u65B9\u7F51\u7AD9\u7684\u7F51\u5740\u662F:",
		"id":23137
	},
	{
		"answer":"Z",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyqfzdykjjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u524D\u7FFB'\u81EA\u5B9A\u4E49\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u7EC4'?",
		"id":23138
	},
	{
		"answer":"X",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyhfzdykjjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u540E\u7FFB'\u81EA\u5B9A\u4E49\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u7EC4'?",
		"id":23139
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6570\u5B57\u952E1\u81F35",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyksxzzjddy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FEB\u901F\u9009\u62E9\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u961F\u53CB?",
		"id":23140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90AE\u4EF6",
		"indexes":"rgndhybzxnkytgsmfsjtly",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u4F60\u7684\u597D\u53CB\u4E0D\u5728\u7EBF,\u4F60\u53EF\u4EE5\u901A\u8FC7\u4EC0\u4E48\u65B9\u5F0F\u7ED9\u4ED6\u7559\u8A00?",
		"id":23141
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79C1\u804A",
		"indexes":"yyxnzfskyydddckhbrjl",
		"question":"\u7528\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u65B9\u5F0F\u53EF\u4EE5\u7528\u5355\u72EC\u7684\u7A97\u53E3\u548C\u522B\u4EBA\u4EA4\u6D41?",
		"id":23142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053",
		"indexes":"yxcwdhwnxyznldlfy",
		"question":"\u8981\u60F3\u6210\u4E3A\u5927\u8BDD\u738B,\u4F60\u9700\u8981\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u5927\u91CF\u53D1\u8A00?",
		"id":23143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u65B9\u5DE1\u67E5\u4F7F",
		"indexes":"cxgzyzdjpxbnxyznwNPC",
		"question":"\u67E5\u8BE2\u5404\u804C\u4E1A\u4E3B\u7B49\u7EA7\u6392\u884C\u699C,\u4F60\u9700\u8981\u627E\u54EA\u4F4DNPC?",
		"id":23144
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"xlnb4zcdssnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u80FD\u88AB4\u6574\u9664\u7684\u6570\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u853A\u76F8\u5982",
		"indexes":"fjqzjdslphnwlsrwdgs",
		"question":"\u8D1F\u8346\u8BF7\u7F6A\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u5EC9\u9887\u548C\u54EA\u4F4D\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":23146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6B66",
		"indexes":"szbfdzzs",
		"question":"\u300A\u5B59\u5B50\u5175\u6CD5\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F?",
		"id":23147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u8C10\u53F7",
		"indexes":"wgtdbdCRHgsdctymmwsmh",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u94C1\u9053\u90E8\u7684CRH\u9AD8\u901F\u52A8\u8F66,\u7EDF\u4E00\u547D\u540D\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u53F7?",
		"id":23148
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76F8\u6251",
		"indexes":"fyywgtcxzlxyrbdyzylmdlsllsshxjldsjydj",
		"question":"\u53D1\u6E90\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u5510\u671D\u3002\u73B0\u5728\u6D41\u884C\u4E8E\u65E5\u672C\u7684\u4E00\u79CD\u7531\u4E24\u540D\u5927\u529B\u58EB\u88F8\u9732\u4E0A\u8EAB\u4E92\u76F8\u89D2\u529B\u7684\u6454\u8DE4\u8FD0\u52A8\u53EB?",
		"id":23149
	},
	{
		"answer":"2",
		"indexes":"xlsyosdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5076\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23150
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E2D\u7EFF\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"zghcxlgdjhjzsmj",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u548C\u671D\u9C9C\u4E24\u56FD\u7684\u754C\u6CB3\u53EB\u505A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6C5F",
		"id":23151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u4E8E\u53F7",
		"indexes":"xlsygxfhdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5173\u7CFB\u7B26\u53F7\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23152
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"xlbsyzsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8D28\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5206\u4E4B\u4E94",
		"indexes":"xlbsyjfsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5047\u5206\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5398\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlsyzddwdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u957F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23155
	},
	{
		"answer":"150\u5EA6\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlsydjdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u949D\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23156
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73AB\u7470",
		"indexes":"rmtcylshdlsyjqsssmh",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4EEC\u901A\u5E38\u7528\u6765\u9001\u82B1\u7684\u84DD\u8272\u5996\u59EC\u5176\u5B9E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u82B1",
		"id":23157
	},
	{
		"answer":"21",
		"indexes":"xlnb3zcdssnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u80FD\u88AB3\u6574\u9664\u7684\u6570\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23158
	},
	{
		"answer":"2i",
		"indexes":"xlsyxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u865A\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23159
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7BAD\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"cybbcyyyszsmblg",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u767E\u6B65\u7A7F\u6768\u201D\u539F\u610F\u662F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48\u672C\u9886\u9AD8?",
		"id":23160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79D2",
		"indexes":"xlsysjdwdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C1A\u65B9\u5B9D\u5251",
		"indexes":"hsdsmbjjyxzhzdql",
		"question":"\u7687\u4E0A\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u5B9D\u5251,\u5177\u6709\u5148\u65A9\u540E\u594F\u7684\u6743\u529B?",
		"id":23162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u4E16\u7F8E",
		"indexes":"jjmdzmasjbgbngfxhzs",
		"question":"\u4EAC\u5267\u540D\u6BB5\u300A\u94E1\u7F8E\u6848\u300B\u662F\u8BB2\u5305\u516C\u628A\u54EA\u4E2A\u8D1F\u5FC3\u6C49\u65A9\u9996?",
		"id":23163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5206\u4E4B\u4E8C\u5341\u4E03",
		"indexes":"xlsykyhczsdfssnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5316\u6210\u6574\u6570\u7684\u5206\u6570\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23164
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D\u5206\u4E4B\u4E09",
		"indexes":"xlbsyzjfsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6700\u7B80\u5206\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23165
	},
	{
		"answer":"60\u00B0\u548C120\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwbjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u8865\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9?",
		"id":23166
	},
	{
		"answer":"37\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsydyxxdjdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u4E00\u8C61\u9650\u7684\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23167
	},
	{
		"answer":"16",
		"indexes":"xlkykpfgdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u53EF\u4EE5\u5F00\u5E73\u65B9\u6839\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23168
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.333\u2026\u2026",
		"indexes":"xlsyxhxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5FAA\u73AF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23169
	},
	{
		"answer":"0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwyjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u4F59\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9?",
		"id":23170
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5149\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsdlzdddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u662F\u5EA6\u91CF\u957F\u5EA6\u7684\u5355\u4F4D?",
		"id":23171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u514B",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8D28\u91CF\u5355\u4F4D?",
		"id":23172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EA9",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsymjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u9762\u79EF\u5355\u4F4D?",
		"id":23173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ACB\u65B9\u5398\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsytjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4F53\u79EF\u5355\u4F4D?",
		"id":23174
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0A\u6D77",
		"indexes":"F1zgzzngcsjx",
		"question":"F1\u4E2D\u56FD\u7AD9\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u8FDB\u884C?",
		"id":23175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u5E86",
		"indexes":"zg1997nsldzxssng",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD1997\u5E74\u8BBE\u7ACB\u7684\u76F4\u8F96\u5E02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":23176
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"lsyjjjyxldtwsbsnggjdbz",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u60A0\u4E45,\u6781\u5177\u5F71\u54CD\u529B\u7684\u300A\u6CF0\u6664\u58EB\u62A5\u300B\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u7684\u62A5\u7EB8?",
		"id":23177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FC8",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsysddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u901F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D?",
		"id":23178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5357\u4E01\u00B7\u683C\u5C14",
		"indexes":"512gjhsjswljnnwzmrw",
		"question":"5.12\u56FD\u5BB6\u62A4\u58EB\u8282\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u7EAA\u5FF5\u54EA\u4F4D\u8457\u540D\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":23179
	},
	{
		"answer":"7",
		"indexes":"xlnygssqs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5947\u6570?",
		"id":23180
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"xlnygssos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u662F\u5076\u6570?",
		"id":23181
	},
	{
		"answer":"112",
		"indexes":"xlnygsos",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5076\u6570?",
		"id":23182
	},
	{
		"answer":"111",
		"indexes":"xlnygsqs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5947\u6570?",
		"id":23183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51CF\u53F7",
		"indexes":"xlnygssxysfh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B66\u8FD0\u7B97\u7B26\u53F7?",
		"id":23184
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731",
		"indexes":"mcdgxs",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u7684\u56FD\u59D3\u662F?",
		"id":23185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u601D\u9088",
		"indexes":"qjyfdzzw",
		"question":"\u300A\u5343\u91D1\u8981\u65B9\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u4E3A?",
		"id":23186
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5341\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23187
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09",
		"indexes":"dzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"gzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u6208\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"fzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u65B9\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23190
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C",
		"indexes":"bzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u516B\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23191
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"hzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C49\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23192
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D",
		"indexes":"gzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5173\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B?",
		"id":23193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"sgyybssdzz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8457\u4F5C",
		"id":23194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"kmbsz",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u4E0D\u662F\u6307",
		"id":23195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49",
		"indexes":"ggzjdsslhtjyxsfcbztkqsyjzjdxyhzbswgnbwxgdmzdkpc",
		"question":"\u6EDA\u6EDA\u957F\u6C5F\u4E1C\u901D\u6C34,\u6D6A\u82B1\u6DD8\u5C3D\u82F1\u96C4.\u662F\u975E\u6210\u8D25\u8F6C\u5934\u7A7A.\u9752\u5C71\u4F9D\u65E7\u5728,\u51E0\u5EA6\u5915\u9633\u7EA2...\u8FD9\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u90E8\u6587\u5B66\u53E4\u5178\u540D\u8457\u7684\u5F00\u7BC7\u8BCD",
		"id":23196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"wggdwxmzsgyyzszlyggwgzljqlzdqdyxxxzgyxbss",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u6587\u5B66\u540D\u8457\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u5851\u9020\u4E86\u4E00\u4E2A\u8FC7\u4E94\u5173\u65A9\u516D\u5C06,\u5343\u91CC\u8D70\u5355\u9A91\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u5F62\u8C61,\u8FD9\u4E2A\u82F1\u96C4\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"syqjjdbssdyxgs",
		"question":"\u6C34\u6DF9\u4E03\u519B\u8BB2\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u6545\u4E8B\uFF1F",
		"id":23198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"yryhsjdbssyccdzdgs",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u8BB2\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u4E0E\u66F9\u64CD\u6597\u667A\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":23199
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u3001\u8700\u3001\u5434",
		"indexes":"txsfbsztxflwnjg",
		"question":"'\u5929\u4E0B\u4E09\u5206'\u4E0D\u662F\u6307\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u88C2\u4E3A\u54EA\u51E0\u56FD",
		"id":23200
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"szqrsgmlhqqmhjdbssdgs",
		"question":"\u820C\u6218\u7FA4\u5112\u3001\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u548C\u4E03\u64D2\u5B5F\u83B7\u8BB2\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":23201
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"csbzdxdzlbbxzdbs",
		"question":"\u300A\u51FA\u5E08\u8868\u300B\u4E2D\u7684'\u5148\u5E1D'\u6307\u5218\u5907,'\u965B\u4E0B'\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23202
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4",
		"indexes":"mchxzqsspyxjsrqjwllyssjybxrszsssdssgyyzlbhccdydgszggsbs",
		"question":"'\u52C9\u4ECE\u864E\u7A74\u6682\u6816\u8EAB,\u8BF4\u7834\u82F1\u96C4\u60CA\u715E\u4EBA.\u5DE7\u5C06\u95FB\u96F7\u6765\u63A9\u9970,\u968F\u673A\u5E94\u53D8\u4FE1\u5982\u795E\u300B'\u8FD9\u9996\u8BD7\u8BF4\u7684\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u5218\u5907\u548C\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E00\u6BB5\u6545\u4E8B.\u8FD9\u4E2A\u6545\u4E8B\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"cywsjbzqdfbsgjsgyydsmzyzzydjhgccyqdzbhlzqnbdhcxcyddfdgsyheld",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED'\u4E07\u4E8B\u4FF1\u5907,\u53EA\u6B20\u4E1C\u98CE'\u4E0D\u662F\u6839\u636E\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79\u4E2D'\u5468\u745C\u5B9A\u8BA1\u706B\u653B\u66F9\u64CD,\u4E00\u5207\u90FD\u51C6\u5907\u597D\u4E86,\u53EA\u7F3A\u80FD\u628A\u5927\u706B\u5439\u5411\u66F9\u8425\u7684\u4E1C\u98CE.'\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u6F14\u5316\u800C\u6765\u7684.",
		"id":23204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"bszglyzylszhdycyssddzl",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0E\u5468\u745C\u8054\u624B\u6307\u6325\u7684\u4E00\u573A\u4EE5\u5C11\u80DC\u591A\u7684\u6218\u4F8B",
		"id":23205
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8A00\u8FC7\u5176\u5B9E\uFF0C\u671F\u671F\u827E\u827E",
		"indexes":"yxnlgbsysggsygdcyhsy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E24\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0E\u4E09\u56FD\u6545\u4E8B\u6709\u5173\u7684\u6210\u8BED\u6216\u4FD7\u8BED",
		"id":23206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8857\u4EAD\u5931\u5B88",
		"indexes":"zglhlzmsbsywhs",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6325\u6CEA\u65A9\u9A6C\u8C21\u4E0D\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u4F55\u4E8B.",
		"id":23207
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5141",
		"indexes":"dcdyfbss",
		"question":"\u8C82\u5A75\u7684\u4E49\u7236\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":23208
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"dmcbszdfbyzlbtqcsseqdjzxdbssmzy",
		"question":"\u675C\u7267\u300A\u8D64\u58C1\u300B\u8BD7\u4E2D'\u4E1C\u98CE\u4E0D\u4E0E\u5468\u90CE\u4FBF,\u94DC\u96C0\u6625\u6DF1\u9501\u4E8C\u4E54'\u7684\u53E5\u5B50\u5199\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u6218\u5F79;",
		"id":23209
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6253\u795D\u5BB6\u5E84",
		"indexes":"xlgszssgyyzdyxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u6545\u4E8B\u4E2D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u9879\u662F:",
		"id":23210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"tysjybszsdjljxd",
		"question":"\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u4E0D\u662F\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u5BB6\u91CC\u8FDB\u884C\u7684",
		"id":23211
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"cszdrzzldbsyxnw",
		"question":"\u5E38\u5C71\u771F\u5B9A\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5B57\u5B50\u9F99\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":23212
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"tqtzmbswhrsq",
		"question":"\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0\u4E4B\u540D\u4E0D\u662F\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u53D6\uFF1F",
		"id":23213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"ydxxkhraqxrkzdbss",
		"question":"'\u4E00\u4EE3\u67AD\u96C4\uFF0C\u5BBD\u539A\u4EC1\u7231\uFF0C\u6C42\u8D24\u82E5\u6E34'\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgyyztysjydsdxfbssgjdmmszbsmqdmmhsqlyyddmrzsrycbs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49\u7684\u4E09\u5F1F\u5144\u5206\u522B\u662F\u53CC\u80A1\u5251\u7684\u67D0\u67D0\uFF0C\u4F7F\u4E08\u516B\u86C7\u77DB\u67AA\u7684\u67D0\u67D0\u548C\u4F7F\u9752\u9F99\u5043\u6708\u5200\u7684\u67D0\u4EBA\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4E09\u4EBA\u4F9D\u6B21\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23215
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u52AD",
		"indexes":"rnygsyplrwdmsplccwzsznclszjxcmsbs",
		"question":"\u6C5D\u5357\u6709\u4E2A\u5584\u4E8E\u8BC4\u8BBA\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u540D\u58EB\uFF0C\u8BC4\u8BBA\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\uFF1A'\u6CBB\u4E16\u4E4B\u80FD\u81E3\uFF0C\u4E71\u4E16\u4E4B\u5978\u96C4'\uFF0C\u6B64\u540D\u58EB\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"zzhzhdxzqzgzyrwxqxjsrzyjzjgjczdbs",
		"question":"'\u667A\u8005\u548C\u667A\u6167\u7684\u8C61\u5F81\uFF0C\u6E05\u5FE0\u803F\u76F4\uFF0C\u7528\u4EBA\u552F\u8D24\uFF0C\u8C26\u865A\u3001\u8C28\u614E\u3001\u8BA4\u771F\u53C8\u5C3D\u804C\u3001\u97A0\u8EAC\u5C3D\u7601'\uFF0C\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u548C\u620F\u66F2\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"sgyydzzlgzbsymmcd",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0D\u662F\u5143\u672B\u660E\u521D\u7684",
		"id":23218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u672B\u660E\u521D",
		"indexes":"zzlgzbssmcddr",
		"question":"\u4F5C\u8005\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u671D\u4EE3\u7684\u4EBA",
		"id":23219
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74",
		"indexes":"sgyyjdbssmsqdsq",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u8BB2\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E8B\u60C5",
		"id":23220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u548C\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"sgyyznlwrwbsqmzjlyx",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E24\u4F4D\u4EBA\u7269\u4E0D\u662F\u9752\u6885\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\uFF1F",
		"id":23221
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD\u3001\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u3001\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzyrwzbcsjjjzjyjycbs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u4E3B\u8981\u4EBA\u7269\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0'\u4E09\u7EDD'\uFF1A'\u5978\u7EDD'\u3001'\u667A\u7EDD'\u3001'\u4E49\u7EDD'\u4F9D\u6B21\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u4E54",
		"indexes":"zydqzbs",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u7684\u59BB\u5B50\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23223
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u7433",
		"indexes":"cjtysqcxwmlccdzzsdyssbhgjccdbs",
		"question":"\u66FE\u7ECF\u66FF\u8881\u7ECD\u8D77\u8349\u6A84\u6587,\u9A82\u4E86\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u7956\u5B97\u4E09\u4EE3.\u8881\u7ECD\u5931\u8D25\u540E\u5F52\u964D\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23224
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06",
		"indexes":"zglqlxclgxssjygzcmyfw",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u53D6\u4E86\u897F\u5DDD\uFF0C\u8BBA\u529F\u884C\u8D4F\u65F6\uFF0C\u5C06\u6709\u529F\u4E4B\u81E3\u6CA1\u6709\u5C01\u4E3A",
		"id":23226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"yxsszglfdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5C01\u7684'\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06'",
		"id":23227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4EEA",
		"indexes":"zglzwzyjdhssmytfszcqjgz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F\u4EA4\u4EE3\u540E\u4E8B\u65F6\uFF0C\u6CA1\u6709\u6258\u4ED8\u8C01\u4E3B\u6301\u5168\u5C40\u5DE5\u4F5C",
		"id":23228
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"zglzwzyjdhssmybbqjjls",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F\u4EA4\u4EE3\u540E\u4E8B\u65F6\uFF0C\u6CA1\u6709\u628A\u5175\u6743\u4EA4\u7ED9\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":23229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5CB1",
		"indexes":"wyfhslsjhcdzdyyyqsyyzhhsyyyhrhlzlwyyxnwbs",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5EF6\u653E\u706B\u70E7\u4E86\u8700\u519B\u56DE\u64A4\u7684\u6808\u9053\uFF0C\u626C\u8A00\u8981\u64D2\u6740\u6768\u4EEA\uFF0C\u6700\u540E\u8FD8\u662F\u6768\u4EEA\u4E0E\u4F55\u4EBA\u5408\u529B\u65A9\u4E86\u9B4F\u5EF6\uFF0C\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD\u3001\u8D75\u4E91\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u9A6C\u8D85\u3001\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"yxnxrbswhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u4EBA\u4E0D\u662F\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06",
		"id":23231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C60\u6237",
		"indexes":"sgmjzfzydbssmcs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u731B\u5C06\u5F20\u98DE\uFF0C\u5B57\u76CA\u5FB7\uFF0C\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u51FA\u8EAB",
		"id":23232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u8083",
		"indexes":"ccjjsnywbszypsqdtzglxsd",
		"question":"\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u65F6\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5468\u745C\u6D3E\u8C01\u53BB\u6253\u63A2\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u865A\u5B9E\u7684",
		"id":23233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"xlbdtjlzgldbs",
		"question":"\u5411\u5218\u5907\u7684\u63A8\u8350\u4E86\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"kcjbszglysbcdxz",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0E\u8C01\u6446\u51FA\u7684\u865A\u62DB",
		"id":23235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5DDD\u897F\u57CE",
		"indexes":"kcjbszglzsmdfssdyzhbzj",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9\u5B9E\u65BD\u7684\u4E00\u62DB\u7F13\u5175\u4E4B\u8BA1",
		"id":23236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"dmbsszsdsx",
		"question":"\u9093\u8302\u4E0D\u662F\u6B7B\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u624B\u4E0B",
		"id":23237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8700\u56FD",
		"indexes":"djszyhzbsngdzj",
		"question":"\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u6218\u5F79\u9EC4\u5FE0\u4E0D\u662F\u54EA\u56FD\u7684\u4E3B\u5C06",
		"id":23238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732E\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"cchsxcslsytcydgsslyzlzrbs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8C01\u8BB8\u660C\u72E9\u730E\u65F6\uFF0C\u7528\u4ED6\u66FE\u7528\u7684\u5F13\u5C04\u6740\u4E86\u4E00\u53EA\u9E7F\uFF0C\u8FD9\u4EBA\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23239
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u864E\u5C06",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdcw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5218\u5907\u7684\u79F0\u8C13",
		"id":23240
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"lbdzbs",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u7684\u5B57\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"gy201nccygddzzdbdbsnwjengrn",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143201\u5E74\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u4E8E\u5B98\u6E21\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u5927\u8D25\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF0C\u8FDB\u800C\u5357\u653B\u6C5D\u5357",
		"id":23242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u80DC",
		"indexes":"lbshdkghdxcbshjdzzzsjwsdhd",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\uFF0C\u8700\u6C49\u7684\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u76F8\u4F20\u4E0D\u662F\u6C49\u666F\u5E1D\u4E4B\u5B50\u4E2D\u5C71\u9756\u738B\u8C01\u7684\u540E\u4EE3\u3002",
		"id":23243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u7384",
		"indexes":"whjzydhzybssdsx",
		"question":"\u4E94\u864E\u5C06\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u624B\u4E0B",
		"id":23244
	},
	{
		"answer":"207\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lbsgmlqdzgljrdclzddzlfzdgbszgydsn",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90\u8BF7\u5F97\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u52A0\u5165\uFF0C\u5F97\u51FA\u9686\u4E2D\u5BF9\u7684\u6218\u7565\u65B9\u9488\uFF0C\u5927\u6982\u4E0D\u662F\u5728\u516C\u5143\u591A\u5C11\u5E74",
		"id":23245
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9879\u7FBD\u5C04\u7BAD\uFF0D\u767E\u53D1\u767E\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"xmnjxhyzq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u53E5\u6B47\u540E\u8BED\u6B63\u786E",
		"id":23246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u58F0\u4E1C\u51FB\u897F\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"ccxbtfzxjgnycbxysccmsbzhjxgczbzjqjzcxbjrczyqjxkdqcysjjjjwzxxsyjzjbs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u5174\u5175\u8BA8\u4F10\u5F20\u7EE3\uFF0C\u4E45\u653B\u5357\u9633\u57CE\u4E0D\u4E0B\u3002\u4E8E\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u547D\u58EB\u5175\u505A\u597D\u7EE7\u7EED\u653B\u57CE\u51C6\u5907\uFF0C\u81EA\u5DF1\u5374\u5047\u88C5\u4ECE\u897F\u5317\u89D2\u5165\u57CE\u3002\u8FD9\u4E00\u5207\u8D3E\u8BE9\u770B\u5F97\u6E05\u695A\uFF0C\u4E8E\u662F\u5C06\u8BA1\u5C31\u8BA1\u4E3A\u5F20\u7EE3\u732E\u4E0A\u4E00\u8BA1\uFF0C\u8FD9\u8BA1\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23247
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u9042",
		"indexes":"ljjbsccylljmcysd",
		"question":"\u79BB\u95F4\u8BA1\u4E0D\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u7528\u6765\u79BB\u95F4\u9A6C\u8D85\u4E0E\u8C01\u7684",
		"id":23248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u8FDB",
		"indexes":"dhmnwqyhgzdyqgtnlxlddzbssdsmqjjjjdmlyybj",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74\uFF0C\u5916\u621A\u4E0E\u5BA6\u5B98\u4E89\u6597\uFF0C\u5F15\u8D77\u5BAB\u5EF7\u5185\u4E71\u3002\u897F\u51C9\u7684\u8463\u5353\u4E0D\u662F\u6536\u5230\u8C01\u547D\u5176\u8FDB\u4EAC\u6551\u9A7E\u7684\u5BC6\u4EE4\uFF0C\u72B9\u8C6B\u4E0D\u51B3",
		"id":23250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F8E\u4EBA\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"stwykddzlbjshsztysqsdbssmjrdcljdzlbcerqfzlrhb",
		"question":"\u53F8\u5F92\u738B\u5141\u770B\u5230\u8463\u5353\u3001\u5415\u5E03\u7686\u662F\u597D\u8272\u4E4B\u5F92\uFF0C\u4E8E\u662F\u5DE7\u4F7F\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u8BA1\uFF0C\u8BA9\u8C82\u8749\u79BB\u95F4\u8463\u5353\u5415\u5E03\uFF0C\u4ECE\u800C\u8BA9\u5176\u7236\u5B50\u4E24\u4EBA\u706B\u5E76",
		"id":23251
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u5E72",
		"indexes":"yxnwbsddwyszybzyjjjjsccsscmzysjldd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5230\u4E1C\u5434\u6E38\u8BF4\u5468\u745C\uFF0C\u88AB\u5468\u745C\u5C06\u8BA1\u5C31\u8BA1\uFF0C\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u6740\u6B7B\u8521\u7441\u5F20\u5141\u6C34\u519B\u4E24\u90FD\u7763\uFF0C",
		"id":23252
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"yzyytsykrjdbs",
		"question":"\u4E0E\u5468\u745C\u4E00\u540C\u4E0A\u6F14\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"dsjgzdwysptbjltjptbqjs",
		"question":"\u5F53\u65F6\u848B\u5E72\u5728\u4E1C\u5434\u9047\u4E0A\u5E9E\u7EDF\uFF0C\u5E76\u6781\u529B\u63A8\u8350\u5E9E\u7EDF\u4E0D\u53BB\u89C1\u8C01",
		"id":23254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"ptyxrdwylbqsxjccrcjjmzcyhlszycbrlpdcjbs",
		"question":"\u5E9E\u7EDF\u6709\u5FC3\u8BA9\u4E1C\u5434\u4E0E\u5218\u5907\u53D6\u80DC\uFF0C\u732E\u8BA1\u66F9\u64CD\uFF0C\u8BA9\u66F9\u519B\u5C06\u6BCF\u53EA\u8239\u7528\u73AF\u8FDE\u4E0A\uFF0C\u8FD9\u6837\u66F9\u5175\u5982\u5C65\u5E73\u5730\uFF0C\u6B64\u8BA1\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20",
		"indexes":"zfdbbbxsm",
		"question":"\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u7238\u7238\u4E0D\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23256
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"mzctrzqzhbssm",
		"question":"'\u9A6C\u4E2D\u8D64\u5154\uFF0C\u4EBA\u4E2D\uFF1F'\u5176\u4E2D?\u53F7\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C21",
		"indexes":"hlzmSUSUzbygzmx",
		"question":"\u6325\u6CEA\u65A9\u9A6CSU\uFF0CSU\u5B57\u4E0D\u5E94\u8BE5\u600E\u4E48\u5199",
		"id":23258
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4F10\u65F6\u75C5\u6B7B\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F",
		"indexes":"kmbszmsd",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u4E0D\u662F\u600E\u4E48\u6B7B\u7684",
		"id":23259
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u4E91",
		"indexes":"yxzdsgyds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23260
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u4E91\u957F",
		"indexes":"shmcwdyzdcqswnfwrygzwtrxrjcqybyzrqgbzgsfxdbss",
		"question":"\u8BD7'\u6C49\u672B\u624D\u65E0\u654C\uFF0C\u4E91\u957F\u72EC\u51FA\u7FA4\uFF0C\u795E\u5A01\u80FD\u594B\u6B66\uFF0C\u5112\u96C5\u66F4\u77E5\u6587\uFF0C\u5929\u65E5\u5FC3\u5982\u955C\uFF0C\u300A\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u4E49\u8584\u4E91\uFF0C\u662D\u7136\u5343\u53E4\uFF0C\u4E0D\u6B62\u51A0\u4E09\u5206'\u5199\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"yxzdszglds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23262
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u572D",
		"indexes":"zgldfqbj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u4E0D\u53EB",
		"id":23263
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"hjzczybswhrss",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u8D3C\u7A0B\u5FD7\u8FDC\u4E0D\u662F\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u6740?",
		"id":23264
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"cbzzzxczjccdbs",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u732E\u7B56\u8BC8\u964D\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23265
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC\u96C0\u53F0",
		"indexes":"ccyrjxyjxwlsdzddjlyzjtqmbs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u56E0\u4EBA\u8FDB\u732E\u4E00\u5409\u7965\u7269\uFF0C\u52B3\u5E08\u52A8\u4F17\u7684\u642D\u5EFA\u4E86\u4E00\u5EA7\u5DE8\u53F0\uFF0C\u5176\u540D\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23266
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4E15",
		"indexes":"lsfqzlsbsyzsdqz",
		"question":"\u300C\u6D1B\u795E\u8D4B\u300D\u5176\u4E2D\u6D1B\u795E\u4E0D\u662F\u610F\u6307\u8C01\u7684\u59BB\u5B50?",
		"id":23267
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94\u4E08\u539F",
		"indexes":"kmzhycbfsbsddfbs",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u6B21\u5317\u4F10\u65F6\u75C5\u6B7B\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"zzzzyjbljszsfjmxbkqebyjcddbs",
		"question":"\u5728\u4F5C\u6218\u4E2D\u773C\u775B\u88AB\u6D41\u7BAD\u5C04\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8BF4\uFF1A\u300C\u7236\u7CBE\u6BCD\u8840\u4E0D\u53EF\u5F03\u300D\u800C\u628A\u773C\u775B\u5403\u6389\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23269
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"sgsqcwddghyxdbss",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u4ECE\u672A\u5F97\u5230\u8FC7\u6C49\u7389\u73BA\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795D\u878D",
		"indexes":"kmznmscqqqzmhmhdfrbj",
		"question":"\u5B54\u660E\u5F81\u5357\u86EE\u65F6\u66FE\u4E03\u64D2\u4E03\u7EB5\u5B5F\u83B7\uFF0C\u5B5F\u83B7\u7684\u592B\u4EBA\u4E0D\u53EB\uFF1F",
		"id":23271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"gydyzbss",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u517B\u5B50\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23272
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u575A",
		"indexes":"nywjzlbyqtk",
		"question":"\u90A3\u4E00\u4F4D\u541B\u4E3B\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u6709\u53BB\u6295\u9760?",
		"id":23273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"qbcsdbs",
		"question":"\u4E03\u6B65\u6210\u8BD7\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u8D21",
		"indexes":"yxnwbsxccbgscxqxdzxhbscss",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u62A5\u544A\u5B59\u7B56\u88AD\u53D6\u8BB8\u90FD\u4E4B\u5FC3\uFF0C\u540E\u88AB\u5B59\u7B56\u6240\u6740?",
		"id":23275
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u677F\u6865\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"szycmdzygbssm",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u8D75\u4E91\u6210\u540D\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u5404\u4E0D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23277
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"qwcjdglbjsddfqsbshr",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u66FE\u7ECF\u5F53\u8FC7\u5218\u5907\u519B\u5E08\u7684\u300C\u5355\u798F\u300D\u5176\u5B9E\u4E0D\u662F\u4F55\u4EBA?",
		"id":23278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u6027",
		"indexes":"xhdbsbssqyy",
		"question":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7\u4E0D\u662F\u88AB\u8C01\u5C04\u53BB\u4E00\u773C?",
		"id":23279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E54\u56FD\u516C",
		"indexes":"zyqdxqbssdne",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u5A36\u7684\u5C0F\u4E54\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u5973\u513F?",
		"id":23280
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E25\u989C",
		"indexes":"cszydtjjwjjjdsdzhhstjzfdjlbs",
		"question":"\u79F0\u8700\u4E2D\u6709\u65AD\u5934\u5C06\u519B\uFF0C\u65E0\u964D\u5C06\u519B\uFF0C\u4F46\u662F\u5230\u6700\u540E\u8FD8\u662F\u6295\u964D\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u5C06\u9886\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23281
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6062",
		"indexes":"tlbsjlmcdbs",
		"question":"\u66FF\u5218\u5907\u8BF4\u964D\u4E86\u9A6C\u8D85\u7684\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23282
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwkmjwdfhbsysjyebgzyprzs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5B54\u660E\u501F\u5B8C\u4E1C\u98CE\u540E\u4E0D\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u63A5\u5E94\uFF0C\u800C\u907F\u8FC7\u5468\u745C\u6D3E\u4EBA\u8FFD\u6740?",
		"id":23283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"cbzzddgcymzlzcdbs",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u7684\u5927\u529F\u81E3\uFF0C\u6709\u300C\u7F8E\u5468\u90CE\u300D\u4E4B\u79F0\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwzsxrdzjaddbss",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u53EA\u8EAB\u9677\u5165\u654C\u9635\u6551\u963F\u6597\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"gylccsdzdbs",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u79BB\u66F9\u64CD\u65F6\u5E26\u8D70\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9E\u7EDF",
		"indexes":"sdlbrtxdjxdqyzdbs",
		"question":"\u8BF4\u52A8\u5218\u5907\uFF0C\u8BA9\u4ED6\u4E0B\u5B9A\u51B3\u5FC3\u593A\u53D6\u76CA\u5DDE\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u4E11",
		"indexes":"ptbbsqzydyybs",
		"question":"\u5E9E\u7EDF\u4E0D\u88AB\u5B59\u6743\u91CD\u7528\u7684\u539F\u56E0\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23288
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"dwbssjsjccd",
		"question":"\u5178\u97E6\u4E0D\u662F\u8C01\u4ECB\u7ECD\u7ED9\u66F9\u64CD\u7684?",
		"id":23289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F92\u624B\u640F\u864E",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxcjhcdyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E9B\u4E0D\u662F\u8BB8\u891A\u53EB\u864E\u75F4\u7684\u539F\u56E0",
		"id":23290
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u742C",
		"indexes":"zglshsgnzbsysdz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u6B7B\u540E\uFF0C\u8700\u56FD\u5185\u653F\u4E0D\u662F\u7531\u8C01\u4EE3\u4E4B?",
		"id":23291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4E2A\u9526\u56CA",
		"indexes":"lbdwgqxnszgljtdbs",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5230\u5434\u56FD\u300C\u5A36\u65B0\u5A18\u300D\u65F6\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7ED9\u4ED6\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"qwcyhssdjdbsxmnwjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u6210\u8BED& #39;\u6D51\u8EAB\u662F\u80C6& #39;\u5C06\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":23293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"sgyyzcrdbmjszbsbnwjssp",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u4E2D\uFF0C\u66F9\u4EC1\u7684\u516B\u95E8\u91D1\u9501\u9635\u4E0D\u662F\u88AB\u54EA\u4F4D\u519B\u5E08\u6240\u7834?",
		"id":23294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u826F",
		"indexes":"rcmswcbmzlszdbs",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u79F0\u300C\u9A6C\u6C0F\u4E94\u5E38\uFF0C\u767D\u7709\u6700\u826F\u300D\u6240\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F?",
		"id":23295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsszglhhxdlxtnstnsszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u548C\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D\u5218\u534F\u540C\u5E74\u751F,\u540C\u5E74\u6B7B,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssdcsxgdrwzszjzdslbydzdsbstpbdzfjzzydzfmccszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8C82\u8749\u662F\u865A\u6784\u7684\u4EBA\u7269,\u6B63\u53F2\u4E2D\u8BB0\u8F7D\u7684\u662F\u5415\u5E03\u4E0E\u8463\u5353\u7684\u4F8D\u5A62\u79C1\u901A,\u6015\u88AB\u8463\u5353\u53D1\u89C9,\u6700\u7EC8\u4E0E\u8463\u5353\u53CD\u76EE\u6210\u4EC7,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsshxdqsbfdtcphdhzszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D\u5176\u5B9E\u6BD4\u5E9F\u6389\u4ED6\u66F9\u4E15\u6D3B\u5F97\u8FD8\u957F,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsssgsqmdsdzeszdyyflsdrszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6,\u53D6\u540D\u90FD\u662F\u5355\u5B57,\u800C\u53CC\u5B57\u591A\u7528\u4E8E\u72AF\u4E86\u4E8B\u7684\u4EBA,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23299
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssgydwqbsqlyydywsgshmyzzwqszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u6B66\u5668\u4E0D\u662F\u9752\u9F99\u5043\u6708\u5200,\u56E0\u4E3A\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u8FD8\u6CA1\u6709\u8FD9\u79CD\u6B66\u5668,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssshmjwpqsbhxznrsdzybgsgszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u8700\u6C49\u540D\u5C06\u738B\u5E73\u5176\u5B9E\u4E0D\u4F1A\u5199\u5B57,\u80FD\u8BA4\u8BC6\u7684\u5B57\u4E5F\u4E0D\u8FC7\u5341\u4E2A,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsscccxlddxssqsdszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u201C\u66F9\u51B2\u79F0\u8C61\u201D\u91CC\u7684\u5927\u8C61\u662F\u5B59\u6743\u9001\u7684,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsszfdzqxhssdjszzzbzsdxhydynszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u6B63\u59BB\u590F\u4FAF\u6C0F\u662F\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\u88AB\u65A9\u6740\u7684\u590F\u4FAF\u6E0A\u7684\u517B\u5973,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssddydbbszfeslbszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u6253\u7763\u90AE\u7684\u5E76\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u98DE\u800C\u662F\u5218\u5907,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsszglhhxdlxtnstnssjdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u548C\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D\u5218\u534F\u540C\u5E74\u751F,\u540C\u5E74\u6B7B,\u662F\u5047\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23305
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssdcszsdrwlbytstpbdzfjzzydzfmccszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8C82\u8749\u662F\u771F\u5B9E\u7684\u4EBA\u7269,\u5415\u5E03\u4E0E\u5979\u79C1\u901A,\u6015\u88AB\u8463\u5353\u53D1\u89C9,\u6700\u7EC8\u4E0E\u8463\u5353\u53CD\u76EE\u6210\u4EC7,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsshxdqsbfdtcphddszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D\u5176\u5B9E\u6BD4\u5E9F\u6389\u4ED6\u66F9\u4E15\u6D3B\u5F97\u77ED,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsssgsqmdsszedzdyyflsdrszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6,\u53D6\u540D\u90FD\u662F\u53CC\u5B57,\u800C\u5355\u5B57\u591A\u7528\u4E8E\u72AF\u4E86\u4E8B\u7684\u4EBA,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssgydwqsqlyydywsgsyzzwqszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u6B66\u5668\u662F\u9752\u9F99\u5043\u6708\u5200,\u56E0\u4E3A\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u6709\u8FD9\u79CD\u6B66\u5668,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssshmjwpxfwcssydrjszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u8700\u6C49\u540D\u5C06\u738B\u5E73\u5B66\u5BCC\u4E94\u8F66,\u662F\u5C11\u6709\u7684\u5112\u5C06,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23310
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsscccxlddxsccsdszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u201C\u66F9\u51B2\u79F0\u8C61\u201D\u91CC\u7684\u5927\u8C61\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u9001\u7684,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23311
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lsszfdzqxhssdjszzzbzsdxhydmmszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u6B63\u59BB\u590F\u4FAF\u6C0F\u662F\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\u88AB\u65A9\u6740\u7684\u590F\u4FAF\u6E0A\u7684\u59B9\u59B9,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"lssddydbbszfesgyszdm",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A,\u6253\u7763\u90AE\u7684\u5E76\u4E0D\u662F\u5F20\u98DE\u800C\u662F\u5173\u7FBD,\u662F\u771F\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"czyyszdynwiszsdys",
		"question":"\u201C\u91C7\u4E4B\u6B32\u9057\u8C01\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u9057\u201D\u5FF5wi,\u662F\u8D60\u9001\u7684\u610F\u601D\u3002",
		"id":23314
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"grswssrmphzsymdyjlbxd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u8BF4\u95FB\u6C34\u58F0\u5982\u9E23\u4F69\u73AF,\u8FD9\u662F\u8881\u7267\u7684\u6E38\u8BB0\u91CC\u8FB9\u5199\u7684\u3002",
		"id":23315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"yjtszjcsyjysjxsmdmhzy",
		"question":"\u201C\u8981\u89C1\u5929\u5B59\u7EC7\u9526\u6210\u201D\u662F\u53F6\u5609\u83B9\u9001\u7ED9\u5B66\u751F\u4EEC\u7684\u7F8E\u597D\u795D\u613F\u3002",
		"id":23316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"yyxzssxsjsqywhczls",
		"question":"\u201C\u4EA6\u4F59\u5FC3\u4E4B\u6240\u5584\u516E,\u867D\u4E5D\u6B7B\u5176\u72B9\u672A\u6094\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u79BB\u9A9A\u300B\u3002",
		"id":23317
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"hjjmysntdcsywfgbt",
		"question":"\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u6CA1\u6709\u6536\u5357\u5510\u7684\u8BCD,\u662F\u56E0\u4E3A\u98CE\u683C\u4E0D\u540C\u3002",
		"id":23318
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"gmrslhzsblgzcwsdfzc",
		"question":"\u90ED\u6CAB\u82E5\u8BF4\u674E\u540E\u4E3B\u662F\u201C\u53D8\u4F36\u5DE5\u4E4B\u8BCD\u4E3A\u58EB\u5927\u592B\u4E4B\u8BCD\u201D\u3002",
		"id":23319
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"qydmrdbdsscddmh",
		"question":"\u5C48\u539F\u7684\u7F8E\u4EBA\u4EE3\u8868\u7684\u662F\u662F\u624D\u5FB7\u7684\u7F8E\u597D\u3002",
		"id":23320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"hjjsgczc",
		"question":"\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u662F\u6B4C\u8F9E\u4E4B\u8BCD\u3002",
		"id":23321
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"sdpyjrdzzzeyzbb",
		"question":"\u82CF\u4E1C\u5761\u56E0\u5377\u5165\u515A\u4E89\u4E4B\u4E2D\u800C\u4E00\u518D\u88AB\u8D2C\u3002",
		"id":23322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"hcznxnxdzhzjszhnrsfdgq",
		"question":"\u597D\u8BCD\u53EA\u80FD\u5199\u5973\u6027\u7684\u7C2A\u82B1\u7167\u955C\u3001\u68B3\u5986\u3001\u6000\u5FF5\u4EBA\u3001\u601D\u5987\u7684\u611F\u60C5\u3002",
		"id":23323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"gjqfjbsswzdcj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8FC7\u5C3D\u5343\u5E06\u7686\u4E0D\u662F\u201D\u662F\u97E6\u5E84\u7684\u8BCD\u53E5\u3002",
		"id":23324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"hjjlbddysgcspsm",
		"question":"\u300A\u82B1\u95F4\u96C6\u300B\u91CC\u8FB9\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u9996\u6B4C\u8BCD\u662F\u300A\u83E9\u8428\u86EE\u300B\u3002",
		"id":23325
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79CB\u591C\u666F\u8272",
		"indexes":"ylwtsmtjfyhdcmzljcmxds",
		"question":"\u201C\u6708\u843D\u4E4C\u557C\u971C\u6EE1\u5929,\u6C5F\u67AB\u6E14\u706B\u5BF9\u6101\u7720\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u4E24\u53E5\u8BCD\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23326
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u671D\u540D\u5C06\u674E\u5E7F",
		"indexes":"dslcfjzbjhmdyszdlcfjzds",
		"question":"\u201C\u4F46\u4F7F\u9F99\u57CE\u98DE\u5C06\u5728,\u4E0D\u6559\u80E1\u9A6C\u5EA6\u9634\u5C71\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u9F99\u57CE\u98DE\u5C06\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23327
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u752B",
		"indexes":"xmswldswgtcjcdsrqzhcssds",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u56DB\u4F4D\u6765\u90FD\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5510\u671D\u6770\u51FA\u7684\u8BD7\u4EBA,\u5176\u4E2D\u53F7\u79F0\u201C\u8BD7\u5723\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23328
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E90\u5C71",
		"indexes":"lbbxdflzxsqcysyhljtzdsngfjq",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u7B14\u4E0B\u7684\u201C\u98DE\u6D41\u76F4\u4E0B\u4E09\u5343\u5C3A,\u7591\u662F\u94F6\u6CB3\u843D\u4E5D\u5929\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u98CE\u666F\u533A?",
		"id":23329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u675C\u7267\u300A\u79CB\u5915\u300B",
		"indexes":"tjyslrswkqnznxcz",
		"question":"\u201C\u5929\u9636\u591C\u8272\u51C9\u5982\u6C34,\u5367\u770B\u7275\u725B\u7EC7\u5973\u661F\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA",
		"id":23330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u53C8\u7EFF\u6C5F\u5357\u5CB8",
		"indexes":"yxnyjssdsrwasbcgzzdmj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u5B8B\u4EE3\u8BD7\u4EBA\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u300A\u6CCA\u8239\u74DC\u6D32\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u540D\u53E5",
		"id":23331
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529D\u541B\u66F4\u5C3D\u4E00\u676F\u9152",
		"indexes":"yxznbdsrhlpyyyxbdsjs",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6700\u80FD\u8868\u8FBE\u8BD7\u4EBA\u548C\u8001\u670B\u53CB\u4F9D\u4F9D\u60DC\u522B\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BCD\u5B50\u60C5\u6DF1",
		"indexes":"syccxbdschbddsxgqs",
		"question":"\u201C\u8C01\u8A00\u5BF8\u8349\u5FC3,\u62A5\u5F97\u4E09\u6625\u6656\u3002\u201D\u8868\u8FBE\u7684\u601D\u60F3\u611F\u60C5\u662F",
		"id":23333
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5236\u5EA6\u4E0D\u5408\u7406",
		"indexes":"lsmnszshwxtnfyesjlds",
		"question":"\u674E\u7EC5\u300A\u60AF\u519C\u300B\u8BD7\u4E2D\u201C\u56DB\u6D77\u65E0\u95F2\u7530,\u519C\u592B\u72B9\u997F\u6B7B\u3002\u201D\u63ED\u9732\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23334
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6842\u82B1",
		"indexes":"hxqbshszshzdylzdhzds",
		"question":"\u201C\u4F55\u987B\u5029\u78A7\u6DF1\u7EA2\u8272,\u81EA\u662F\u82B1\u4E2D\u7B2C\u4E00\u6D41\u201C\u4E2D\u7684\u82B1\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AF9\u5B50",
		"indexes":"ydqsbfslgyzpyzqmwjhjjredxnbfmxdsnzzw",
		"question":"\u201C\u54AC\u5B9A\u9752\u5C71\u4E0D\u653E\u677E,\u7ACB\u6839\u539F\u5728\u7834\u5CA9\u4E2D\u3002\u5343\u78E8\u4E07\u51FB\u8FD8\u575A\u52B2,\u4EFB\u5C14\u4E1C\u897F\u5357\u5317\u98CE\u3002\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u79CD\u690D\u7269?",
		"id":23336
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5408\u6B22\u82B1",
		"indexes":"hhszsyybdsdjxrxnwjrkzdhhzds",
		"question":"\u201C\u5408\u660F\u5C1A\u77E5\u65F6,\u9E33\u9E2F\u4E0D\u72EC\u5BBF\u3002\u4F46\u89C1\u65B0\u4EBA\u7B11,\u90A3\u95FB\u65E7\u4EBA\u54ED\u3002\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u5408\u660F\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23337
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167\u300A\u6B66\u9675\u6625\u300B",
		"indexes":"wsrfssxyylxlcznwcrnsc",
		"question":"\u201C\u7269\u662F\u4EBA\u975E\u4E8B\u4E8B\u4F11,\u6B32\u8BED\u6CEA\u5148\u6D41\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BCD\u4EBA\u90A3\u9996\u8BCD?",
		"id":23338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8DEF\u4E0A\u884C\u4EBA\u6B32\u65AD\u9B42",
		"indexes":"qmsjyffdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u6E05\u660E\u65F6\u8282\u96E8\u7EB7\u7EB7\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23339
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7267\u7AE5\u9065\u6307\u674F\u82B1\u6751",
		"indexes":"jwjjhcydxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u501F\u95EE\u9152\u5BB6\u4F55\u5904\u6709\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u70DF\u6563\u5165\u4E94\u4FAF\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"rmhgclzdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E5\u66AE\u6C49\u5BAB\u4F20\u8721\u70DB\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5362\u6A58\u6768\u6885\u6B21\u7B2C\u65B0",
		"indexes":"lfsxsscdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u7F57\u6D6E\u5C71\u4E0B\u56DB\u65F6\u6625\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23342
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F9E\u957F\u4F5C\u5CAD\u5357\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"rdlzsbkdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E5\u5556\u8354\u679D\u4E09\u767E\u9897\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23343
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u9650\u98CE\u5149\u5C3D\u88AB\u5360",
		"indexes":"blpdysjdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0D\u8BBA\u5E73\u5730\u4E0E\u5C71\u5C16\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23344
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E3A\u8C01\u8F9B\u82E6\u4E3A\u8C01\u751C",
		"indexes":"cdbhcmhdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u91C7\u5F97\u767E\u82B1\u6210\u871C\u540E\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23345
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E94\u5C06\u6027\u547D\u9010\u8F7B\u8F66",
		"indexes":"wdymybzdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u95FB\u9053\u7389\u95E8\u72B9\u88AB\u906E\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u5165\u6C5F\u98CE\u534A\u5165\u4E91",
		"indexes":"jcsgrffdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u9526\u57CE\u4E1D\u7BA1\u65E5\u7EB7\u7EB7\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u95F4\u80FD\u5F97\u51E0\u56DE\u95FB",
		"indexes":"cqzytsydxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6B64\u66F2\u53EA\u5E94\u5929\u4E0A\u6709\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u526A\u526A\u8F7B\u98CE\u9635\u9635\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"wascyjlxjlscdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u300A\u6625\u591C\u300B\u201C\u91D1\u7089\u9999\u5C3D\u6F0F\u58F0\u6B8B\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23349
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u79FB\u82B1\u5F71\u4E0A\u680F\u6746",
		"indexes":"csnrmbddxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6625\u8272\u607C\u4EBA\u7720\u4E0D\u5F97\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u60C5\u4F55\u4F3C\u65E0\u60C5",
		"indexes":"xjzrbjdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u76F8\u89C1\u4E89\u5982\u4E0D\u89C1\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D",
		"indexes":"klhggqgcyjtddwxrdsnwsr",
		"question":"\u201C\u53EF\u601C\u8352\u53E4\u9F9A\u6CC9\u9AA8,\u66FE\u6709\u60CA\u5929\u52A8\u5730\u6587\u201D\u5F62\u5BB9\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA?",
		"id":23352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706B\u70E7\u8D64\u58C1",
		"indexes":"dfbyzlbtqcsseqzlddfzdssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E1C\u98CE\u4E0D\u4E0E\u5468\u90CE\u4FBF,\u94DC\u96C0\u6625\u6DF1\u9501\u4E8C\u4E54\u201D\u8FD9\u91CC\u7684\u4E1C\u98CE\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u661F\u4E71\u7D2B\u70DF",
		"indexes":"lhztddxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u7089\u706B\u7167\u5929\u5730\u201C\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u4E91\u6DF1\u5904\u6709\u4EBA\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"yshssjxdxjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u8FDC\u4E0A\u5BD2\u5C71\u77F3\u5F84\u659C\u201C\u7684\u4E0B\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u628A\u9152\u95EE\u9752\u5929",
		"indexes":"myjsydxjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u660E\u6708\u51E0\u65F6\u6709\u201C\u7684\u4E0B\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98DE\u6765\u98DE\u53BB\u843D\u8C01\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"lycdtlhdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4E1C\u6843\u674E\u82B1\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5750\u89C1\u843D\u82B1\u957F\u53F9\u606F",
		"indexes":"lynexysdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6D1B\u9633\u5973\u513F\u60DC\u989C\u8272\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u7ACB\u758F\u7BF1\u8DA3\u65E0\u7A77",
		"indexes":"hkbbbhcdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u82B1\u5F00\u4E0D\u5E76\u767E\u82B1\u4E1B\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F55\u66FE\u5782\u843D\u5317\u98CE\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"nkztblhdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5B81\u53EF\u679D\u5934\u62B1\u843D\u82B1\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u767E\u676F",
		"indexes":"lbdjjjzhxyydsbn",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u7684\u300A\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152\u300B\u4E2D\u201C\u4F1A\u987B\u4E00\u996E\u201D\u591A\u5C11\u676F\u5462",
		"id":23361
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5144\u59B9\u5173\u7CFB",
		"indexes":"bfyjrjsedlzdjrhlynssmgx",
		"question":"\u201C\u5317\u65B9\u6709\u4F73\u4EBA,\u7EDD\u4E16\u800C\u72EC\u7ACB\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u4F73\u4EBA\u548C\u674E\u5EF6\u5E74\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB?",
		"id":23362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6211\u8A00\u79CB\u65E5\u80DC\u6625\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgfqbjldxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u81EA\u53E4\u9022\u79CB\u60B2\u5BC2\u5BE5\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23363
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FBF\u5F15\u8BD7\u60C5\u5230\u78A7\u9704",
		"indexes":"qkyhpysdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6674\u7A7A\u4E00\u9E64\u6392\u4E91\u4E0A\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u76D8\u73CD\u7F9E\u76F4\u4E07\u94B1",
		"indexes":"jzqjdsqdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u91D1\u6A3D\u6E05\u9152\u6597\u5341\u5343\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23365
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FFD\u590D\u4E58\u821F\u68A6\u65E5\u8FB9",
		"indexes":"xlcdbxsdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u95F2\u6765\u5782\u9493\u78A7\u6EAA\u4E0A\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F39\u7434\u590D\u957F\u5578",
		"indexes":"dzyhldxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u72EC\u5750\u5E7D\u7BC1\u91CC\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23367
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u6708\u6765\u76F8\u7167",
		"indexes":"slrbzqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6DF1\u6797\u4EBA\u4E0D\u77E5\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23368
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5367\u85AA\u5C1D\u80C6",
		"indexes":"lbgknyglssjezyzlg",
		"question":"\u674E\u767D\u611F\u6168\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6\u800C\u4F5C\u300A\u8D8A\u4E2D\u89C8\u53E4\u300B",
		"id":23369
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B1\u4E2D\u6C14\u8282\u6700\u9AD8\u575A",
		"indexes":"xnfhylrdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u96EA\u8650\u98CE\u53F7\u6108\u51DB\u7136\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23370
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u803B\u5411\u4E1C\u541B\u66F4\u4E5E\u601C",
		"indexes":"gszhplqdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u8FC7\u65F6\u81EA\u4F1A\u98D8\u96F6\u53BB\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u8BD8",
		"indexes":"wwrcsftdzs",
		"question":"\u738B\u7EF4\u4EBA\u79F0\u201C\u8BD7\u4F5B\u201D,\u4ED6\u7684\u5B57\u662F",
		"id":23372
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u9752\u886B",
		"indexes":"ppxlyxmngcy",
		"question":"\u300A\u7435\u7436\u884C\u300B\u91CC\u6709\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u6210\u8BED",
		"id":23373
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EE5\u89C2\u6CA7\u6D77",
		"indexes":"dljsdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E1C\u4E34\u78A3\u77F3\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C71\u5C9B\u7AE6\u5CD9",
		"indexes":"shdddxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C34\u4F55\u6FB9\u6FB9\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767E\u8349\u4E30\u8302",
		"indexes":"smcsdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6811\u6728\u4E1B\u751F\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u628A\u8F9B\u9178\u6CEA",
		"indexes":"mzhtydxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6EE1\u7EB8\u8352\u5510\u8A00\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23377
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"zwzzzdsxmnwsr",
		"question":"\u201C\u9189\u7FC1\u201D\u6700\u65E9\u6307\u7684\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA",
		"id":23378
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u91CC\u6C5F\u9675\u4E00\u65E5\u8FD8",
		"indexes":"ccbdcyjdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u671D\u8F9E\u767D\u5E1D\u5F69\u4E91\u95F4\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23379
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u821F\u5DF2\u8FC7\u4E07\u91CD\u5C71",
		"indexes":"laystbzdxyjsm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E24\u5CB8\u733F\u58F0\u557C\u4E0D\u4F4F\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23380
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u5929\u516B\u6708\u5373\u98DE\u96EA",
		"indexes":"bfjdbczdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5317\u98CE\u5377\u5730\u767D\u8349\u6298\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23381
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u6811\u4E07\u6811\u68A8\u82B1\u5F00",
		"indexes":"hryycflxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5FFD\u5982\u4E00\u591C\u6625\u98CE\u6765\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23382
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72D0\u88D8\u4E0D\u6696\u9526\u887E\u8584",
		"indexes":"srzlslmxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6563\u5165\u73E0\u5E18\u6E7F\u7F57\u5E55\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23383
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90FD\u62A4\u94C1\u8863\u51B7\u96BE\u7740",
		"indexes":"jjjgbdkdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5C06\u519B\u89D2\u5F13\u4E0D\u5F97\u63A7\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23384
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6101\u4E91\u60E8\u6DE1\u4E07\u91CC\u51DD",
		"indexes":"hhlgbzbxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u701A\u6D77\u9611\u5E72\u767E\u4E08\u51B0\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23385
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u7434\u7435\u7436\u4E0E\u7F8C\u7B1B",
		"indexes":"zjzjygkxjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E2D\u519B\u7F6E\u9152\u996E\u5F52\u5BA2\u201D\u4E0B\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23386
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F1A\u9762\u5B89\u53EF\u77E5",
		"indexes":"dlzqzdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u9053\u8DEF\u963B\u4E14\u957F\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23387
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534A\u6C5F\u745F\u745F\u534A\u6C5F\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"ydcypszdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\u9053\u6B8B\u9633\u94FA\u6C34\u4E2D\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23388
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9732\u4F3C\u73CD\u73E0\u6708\u4F3C\u5F13",
		"indexes":"kljycsyqjxyj",
		"question":"\u53EF\u601C\u4E5D\u6708\u521D\u4E09\u591C,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23389
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u753B\u697C\u897F\u7554\u6842\u5802\u4E1C",
		"indexes":"zyxczyfqjxyj",
		"question":"\u6628\u591C\u661F\u8FB0\u6628\u591C\u98CE,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23390
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5FC3\u6709\u7075\u7280\u4E00\u70B9\u901A",
		"indexes":"swcfsfyqjxyj",
		"question":"\u8EAB\u65E0\u5F69\u51E4\u53CC\u98DE\u7FFC,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23391
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5206\u66F9\u5C04\u8986\u814A\u706F\u7EA2",
		"indexes":"gzsgcjnqjxyj",
		"question":"\u9694\u5EA7\u9001\u94A9\u6625\u9152\u6696,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23392
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u6CCA\u79E6\u6DEE\u8FD1\u9152\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"ylhsylsdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u70DF\u7B3C\u5BD2\u6C34\u6708\u7B3C\u6C99\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23393
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9694\u6C5F\u72B9\u5531\u540E\u5EAD\u82B1",
		"indexes":"snbzwghdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u5546\u5973\u4E0D\u77E5\u4EA1\u56FD\u6068\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23394
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u77E5\u5411\u8C01\u8FB9",
		"indexes":"ypwydbjqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E00\u7247\u6C6A\u6D0B\u90FD\u4E0D\u89C1\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23395
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u4E34\u78A3\u77F3\u6709\u9057\u7BC7",
		"indexes":"wsyqnwwhbjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5F80\u4E8B\u8D8A\u5343\u5E74\u9B4F\u6B66\u6325\u97AD\u201D,\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23396
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6362\u4E86\u4EBA\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xsqfjysjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8427\u745F\u79CB\u98CE\u4ECA\u53C8\u662F\u201D\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23397
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u60CA\u8D77\u9E33\u9E2F\u51FA\u6D6A\u82B1",
		"indexes":"wdaskfjqjxj",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E0\u7AEF\u5CB8\u4E0A\u72C2\u98CE\u6025\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u53E5",
		"id":23398
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B32\u996E\u7435\u7436\u9A6C\u4E0A\u50AC",
		"indexes":"ptmjygbqjxj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8461\u8404\u7F8E\u9152\u591C\u5149\u676F\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u53E5",
		"id":23399
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6708\u660E\u7F8C\u7B1B\u620D\u697C\u95F4",
		"indexes":"xjhtmmhxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u96EA\u51C0\u80E1\u5929\u7267\u9A6C\u8FD8\u201D,\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23400
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96EA\u4E0A\u7A7A\u7559\u9A6C\u884C\u5904",
		"indexes":"shlzbjjdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u5C71\u56DE\u8DEF\u8F6C\u4E0D\u89C1\u541B\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23401
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6D45\u8349\u624D\u80FD\u6CA1\u9A6C\u8E44",
		"indexes":"lhjymrydxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E71\u82B1\u6E10\u6B32\u8FF7\u4EBA\u773C\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23402
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F53\u987B\u5415\u5E03\u9A91",
		"indexes":"ctwryjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u8D64\u5154\u65E0\u4EBA\u7528\u201D,\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23403
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u95F4\u591A\u5C11\u884C\u4EBA\u6CEA",
		"indexes":"ygtxqjsxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u90C1\u5B64\u53F0\u4E0B\u6E05\u6C5F\u6C34\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23404
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EF\u601C\u65E0\u6570\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xbwzaqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u897F\u5317\u671B\u957F\u5B89\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23405
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BED\u4E0D\u60CA\u4EBA\u6B7B\u4E0D\u4F11",
		"indexes":"wrxpdjjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E3A\u4EBA\u6027\u7656\u803D\u4F73\u53E5\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23406
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E0\u5BB6\u6B22\u4E50\u51E0\u5BB6\u6101",
		"indexes":"yzwwzjzqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6708\u5B50\u5F2F\u5F2F\u7167\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23407
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u6CC9\u6EE1\u6E05\u542C",
		"indexes":"syyslqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u677E\u6708\u591C\u751F\u51C9\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23408
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7528\u7BAD\u5F53\u7528\u957F",
		"indexes":"wgdwqqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u633D\u5F13\u5F53\u633D\u5F3A\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23409
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64D2\u8D3C\u5148\u64D2\u738B",
		"indexes":"srxsmqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5C04\u4EBA\u5148\u5C04\u9A6C\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23410
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53EA\u7F18\u8EAB\u5728\u6700\u9AD8\u5C42",
		"indexes":"bwfyzwyqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E0D\u754F\u6D6E\u4E91\u906E\u671B\u773C\u201D\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23411
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u6C5F\u6C34\u6696\u9E2D\u5148\u77E5",
		"indexes":"zwthslzdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u7AF9\u5916\u6843\u82B1\u4E09\u4E24\u679D\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23412
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82B3\u8349\u840B\u840B\u9E66\u9E49\u6D32",
		"indexes":"qcllhysdxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u6674\u5DDD\u5386\u5386\u6C49\u9633\u6811\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23413
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6625\u98CE\u4E0D\u5EA6\u7389\u95E8\u5173",
		"indexes":"qdhxyyldxyjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u7F8C\u7B1B\u4F55\u987B\u6028\u6768\u67F3\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23414
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5404\u9886\u98CE\u9A9A\u6570\u767E\u5E74",
		"indexes":"jsdycrcdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C5F\u5C71\u4EE3\u6709\u624D\u4EBA\u51FA\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23415
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A6\u56DE\u5439\u89D2\u8FDE\u8425",
		"indexes":"zltdkjdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u9189\u91CC\u6311\u706F\u770B\u5251\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23416
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C01\u5BB6\u65B0\u71D5\u5544\u6625\u6CE5",
		"indexes":"jczyznsdxjs",
		"question":"\u201C\u51E0\u5904\u65E9\u83BA\u4E89\u6696\u6811\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u53E5\u662F",
		"id":23417
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94DC\u96C0\u6625\u6DF1\u9501\u4E8C\u4E54",
		"indexes":"dfbyzlbdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E1C\u98CE\u4E0D\u4E0E\u5468\u90CE\u4FBF\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23418
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u559C",
		"indexes":"jhfgltxygzdfhzyjbtmszssdmzssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E45\u65F1\u9022\u7518\u9716,\u4ED6\u4E61\u9047\u6545\u77E5\u3002\u6D1E\u623F\u82B1\u70DB\u591C,\u91D1\u699C\u9898\u540D\u65F6\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u9996\u8BD7\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23419
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u98CE\u65E0\u529B\u767E\u82B1\u6B8B",
		"indexes":"xjsnbynqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u76F8\u89C1\u65F6\u96BE\u522B\u4EA6\u96BE\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23420
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8721\u70AC\u6210\u7070\u6CEA\u59CB\u5E72",
		"indexes":"ccdssfjqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6625\u8695\u5230\u6B7B\u4E1D\u65B9\u5C3D\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23421
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591C\u541F\u5E94\u89C9\u6708\u5149\u5BD2",
		"indexes":"xjdcybgqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6653\u955C\u4F46\u6101\u4E91\u9B13\u6539\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23422
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u9E1F\u6BB7\u52E4\u4E3A\u63A2\u770B",
		"indexes":"pscqwdlqjxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u84EC\u5C71\u6B64\u53BB\u65E0\u591A\u8DEF\u201D,\u8BF7\u63A5\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23423
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70C8\u706B\u711A\u70E7\u82E5\u7B49\u95F2",
		"indexes":"qcwzcssxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u9524\u4E07\u51FF\u51FA\u6DF1\u5C71\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23424
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8981\u7559\u6E05\u767D\u5728\u4EBA\u95F4",
		"indexes":"fssghbpxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u7C89\u8EAB\u788E\u9AA8\u6D51\u4E0D\u6015\u201D\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23425
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C46\u853B\u68A2\u5934\u4E8C\u6708\u521D",
		"indexes":"ppnnssyxyj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5A09\u5A09\u8885\u8885\u5341\u4E09\u4F59\u201D,\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5",
		"id":23426
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u53BB\u79CB\u6765",
		"indexes":"cyqylhczsjtsylxr",
		"question":"\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u4E03\u6708\u6D41\u706B\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u300A\u8BD7\u7ECF\u300B,\u5B83\u662F\u7528\u6765\u5F62\u5BB9",
		"id":23427
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706F\u706B\u5373\u5C06\u7184\u706D",
		"indexes":"zlxtqbdmrhsnrqzdhlsczdhlssz",
		"question":"\u201C\u4F17\u91CC\u5BFB\u5979\u5343\u767E\u5EA6\u3002\u84E6\u7136\u56DE\u9996,\u90A3\u4EBA\u5374\u5728\u706F\u706B\u9611\u73CA\u5904\u201D\u4E2D\u201C\u706F\u706B\u9611\u73CA\u201C\u662F\u6307",
		"id":23428
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u665A\u6625",
		"indexes":"lqzdrmlldlfhssmxsmjjdjx",
		"question":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167\u7684\u300A\u5982\u68A6\u4EE4\u300B\u91CC\u7684\u201C\u7EFF\u80A5\u7EA2\u7626\u201D\u662F\u63CF\u5199\u4EC0\u4E48\u5B63\u8282\u7684\u666F\u8C61",
		"id":23429
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E5D\u6708",
		"indexes":"cjdlxyrjnsdshfsbxdrsxwqwbcwjydyfs",
		"question":"\u201C\u91C7\u83CA\u4E1C\u7BF1\u4E0B,\u60A0\u7136\u89C1\u5357\u5C71\u201C\u7684\u751F\u6D3B\u65B9\u5F0F\u88AB\u73B0\u4EE3\u4EBA\u6240\u5411\u5F80\u3002\u8BF7\u95EE\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u83CA\u6708\u201C\u7684\u6708\u4EFD\u662F",
		"id":23430
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC\u5929",
		"indexes":"sjhryycflqswslhkmxdsngjjdjs",
		"question":"\u8BD7\u53E5\u201C\u5FFD\u5982\u4E00\u591C\u6625\u98CE\u6765,\u5343\u6811\u4E07\u6811\u68A8\u82B1\u5F00\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B63\u8282\u7684\u666F\u8272",
		"id":23431
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5BD2\u98DF\u8282",
		"indexes":"qmsjyfflsxrydhqwwgdqmjydzdchxlnyzbs",
		"question":"\u201C\u6E05\u660E\u65F6\u8282\u96E8\u7EB7\u7EB7,\u8DEF\u4E0A\u884C\u4EBA\u6B32\u65AD\u9B42\u201D,\u8BF7\u95EE,\u6211\u56FD\u5BF9\u6E05\u660E\u8282\u6709\u591A\u79CD\u7684\u79F0\u547C,\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u4E0D\u662F",
		"id":23432
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u9633",
		"indexes":"dzyxwykmfjjbsqyzxddgcbczysyrzsgsmxlwgmjygctjldqjzgctjls",
		"question":"\u201C\u72EC\u5728\u5F02\u4E61\u4E3A\u5F02\u5BA2,\u6BCF\u9022\u4F73\u8282\u500D\u601D\u4EB2\u3002\u9065\u77E5\u5144\u5F1F\u767B\u9AD8\u5904,\u7F16\u63D2\u8331\u8438\u5C11\u4E00\u4EBA\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u9996\u53E4\u8BD7\u63CF\u5199\u4E86\u6211\u56FD\u6C11\u95F4\u4E00\u4E2A\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u4EE4\u7684\u60C5\u666F\u3002\u8FD9\u4E2A\u4F20\u7EDF\u8282\u4EE4\u662F",
		"id":23433
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5973\u5B50\u5341\u4E09\u56DB\u5C81",
		"indexes":"jkczdkcgqlmhnfsqzdkz",
		"question":"\u59DC\u5914\u8BCD\u201C\u7EB5\u8C46\u853B\u8BCD\u5DE5,\u9752\u697C\u68A6\u597D,\u96BE\u8D4B\u6DF1\u60C5\u201D\u4E2D\u201C\u8C46\u853B\u201D\u6307",
		"id":23434
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u660E\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u989C\u826F",
		"indexes":"xlmyzbtgzljwzxmttdyngrwygqxzmdzqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C1C\u8BED\u201C\u51FF\u58C1\u5077\u5149,\u5634\u91CC\u8FDB\u868A\u5B50,\u76F8\u8C8C\u5802\u5802\u201D\u90FD\u4E0E\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u6709\u5173?\u8BF7\u9009\u62E9\u8C1C\u5E95\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u7EC4",
		"id":23435
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96F7\u540C\u3001\u5F20\u82DE\u3001\u7530\u4E30",
		"indexes":"xlmyymyytlfcddzdyngrwygqxzmdzqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C1C\u8BED\u201C\u4E00\u6A21\u4E00\u6837,\u6843\u674E\u9022\u6625,\u5927\u5730\u4E3B\u201D\u90FD\u4E0E\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u6709\u5173?\u8BF7\u9009\u62E9\u8C1C\u5E95\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u7EC4\u3002",
		"id":23436
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u89C8\u3001\u848B\u5E72\u3001\u5F90\u6643",
		"indexes":"xlmygsyclpbmmydyngrwygqxzmdzqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C1C\u8BED\u201C\u66F4\u4E0A\u4E00\u5C42\u697C,\u78B0\u676F,\u6162\u6162\u6447\u201D\u90FD\u4E0E\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u6709\u5173?\u8BF7\u9009\u62E9\u8C1C\u5E95\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u7EC4\u3002",
		"id":23437
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u8868\u3001\u6CD5\u6B63\u3001\u5468\u4ED3",
		"indexes":"xlmyhcwssffmsmtldyngrwygqxzmdzqdyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u8C1C\u8BED\u201C\u6C49\u671D\u6587\u4E66,\u8D4F\u7F5A\u5206\u660E,\u56DB\u9762\u5C6F\u7CAE\u201D\u90FD\u4E0E\u54EA\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7269\u6709\u5173?\u8BF7\u9009\u62E9\u8C1C\u5E95\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u7EC4\u3002",
		"id":23438
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"wylydscddzdgczmyyntjc",
		"question":"\u738B\u5141\u5229\u7528\u8C82\u7985\u9664\u6389\u8463\u5353\u7684\u8FC7\u7A0B\u4E2D\u6CA1\u6709\u7528\u54EA\u6761\u8BA1\u7B56",
		"id":23439
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u5B57\u7384\u5FB7,\u66F9\u64CD\u5B57\u5B5F\u5FB7,\u5F20\u98DE\u5B57\u7FFC\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"gysgyyzqdyxs",
		"question":"\u5173\u4E8E\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B,\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u4E00\u9879\u662F",
		"id":23440
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"lbsbdwhsjmys",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u6CA1\u6709\u8C01",
		"id":23441
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"yxssylbsbdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23442
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8D85",
		"indexes":"yxssylbsbdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23443
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"yxssylbsbdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23444
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"yxssylbsbdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23445
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"yxssylbsbdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5218\u5907\u8EAB\u8FB9\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23446
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"zglkysfgdssfzsr",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u56F0\u4E8E\u4E0A\u65B9\u8C37\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u7236\u5B50\u4E09\u4EBA",
		"id":23447
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"qlchqqsrbbdszhr",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u91CC\u8349,\u4F55\u9752\u9752!\u5341\u65E5\u535C,\u4E0D\u5F97\u751F!\u201D\u6307\u4F55\u4EBA",
		"id":23448
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE",
		"indexes":"zbpyzzbwjcycwwrddss",
		"question":"\u957F\u5742\u5761\u4E00\u6218\u4E2D,\u88AB\u9B4F\u5C06\u7A0B\u6631\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4E07\u4EBA\u654C\u201D\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23449
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u706B\u70E7\u535A\u671B\u5761",
		"indexes":"zglccmldycycwwzzjsqlzwdzys",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u521D\u51FA\u8305\u5E90\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u201C\u8FD0\u7B79\u5E37\u5E44\u4E4B\u4E2D,\u51B3\u80DC\u5343\u91CC\u4E4B\u5916\u201D\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F",
		"id":23450
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518",
		"indexes":"lbclmslwfrhyyws",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u9664\u4E86\u7CDC\u3001\u5B59\u4E24\u4F4D\u592B\u4EBA,\u8FD8\u6709\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F",
		"id":23451
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"gyzlkccswydzdccdzws",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5728\u79BB\u5F00\u66F9\u64CD\u65F6\u552F\u4E00\u5E26\u8D70\u7684\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u8D60\u7269\u662F",
		"id":23452
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"csgxmngqemxdss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5782\u624B\u8FC7\u819D,\u76EE\u80FD\u987E\u5176\u8033\u3002\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23453
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F2\u963F",
		"indexes":"sjzyhc",
		"question":"\u5B59\u575A\u846C\u4E8E\u4F55\u5904",
		"id":23454
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5415\u5E03\u88AD\u7834\u886E\u5DDE,\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u8179\u80CC\u53D7\u654C",
		"indexes":"ccwhfqldycgdxz",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\u4F55\u653E\u5F03\u4E86\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u653B\u6253\u5F90\u5DDE?",
		"id":23455
	},
	{
		"answer":"26",
		"indexes":"scgsdnl",
		"question":"\u5B59\u7B56\u8FC7\u4E16\u7684\u5E74\u9F84?",
		"id":23456
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u672F",
		"indexes":"zjlyxhlbyjjswjktl",
		"question":"\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\u540E,\u5218\u5907\u4EE5\u622A\u51FB\u8C01\u4E3A\u501F\u53E3\u9003\u79BB?",
		"id":23457
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u5FBD",
		"indexes":"sjxsss",
		"question":"\u201C\u6C34\u955C\u5148\u751F\u201D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23458
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u6743",
		"indexes":"fydkbyzbmxdss",
		"question":"\u201C\u65B9\u9890\u5927\u53E3,\u78A7\u773C\u7D2B\u9B13\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23459
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5141",
		"indexes":"wyfdzsxdzbsbmds",
		"question":"?\u672A\u56E0\u5E9F\u5E1D\u4E4B\u4E8B\u5411\u8463\u5353\u8868\u793A\u4E0D\u6EE1\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23460
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49\u732E\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"dygcgysmrgdss",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u79F0\u5173\u7FBD\u662F\u7F8E\u9AEF\u516C\u7684\u662F\u8C01",
		"id":23461
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5367\u725B\u5C71",
		"indexes":"zcpjdstjsmmz",
		"question":"\u5468\u4ED3\u76D8\u8E1E\u7684\u5C71\u5934\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":23462
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4E15",
		"indexes":"hsdbhrfc",
		"question":"\u6C49\u5C11\u5E1D\u88AB\u4F55\u4EBA\u5E9F\u9EDC?",
		"id":23463
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u6B66\u9A91\u7740\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\u5BF9\u9635\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"pzzwzsxhedssgzdcbzryybsmqwngsczbscwd",
		"question":"\u6F58\u748B,\u5F20\u6B66,\u5F20\u677E,\u590F\u4FAF\u6069\u90FD\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u6301\u5B9D\u4E4B\u4EBA\u201D,\u4E5F\u56E0\u201C\u5B9D\u201D\u4E27\u547D,\u8BF7\u95EE\u54EA\u4E2A\u6240\u6301\u4E4B\u5B9D\u662F\u9519\u8BEF\u7684",
		"id":23464
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5140\u7A81",
		"indexes":"tjbdldss",
		"question":"\u85E4\u7532\u5175\u7684\u8001\u5927\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23465
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"njwftxrbjtxrfwsssd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5B81\u6559\u6211\u8D1F\u5929\u4E0B\u4EBA,\u4E0D\u53EB\u5929\u4E0B\u4EBA\u8D1F\u6211\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u8BF4\u7684?",
		"id":23466
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B50\u6052",
		"indexes":"cpzsm",
		"question":"\u66F9\u4E15\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23467
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"yxsbssqzmdnr",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u5B59\u6743\u62DB\u52DF\u7684\u80FD\u4EBA?",
		"id":23468
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"nsscsxwyrrqssztywfmxdss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5E74\u5341\u56DB\u4ECE\u5E08\u5B66\u6B66,\u6709\u4EBA\u8FB1\u5176\u5E08,\u6740\u4E4B,\u9003\u4E8E\u5916\u65B9\u3002\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23469
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D3E\u8BE9",
		"indexes":"zxzsdqsxtjl",
		"question":"\u5F20\u7EE3\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u529D\u8BF4\u4E0B\u6295\u964D\u4E86?",
		"id":23470
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8521\u9633",
		"indexes":"gyfylqhsxccqy",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5C01\u5370\u79BB\u53BB\u540E,\u8C01\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u8BF7\u7F28?",
		"id":23471
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0B\u90B3",
		"indexes":"bmlznl",
		"question":"\u767D\u95E8\u697C\u5728\u54EA\u91CC?",
		"id":23472
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u5C06\u519B",
		"indexes":"lbzydzsqmsdgxs",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5728\u8863\u5E26\u8BCF\u4E0A\u7B7E\u540D\u65F6\u7684\u5B98\u8854\u662F?",
		"id":23473
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u627F",
		"indexes":"ssslxddydchdfcc",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u6536\u4E86\u732E\u5E1D\u7684\u8863\u5E26\u7B56\u5212\u5BF9\u4ED8\u66F9\u64CD?",
		"id":23474
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"gpssdez",
		"question":"\u5173\u5E73\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u513F\u5B50?",
		"id":23475
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u8868",
		"indexes":"lbzrndbhtks",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5728\u6C5D\u5357\u5927\u8D25\u540E\u6295\u9760\u8C01?",
		"id":23476
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76CA\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"bzglywtfzgds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u8A89\u4E3A\u201C\u5929\u5E9C\u4E4B\u56FD\u201D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23477
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"tfdzlmdmzs",
		"question":"\u8BA8\u4F10\u8463\u5353\u8054\u76DF\u7684\u76DF\u4E3B\u662F?",
		"id":23478
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7530\u4E30",
		"indexes":"wysgdzbhzyzzsdysmsss",
		"question":"\u95FB\u8881\u7ECD\u5B98\u6E21\u6218\u8D25\u540E,\u5728\u72F1\u4E2D\u81EA\u6740\u7684\u8881\u7ECD\u8C0B\u58EB\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23479
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u79C0,\u97E9\u798F,\u5B5F\u5766,\u738B\u690D,\u535E\u559C,\u79E6\u742A",
		"indexes":"gygwgzljzdsnlj",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u8FC7\u4E94\u5B98\u65A9\u516D\u5C06,\u65A9\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u516D\u5C06?",
		"id":23480
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u8FBD",
		"indexes":"ylbgylbtxccds",
		"question":"\u7531\u5218\u5907\u3001\u5173\u7FBD\u529B\u4FDD\u6295\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23481
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90ED\u5609",
		"indexes":"ccwdldytzbgdss",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\u5B9A\u8FBD\u4E1C,\u4E8E\u9014\u4E2D\u75C5\u6545\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23482
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u7EE3",
		"indexes":"cczwcdbyszldj",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u5728\u5B9B\u57CE\u5927\u8D25\u4E8E\u8C01,\u6298\u4E86\u5927\u5C06?",
		"id":23483
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u4EC1",
		"indexes":"sywlklxbcqbgd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u6B32\u4E3A\u5415\u65F7\u5415\u7FD4\u62A5\u4EC7\u8D77\u5175\u653B\u6253?",
		"id":23484
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u8083",
		"indexes":"sstdzsjllb",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u66FF\u8463\u5353\u8BF4\u964D\u4E86\u5415\u5E03?",
		"id":23485
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u5B81",
		"indexes":"xlbssczgjlzssfddjs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4E0D\u662F\u5B59\u7B56\u5728\u653B\u51FB\u5218\u7E47\u65F6\u6536\u670D\u7684\u5927\u5C06\u662F",
		"id":23486
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u8FBD",
		"indexes":"ccpssflgytj",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6D3E\u8C01\u8BF4\u670D\u4E86\u5173\u7FBD\u6295\u964D?",
		"id":23487
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"szjcmrhzmswcysdfywmyslczdhxzxqpdgxdwfllzdhxds",
		"question":"\u201C\u8EAB\u957F\u4E5D\u5C3A,\u9762\u5982\u7EA2\u67A3,\u7709\u4F3C\u5367\u8695,\u4E00\u53CC\u4E39\u51E4\u773C,\u5A01\u731B\u6709\u795E,\u4E24\u5C3A\u957F\u7684\u80E1\u987B,\u5728\u80F8\u524D\u98D8\u8361,\u66F4\u663E\u5F97\u5A01\u98CE\u51DB\u51DB\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u6BB5\u8BDD\u5199\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23488
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"ccxqxbdswlsss",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u732E\u4E03\u661F\u5B9D\u5200,\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u6740\u6B7B\u8C01?",
		"id":23489
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u5929\u753B\u621F",
		"indexes":"lbdbqssm",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u7684\u5175\u5668\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23490
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u548C\u8881\u7ECD",
		"indexes":"ymsjslbswldhshsdzz",
		"question":"\u8F95\u95E8\u5C04\u621F\u65F6,\u5415\u5E03\u662F\u4E3A\u4E86\u8C03\u548C\u8C01\u548C\u8C01\u7684\u6218\u4E89?",
		"id":23491
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8881\u7ECD\u548C\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"gdzzfszshszj",
		"question":"\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u8C01\u548C\u8C01\u4E4B\u95F4?",
		"id":23492
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u3001\u5B59\u8054\u519B\u548C\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"cbzzfszshszj",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u8C01\u548C\u8C01\u4E4B\u95F4?",
		"id":23493
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91\u3001\u5F20\u98DE\u3001\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"ccbzhrdsxhydls",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u8D25\u8D70\u534E\u5BB9\u9053\u65F6,\u5148\u540E\u9047\u5230\u4E86\u8C01?",
		"id":23494
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"zgljzydjnzbzlbqdsfrdsdjg",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7ED9\u8D75\u4E91\u7684\u9526\u56CA\u4E2D,\u5E2E\u52A9\u5218\u5907\u53D6\u5230\u5B59\u592B\u4EBA\u7684\u662F\u7B2C\u51E0\u4E2A?",
		"id":23495
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u90B5",
		"indexes":"sspjccszsznclszjx",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u8BC4\u4EF7\u66F9\u64CD\u662F\u201C\u6CBB\u4E16\u4E4B\u80FD\u81E3,\u4E71\u4E16\u4E4B\u5978\u96C4\u201D",
		"id":23496
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"lyzsz",
		"question":"\u5218\u8C6B\u5DDE\u662F\u6307?",
		"id":23497
	},
	{
		"answer":"27",
		"indexes":"zglcssyddnl",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u51FA\u5C71\u65F6\u6709\u591A\u5927\u5E74\u9F84?",
		"id":23498
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7",
		"indexes":"bmhxcwwtjjds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u7962\u8861\u620F\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5B8C\u4F53\u5C06\u519B\u201D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23499
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51E4\u4EEA\u4EAD",
		"indexes":"lbdczhcxhbdzzj",
		"question":"\u5415\u5E03\u3001\u8C82\u5A75\u5728\u4F55\u5904\u76F8\u4F1A\u88AB\u8463\u5353\u649E\u89C1?",
		"id":23500
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5CB1",
		"indexes":"wybhrss",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5EF6\u88AB\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u6740",
		"id":23501
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5143200\u5E74",
		"indexes":"sgsgdzzfsz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218\u53D1\u751F\u5728",
		"id":23502
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u864E\u7262\u5173",
		"indexes":"sgyyzsyzlbdgsfsz",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u201C\u4E09\u82F1\u6218\u5415\u5E03\u201D\u7684\u6545\u4E8B\u53D1\u751F\u5728",
		"id":23503
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6843\u56ED\u4E09\u7ED3\u4E49",
		"indexes":"xlsgyydqjzyzglwgdy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u7684\u60C5\u8282\u4E2D,\u4E0E\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u65E0\u5173\u7684\u6709",
		"id":23504
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"zrydszgdgllbbzjbzybsbzs",
		"question":"\u5728\u201C\u5982\u9C7C\u5F97\u6C34\u201D\u8FD9\u4E2A\u5178\u6545\u91CC,\u5218\u5907\u628A\u81EA\u5DF1\u6BD4\u505A\u201C\u9C7C\u201D,\u628A\u8C01\u6BD4\u4F5C\u201C\u6C34\u201D?",
		"id":23505
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"cbzzzjztjyjjcjdwgjls",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u4E2D\u5047\u88C5\u6295\u964D\u4EE5\u63A5\u8FD1\u66F9\u519B\u7684\u5434\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F?",
		"id":23506
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E9E\u7EDF",
		"indexes":"sgyyfcs",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u51E4\u96CF\u662F",
		"id":23507
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"sgyyzssbczxbw",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u662F\u8C01\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C\u5C0F\u9738\u738B",
		"id":23508
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"sgzbcwzjds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u667A\u7EDD\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23509
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"sgzbcwjjds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u5978\u7EDD\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23510
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7518\u5B81",
		"indexes":"slbrjcybsybyj",
		"question":"\u8C01\u7387\u767E\u4EBA\u52AB\u66F9\u8425,\u4E0D\u635F\u4E00\u5175\u4E00\u5C06",
		"id":23511
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"yztdsfdyjrmlcsmxdsnglsrw",
		"question":"\u201C\u5DF2\u77E5\u5929\u5B9A\u4E09\u5206\u9F0E,\u72B9\u7AED\u4EBA\u8C0B\u516D\u51FA\u5E08\u201D\u63CF\u5199\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":23512
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u900A",
		"indexes":"hslyqbldwjss",
		"question":"\u706B\u70E7\u8FDE\u8425\u4E03\u767E\u91CC\u7684\u5434\u5C06\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23513
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F5D\u9675\u4E4B\u6218\u3001\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u3001\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzzydsdzys",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u6700\u4E3B\u8981\u7684\u4E09\u5927\u6218\u5F79\u662F",
		"id":23514
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8303\u7586\u3001\u5F20\u8FBE",
		"indexes":"czfjzejqssds",
		"question":"\u8D81\u5F20\u98DE\u9152\u9189\u800C\u5C06\u5176\u6740\u6B7B\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":23515
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"hzzs",
		"question":"\u540E\u4E3B\u6307\u8C01",
		"id":23516
	},
	{
		"answer":"120",
		"indexes":"wgsdmzzydsgyygydsh",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u56DB\u5927\u540D\u8457\u4E4B\u4E00\u7684\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u56DE?",
		"id":23517
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u8C21",
		"indexes":"zglscfwsyysddysljtegbccd",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u9996\u6B21\u4F10\u9B4F\u65F6\u7531\u4E8E\u8C01\u7684\u5927\u610F\u5931\u4E86\u8857\u4EAD\u800C\u529F\u8D25\u5782\u6210\u7684",
		"id":23518
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EF2\u9896",
		"indexes":"dzdzs",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u7684\u5B57\u662F",
		"id":23519
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"jscslhzhds",
		"question":"\u7BAD\u5C04\u9648\u751F\u3001\u529B\u559D\u5F20\u864E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23520
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7962\u8861",
		"indexes":"zcskyzjwysxkydpykmds",
		"question":"\u81EA\u79F0\u201C\u4E0A\u53EF\u4EE5\u81F4\u541B\u4E3A\u5C27\u821C,\u4E0B\u53EF\u4EE5\u5FB7\u914D\u4E8E\u5B54\u5B5F\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23521
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A0B\u666E",
		"indexes":"bsqfwtcfddds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u5B59\u6743\u5C01\u4E3A\u201C\u8BA8\u66F9\u526F\u90FD\u7763\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23522
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"bmczgegfqpds",
		"question":"\u88AB\u9A6C\u8D85\u8FFD\u8D76\u800C\u5272\u53D1\u5F03\u888D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23523
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E6\u5B93",
		"indexes":"zyjyzwddtsyxqaq",
		"question":"\u5728\u5BB4\u95F4\u4E0E\u5F20\u6E29\u5BF9\u7B54\u5929\u4E8B\u4EE5\u524A\u5176\u50B2\u6C14",
		"id":23524
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u771F",
		"indexes":"smybcrgqbqsjsxrt",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF\u88AB\u66F9\u777F\u9769\u53BB\u5175\u6743\u65F6,\u4EC5\u8C01\u4FE1\u4EFB\u4ED6",
		"id":23525
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6EE1\u5BA0",
		"indexes":"sstccsjlxh",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u66FF\u66F9\u64CD\u8BF4\u964D\u4E86\u5F90\u6643",
		"id":23526
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u98DE\u65AD\u6865\u800C\u53BB",
		"indexes":"ccchssddzfzzbqsgbyz",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u4ECE\u4F55\u4E8B\u4E0A\u65AD\u5B9A\u5F20\u98DE\u5728\u957F\u5742\u6865\u662F\u6545\u5E03\u7591\u9635",
		"id":23527
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u677E",
		"indexes":"yyzsdgmsblzss",
		"question":"\u7531\u4E8E\u5F20\u8083\u7684\u544A\u5BC6,\u8C01\u88AB\u5218\u748B\u6240\u6740",
		"id":23528
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u826F",
		"indexes":"gyzggldszysyqxq",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5728\u522E\u9AA8\u7597\u6BD2\u65F6,\u5728\u4E0E\u8C01\u4E00\u8D77\u4E0B\u68CB",
		"id":23529
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u6654",
		"indexes":"jxbncwfsssrjs",
		"question":"\u5EFA\u5174\u516B\u5E74\u66F9\u9B4F\u4F10\u8700\u65F6,\u8C01\u4EFB\u519B\u5E08",
		"id":23530
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"dzbtfdjdbhjdqd",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u88AB\u8BA8\u4F10\u5927\u519B\u6253\u8D25\u540E\u51B3\u5B9A\u8FC1\u90FD",
		"id":23531
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EF2\u8FBE",
		"indexes":"smyzsm",
		"question":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23532
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9093\u827E",
		"indexes":"stdlypxdtxlcd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5077\u6E21\u4E86\u9634\u5E73\u5C0F\u9053\u7A81\u88AD\u4E86\u6210\u90FD",
		"id":23533
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u57CE",
		"indexes":"gyzcsljjjxsljzzhtjddfs",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u5728\u66F9\u3001\u5B59\u4E24\u519B\u5939\u51FB\u4E0B\u5931\u4E86\u8346\u5DDE,\u6700\u540E\u9000\u62D2\u7684\u5730\u65B9\u662F",
		"id":23534
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u822B",
		"indexes":"szjcwydfydcxxredpcjd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u8BC8\u964D\u66F9\u9B4F,\u4EE5\u65AD\u53D1\u8D62\u5F97\u66F9\u4F11\u4FE1\u4EFB\u800C\u5927\u7834\u66F9\u519B\u7684",
		"id":23535
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"zglrwssyfxylqyeyz",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u8BA4\u4E3A\u8C01\u7D20\u6709\u53CD\u76F8,\u56E0\u601C\u5176\u52C7\u800C\u7528\u4E4B",
		"id":23536
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u5141",
		"indexes":"cczlzyzjwzlssddcmhs",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u4E2D\u4E86\u5468\u745C\u4E4B\u8BA1\u8BEF\u65A9\u4E86\u6C34\u5E08\u90FD\u7763\u8521\u7441\u548C\u8C01",
		"id":23537
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732E\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"dzsldlxsc",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u6240\u7ACB\u7684\u5218\u534F\u53F2\u79F0",
		"id":23538
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907\u643A\u592B\u4EBA\u9003\u56DE\u8346\u5DDE",
		"indexes":"shszceqzy",
		"question":"\u662F\u4F55\u4E8B\u9020\u6210\u201C\u4E8C\u6C14\u5468\u745C\u201D",
		"id":23539
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"sgzbcwyjds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D\u88AB\u79F0\u4E3A\u201C\u4E49\u7EDD\u201D\u7684\u662F",
		"id":23540
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u4E2A",
		"indexes":"mcjghddynjwd",
		"question":"\u660E\u671D\u51E0\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u4EE5\u5357\u4EAC\u4E3A\u90FD?",
		"id":23541
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9648\u53CB\u8C05",
		"indexes":"hjjxshbsss",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u5DFE\u519B\u5F90\u5BFF\u8F89\u88AB\u8C01\u6740\u6B7B?",
		"id":23542
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u671B\u6D77\u6F6E\u300B",
		"indexes":"sqgzslhhczynsc",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u79CB\u6842\u5B50,\u5341\u91CC\u8377\u82B1\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u54EA\u9996\u8BCD?",
		"id":23543
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59D2",
		"indexes":"yjlxchxsm",
		"question":"\u79B9\u5EFA\u7ACB\u590F\u671D\u540E\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23544
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9ECE\u5143\u6D2A",
		"indexes":"wcqy1911n10y10rhsbbwhbjzfdd",
		"question":"\u6B66\u660C\u8D77\u4E49(1911\u5E7410\u670810\u65E5)\u540E\u8C01\u88AB\u903C\u4E3A\u6E56\u5317\u519B\u653F\u5E9C\u90FD\u7763?",
		"id":23545
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u592A\u6781",
		"indexes":"dqdghsnwqchddd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5927\u6E05\u201D\u7684\u56FD\u53F7\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u6E05\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\u5B9A\u7684?",
		"id":23546
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E21\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"19471949zgrmjfjjxlsnjfzznygbsysdzy",
		"question":"1947\u20141949\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EBA\u6C11\u89E3\u653E\u519B\u8FDB\u884C\u4E86\u4E09\u5E74\u89E3\u653E\u6218\u4E89\u3002\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E09\u5927\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":23547
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u79C0\u592B",
		"indexes":"bsdxhdsyzzbbycbdztwlbnwdcbzthes",
		"question":"\u516B\u5C81\u7684\u5C0F\u7687\u5E1D\u5B8B\u5E7C\u4E3B\u8D75\u663A\u88AB\u5143\u671D\u903C\u7684\u8D70\u6295\u65E0\u8DEF,\u88AB\u54EA\u4F4D\u5927\u81E3\u80CC\u7740\u8DF3\u6D77\u800C\u6B7B?",
		"id":23548
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5171\u548C",
		"indexes":"zgzglwzxgtglzwcwsm",
		"question":"\u53EC\u516C\u3001\u5468\u516C\u4E24\u4F4D\u5BB0\u76F8\u5171\u540C\u7BA1\u7406\u653F\u52A1,\u79F0\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23549
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u71B9\u5B97",
		"indexes":"wzxsznghddzqjlz",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5FE0\u8D24\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5F53\u653F\u671F\u95F4\u4E71\u653F?",
		"id":23550
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u6587\u5B97",
		"indexes":"tcnwhdzwqjfslglzb",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u5728\u4F4D\u671F\u95F4\u53D1\u751F\u4E86\u7518\u9732\u4E4B\u53D8?",
		"id":23551
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5D6C\u9A7F",
		"indexes":"ygfszsmdf",
		"question":"\u6768\u8D35\u5983\u6B7B\u5728\u4EC0\u4E48\u5730\u65B9?",
		"id":23552
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DEB\u86CA\u6848",
		"indexes":"mgsdabbhnya",
		"question":"\u660E\u5BAB\u4E09\u5927\u6848\u4E0D\u5305\u542B\u54EA\u4E00\u6848?",
		"id":23553
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u970D\u5149",
		"indexes":"hxdksdzcdsdw",
		"question":"\u6C49\u5BA3\u5E1D\u9760\u8C01\u7684\u652F\u6301\u767B\u4E0A\u5E1D\u4F4D?",
		"id":23554
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xypfczsls",
		"question":"\u9879\u7FBD\u7834\u91DC\u6C89\u821F\u6740\u4E86\u8C01?",
		"id":23555
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9756\u5EB7\u4E4B\u53D8",
		"indexes":"gy1127njgjdgrkfshzsqzbfscsm",
		"question":"\u516C\u51431127\u5E74,\u91D1\u56FD\u519B\u961F\u653B\u5165\u5F00\u5C01,\u5B8B\u5FBD\u5B97\u3001\u5B8B\u94A6\u5B97\u88AB\u4FD8,\u53F2\u79F0\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23556
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u571F\u85E9",
		"indexes":"tghzzywsdqxjznqcwtdsm",
		"question":"\u5410\u8C37\u6D51\u6700\u7EC8\u56E0\u4E3A\u8C01\u7684\u4FB5\u88AD\u4E3E\u65CF\u5185\u8FC1\u6210\u4E3A\u5510\u7684\u5C5E\u6C11?",
		"id":23557
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u732A\u513F",
		"indexes":"alsszsdsl",
		"question":"\u5B89\u7984\u5C71\u6B7B\u5728\u8C01\u7684\u624B\u91CC?",
		"id":23558
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u5B9A\u738B",
		"indexes":"qccndsfzlbbhng",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u521D\u5E74\u7684\u201C\u4E09\u85E9\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u4E0D\u5305\u542B\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":23559
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u7A46\u738B",
		"indexes":"snwztzyxyklhwmdcs",
		"question":"\u662F\u54EA\u4F4D\u5468\u5929\u5B50\u6709\u897F\u6E38\u6606\u4ED1\u4F1A\u738B\u6BCD\u7684\u4F20\u8BF4?",
		"id":23560
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5BFC",
		"indexes":"wymgtxldwzdss",
		"question":"\u201C\u738B\u4E0E\u9A6C,\u5171\u5929\u4E0B\u201D\u91CC\u7684\u738B\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23561
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BD7",
		"indexes":"skqsdnrssfffdaznrflngbsqzdsbfl",
		"question":"\u300A\u56DB\u5E93\u5168\u4E66\u300B\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\u662F\u5341\u5206\u4E30\u5BCC\u7684\u3002\u6309\u7167\u5185\u5BB9\u5206\u7C7B,\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5176\u4E2D\u7684\u56DB\u90E8\u5206\u7C7B?",
		"id":23562
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9C81\u9690\u516C",
		"indexes":"zcjyclgnwgjks",
		"question":"\u300A\u5DE6\u4F20\u300B\u7EAA\u5143\u4ECE\u9C81\u56FD\u54EA\u4F4D\u56FD\u541B\u5F00\u59CB?",
		"id":23563
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167",
		"indexes":"sdzrjsywgxzjsxybkgjdsssd",
		"question":"\u751F\u5F53\u4F5C\u4EBA\u6770,\u6B7B\u4EA6\u4E3A\u9B3C\u96C4,\u81F3\u4ECA\u601D\u9879\u7FBD,\u4E0D\u80AF\u8FC7\u6C5F\u4E1C\u3002\u662F\u8C01\u8BF4\u7684?",
		"id":23564
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u90C3",
		"indexes":"sgsqmsczjtyzbjnwwgdj",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u9A6C\u8C21\u66FE\u5728\u8857\u4EAD\u4E00\u6218\u8D25\u7ED9\u54EA\u4F4D\u9B4F\u56FD\u5927\u5C06?",
		"id":23565
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5112\u5BB6\u601D\u60F3",
		"indexes":"grswszzymdghyqddsjszxdnszdjhzyzyzzsysmsx",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EBA\u6240\u8C13\u201C\u614E\u7EC8\u8FFD\u8FDC,\u6C11\u5FB7\u5F52\u539A\u77E3\u201D,\u5F3A\u8C03\u7684\u662F\u796D\u7940\u7956\u5148\u3001\u60BC\u5FF5\u6B7B\u8005\u7684\u6559\u5316\u4F5C\u7528\u3002\u8FD9\u4E00\u4E3B\u5F20\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u601D\u60F3?",
		"id":23566
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u4E09\u5F69",
		"indexes":"tcgjygzkwszcqlhszyldcstqcw",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u5DE5\u5320\u7528\u5404\u79CD\u77FF\u7269\u70E7\u5236\u51FA\u9752\u3001\u7EFF\u3001\u9EC4\u4E09\u79CD\u8273\u4E3D\u7684\u5F69\u8272\u9676\u5668\u79F0\u4E3A?",
		"id":23567
	},
	{
		"answer":"103",
		"indexes":"wxbfcxljt",
		"question":"\u201C\u620A\u620C\u53D8\u6CD5\u201D\u6301\u7EED\u4E86\u51E0\u5929?",
		"id":23568
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u4EAC",
		"indexes":"zyzjlmchmcddnjhlmczbdcyqdnl",
		"question":"\u6731\u5143\u748B\u5EFA\u7ACB\u660E\u671D\u540E,\u660E\u521D\u5B9A\u90FD\u5357\u4EAC,\u540E\u6765\u660E\u6210\u7956\u628A\u90FD\u57CE\u6709\u8FC1\u5230\u90A3\u91CC?",
		"id":23569
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591A\u5C14\u886E",
		"indexes":"qszdnzshwzysddsdzc",
		"question":"\u6E05\u987A\u6CBB\u5E1D\u80FD\u5750\u4E0A\u7687\u4F4D\u4E3B\u8981\u662F\u5F97\u5230\u8C01\u7684\u652F\u6301?",
		"id":23570
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7435\u7436",
		"indexes":"gdlcdmqsmmfzyynzlqyz",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u6D41\u4F20\u7684\u540D\u66F2\u201C\u5341\u9762\u57CB\u4F0F\u201D\u4E3B\u8981\u7531\u54EA\u79CD\u4E50\u5668\u6F14\u594F?",
		"id":23571
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E05\u671D",
		"indexes":"fcztypxxyfwdxcdcyyppjwaxbjyszyqjzshzzkncxyngcd",
		"question":"\u201C\u756A\u83DC\u4E89\u63A8\u4E00\u54C1\u9999,\u897F\u6D0B\u98CE\u5473\u7779\u5148\u5C1D\u3002\u5200\u53C9\u8000\u773C\u76C6\u76D8\u6D01,\u6211\u7231\u9999\u69DF\u9152\u4E00\u89DE\u3002\u201D\u8FD9\u4E00\u60C5\u666F\u5728\u4E0A\u6D77\u6700\u65E9\u53EF\u80FD\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3?",
		"id":23572
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79E4\u7823",
		"indexes":"tqsgdcjdjsqwhlbscwsm",
		"question":"\u201C\u94DC\u6743\u201D\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u5E38\u89C1\u7684\u91D1\u5C5E\u5668\u7269,\u540E\u6765\u88AB\u4FD7\u79F0\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23573
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u51B0",
		"indexes":"zggdmxslgcxjhddcxlshcrbzjjswhntxwztfdjxgslgcdsjzss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u67D0\u9879\u6C34\u5229\u5DE5\u7A0B\u5174\u5EFA\u540E,\u5F53\u5730\u51FA\u73B0\u4E86\u201C\u6C34\u65F1\u4ECE\u4EBA,\u4E0D\u77E5\u9965\u9991,\u65F6\u65E0\u8352\u5E74,\u5929\u4E0B\u8C13\u4E4B\u5929\u5E9C\u201D\u7684\u666F\u8C61\u3002\u8BE5\u6C34\u5229\u5DE5\u7A0B\u7684\u59CB\u5EFA\u8005\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23574
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u6B21",
		"indexes":"sydygjwhcjcqtfgl",
		"question":"\u968B\u7080\u5E1D(\u6768\u5E7F)\u5373\u4F4D\u540E,\u66FE\u51E0\u6B21\u53BB\u8BA8\u4F10\u9AD8\u4E3D?",
		"id":23575
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u98CE",
		"indexes":"gsfyszdfszsm",
		"question":"\u53E4\u8BD7\u201C\u98CE\u3001\u96C5\u3001\u9882\u201D\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u98CE\u201D\u662F\u6307\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23576
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u516C",
		"indexes":"hcdxzbjjgypqjjwdsmysdfwdskflhfrcxbzzsmzdkssx",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6210\u5E1D\u4E0B\u8BCF\u7F62\u5C06\u519B\u5B98,\u4EE5\u9AA0\u9A91\u5C06\u519B\u4E3A\u5927\u53F8\u9A6C,\u5FA1\u53F2\u5927\u592B\u4E3A\u5927\u53F8\u7A7A,\u5C01\u5217\u4FAF,\u4FF8\u5982\u4E1E\u76F8,\u6807\u5FD7\u7740\u4EC0\u4E48\u5236\u7684\u5F00\u59CB\u5B9E\u884C?",
		"id":23577
	},
	{
		"answer":"1842",
		"indexes":"njtysmshqddnyr",
		"question":"\u300A\u5357\u4EAC\u6761\u7EA6\u300B\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u7B7E\u5B9A\u7684?(\u5E74\u6708\u65E5)",
		"id":23578
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5171\u548C\u5236",
		"indexes":"1915ndlqczyzswgtwtzzbszxxgtzxesyylgctzgtzwlhsjfdzgwywhdgtssmz",
		"question":"1915\u5E74\u5E95,\u6881\u542F\u8D85\u5728\u300A\u5F02\u54C9\u6240\u8C13\u56FD\u4F53\u95EE\u9898\u8005\u300B\u4E2D\u8868\u793A:\u201C\u5728\u73B0\u884C\u56FD\u4F53\u4E4B\u4E0B,\u800C\u601D\u4EE5\u8A00\u8BBA\u9F13\u5439\u4ED6\u79CD\u56FD\u4F53,\u5219\u65E0\u8BBA\u4F55\u65F6\u7686\u53CD\u5BF9\u4E4B\u3002\u201D\u8BE5\u6587\u8981\u7EF4\u62A4\u7684\u201C\u56FD\u4F53\u201D\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5236?",
		"id":23579
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u4E3D\u534E",
		"indexes":"dhmddmqjsm",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u660E\u5E1D\u7684\u6BCD\u4EB2\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23580
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u653B\u5B88\u540C\u76DF",
		"indexes":"sqhzyygghzygglhtmbczjsxxclsm",
		"question":"\u82CF\u79E6\u548C\u5F20\u4EEA\u4E00\u4E2A\u641E\u5408\u7EB5,\u4E00\u4E2A\u641E\u8FDE\u6A2A,\u4ED6\u4EEC\u5F7C\u6B64\u4E4B\u95F4\u9996\u5148\u884C\u6210\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23581
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9690\u592A\u5B50",
		"indexes":"lsmjwhzfljcwxwsyzgslnwyyzzwsm",
		"question":"\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u7EE7\u4F4D\u540E,\u8FFD\u5C01\u674E\u5EFA\u6210\u4E3A\u606F\u738B,\u8C25\u201C\u9690\u201D,\u8D1E\u89C2\u5341\u516D\u5E74\u4E94\u6708,\u53C8\u8FFD\u8D60\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23582
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u94A6\u5B97",
		"indexes":"bsdzhyghdss",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u7684\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23583
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B54\u7960",
		"indexes":"skskzglsdqfsgtsdfdjcbbhyxng",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u5B54\u201D\u662F\u5B54\u5B50\u6545\u91CC\u5C71\u4E1C\u66F2\u961C\u4E09\u4E2A\u7279\u6B8A\u5730\u65B9\u7684\u7B80\u79F0,\u4E0D\u5305\u542B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A?",
		"id":23584
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341",
		"indexes":"tdgcyjghdbhwzt",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u5171\u4F20\u6709\u51E0\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D(\u4E0D\u542B\u6B66\u5219\u5929)?",
		"id":23585
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D4\u5B59\u901A",
		"indexes":"sdlbsrswfjlzgdkyzltx",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5BF9\u5218\u90A6\u8BF4:\u201C\u5112\u751F\u65E0\u6CD5\u5EFA\u7ACB\u6218\u529F,\u4F46\u53EF\u4EE5\u6CBB\u7406\u5929\u4E0B\u3002\u201D",
		"id":23586
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5951\u4E39",
		"indexes":"sjtdlhdzhjyyslzgrjs",
		"question":"\u77F3\u656C\u746D\u5F53\u4E86\u7687\u5E1D\u4E4B\u540E,\u5C06\u71D5\u4E91\u5341\u516D\u5DDE\u5272\u8BA9\u7ED9\u8C01?",
		"id":23587
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u606D\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"hblxlrscdnwhddxzcj",
		"question":"\u5FFD\u5FC5\u70C8\u4E0B\u4EE4\u8BA9\u5B8B\u671D\u7684\u54EA\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u5230\u897F\u85CF\u51FA\u5BB6?",
		"id":23588
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u4E0E\u4EBA\u7684\u5173\u7CFB",
		"indexes":"kmxszytldsgx",
		"question":"\u5B54\u5B5F\u5B66\u8BF4\u4E3B\u8981\u8BA8\u8BBA\u7684\u662F\u5173\u7CFB?",
		"id":23589
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zxshddsmr",
		"question":"\u989B\u987C\u662F\u9EC4\u5E1D\u7684\u4EC0\u4E48\u4EBA?",
		"id":23590
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u5168\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"sjsltc",
		"question":"\u8C01\u7ED3\u675F\u4E86\u5510\u671D?",
		"id":23591
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u732A\u738B",
		"indexes":"smdlybqfdlzyxcwsmw",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u660E\u5E1D\u5218\u5F67\u88AB\u524D\u5E9F\u5E1D\u5218\u5B50\u4E1A\u620F\u79F0\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u738B?",
		"id":23592
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u5E7F",
		"indexes":"tzwqsdmjbbhs",
		"question":"\u5510\u4E2D\u665A\u671F\u4E09\u5927\u540D\u5C06\u4E0D\u5305\u542B\u8C01?",
		"id":23593
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u672B\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"sjtjzldslmhtshtdhdss",
		"question":"\u77F3\u656C\u746D\u501F\u52A9\u8FBD\u7684\u52BF\u529B\u706D\u540E\u5510\u65F6,\u540E\u5510\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23594
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u5B59\u65E0\u5FCC",
		"indexes":"lyg24gcsjsw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u960124\u529F\u81E3,\u8C01\u5C45\u9996\u4F4D?",
		"id":23595
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C79",
		"indexes":"bysjbbywszdwwsnszdw",
		"question":"\u5317\u6D0B\u4E09\u6770\u88AB\u6BD4\u55BB\u4E3A\u4E09\u79CD\u52A8\u7269,\u95EE\u662F\u54EA\u4E09\u79CD\u52A8\u7269?",
		"id":23596
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u535A\u5C14\u6D4E\u5409\u7279\u6C0F",
		"indexes":"qcdzfxsm",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u7684\u5E84\u5983\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23597
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u81BA\u548C\u675C\u5BC6",
		"indexes":"dhsqmsfpryqmsjdyldqmsyhhqzldfbzs",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u65F6\u671F,\u540D\u58EB\u8303\u6EC2\u5165\u72F1,\u5176\u6BCD\u8BF4:\u201C\u4ECA\u5F97\u4E0E\u674E\u675C\u9F50\u540D,\u6B7B\u4EA6\u4F55\u6068?\u201D\u5176\u4E2D\u674E\u675C\u5206\u522B\u6307\u8C01?",
		"id":23598
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9646\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"zglssdsrzcsss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u5723\u4EBA\u4E2D,\u201C\u8336\u5723\u201D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23599
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5F81",
		"indexes":"ttzpszbss",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u6D3E\u8C01\u4E3B\u7F16\u300A\u968B\u4E66\u300B?",
		"id":23600
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u94ED\u4F20",
		"indexes":"twsrxfss",
		"question":"\u53F0\u6E7E\u9996\u4EFB\u5DE1\u629A\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23601
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u6C38",
		"indexes":"sqgzslhhssxxdc",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E09\u79CB\u6842\u5B50,\u5341\u91CC\u8377\u82B1\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u5199\u4E0B\u7684\u8BCD?",
		"id":23602
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u6B66\u5B97",
		"indexes":"hrsmczmdqgtcsznyghdzznj",
		"question":"\u6D77\u745E\u662F\u660E\u671D\u8457\u540D\u7684\u6E05\u5B98,\u4ED6\u51FA\u751F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u6267\u653F\u5E74\u95F4?",
		"id":23603
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9647\u897F\u90E1\u516C",
		"indexes":"lhzlytjhstzzgyfcdlydjwywmhgfwsm",
		"question":"\u674E\u540E\u4E3B(\u674E\u715C)\u6295\u964D\u540E,\u5B8B\u592A\u5B97(\u8D75\u5149\u4E49)\u5E9F\u9664\u6389\u674E\u715C\u7684\u7235\u4F4D,\u7531\u8FDD\u547D\u4FAF\u6539\u5C01\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23604
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7687\u592A\u5F1F",
		"indexes":"twzlysysmsfjhwd",
		"question":"\u5510\u6B66\u5B97\u674E\u708E\u662F\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u8EAB\u4EFD\u5373\u7687\u4F4D\u7684?",
		"id":23605
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u521D",
		"indexes":"ccshcpcdddlyjysmnh",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u6B7B\u540E,\u66F9\u4E15\u79F0\u5E1D,\u5B9A\u90FD\u6D1B\u9633,\u5EFA\u5143\u4EC0\u4E48(\u5E74\u53F7)?",
		"id":23606
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u9AD8\u5B97",
		"indexes":"xtjmwytcnghdzzsq",
		"question":"\u897F\u7A81\u53A5\u706D\u4EA1\u4E8E\u5510\u671D\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u6267\u653F\u65F6\u671F?",
		"id":23607
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u795E\u519C\u672C\u8349\u7ECF\u300B",
		"indexes":"wgzzdybywxzzssm",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u836F\u7269\u5B66\u8457\u4F5C\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23608
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EAA\u6653\u5C9A",
		"indexes":"skqsdzzgss",
		"question":"\u300A\u56DB\u5E93\u5168\u4E66\u300B\u7684\u603B\u64B0\u5B98\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23609
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"csssgwgddjjsssltn",
		"question":"\u66F9\u723D\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u9B4F\u56FD\u7684\u5927\u5C06\u519B,\u662F\u8C01\u6740\u4E86\u4ED6\u5462?",
		"id":23610
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E5\u8BB0\u4F53",
		"indexes":"xxkyjysmxswzdzgdlmz",
		"question":"\u300A\u5F90\u971E\u5BA2\u6E38\u8BB0\u300B\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u5F62\u5F0F\u4E3A\u4E3B\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u5730\u7406\u540D\u8457?",
		"id":23611
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u82D7\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"wasbfznyflybczcpjlf",
		"question":"\u738B\u5B89\u77F3\u53D8\u6CD5\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u6CD5\u4EE4\u53C8\u88AB\u79F0\u4F5C\u201C\u5E38\u5E73\u7ED9\u655B\u6CD5\u201D?",
		"id":23612
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u5468",
		"indexes":"swdyjbsngzqdhqhjsts",
		"question":"\u968B\u6587\u5E1D\u6768\u575A\u672C\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u653F\u6743\u7684\u7687\u4EB2\u548C\u519B\u4E8B\u7EDF\u5E05?",
		"id":23613
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u795E\u5B97",
		"indexes":"shzdfqss",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u5FBD\u5B97\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23614
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6C49",
		"indexes":"zgdygqswgdcdsnc",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5F3A\u76DB\u7A33\u56FA\u7684\u671D\u4EE3\u662F\u54EA\u671D?",
		"id":23615
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5747\u7530\u514D\u7CAE",
		"indexes":"lzcqytcsmkhsdnmyh",
		"question":"\u674E\u81EA\u6210\u8D77\u4E49\u63D0\u51FA\u4EC0\u4E48\u53E3\u53F7,\u6DF1\u5F97\u519C\u6C11\u62E5\u62A4?",
		"id":23616
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u8336\u7ECF\u300B",
		"indexes":"cslyzysms",
		"question":"\u201C\u8336\u5723\u201D\u9646\u7FBD\u8457\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E66?",
		"id":23617
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9E3F\u7AE0",
		"indexes":"xlrznwccydbqzfqdxcty",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u4EBA\u4E2D,\u90A3\u4F4D\u66FE\u53C2\u4E0E\u4EE3\u8868\u6E05\u653F\u5E9C\u7B7E\u8BA2\u300A\u8F9B\u4E11\u6761\u7EA6\u300B?",
		"id":23618
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516B\u5E74",
		"indexes":"ywsgdfddsfzlgjlljn",
		"question":"\u7531\u5434\u4E09\u6842\u7B49\u53D1\u52A8\u7684\u201C\u4E09\u85E9\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u5171\u7ECF\u5386\u4E86\u51E0\u5E74?",
		"id":23619
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E90\u9675\u738B",
		"indexes":"tzzlxbqmwztfchsfwsm",
		"question":"\u5510\u4E2D\u5B97\u674E\u663E\u88AB\u5176\u6BCD(\u6B66\u5219\u5929)\u5E9F\u9EDC\u540E,\u53D7\u5C01\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23620
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u859B\u4EC1\u8D35",
		"indexes":"tgzsqtjgkprzprszaddhfyswdhdltjewrzfgl",
		"question":"\u5510\u9AD8\u5B97\u65F6\u671F,\u5510\u519B\u653B\u514B\u5E73\u58E4,\u5728\u5E73\u58E4\u8BBE\u7F6E\u5B89\u4E1C\u7763\u62A4\u5E9C,\u4EE5\u8C01\u4E3A\u7763\u62A4,\u5E26\u9886\u5510\u519B\u4E8C\u4E07\u4EBA\u9A7B\u9632\u9AD8\u4E3D?",
		"id":23621
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CE2\u65AF",
		"indexes":"ssmgdgyscxzqwdscxzsgdnl",
		"question":"\u53F2\u4E0A\u8499\u53E4\u5E1D\u56FD\u6709\u4E09\u6B21\u897F\u5F81,\u8BF7\u95EE\u7B2C\u4E09\u6B21\u897F\u5F81\u662F\u653B\u6253\u54EA\u91CC?",
		"id":23622
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB",
		"indexes":"hqbqssjs",
		"question":"\u970D\u53BB\u75C5\u53BB\u4E16\u65F6\u51E0\u5C81?",
		"id":23623
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5144\u5F1F",
		"indexes":"scysqssmgx",
		"question":"\u5B59\u7B56\u4E0E\u5B59\u6743\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5173\u7CFB?",
		"id":23624
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u6148",
		"indexes":"sjdybfyxzzxyjldzzss",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u7B2C\u4E00\u90E8\u6CD5\u533B\u5B66\u4E13\u8457\u300A\u6D17\u51A4\u96C6\u5F55\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23625
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u4EF2\u666F",
		"indexes":"zglssdsrzyszdss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u5723\u4EBA\u4E2D,\u201C\u533B\u5723\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23626
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9053\u5FB7\u7ECF\u300B",
		"indexes":"lzsdjxpdcsrlzym",
		"question":"\u8001\u5B50\u662F\u9053\u5BB6\u5B66\u6D3E\u7684\u521B\u59CB\u4EBA\u3002\u300A\u8001\u5B50\u300B\u53C8\u540D?",
		"id":23627
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u987E\u607A\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"gdmhlsftdzzss",
		"question":"\u53E4\u4EE3\u540D\u753B\u201C\u6D1B\u795E\u8D4B\u56FE\u201D\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23628
	},
	{
		"answer":"209",
		"indexes":"gyqdsncswgldlycsshddnmqy",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143\u524D\u591A\u5C11\u5E74,\u9648\u80DC\u3001\u5434\u5E7F\u9886\u5BFC\u4E86\u4E00\u6B21\u58F0\u52BF\u6D69\u5927\u7684\u519C\u6C11\u8D77\u4E49?",
		"id":23629
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"dzrlyhstzcljbfkcwgdljdyz",
		"question":"\u8463\u5353\u5165\u6D1B\u9633\u540E,\u8C01\u9003\u81F3\u9648\u7559\u805A\u5175\u53CD\u6297,\u6210\u4E3A\u5173\u4E1C\u8054\u519B\u7684\u4E00\u652F?",
		"id":23630
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5929\u5DE5\u5F00\u7269\u300B",
		"indexes":"syxsmmymddsrtcbzgyblcqgdszbsssm",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u5E94\u661F\u662F\u660E\u672B\u6709\u540D\u7684\u8BFB\u4E66\u4EBA,\u4ED6\u66FE\u7F16\u7E82\u8FC7\u4E00\u672C\u6D41\u4F20\u5343\u53E4\u7684\u4E66,\u8FD9\u672C\u4E66\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23631
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u56DB",
		"indexes":"hmdshgwdddjgez",
		"question":"\u6C49\u660E\u5E1D\u662F\u6C49\u5149\u6B66\u5E1D\u7684\u7B2C\u51E0\u4E2A\u513F\u5B50?",
		"id":23632
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u5E73\u516C\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"gy710nlljyslhfdzbylqfldcd",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143710\u5E74,\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u4E0E\u8C01\u8054\u5408\u53D1\u52A8\u653F\u53D8,\u62E5\u7ACB\u5176\u7236\u674E\u65E6\u79F0\u5E1D?",
		"id":23633
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u65AF",
		"indexes":"qccgyxsdbgzshrsx",
		"question":"\u79E6\u671D\u4F20\u56FD\u7389\u73BA\u4E0A\u7684\u516B\u4E2A\u5B57\u662F\u4F55\u4EBA\u6240\u5199?",
		"id":23634
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u548C\u6C0F\u74A7",
		"indexes":"cgyxzzgsqycsm",
		"question":"\u4F20\u56FD\u7389\u73BA\u5728\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u53C8\u79F0\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23635
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6563\u6587",
		"indexes":"tsbdjsasmlpdd",
		"question":"\u201C\u5510\u5B8B\u516B\u5927\u5BB6\u201D\u662F\u6309\u4EC0\u4E48\u6765\u8BC4\u5B9A\u7684?",
		"id":23636
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u9756",
		"indexes":"tccnywdjjpdlpfnsddtjtss",
		"question":"\u5510\u671D\u521D\u5E74,\u4E00\u4F4D\u5927\u5C06\u519B\u5E73\u5B9A\u4E86\u9891\u7E41\u95F9\u4E8B\u7684\u4E1C\u7A81\u53A5,\u4ED6\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23637
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20\u65ED",
		"indexes":"zglssdsrzcszdss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u5723\u4EBA\u4E2D,\u201C\u8349\u5723\u201D\u6307\u7684\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23638
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C09\u8FDF\u606D",
		"indexes":"lsmzxwmslxdhmsdbqxlybg",
		"question":"\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u5728\u7384\u6B66\u95E8\u6740\u4E86\u5144\u5F1F\u540E,\u547D\u8C01\u5E26\u5175\u53BB\u5411\u674E\u6E0A\u903C\u5BAB?",
		"id":23639
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u5341\u516B\u5E74",
		"indexes":"zcgsftwdshlzmzyzdspjldsn",
		"question":"\u90D1\u6210\u529F\u6536\u590D\u53F0\u6E7E\u5C9B\u65F6,\u8377\u5170\u6B96\u6C11\u8005\u5DF2\u5728\u5C9B\u4E0A\u76D8\u8E1E\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5E74?",
		"id":23640
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u56DB\u5E93\u5168\u4E66\u300B",
		"indexes":"qlhdwlcfsmxfzmdzsltygdjzjzlnbqg",
		"question":"\u4E7E\u9686\u7687\u5E1D\u4E3A\u4E86\u5B58\u653E\u4EC0\u4E48\u6548\u4EFF\u8457\u540D\u7684\u85CF\u4E66\u697C\u201C\u5929\u4E00\u9601\u201D\u7684\u5EFA\u7B51\u5EFA\u9020\u4E86\u5357\u5317\u4E03\u9601?",
		"id":23641
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lssxjdbwzlcxdj",
		"question":"\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u897F\u664B\u7684\u201C\u516B\u738B\u4E4B\u4E71\u201D\u6301\u7EED\u591A\u4E45?",
		"id":23642
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u81BA",
		"indexes":"dhhdsqfsldgzhjyswsddrttsbbgdtmdzsjgbdwg",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u6853\u5E1D\u65F6\u671F\u53D1\u751F\u4E86\u201C\u515A\u9522\u4E4B\u7978\u201D,\u5C06\u4EE5\u8C01\u4E3A\u9996\u7684\u515A\u4EBA\u7EDF\u7EDF\u641C\u6355,\u5E76\u89C4\u5B9A\u4ED6\u4EEC\u90FD\u7EC8\u8EAB\u7981\u9522,\u4E0D\u5F97\u4E3A\u5B98?",
		"id":23643
	},
	{
		"answer":"16\u5C81",
		"indexes":"hwdlcjsdjwd",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D\u5218\u5F7B\u51E0\u5C81\u767B\u57FA\u4E3A\u5E1D?",
		"id":23644
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8912\u59D2",
		"indexes":"fhxzhszywwlths",
		"question":"\u70FD\u706B\u620F\u8BF8\u4FAF\u662F\u5468\u5E7D\u738B\u4E3A\u4E86\u8BA8\u597D\u8C01?",
		"id":23645
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E58\u519B",
		"indexes":"cgfsqmdydmjtlldjdjsm",
		"question":"\u66FE\u56FD\u85E9\u662F\u6E05\u672B\u7684\u4E00\u4EE3\u540D\u5C06,\u4ED6\u7387\u9886\u7684\u519B\u961F\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23646
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62D6\u96F7",
		"indexes":"mgdsrdhmgssdez",
		"question":"\u8499\u53E4\u7B2C\u56DB\u4EFB\u5927\u6C57\u8499\u54E5\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u513F\u5B50?",
		"id":23647
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u5168\u8001\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"qlzwhfmyhdjsdtgzhdhswgyctzxwsm",
		"question":"\u4E7E\u9686\u5728\u6587\u5316\u65B9\u9762\u6709\u5F88\u5927\u5EFA\u6811,\u4F46\u4ED6\u66F4\u81EA\u8C6A\u7684\u8FD8\u662F\u6B66\u529F,\u56E0\u6B64\u4ED6\u81EA\u8BE9\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23648
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u4E03\u7565\u300B",
		"indexes":"hcdsqylxlxfzbcdybwgzzdtsflmljsm",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6210\u5E1D\u65F6\u671F,\u7531\u5218\u5411\u3001\u5218\u6B46\u7236\u5B50\u7F16\u6210\u7684\u4E00\u90E8\u6211\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u56FE\u4E66\u5206\u7C7B\u76EE\u5F55\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23649
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u6709\u4E3A",
		"indexes":"wxljzbbks",
		"question":"\u201C\u620A\u620C\u516D\u541B\u5B50\u201D\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u8C01?",
		"id":23650
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5EB7\u7199",
		"indexes":"twynghdzzsqzsbrqcbt",
		"question":"\u53F0\u6E7E\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u6267\u653F\u65F6\u671F\u6B63\u5F0F\u5E76\u5165\u6E05\u671D\u7248\u56FE?",
		"id":23651
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u592A\u771F",
		"indexes":"txzryyhzqcjrjngchwsm",
		"question":"\u5510\u7384\u5B97\u8BA9\u6768\u7389\u73AF\u81EA\u8BF7\u51FA\u5BB6,\u5165\u5C45\u5357\u5BAB,\u8D50\u53F7\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23652
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96CD\u6B63",
		"indexes":"qcsdjjfhgjjczzsznghdzzqjsld",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u65F6\u7684\u519B\u673A\u623F(\u540E\u6539\u519B\u673A\u5904)\u6700\u65E9\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u6267\u653F\u671F\u95F4\u8BBE\u7ACB\u7684?",
		"id":23653
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F16\u5E74\u4F53",
		"indexes":"bsrsmgsymzmdzjnmtszdzztjsybysmwxsdlssn",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u4EBA\u53F8\u9A6C\u5149\u662F\u4E00\u540D\u8457\u540D\u7684\u4F5C\u5BB6,\u90A3\u4E48\u4ED6\u6240\u8457\u7684\u300A\u8D44\u6CBB\u901A\u9274\u300B\u662F\u4E00\u90E8\u4EE5\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E3A\u5F62\u5F0F\u7684\u5386\u53F2\u4E66\u5462?",
		"id":23654
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B89\u53F2\u4E4B\u4E71",
		"indexes":"yypgddljpnsyyqzssmlssj",
		"question":"\u201C\u6E14\u9633\u9F19\u9F13\u52A8\u5730\u6765,\u60CA\u7834\u9713\u88F3\u7FBD\u8863\u66F2\u201D,\u8FD9\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":23655
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516C\u5143881\u5E74",
		"indexes":"gy875nhcqybynngrza",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143875\u5E74,\u9EC4\u5DE2\u8D77\u4E49,\u5E76\u4E8E\u54EA\u5E74\u653B\u5165\u957F\u5B89?",
		"id":23656
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u6DEE\u5357\u5B50\u300B",
		"indexes":"sfsxyygwjlyzyytdzddyzddyczwgzmdnbzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u56DB\u65B9\u4E0A\u4E0B\u66F0\u5B87,\u53E4\u5F80\u4ECA\u6765\u66F0\u5B99,\u4EE5\u55BB\u5929\u5730\u201D,\u8FD9\u6BB5\u5BF9\u5B87\u5B99\u7684\u5B9A\u4E49,\u51FA\u81EA\u6211\u56FD\u8457\u540D\u7684\u54EA\u90E8\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":23657
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u536B\u56FD",
		"indexes":"cqzgqjdzhgzhygwyqgzsdsng",
		"question":"\u6625\u79CB\u6218\u56FD\u671F\u95F4\u7684\u8BF8\u4FAF\u56FD\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EA1\u4E8E\u79E6\u56FD\u4E4B\u624B\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u56FD?",
		"id":23658
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"dtkgesggczfxlpmdj",
		"question":"\u5927\u5510\u5F00\u56FD\u4E8C\u5341\u56FD\u529F\u81E3\u4E2D,\u623F\u7384\u9F84\u6392\u540D\u7B2C\u51E0?",
		"id":23659
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671D\u9C9C",
		"indexes":"gy1627nhtjpbjmlnlsqcwhjdfsg",
		"question":"\u516C\u51431627\u5E74,\u7687\u592A\u6781\u6D3E\u5175\u527F\u706D\u4E86\u54EA\u91CC,\u4F7F\u5176\u6210\u4E3A\u540E\u91D1\u7684\u9644\u5C5E\u56FD?",
		"id":23660
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7164\u5C71",
		"indexes":"mczhdznlzy",
		"question":"\u660E\u5D07\u796F\u7687\u5E1D\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\u81EA\u7F22?",
		"id":23661
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6708\u6C0F",
		"indexes":"zjcsxytzcdmdsdbhdgqllnggj",
		"question":"\u5F20\u8E47\u51FA\u4F7F\u897F\u57DF,\u4ED6\u6700\u521D\u7684\u76EE\u7684\u662F\u4EE3\u8868\u6C49\u5E1D\u56FD\u53BB\u8054\u7EDC\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6?",
		"id":23662
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u664B\u706D\u5434",
		"indexes":"qxtscjdypjfcstlyxdzjssdsnglssj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u5BFB\u94C1\u7D22\u6C89\u6C5F\u5E95,\u4E00\u7247\u964D\u5E06\u51FA\u77F3\u5934\u201D\u3002\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u7684\u8FD9\u53E5\u8BD7\u8BF4\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u5386\u53F2\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":23663
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8C\u989C\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"stdlsqgzslhhdnfmssjdhbnx",
		"question":"\u8C01\u542C\u5230\u4E86\u201C\u4E09\u79CB\u6842\u5B50,\u5341\u91CC\u8377\u82B1\u201D\u7684\u5357\u65B9\u63CF\u8FF0,\u9042\u51B3\u5B9A\u6325\u5175\u5357\u4E0B?",
		"id":23664
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u8F7C",
		"indexes":"jmszlssdsj",
		"question":"\u201C\u5BC2\u5BDE\u6C99\u6D32\u51B7\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5?",
		"id":23665
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u9A6C\u5BFA",
		"indexes":"hmdmlzlyczjzlzgdyzfjsyqwzzsyjsm",
		"question":"\u6C49\u660E\u5E1D\u547D\u4EE4\u5728\u6D1B\u9633\u57CE\u4E2D\u5EFA\u9020\u4E86\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u5EA7\u4F5B\u6559\u5BFA\u9662,\u8BF7\u95EE\u8FD9\u5EA7\u5BFA\u9662\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23666
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90D1\u56FD\u6E20",
		"indexes":"zgsntsqdjcsgzpycwwy",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u54EA\u6761\u6C34\u6E20\u7684\u5EFA\u6210\u4F7F\u5173\u4E2D\u5E73\u539F\u6210\u4E3A\u6C83\u91CE?",
		"id":23667
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B50\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"kzsdbxcffyhsdssnhtyqn",
		"question":"\u5B54\u5B50\u8BF4:\u9053\u4E0D\u884C,\u4E58\u6874\u6D6E\u4E8E\u6D77,\u8BF4\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u80FD\u548C\u4ED6\u4E00\u8D77\u5462?",
		"id":23668
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u5E74",
		"indexes":"sqzdljnhd",
		"question":"\u5B8B\u94A6\u5B97\u5F53\u4E86\u51E0\u5E74\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":23669
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7693",
		"indexes":"dwzhywhdss",
		"question":"\u4E1C\u5434\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4F4D\u7687\u5E1D\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23670
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9879\u7FBD",
		"indexes":"bwbjsmcgssyxcmdzsxz",
		"question":"\u201C\u9738\u738B\u522B\u59EC\u201D\u201C\u56DB\u9762\u695A\u6B4C\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u82F1\u96C4\u8FDF\u66AE\u7684\u771F\u5B9E\u5199\u7167?",
		"id":23671
	},
	{
		"answer":"1587\u5E74",
		"indexes":"hryxszyzmdwlswnqwwlswnsgydsn",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u4EC1\u5B87\u5148\u751F\u8457\u6709\u8457\u540D\u7684\u300A\u4E07\u5386\u5341\u4E94\u5E74\u300B,\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E07\u5386\u5341\u4E94\u5E74\u662F\u516C\u5143\u591A\u5C11\u5E74?",
		"id":23672
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8463\u5353",
		"indexes":"hldshhthzzyshjdmmshgzsrlywy",
		"question":"\u6C49\u7075\u5E1D\u6B7B\u540E,\u4F55\u592A\u540E\u6267\u653F,\u8881\u7ECD\u3001\u4F55\u8FDB\u7B49\u5BC6\u8C0B\u6740\u5BA6\u5B98,\u62DB\u8C01\u5165\u6D1B\u9633\u4E3A\u63F4?",
		"id":23673
	},
	{
		"answer":"26",
		"indexes":"scssdd",
		"question":"\u5B59\u7B56\u6B7B\u65F6\u591A\u5927?",
		"id":23674
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67F3\u4E09\u53D8",
		"indexes":"bscrlyymjsm",
		"question":"\u5317\u5B8B\u8BCD\u4EBA\u67F3\u6C38\u539F\u540D\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23675
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u738B\u516B\u5366",
		"indexes":"htbgycsm",
		"question":"\u540E\u5929\u516B\u5366\u53C8\u79F0\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23676
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB\u5E74",
		"indexes":"xyhlbwzddwjxljndchzz",
		"question":"\u9879\u7FBD\u548C\u5218\u90A6\u4E3A\u4E89\u593A\u5E1D\u4F4D,\u8FDB\u884C\u4E86\u51E0\u5E74\u7684\u695A\u6C49\u6218\u4E89?",
		"id":23677
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u53EF\u6C57",
		"indexes":"ttzsqjwtjszpdmggynwslfwtcbfzmzzclsmwsm",
		"question":"\u5510\u592A\u5B97\u65F6\u671F\u5C06\u4E3A\u7A81\u53A5\u6240\u652F\u914D\u7684\u8499\u53E4\u9AD8\u539F\u7EB3\u4E3A\u52BF\u529B\u8303\u56F4,\u5510\u671D\u5317\u65B9\u8BF8\u6C11\u65CF\u4E13\u79F0\u674E\u4E16\u6C11\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23678
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5C14\u96C5\u300B",
		"indexes":"zgzzdcdjsm",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u8BCD\u5178\u53EB\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23679
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u671D",
		"indexes":"mxbtdzzsksncr",
		"question":"\u300A\u68A6\u6EAA\u7B14\u8C08\u300B\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u6C88\u62EC\u662F\u54EA\u671D\u4EBA?",
		"id":23680
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u516D\u5E74",
		"indexes":"lhqhgzqdsnswglsswsbddntzzzy",
		"question":"\u5415\u540E\u524D\u540E\u5171\u638C\u6743\u591A\u5C11\u5E74,\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u4E3A\u6570\u4E0D\u591A\u7684\u5973\u7EDF\u6CBB\u8005\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":23681
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u4E09",
		"indexes":"tszlhstxzddjgez",
		"question":"\u5510\u8083\u5B97\u674E\u4EA8\u662F\u5510\u7384\u5B97\u7684\u7B2C\u51E0\u4E2A\u513F\u5B50?",
		"id":23682
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u76F8\u5982",
		"indexes":"hwddhhcajbdrlgthlyqjqsxlzmf",
		"question":"\u6C49\u6B66\u5E1D\u7684\u7687\u540E\u9648\u963F\u5A07\u88AB\u6253\u5165\u51B7\u5BAB,\u5979\u82B1\u4E86\u4E00\u5343\u91D1\u6C42\u8C01\u5199\u4E86\u300A\u957F\u95E8\u8D4B\u300B?",
		"id":23683
	},
	{
		"answer":"12",
		"indexes":"jrbslzhsdcywdyxzwbdyndhddhxhygjlljghd",
		"question":"\u5047\u5982\u4E0D\u7B97\u5415\u96C9\u548C\u5C11\u5E1D\u3001\u660C\u9091\u738B\u7B49\u4E00\u4E9B\u5728\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5230\u4E00\u5E74\u7684\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u8BDD,\u897F\u6C49\u4E00\u5171\u7ECF\u5386\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D?",
		"id":23684
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u590F\u5386",
		"indexes":"z4000dnqdxcjksyllfsyrmdbzggldctlfjzsm",
		"question":"\u57284000\u591A\u5E74\u524D\u7684\u590F\u671D,\u5C31\u5F00\u59CB\u6709\u4E86\u5386\u6CD5,\u6240\u4EE5\u4EBA\u4EEC\u90FD\u628A\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u4F20\u7EDF\u5386\u6CD5\u53EB\u505A\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23685
	},
	{
		"answer":"28\u5E74",
		"indexes":"txzlljzzcqqgydlqswydsssckyzzqwkyzgnhcxldsn",
		"question":"\u5510\u7384\u5B97\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u6267\u653F\u521D\u671F,\u5168\u56FD\u9047\u5230\u4E86\u524D\u6240\u672A\u6709\u7684\u76DB\u4E16,\u53F2\u79F0\u201C\u5F00\u5143\u4E4B\u6CBB\u201D,\u8BF7\u95EE\u201C\u5F00\u5143\u201D\u8FD9\u4E2A\u5E74\u53F7\u6301\u7EED\u4E86\u591A\u5C11\u5E74?",
		"id":23686
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u5DFE\u519B",
		"indexes":"ychqymggzwzdtzjjdgztbshzrmdldhnysfckdzlsmqydbf",
		"question":"\u5143\u671D\u540E\u671F,\u4EE5\u8499\u53E4\u8D35\u65CF\u4E3A\u4E3B\u7684\u7EDF\u6CBB\u9636\u7EA7,\u5BF9\u5404\u65CF\u7279\u522B\u662F\u6C49\u65CF\u4EBA\u6C11\u7684\u63A0\u593A\u548C\u5974\u5F79\u5341\u5206\u6B8B\u9177,\u5BFC\u81F4\u4E86\u4EC0\u4E48\u8D77\u4E49\u7684\u7206\u53D1?",
		"id":23687
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5317\u5EAD\u90FD\u62A4\u5E9C",
		"indexes":"702nwztslsmjgglxtjgd",
		"question":"702\u5E74,\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u8BBE\u7ACB\u4EC0\u4E48\u673A\u6784\u7BA1\u7406\u897F\u7A81\u53A5\u6545\u5730?",
		"id":23688
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5723\u7956",
		"indexes":"qkxddmhssm",
		"question":"\u6E05\u5EB7\u7199\u5E1D\u7684\u5E99\u53F7\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":23689
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6BD5\u5347",
		"indexes":"hzyssssfmd",
		"question":"\u6D3B\u5B57\u5370\u5237\u672F\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u660E\u7684?",
		"id":23690
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u96CD\u6B63",
		"indexes":"tdrmzysxynghdzwsq",
		"question":"\u644A\u4E01\u5165\u4EA9\u4E3B\u8981\u5B9E\u884C\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5728\u4F4D\u65F6\u671F?",
		"id":23691
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5510\u660E\u7687",
		"indexes":"txzlljdshssmjc",
		"question":"\u5510\u7384\u5B97\u674E\u9686\u57FA\u7684\u8C25\u53F7\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?(\u7B80\u79F0)",
		"id":23692
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91D1",
		"indexes":"sxhyhsgzxngcc",
		"question":"\u201C\u7ECD\u5174\u548C\u8BAE\u201D\u540E,\u5B8B\u9AD8\u5B97\u5411\u54EA\u56FD\u79F0\u81E3?",
		"id":23693
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8036\u5F8B\u963F\u4FDD\u673A",
		"indexes":"ssjlllc",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u5EFA\u7ACB\u4E86\u8FBD\u671D?",
		"id":23694
	},
	{
		"answer":"206",
		"indexes":"gyqdsnqcblblddwzlltfl",
		"question":"\u516C\u5143\u524D\u591A\u5C11\u5E74,\u79E6\u671D\u88AB\u5218\u90A6\u9886\u5BFC\u7684\u6B66\u88C5\u529B\u91CF\u63A8\u7FFB\u4E86?",
		"id":23695
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u3001\u8700\u3001\u5434",
		"indexes":"txsfsztxflwnjg",
		"question":"\u5929\u4E0B\u4E09\u5206\u662F\u6307\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u88C2\u4E3A\u54EA\u51E0\u56FD",
		"id":23696
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u671B\u5E90\u5C71\u7011\u5E03",
		"indexes":"yxngslbdzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u674E\u767D\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23697
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u664B",
		"indexes":"ngszgsqjczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7701\u533A\u7B80\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":23698
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82CF\u6B65\u9752",
		"indexes":"xlnywshrsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u534E\u4EBA\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6?",
		"id":23701
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u514B",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsyzldw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8D28\u91CF\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":23702
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u95EA\u7C73\u7279\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":23703
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u948A",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssdd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u5202\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":23704
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u677E",
		"indexes":"yxngbssgyyzcxgdrw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u51FA\u73B0\u8FC7\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23705
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u534E\u76DB\u987F\u54E5\u4F26\u6BD4\u4E9A\u7279\u533A",
		"indexes":"qzcyxngsmgsd",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7F8E\u56FD\u9996\u90FD\uFF1F",
		"id":23706
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u4E50\u5BAB",
		"indexes":"xmnyzshcgd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u5EA7\u662F\u6C49\u671D\u5BAB\u6BBF\uFF1F",
		"id":23707
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7A3B\u7A57",
		"indexes":"ngsghdnr",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u56FD\u5FBD\u7684\u5185\u5BB9\uFF1F",
		"id":23708
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u501A\u5929\u5C60\u9F99\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"qzcjyzpdsnyg",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u91D1\u5EB8\u4F5C\u54C1\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A?",
		"id":23709
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u666F\u5FB7\u9547",
		"indexes":"xlngsjxsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":23710
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53A6\u95E8",
		"indexes":"xlngstwddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53F0\u6E7E\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":23711
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5CB8\u672C\u9F50\u53F2",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":23712
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9752\u5C9B",
		"indexes":"xlngssdsddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5C71\u4E1C\u7701\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":23713
	},
	{
		"answer":"4",
		"indexes":"xlnygsqs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5947\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":23714
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u59C6\u96F7\u7279",
		"indexes":"xlnybjdbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u672C\u7ECF\u5178\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23715
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u624B\u51A2\u6CBB\u866B",
		"indexes":"yxnwsmhj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6F2B\u753B\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":23716
	},
	{
		"answer":"14",
		"indexes":"59",
		"question":"5+9=?",
		"id":23717
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6469\u6258\u7F57\u62C9",
		"indexes":"yxsysjppds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u5C5E\u4E8E\u624B\u673A\u54C1\u724C\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23718
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8F7B\u6D6E",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":23719
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsysxjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E0A\u4E0B\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23720
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AD8\u96C4",
		"indexes":"xlngstwddm",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53F0\u6E7E\u7684\u5730\u540D?",
		"id":23721
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71D5\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykyfdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u98DE\u7684\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":23722
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EF4\u543E\u5C14\u65CF",
		"indexes":"nygbszgdssmz",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u5C11\u6570\u6C11\u65CF?",
		"id":23723
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u76D8",
		"indexes":"yxhzbsyzyjgds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6C49\u5B57\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5DE6\u53F3\u7ED3\u6784\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23724
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4FAF",
		"indexes":"ngsyppbssrd",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u504F\u65C1\u90E8\u9996\u662F\u4EBB\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":23725
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u77F3\u6CB9",
		"indexes":"xmngbsITgs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662FIT\u516C\u53F8\uFF1F",
		"id":23726
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5916\u4EA4\u5B66\u9662",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzzbj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":23727
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6731\u7531\u68C0",
		"indexes":"xlnwsmchd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u660E\u671D\u7687\u5E1D\uFF1F",
		"id":23728
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53F8\u9A6C\u61FF",
		"indexes":"lygessgcbbkxmnw",
		"question":"\u51CC\u70DF\u9601\u4E8C\u5341\u56DB\u529F\u81E3\u4E0D\u5305\u62EC\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":23729
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u90B5\u4F73\u4E00",
		"indexes":"sszgddyccjsjbjsjddqy",
		"question":"\u8C01\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u961F\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u53C2\u52A0\u4E16\u754C\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u7684\u7403\u5458",
		"id":23730
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u908B\u9062",
		"indexes":"ngsbyc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8D2C\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":23731
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u6893\u5C90",
		"indexes":"xmsbssgyyzdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23732
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xmnygjdbzbjsjn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u70B9\u4E0D\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\u5E02\u5883\u5185\uFF1F",
		"id":23733
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u52C7\u6562",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbyc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u8BCD\u662F\u8912\u4E49\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":23734
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u71D5\u5B50",
		"indexes":"xlnygsykyfdn",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u53EF\u4EE5\u98DE\u7684\u9E1F\uFF1F",
		"id":23736
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u516D",
		"indexes":"hzyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u597D\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":23737
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E24\u6D77\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"yxngsyyxzdwdx",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u94F6\u884C\u4E2D\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u5927\u884C\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":23738
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EA6\u514B\u767D",
		"indexes":"xlnybjdbsyzggddw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u672C\u7ECF\u5178\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u5178\u8BFB\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23739
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u80DC",
		"indexes":"lbshdkghdxcshjdzzzsjwsdhd",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\uFF0C\u8700\u6C49\u7684\u5F00\u56FD\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u76F8\u4F20\u662F\u6C49\u666F\u5E1D\u4E4B\u5B50\u4E2D\u5C71\u9756\u738B\u8C01\u7684\u540E\u4EE3\u3002",
		"id":23740
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u53EA",
		"indexes":"xhdbcxsqljzy",
		"question":"\u590F\u4FAF\u60C7\u88AB\u66F9\u6027\u5C04\u53BB\u4E86\u51E0\u652F\u773C?",
		"id":23741
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B8B\u6C5F",
		"indexes":"nwslshh",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4F4D\u662F\u6881\u5C71\u597D\u6C49\uFF1F",
		"id":23742
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u5170\u5DF4\u6258",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsyzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":23743
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7D22\u59C6\u6CB3\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"yxncbsdecsjdzzdzmzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u573A\u4E0D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u6218\u5F79\uFF1F",
		"id":23744
	},
	{
		"answer":"21\u7EA7\u4EE5\u5185",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzjsdskyhdzdjfqwjsbdyzjdsjdwjkyhdjfn",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u51FB\u6740\u5BF9\u624B\u53EF\u4EE5\u83B7\u5F97\u6218\u6597\u79EF\u5206\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u51FB\u6740\u4E0D\u4F4E\u4E8E\u81EA\u5DF1\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u7684\u73A9\u5BB6\u53EF\u4EE5\u83B7\u5F97\u79EF\u5206\u5462\uFF1F",
		"id":23745
	},
	{
		"answer":"8",
		"indexes":"glrwybydsb",
		"question":"\u56FD\u4EE4\u4EFB\u52A1\u4E00\u822C\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u6B65\uFF1F",
		"id":23746
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsrgyrzpdhhkybmfzzbcbdgjwpnmtyds",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5982\u679C\u6709\u4EBA\u5728\u9891\u9053\u558A\u8BDD\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u5E2E\u5FD9\u590D\u5236\u88C5\u5907\u3001\u7FC5\u8180\u7B49\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u4ED6\u4E00\u5B9A\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23747
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679C\u65AD\u62D2\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsyrgsnyffkymffzgjzbnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u6709\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u9AD8\u7EA7\u88C5\u5907\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23748
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsgjdzbcbdgjwpskytgmxtssdmffzm",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7684\u88C5\u5907\u3001\u7FC5\u8180\u7B49\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\u65F6\u53EF\u4EE5\u901A\u8FC7\u67D0\u4E9B\u7279\u6B8A\u624B\u6BB5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":23749
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u597D\u53CB\u7684\u53F7\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u76D7",
		"indexes":"dhpshytrxnjqjwpzsnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u76D7\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u597D\u53CB\u7A81\u7136\u5411\u4F60\u501F\u94B1\u501F\u7269\u54C1\uFF0C\u8FD9\u65F6\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23750
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u597D\u53CB\u7684\u53F7\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u76D7\uFF0C\u53D1\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"dhpshytrxnfsqgdwjhwlljzsnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u76D7\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u597D\u53CB\u7A81\u7136\u5411\u4F60\u53D1\u9001\u5947\u602A\u7684\u6587\u4EF6\u6216\u7F51\u7EDC\u94FE\u63A5\uFF0C\u8FD9\u65F6\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23751
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u597D\u53CB\u7684\u53F7\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u76D7",
		"indexes":"dhpshyqljbdswxrdrdtmtrxwsygzwps",
		"question":"\u3010\u76D7\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u597D\u53CB\u3001\u60C5\u4FA3\u3001\u7ED3\u62DC\u90FD\u662F\u6211\u4FE1\u4EFB\u7684\u4EBA\uFF0C\u5F53\u4ED6\u4EEC\u7A81\u7136\u60F3\u6211\u7D22\u8981\u8D35\u91CD\u7269\u54C1\u65F6\uFF1A",
		"id":23752
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67E5\u770B\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\u7269\u54C1\u548C\u7B49\u7EA7\u662F\u5426\u6B63\u786E",
		"indexes":"gfbtpspzwwsyxjdmzjxzplrpz1hpzlksqxsqsygssz1ygszmLdxxydzzqkwmyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u6446\u644A\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u5F80\u5F80\u4F7F\u7528\u76F8\u8FD1\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u8FDB\u884C\u8BC8\u9A97\uFF0C\u4F8B\u5982\uFF1A\u201C\u9A97\u5B501\u201D\u548C\u201C\u9A97\u5B50l\u201D\uFF0C\u770B\u4E0A\u53BB\u76F8\u4F3C\uFF0C\u5176\u5B9E\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B571\uFF0C\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5B57\u6BCDL\u7684\u5C0F\u5199\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23753
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u518D\u6B21\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B\u7269\u54C1\u662F\u5426\u6B63\u786E",
		"indexes":"gfbtpsjysyddqtwwfjyxydyhzjyydzzqkswmyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u6446\u644A\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u5F53\u524D\u644A\u4F4D\u65E0\u6CD5\u4EA4\u6613\uFF0C\u9700\u8981\u7B49\u4E00\u4F1A\u518D\u4EA4\u6613\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u65F6\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23754
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64E6\u4EAE\u53CC\u773C\uFF0C\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B",
		"indexes":"gfbtpspzwwydjzdwpmcgjzwpjxjylryxjmmcdxmydzzqkwmyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u6446\u644A\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u5F80\u5F80\u7528\u4F4E\u4EF7\u503C\u7684\u7269\u54C1\uFF0C\u5192\u5145\u9AD8\u4EF7\u503C\u7269\u54C1\u8FDB\u884C\u4EA4\u6613\uFF0C\u4F8B\u5982\uFF1A\u7528\u6A61\u80F6\u6728\u5192\u5145\u5E1D\u4F11\u6728\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23755
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65E0\u8BBA\u9A97\u5B50\u600E\u4E48\u8BF4\uFF0C\u90FD\u4E0D\u8981\u4E22\u5F03\u88C5\u5907",
		"indexes":"rzbpspztchygzsdpndqgzzbydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u6254\u88C5\u5907\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u901A\u5E38\u4F1A\u4EE5\u5404\u79CD\u624B\u6BB5\u9A97\u4F60\u4E22\u5F03\u8D35\u91CD\u88C5\u5907\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23756
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D2D\u4E70\u5B88\u62A4\u795E\u77F3\u8FDB\u884C\u7ED1\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"rzbpsdgjzbzyxdbhsds",
		"question":"\u3010\u6254\u88C5\u5907\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5BF9\u9AD8\u7EA7\u88C5\u5907\u6700\u6709\u6548\u7684\u4FDD\u62A4\u624B\u6BB5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23757
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u5BF9\u65B9\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"hhjypsjysdftrsxwjxhhydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u5BF9\u65B9\u7A81\u7136\u8BF4\u5E0C\u671B\u8FDB\u884C\u6362\u53F7\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23758
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8981\u6C42\u8FDB\u884C\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u7684\u5927\u6982\u7387\u662F\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"hhjypsgyhhjysfzqds",
		"question":"\u3010\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5173\u4E8E\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u8BF4\u6CD5\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23759
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u786E\u4FDD\u81EA\u8EAB\u8D35\u91CD\u7269\u54C1\u662F\u5426\u7ED1\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"PKpspzhtggzsdhyndkPKydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010PK\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u4F1A\u901A\u8FC7\u5404\u79CD\u624B\u6BB5\uFF0C\u5FFD\u60A0\u4F60\u6253\u5F00PK\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23760
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u81EA\u8EAB\u8D35\u91CD\u88C5\u5907\u662F\u5426\u7ED1\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"PKpskPKdshxyzy",
		"question":"\u3010PK\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5F00PK\u7684\u65F6\u5019\u9700\u8981\u6CE8\u610F\uFF1A",
		"id":23761
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u5BF9\u65B9\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"wlpsyxztrymzjnscdnsfcbydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7A81\u7136\u6709\u59B9\u7EB8\u52A0\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u5BF9\u4F60\u5341\u5206\u5D07\u62DC\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23762
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u62A0\u811A\u5927\u6C49\u4F2A\u88C5\u7684",
		"indexes":"wlpsnxzdjnhybzpyqzsgzxgzpdjnxnsjskns",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u90A3\u4E9B\u4E3B\u52A8\u52A0\u4F60\u597D\u53CB\uFF0C\u5E76\u5728\u670B\u53CB\u5708\u5C55\u793A\u5404\u79CD\u6027\u611F\u81EA\u62CD\u7684\u9753\u5973\u578B\u7537\uFF0C\u5B9E\u9645\u4E0A\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23763
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"jmsgdpsjyhwchylxnscsclhzjngddsgdyqzxjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u5BC4\u5356\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4EA4\u6613\u540E\u5B8C\u6210\u540E\u53C8\u8054\u7CFB\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u7B97\u9519\u4E86\uFF0C\u4F1A\u518D\u7ED9\u4F60\u66F4\u591A\u7684\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\uFF0C\u8981\u6C42\u91CD\u65B0\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23764
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BE5\u5546\u5BB6\u540D\u5B57\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u4EFF\u5192\uFF0C\u4ED4\u7EC6\u6838\u5BF9\u540E\u518D\u4EA4\u6613",
		"indexes":"jmsgdpsysjjysfxgsjdjjdzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u5BC4\u5356\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4E0E\u5546\u5BB6\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u53D1\u73B0\u8BE5\u5546\u5BB6\u7B49\u7EA7\u8F83\u4F4E\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23765
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u5BA2\u670D\u4E0D\u4F1A\u79C1\u804A\uFF0C\u53EF\u80FD\u9047\u5230\u9A97\u5B50\u4E86",
		"indexes":"jkfpsdyrslnszjsQQsgkfsnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u5047\u5BA2\u670D\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5F53\u6709\u4EBA\u79C1\u804A\u4F60\uFF0C\u8BF4\u81EA\u5DF1\u662FQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u5BA2\u670D\u65F6\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23766
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u6838\u5B9E\u5BF9\u65B9\u8EAB\u4EFD\u540E\u518D\u6DF1\u5165\u6C9F\u901A",
		"indexes":"jkfpsQQyxwywgsdzcskffldyjxysjyzxgmmdczydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u5047\u5BA2\u670D\u9A97\u672F\u3011QQ\u90AE\u7BB1\u65E0\u7F18\u65E0\u6545\u6536\u5230\u81EA\u79F0\u662F\u5BA2\u670D\u53D1\u6765\u7684\u90AE\u4EF6\uFF0C\u9700\u8981\u624B\u673A\u9A8C\u8BC1\u3001\u4FEE\u6539\u5BC6\u7801\u7B49\u64CD\u4F5C\u3002\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23767
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0B\u8F7D\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C\u6587\u4EF6\uFF0C\u4F1A\u5BFC\u81F4\u81EA\u5DF1\u53F7\u88AB\u76D7",
		"indexes":"zhpssczjbwyxlyhdhdxzjzsdsxynqwpxzzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u8D60\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u58F0\u79F0\u81EA\u5DF1\u4E0D\u73A9\u6E38\u620F\u4E86\uFF0C\u6709\u5F88\u591A\u597D\u4E1C\u897F\u76F4\u63A5\u8D60\u9001\uFF0C\u4F46\u662F\u9700\u8981\u4F60\u53BB\u7F51\u76D8\u4E0B\u8F7D\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23768
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u67E5\u770B\u4ED6\u7684\u8D26\u53F7\u7B49\u7EA7",
		"indexes":"gfmzpsyxzjccxyxgfmzmcgjwjzjdyxdbbffs",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7ECF\u5E38\u51FA\u73B0\u4E00\u4E9B\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u5192\u5145\u9AD8\u7EA7\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u6700\u7B80\u5355\u6709\u6548\u7684\u8FA8\u522B\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23769
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B\u5BF9\u65B9\u540D\u5B57\u3001\u7B49\u7EA7\u76F8\u5173\u4FE1\u606F\u662F\u5426\u6B63\u786E",
		"indexes":"gfmzpsyxzrhbmzygfmzzp",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u5982\u4F55\u907F\u514D\u906D\u9047\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u8BC8\u9A97\uFF1F",
		"id":23770
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B\u62C5\u4FDD\u4EBA\u540D\u5B57\u3001\u7B49\u7EA7\u76F8\u5173\u4FE1\u606F\u662F\u5426\u6B63\u786E",
		"indexes":"dbjypsscwlaqqjjysxyzygbsymdrjxdbrhzdjyzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u62C5\u4FDD\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u58F0\u79F0\u4E3A\u4E86\u5B89\u5168\u8D77\u89C1\uFF0C\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\u9700\u8981\u627E\u4E00\u4E2A\u699C\u4E0A\u6709\u540D\u7684\u4EBA\u8FDB\u884C\u62C5\u4FDD\uFF0C\u7136\u540E\u7EC4\u961F\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23771
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9519\uFF0C\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\u9700\u8981\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B\u62C5\u4FDD\u4EBA\u4FE1\u606F\u662F\u5426\u65E0\u8BEF",
		"indexes":"dbjypsydbrzcdjysfjnwwys",
		"question":"\u3010\u62C5\u4FDD\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6709\u62C5\u4FDD\u4EBA\u5728\u573A\u7684\u4EA4\u6613\u662F\u5426\u5C31\u80FD\u4E07\u65E0\u4E00\u5931\uFF1F",
		"id":23772
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B\u7269\u54C1\u4FE1\u606F\u6B63\u786E\u540E\u518D\u4EA4\u6613",
		"indexes":"yjlzpsjxwpjysxmsfzqds",
		"question":"\u3010\u4EE5\u5047\u4E71\u771F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u8FDB\u884C\u7269\u54C1\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u8BF4\u6CD5\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23773
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64E6\u4EAE\u53CC\u773C\uFF0C\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B",
		"indexes":"yjlzpsyxlmhypznddjwpmcgdjwpjxjywmyd",
		"question":"\u3010\u4EE5\u5047\u4E71\u771F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u91CC\u9762\u4F1A\u6709\u9A97\u5B50\u62FF\u4F4E\u7B49\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\uFF0C\u5192\u5145\u9AD8\u7B49\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\u8FDB\u884C\u4EA4\u6613\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u5F53\uFF1A",
		"id":23774
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9047\u5230\u9A97\u5B50\u4E86",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzslnscrsnyjncQbzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u79C1\u804A\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u8BA4\u8BC6\u4F60\uFF0C\u8981\u7ED9\u4F60\u51B2Q\u5E01\uFF0C\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23775
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50\u7684\u5957\u8DEF",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzydxswjscbzdzmbsgdhcsgbxwynjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u9047\u5230\u65B0\u624B\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u4E0D\u77E5\u9053\u600E\u4E48\u628A\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u6362\u6210\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01\uFF0C\u5E0C\u671B\u4E0E\u4F60\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23776
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u53D1\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C\uFF0C\u5343\u4E07\u522B\u4FE1\u4ED6",
		"indexes":"mcshpszyxzyrzdslnstpyynysdhrntjQQrhjnfwjzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u5192\u5145\u6536\u8D27\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u6709\u4EBA\u4E3B\u52A8\u79C1\u804A\u4F60\uFF0C\u8BF4\u4ED6\u670B\u53CB\u6709\u4F60\u8981\u6536\u7684\u8D27\uFF0C\u8BA9\u4F60\u6DFB\u52A0QQ\uFF0C\u7136\u540E\u7ED9\u4F60\u53D1\u6587\u4EF6\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23777
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50\uFF0C\u53D1\u7684\u90FD\u662F\u6728\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"mcshpszyxzrgyrxnfsgzwjljnmthykns",
		"question":"\u3010\u5192\u5145\u6536\u8D27\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5982\u679C\u6709\u4EBA\u60F3\u4F60\u53D1\u9001\u5404\u79CD\u6587\u4EF6\u3001\u94FE\u63A5\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u4ED6\u5F88\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23778
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u5207\u9E21",
		"indexes":"yxngbscc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5DDD\u83DC\uFF1F",
		"id":23779
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u591A\u60C5\u5251\u5BA2\u65E0\u60C5\u5251",
		"indexes":"qzcnygsgldzp",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u53E4\u9F99\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1?",
		"id":23780
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u773C\u7403",
		"indexes":"rthslbfbzgdqgs",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u4F53\u542B\u6C34\u91CF\u767E\u5206\u6BD4\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u5668\u5B98\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":23781
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u738B\u5141",
		"indexes":"dcdyfss",
		"question":"\u8C82\u8749\u7684\u4E49\u7236\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":23782
	},
	{
		"answer":"O",
		"indexes":"xlnygsydhxs",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6C27\u7684\u5316\u5B66\u5F0F?",
		"id":23783
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8272\u5F53\u6218\u5F79",
		"indexes":"yxncbsdecsjdzzdzmzy",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u573A\u4E0D\u662F\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u8457\u540D\u6218\u5F79?",
		"id":23784
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5408\u7EB5\u8FDE\u6A2A",
		"indexes":"sgyyzxlngsjyzglwg",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0E\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u65E0\u5173",
		"id":23785
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E03\u4E03\u5362\u6C9F\u6865\u4E8B\u53D8",
		"indexes":"yxngsfszdecsjdzzdsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u7B2C\u4E8C\u6B21\u4E16\u754C\u5927\u6218\u4E2D\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":23786
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u53D1\u7684\u8F6F\u4EF6\u6697\u85CF\u75C5\u6BD2\uFF0C\u5343\u4E07\u522B\u76F8\u4FE1",
		"indexes":"fzgjqwyghgbjwpdjgdbdyrgsntyrjkymfcxjgnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u8F85\u52A9\u5DE5\u5177\u8BF7\u52FF\u7528\u3011\u521A\u56DE\u5F52\u4E0D\u4E45\uFF0C\u7269\u54C1\u7684\u4EF7\u683C\u90FD\u4E0D\u61C2\uFF0C\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u4ED6\u6709\u8F6F\u4EF6\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u67E5\u8BE2\u4EF7\u683C\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23787
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F90\u5EB6",
		"indexes":"ssxlbtjlzgl",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u5218\u5907\u63A8\u8350\u4E86\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"id":23789
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"zhpspdlmhhsyzszhdzzrybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u8D60\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9891\u9053\u91CC\u9762\u558A\u8BDD\uFF0C\u8BF4\u8981\u8D60\u9001\u8D26\u53F7\u7684\uFF0C\u8FD9\u79CD\u4EBA\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23790
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679C\u65AD\u62D2\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"zhbdbwjzjmkdlyxlndhydnstkymfbnwcyxrwnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u8D26\u53F7\u7ED1\u5B9A\u4E0D\u5916\u501F\u3011\u6700\u8FD1\u6CA1\u7A7A\u767B\u5F55\u6E38\u620F\u4E86\uFF0C\u4F60\u7684\u597D\u53CB\u5BF9\u4F60\u8BF4\u4ED6\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u5E2E\u4F60\u5B8C\u6210\u6E38\u620F\u4EFB\u52A1\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23791
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F7B\u6613\u76F8\u4FE1\uFF0C\u62D2\u7EDD\u4ED6",
		"indexes":"fzgjqwywcswlxsyxyrgsntyycdndrjnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u8F85\u52A9\u5DE5\u5177\u8BF7\u52FF\u7528\u3011\u5916\u51FA\u65F6\u65E0\u804A\u60F3\u4E0A\u6E38\u620F\uFF0C\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u4ED6\u6709\u8FDC\u7A0B\u7535\u8111\u7684\u8F6F\u4EF6\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23792
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F3A\u5316\u88C5\u5907",
		"indexes":"rjqhlbysmzy",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u9636\u5F3A\u5316\u7075\u5B9D\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u4F5C\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":23793
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88C5\u5907\"\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9\"\u540E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u9ED8\u8BA4\u4F7F\u7528\u7684\u836F\u7269",
		"indexes":"gmlzdbjrhcnzdjzjdjsbj",
		"question":"\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E86\"\u81EA\u52A8\u8865\u7ED9\"\u5982\u4F55\u624D\u80FD\u81EA\u52A8\u7ED9\u81EA\u5DF1\u7684\u89D2\u8272\u8865\u7ED9?",
		"id":23794
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgztydqnygQQhxmsyjsdcksgydm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u540C\u4E00\u5927\u533A\u5185\u4E00\u4E2AQQ\u53F7\u4E0B\u9762\u6240\u6709\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u662F\u5171\u7528\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":23795
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5937\u9675\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qwswlfzzzjsdzys",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u8700\u5434\u4E24\u65B9\u4F5C\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u51B3\u80DC\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":23796
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u5415\u6C0F\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u4E2D\u8BB2\u519C\u4E1A\u653F\u7B56\u7684\u7BC7\u7AE0\u662F\u300A\u4E0A\u519C\u300B\u300A\u4EFB\u5730\u300B\u300A\u8FA9\u571F\u300B\u300A\u5BA1\u65F6\u300B\u3002",
		"indexes":"yxslscqzdyxpznypsjnyzcd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u662F\u300A\u5415\u6C0F\u6625\u79CB\u300B\u4E2D\u7684\u4E00\u4E9B\u7BC7\u7AE0\uFF0C\u54EA\u4E00\u7BC7\u662F\u8BB2\u519C\u4E1A\u653F\u7B56\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":23797
	},
	{
		"answer":"1969\u5E74",
		"indexes":"rlysyldycdysznn",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u6709\u53F2\u4EE5\u6765\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u767B\u6708\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":23798
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56DB",
		"indexes":"fshmgzytsjyyjlxf",
		"question":"\u98DE\u5347\u540E\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u5929\u751F\u5C31\u62E5\u6709\u51E0\u7C7B\u5FC3\u6CD5?",
		"id":23799
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD",
		"indexes":"csmshkszgkslxrsdgxcn",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u5F00\u59CB\uFF0C\u4E2D\u56FD\u5F00\u59CB\u5C65\u884C\u5165\u4E16\u7684\u5404\u9879\u627F\u8BFA\uFF1F",
		"id":23800
	},
	{
		"answer":"1939\u5E74",
		"indexes":"dgrqblsznyn",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u5165\u4FB5\u6CE2\u5170\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":23801
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u519B",
		"indexes":"184nhjmbbfsdsrzspsszzlbzzqybgszjtfsmj",
		"question":"184\u5E74\uFF0C\u9EC4\u5DFE\u6C11\u53D8\u7206\u53D1\uFF0C\u53D7\u5230\u5546\u4EBA\u5F20\u4E16\u5E73\u3001\u82CF\u53CC\u8D44\u52A9\uFF0C\u5218\u5907\u7EC4\u7EC7\u8D77\u4E49\u5175\uFF0C\u8DDF\u968F\u90B9\u9756\u8BA8\u4F10\u4EC0\u4E48\u519B",
		"id":23921
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"ccwyjjzcmzznzbjlrbrlszfbwssgzmjhyjzzwhr",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u8C13\u66F0\u300C\u5C06\u519B\u5728\u5306\u5FD9\u4E4B\u4E2D\uFF0C\u80FD\u6574\u5175\u575A\u5792\uFF0C\u4EFB\u8C24\u4EFB\u52B3\uFF0C\u4F7F\u4E4B\u53CD\u8D25\u4E3A\u80DC\u867D\u53E4\u4E4B\u540D\u5C06\uFF0C\u4F55\u4EE5\u52A0\u5179\u8005!\u300D\u4E3A\u4F55\u4EBA?",
		"id":23922
	},
	{
		"answer":"7.9\u516C\u91CC\u6BCF\u79D2",
		"indexes":"dyyzsdw",
		"question":"\u7B2C\u4E00\u5B87\u5B99\u901F\u5EA6\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":23923
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u5C45\u6613",
		"indexes":"rcjhhshcljslrlssdzp",
		"question":"\u201C\u65E5\u51FA\u6C5F\u82B1\u7EA2\u80DC\u706B\uFF0C\u6625\u6765\u6C5F\u6C34\u7EFF\u5982\u84DD\u201D\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1A",
		"id":23924
	},
	{
		"answer":"1914",
		"indexes":"shszbqdzbgynyyzsjrxsdmqwgmjysmnd",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u5E02\u95F8\u5317\u533A\u7684\u95F8\u5317\u516C\u56ED\u5185\uFF0C\u6709\u4E00\u5EA7\u5B8B\u6559\u4EC1\u5148\u751F\u7684\u5893\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u8BE5\u5893\u5EFA\u4E8E\u4EC0\u4E48\u5E74\u4EE3\uFF1F",
		"id":23925
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwcyhssdjdsxmnwjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u6D51\u8EAB\u662F\u80C6\u201D\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":23926
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62C9\u8428",
		"indexes":"wgngcssyrgzczc",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u7D20\u6709\u201D\u65E5\u5149\u4E4B\u57CE\u201C\u4E4B\u79F0\uFF1F",
		"id":23928
	},
	{
		"answer":"1994",
		"indexes":"zgzqjAlsksynyn",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u8DB3\u7403\u7532A\u8054\u8D5B\u5F00\u59CB\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\uFF1F",
		"id":23929
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7FA4\u82F1\u4F20\u300B",
		"indexes":"kcjszglysbcdxz",
		"question":"\u7A7A\u57CE\u8BA1\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u4E0E\u8C01\u6446\u51FA\u7684\u865A\u62DB",
		"id":23930
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5E73",
		"indexes":"gydyzss",
		"question":"\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u517B\u5B50\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":23931
	},
	{
		"answer":"1938\u5E7412\u6708",
		"indexes":"1977nhfgkhddycgkszngjjjxd",
		"question":"1977\u5E74\u6062\u590D\u9AD8\u8003\u540E\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u9AD8\u8003\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B63\u8282\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":23934
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u64CD",
		"indexes":"sgyyzzsxtdgzzszxxzdss",
		"question":"\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u4E2D\u201C\u5F20\u677E\u732E\u56FE\u201D\u5178\u6545\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5F20\u677E\u6700\u5148\u9009\u62E9\u7684\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":23938
	},
	{
		"answer":"021",
		"indexes":"shsddhqhsds",
		"question":"\u4E0A\u6D77\u5E02\u7684\u7535\u8BDD\u533A\u53F7\u662F\u591A\u5C11\uFF1F",
		"id":23939
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u82F1\u56FD",
		"indexes":"sjsdymypdsz",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u7B2C\u4E00\u679A\u90AE\u7968\u8BDE\u751F\u5728",
		"id":23940
	},
	{
		"answer":"1999",
		"indexes":"zynsxsnggjsjmgdlw",
		"question":"\uFF02\u81EA\u7531\u5973\u795E\u50CF\uFF02\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u9001\u7ED9\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684\u793C\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23941
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u589E\u52A0\u4EB2\u5BC6\u5EA6,\u5E08\u5085\u53EF\u4EE5\u83B7\u5F97\u201C\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u201D",
		"indexes":"tdmcshsfyqzdljyxnxsdd",
		"question":"\u5F92\u5F1F\u6CA1\u51FA\u5E08\uFF0C\u548C\u5E08\u5085\u4E00\u8D77\u7EC4\u961F\u7EC3\u7EA7\uFF0C\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u662F\u5BF9\u7684?",
		"id":23942
	},
	{
		"answer":"6\u4E2A\u6708",
		"indexes":"lzxzgdncxhyp",
		"question":"\u6797\u5219\u5F90\u5728\u5E7F\u4E1C\u54EA\u5904\u9500\u6BC1\u9E26\u7247\uFF1F",
		"id":23944
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0B\u8F7D\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C\u6587\u4EF6\uFF0C\u4F1A\u5BFC\u81F4\u81EA\u5DF1\u53F7\u88AB\u76D7",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzslnscrsnyjncQbzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u79C1\u804A\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u8BA4\u8BC6\u4F60\uFF0C\u8981\u7ED9\u4F60\u51B2Q\u5E01\uFF0C\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23945
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6",
		"indexes":"ggzjdsslhtjyxsfcbztkqsyjzjdxyhzswgnbwxgdmzdkpc",
		"question":"\u6EDA\u6EDA\u957F\u6C5F\u4E1C\u901D\u6C34,\u6D6A\u82B1\u6DD8\u5C3D\u82F1\u96C4.\u662F\u975E\u6210\u8D25\u8F6C\u5934\u7A7A.\u9752\u5C71\u4F9D\u65E7\u5728,\u51E0\u5EA6\u5915\u9633\u7EA2...\u8FD9\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u54EA\u90E8\u6587\u5B66\u53E4\u5178\u540D\u8457\u7684\u5F00\u7BC7\u8BCD",
		"id":23947
	},
	{
		"answer":"1927",
		"indexes":"qsqybfy1927n",
		"question":"\u79CB\u6536\u8D77\u4E49\u7206\u53D1\u4E8E1927\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":23948
	},
	{
		"answer":"6",
		"indexes":"btdtwydsg",
		"question":"\u6446\u644A\u7684\u644A\u4F4D\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u683C\uFF1F",
		"id":23949
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20",
		"indexes":"zfdbbxsm",
		"question":"\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u7238\u7238\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":23950
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u56FD",
		"indexes":"QQsgsyksmtcdyx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u662F\u4E00\u6B3E\u4EC0\u4E48\u9898\u6750\u7684\u6E38\u620F?",
		"id":23952
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8C\u5341\u516D",
		"indexes":"xlnxbsxpsddxzb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E0D\u662F\u5B09\u76AE\u58EB\u7684\u5178\u578B\u88C5\u626E",
		"id":23954
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9996\u9640\u7F57",
		"indexes":"gyddzxzdznygdwzd",
		"question":"\u53E4\u5370\u5EA6\u7684\u79CD\u59D3\u5236\u5EA6\u4E2D\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5730\u4F4D\u6700\u4F4E",
		"id":23955
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5180\u5156\u9752\u5F90\u8346\u626C\u8C6B\u6881\u96CD",
		"indexes":"zggcjzjzznjz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u79F0\u201C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u201D\uFF0C\u4E5D\u5DDE\u6307\u54EA\u4E5D\u5DDE\uFF1F",
		"id":23956
	},
	{
		"answer":"A",
		"indexes":"yxngkjjkyqfzdykjjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u53EF\u4EE5\u524D\u7FFB\"\u81EA\u5B9A\u4E49\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u7EC4\"?",
		"id":23957
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F7B\u4FE1,\u4ED4\u7EC6\u6838\u5BF9",
		"indexes":"gfbtpspzwwsyxjdmzjxzplrpz1hpzlksqxsqsygssz1ygszmLdxxydzzqkwmyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u6446\u644A\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u5F80\u5F80\u4F7F\u7528\u76F8\u8FD1\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u8FDB\u884C\u8BC8\u9A97\uFF0C\u4F8B\u5982\uFF1A\u201C\u9A97\u5B501\u201D\u548C\u201C\u9A97\u5B50l\u201D\uFF0C\u770B\u4E0A\u53BB\u76F8\u4F3C\uFF0C\u5176\u5B9E\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B571\uFF0C\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5B57\u6BCDL\u7684\u5C0F\u5199\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":23960
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5C40",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzydxswjscbzdzmbsgdhcsgbxwynjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u9047\u5230\u65B0\u624B\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u4E0D\u77E5\u9053\u600E\u4E48\u628A\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u6362\u6210\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01\uFF0C\u5E0C\u671B\u4E0E\u4F60\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23962
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679C\u65AD\u62D2\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"yjlzpsjxwpjysxmsfzqds",
		"question":"\u3010\u4EE5\u5047\u4E71\u771F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u8FDB\u884C\u7269\u54C1\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u4E0B\u9762\u8BF4\u6CD5\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":23965
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5C0F\u8BF4\u5BB6\u548C\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"yxsbszglfdwhsj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u8C01\u4E0D\u662F\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5C01\u7684\u201C\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\u201D",
		"id":23966
	},
	{
		"answer":"2000\u4F59",
		"indexes":"zgdygxsppjss",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7B2C\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C0F\u8BF4\u6279\u8BC4\u5BB6\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":23967
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5934\u4E0A\u6709\u95EE\u53F7\u7684",
		"indexes":"znxNPCkyjxrw",
		"question":"\u627E\u54EA\u4E9BNPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u65B0\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":23968
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"csbzdxdzlbbxz",
		"question":"<\u51FA\u5E08\u8868>\u4E2D\u7684\"\u5148\u5E1D\"\u6307\u5218\u5907,\"\u965B\u4E0B\"\u6307",
		"id":23970
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7B2C\u516B\u8F6E",
		"indexes":"wlghhsgmzxdwjqhysxxddbmytzezmybhzymyefdddjldbmytp",
		"question":"\u201C\u4E4C\u62C9\u572D\u56DE\u5408\u201D\u662F\u5173\u8D38\u603B\u534F\u5B9A\u4E3A\u52A0\u5F3A\u548C\u5EF6\u4F38\u73B0\u884C\u7684\u591A\u8FB9\u8D38\u6613\u4F53\u5236\uFF0C\u904F\u5236\u8D38\u6613\u4FDD\u62A4\u4E3B\u4E49\u8513\u5EF6\u800C\u53D1\u52A8\u7684\u7B2C\u51E0\u8F6E\u591A\u8FB9\u8D38\u6613\u8C08\u5224\uFF1F",
		"id":23973
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.1",
		"indexes":"xlsycxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7EAF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":23975
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5566",
		"indexes":"ngsqsc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8F7B\u58F0\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":23976
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9E8B\u9E7F",
		"indexes":"scsbxdsyxngdw",
		"question":"\u4FD7\u79F0\u201C\u56DB\u4E0D\u50CF\u201D\u7684\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23977
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u718A\u732B",
		"indexes":"yxngdwsbrdw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u54FA\u4E73\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":23978
	},
	{
		"answer":"59",
		"indexes":"qcjqmgbzxsnrmqtzdsqcgydsq",
		"question":"\u6E05\u671D\u5C06\u5168\u8499\u53E4\u90E8\u4F17\u6089\u6570\u7EB3\u5165\u76DF\u65D7\u4F53\u5236\uFF0C\u5F53\u65F6\u6E05\u671D\u5171\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u65D7\uFF1F",
		"id":23979
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9001\u4F60\u4E00\u5339\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"nybssmzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u4E09\u6BDB\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23980
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u773C\u955C\u738B\u86C7",
		"indexes":"ntszgcdds",
		"question":"\u54EA\u6761\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u4EA7\u7684\u6BD2\u86C7\uFF1F",
		"id":23981
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u57CE\u51B3",
		"indexes":"nybsjyzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u91D1\u5EB8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23982
	},
	{
		"answer":"212",
		"indexes":"ngsyzysx",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E13\u7528\u4E66\u4FE1\uFF1F",
		"id":23983
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53CC\u57CE\u8BB0",
		"indexes":"nybscesdgszp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u67E5\u5C14\u65AF\u00B7\u72C4\u66F4\u65AF\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23984
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A86\u9A7C\u7965\u5B50",
		"indexes":"nybslszp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u8001\u820D\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23985
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8377\u5858\u6708\u8272",
		"indexes":"nybszzqzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6731\u81EA\u6E05\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23986
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7532\u9AA8\u6587",
		"indexes":"zgwzdybzzqyyngjd",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u6587\u5B57\u7684\u6F14\u53D8\uFF0C\u6700\u65E9\u8D77\u6E90\u4E8E\u54EA\u4E2A\u9636\u6BB5\uFF1F",
		"id":23987
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u9B47",
		"indexes":"nybszalzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5F20\u7231\u73B2\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23988
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u697C\u68A6\u9B47",
		"indexes":"nybszalzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5F20\u7231\u73B2\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23989
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9146\u608C",
		"indexes":"jjssxyysstbxlnwbsjjssstb",
		"question":"\u848B\u4ECB\u77F3\u624B\u4E0B\u4E5F\u6709\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u848B\u4ECB\u77F3\u201C\u5341\u4E09\u592A\u4FDD\u201D\uFF1F",
		"id":23990
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5E73\u6DE1\u751F\u6D3B",
		"indexes":"nybshyzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u6D77\u5CA9\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23991
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9053\u58EB\u5854",
		"indexes":"nybsyqyzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u4F59\u79CB\u96E8\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23992
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7AE5\u5E74",
		"indexes":"nybsgejzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u9AD8\u5C14\u57FA\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23993
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u971C\u8349\u82CD\u82CD\u866B\u5207\u5207",
		"indexes":"czcydsjsnyj",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA<<\u6751\u591C>>\u7684\u8BD7\u53E5\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u53E5?",
		"id":23994
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.333\u2026\u2026",
		"indexes":"xlsycxhxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7EAF\u5FAA\u73AF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":23995
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F0A\u51E1\u8BFA\u592B",
		"indexes":"nybsqhfzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u5951\u8BC3\u592B\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23996
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F46\u897F",
		"indexes":"xlnywsydlwyfxsqdrw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F\u610F\u5927\u5229\u6587\u827A\u590D\u5174\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":23997
	},
	{
		"answer":"1+i",
		"indexes":"xlnygsbsss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u6570\u4E0D\u662F\u5B9E\u6570\uFF1F",
		"id":23998
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7686\u5927\u6B22\u559C",
		"indexes":"nybsssbyzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u838E\u58EB\u6BD4\u4E9A\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":23999
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5450\u558A",
		"indexes":"nybslxzp",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u90E8\u662F\u9C81\u8FC5\u4F5C\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":24000
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E07\u4E8B\u4EE5\u5FE0\u539A\u4E3A\u672C\uFF0C\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A\u4EBA\u7ACB\u8EAB\u3001\u7ACB\u8A00\u3001\u7ACB\u884C\u7684\u57FA\u7840\uFF01",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbzyssgcg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5B50\u591C\u56DB\u65F6\u6B4C\uFF1A\u6625\u6B4C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24001
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"hjjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6A2A\u5251\u51FB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24003
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"wlpsnxzdjnhybzpyqzsgzxgzpdjnxnsjskns",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u90A3\u4E9B\u4E3B\u52A8\u52A0\u4F60\u597D\u53CB\uFF0C\u5E76\u5728\u670B\u53CB\u5708\u5C55\u793A\u5404\u79CD\u6027\u611F\u81EA\u62CD\u7684\u9753\u5973\u578B\u7537\uFF0C\u5B9E\u9645\u4E0A\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24004
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5403\u9971\u4E86\u4F1A\u6253\u55DD",
		"indexes":"clzjddhgs",
		"question":"\u5403\u4E86\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u7684\u540E\u679C\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":24005
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"lbcjzgsmzy",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u66FE\u7ECF\u4F5C\u8FC7\u4EC0\u4E48\u804C\u4E1A?",
		"id":24007
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"yryhsjdssyccdzdgs",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u4E0E\u66F9\u64CD\u6597\u667A\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":24010
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzydxswjscbzdzmbsgdhcsgbxwynjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u9047\u5230\u65B0\u624B\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u4E0D\u77E5\u9053\u600E\u4E48\u628A\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u6362\u6210\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01\uFF0C\u5E0C\u671B\u4E0E\u4F60\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24012
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"jskwsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u91D1\u86C7\u72C2\u821E\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24013
	},
	{
		"answer":"10\u5206\u949F",
		"indexes":"xscpbdxBOSSdzsjsxyc",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u5C0FBOSS\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\u5237\u65B0\u4E00\u6B21\uFF1F",
		"id":24014
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxnlfzsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u7C7B\u526F\u804C\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":24016
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u6C49",
		"indexes":"wgymwrlytsy",
		"question":"\u6211\u56FD\u4EE5\u7164\u4E3A\u71C3\u6599\u51B6\u94C1\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":24017
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"spsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6C34\u7011\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24018
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"jdcchyszbsfdgjzys",
		"question":"\u51B3\u5B9A\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8881\u7ECD\u4E89\u9738\u80DC\u8D1F\u7684\u5173\u952E\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":24019
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F20",
		"indexes":"zfdbbxsm",
		"question":"\u5F20\u98DE\u7684\u7238\u7238\u59D3\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":24020
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CB3\u5317\u6DBF\u90E1",
		"indexes":"sgmjzfzydssmcs",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u731B\u5C06\u5F20\u98DE\uFF0C\u5B57\u7FFC\u5FB7\uFF0C\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u51FA\u8EAB",
		"id":24021
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9047\u5230\u9A97\u5B50\u4E86",
		"indexes":"gfmzpsyxzrhbmzygfmzzp",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u5982\u4F55\u907F\u514D\u906D\u9047\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u8BC8\u9A97\uFF1F",
		"id":24022
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkytghbl",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u63D0\u4F9B\u56DE\u907F\u7387\uFF1F",
		"id":24024
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48",
		"indexes":"yxngsysg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u679C",
		"id":24025
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7ECF\u9A8C,\u5BB6\u4F19",
		"indexes":"ngsqsc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8F7B\u58F0\u8BCD\uFF1F",
		"id":24026
	},
	{
		"answer":"C27",
		"indexes":"qzcxlnywshyxszdrw",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u6307\u51FA\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4F4D\u662F<<\u7EA2\u5CA9>>\u5C0F\u8BF4\u4E2D\u7684\u4EBA\u7269?",
		"id":24030
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"czyoyxdssnys",
		"question":"\u51FA\u81EA\u4E8E\u201C\u6B27\u9633\u4FEE\u201C\u7684\u8BD7\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u9996?",
		"id":24031
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u5B9D\u5FC3\u597D\u7D2F\uFF0C\u5B9D\u5B9D\u8981\u7761\u89C9",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlbgsy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5173\u5C71\u6708\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24032
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6076\u884C\u8C41\u514D\u4EE4\u548C\u65E0\u6094\u91D1\u7827\u90FD\u80FD\u6362\u5230",
		"indexes":"xszdzysmy",
		"question":"\u65B0\u624B\u6307\u5BFC\u8BC1\u6709\u4EC0\u4E48\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":24033
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9999\u6C34",
		"indexes":"yxngsmrhzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u7F8E\u5BB9\u5316\u5986\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":24034
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E4C\u9C81\u6728\u9F50",
		"indexes":"yxngcsbsyzg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":24035
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u593A\u53D6\u653F\u6743",
		"indexes":"zcjjgmpmcdzgmzgmddybs",
		"question":"\u8D44\u4EA7\u9636\u7EA7\u9769\u547D\u6D3E\u8FC8\u51FA\u7684\u4E2D\u56FD\u6C11\u4E3B\u9769\u547D\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B65\u662F?",
		"id":24036
	},
	{
		"answer":"203",
		"indexes":"qwcyhssdjdsxmnwjl",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u6210\u8BED\u201C\u6D51\u8EAB\u662F\u80C6\u201D\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u4E0B\u9762\u54EA\u4F4D\u5C06\u9886?",
		"id":24037
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62A5\u540D\u65F6\u95F4\u76F8\u90BB",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzmgxqsmshjx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u661F\u671F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8FDB\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":24042
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u73A9\u5BB6",
		"indexes":"mlsszdsssyg",
		"question":"\u540D\u843D\u5B59\u5C71\u4E2D\u7684\"\u5B59\u5C71\"\u662F\u4E00\u4E2A",
		"id":24047
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E7E\u9675",
		"indexes":"zgwydjlghdhzdlmz",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u552F\u4E00\u7684\u5C06\u4E24\u4E2A\u7687\u5E1D\u5408\u846C\u7684\u9675\u5893\u5728",
		"id":24050
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u529B\u6C34\u6676",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpkyjsddshfdjgjz",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u53EF\u4EE5\u5C06\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u4F24\u5BB3\u53CD\u5F39\u7ED9\u653B\u51FB\u8005\uFF1F",
		"id":24051
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2\u7EA2\u8089",
		"indexes":"kysjtgzjydhlddjs",
		"question":"\u53EF\u4EE5\u77AC\u95F4\u63D0\u9AD8\u81EA\u5DF1\u4E00\u5B9A\u6D3B\u529B\u7684\u9053\u5177\u662F?",
		"id":24053
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F7B\u6613\u76F8\u4FE1\uFF0C\u62D2\u7EDD\u4ED6",
		"indexes":"zspszyxzydxswjscbzdzmbsgdhcsgbxwynjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u719F\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u9047\u5230\u65B0\u624B\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u4E0D\u77E5\u9053\u600E\u4E48\u628A\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u6362\u6210\u4E09\u56FD\u5E01\uFF0C\u5E0C\u671B\u4E0E\u4F60\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24056
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u5408\u6210,\u4ECENPC\u8D2D\u4E70",
		"indexes":"yxzddjlyy",
		"question":"\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7684\u9053\u5177\u6765\u6E90\u6709\uFF1A",
		"id":24060
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7CA4",
		"indexes":"ngszgsqjczy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u7701\u533A\u7B80\u79F0\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":24064
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u67A3",
		"indexes":"yxngsswsw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u9178\u5473\u98DF\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":24065
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EA2,\u6A59,\u9EC4,\u7EFF,\u84DD,\u975B,\u7D2B",
		"indexes":"ngsrlrykykddqcg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4EBA\u7C7B\u8089\u773C\u53EF\u4EE5\u770B\u5230\u7684\u4E03\u5F69\u5149\uFF1F",
		"id":24066
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u87D1\u8782",
		"indexes":"xlnyzsfxlkc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u79CD\u662F\u98DE\u884C\u7C7B\u6606\u866B?",
		"id":24067
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51CF\u53F7",
		"indexes":"xlsygxfhdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5173\u7CFB\u7B26\u53F7\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":24068
	},
	{
		"answer":"45\u00B0\u548C45\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwbjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u8865\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9\uFF1F",
		"id":24069
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u597D\u53CB\u7684\u53F7\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u76D7\uFF0C\u53D1\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"hhjypsgyhhjysfzqds",
		"question":"\u3010\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5173\u4E8E\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u8BF4\u6CD5\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24070
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u5E08",
		"indexes":"yxngzyssyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":24073
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B0\u624B\u8F85\u52A9\u5E08",
		"indexes":"cxgzyzdjpxbnxyznwNPC",
		"question":"\u67E5\u8BE2\u5404\u804C\u4E1A\u4E3B\u7B49\u7EA7\u6392\u884C\u699C,\u4F60\u9700\u8981\u627E\u54EA\u4F4DNPC?",
		"id":24074
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"bmjssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u706D\u91D1\u8EAB\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24076
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"lzqjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u529B\u65A9\u5343\u94A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24077
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7406\u8D22\u8BA1\u5212\uFF0C\u5E2E\u4F60\u6210\u4E3A\u201C\u7CD5\u5BCC\u5E05\u201D",
		"indexes":"mqwgtzezgdxykssmk",
		"question":"\u76EE\u524D\u6211\u56FD\u900F\u652F\u989D\u6700\u9AD8\u7684\u4FE1\u7528\u5361\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u5361\uFF1F",
		"id":24079
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u786E\u4FDD\u81EA\u8EAB\u8D35\u91CD\u7269\u54C1\u662F\u5426\u7ED1\u5B9A",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsgjdzbcbdgjwpskytgmxtssdmffzm",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7684\u88C5\u5907\u3001\u7FC5\u8180\u7B49\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\u65F6\u53EF\u4EE5\u901A\u8FC7\u67D0\u4E9B\u7279\u6B8A\u624B\u6BB5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24080
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u7406\u4F1A,\u76F4\u63A5\u5220\u9664",
		"indexes":"jkfpsQQyxwywgsdzcskffldyjxysjyzxgmmdczydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u5047\u5BA2\u670D\u9A97\u672F\u3011QQ\u90AE\u7BB1\u65E0\u7F18\u65E0\u6545\u6536\u5230\u81EA\u79F0\u662F\u5BA2\u670D\u53D1\u6765\u7684\u90AE\u4EF6\uFF0C\u9700\u8981\u624B\u673A\u9A8C\u8BC1\u3001\u4FEE\u6539\u5BC6\u7801\u7B49\u64CD\u4F5C\u3002\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24081
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64E6\u4EAE\u53CC\u773C\uFF0C\u4ED4\u7EC6\u67E5\u770B",
		"indexes":"gfmzpsyxzjccxyxgfmzmcgjwjzjdyxdbbffs",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7ECF\u5E38\u51FA\u73B0\u4E00\u4E9B\u9AD8\u4EFF\u540D\u5B57\u5192\u5145\u9AD8\u7EA7\u73A9\u5BB6\uFF0C\u6700\u7B80\u5355\u6709\u6548\u7684\u8FA8\u522B\u65B9\u6CD5\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24082
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"txsfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6311\u8845\u56DB\u65B9\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24085
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u795E\u884C\u4E4B\u5377",
		"indexes":"yxngdjskyzscngmdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u662F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u5546\u57CE\u5185\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":24088
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u5B50,\u60F3\u76D7\u53D6\u8D26\u53F7",
		"indexes":"mcshpszyxzrgyrxnfsgzwjljnmthykns",
		"question":"\u3010\u5192\u5145\u6536\u8D27\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u5728\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5982\u679C\u6709\u4EBA\u60F3\u4F60\u53D1\u9001\u5404\u79CD\u6587\u4EF6\u3001\u94FE\u63A5\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u4ED6\u5F88\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24090
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u6E21",
		"indexes":"jdcchyszbsfdgjzys",
		"question":"\u51B3\u5B9A\u66F9\u64CD\u548C\u8881\u7ECD\u4E89\u9738\u80DC\u8D1F\u7684\u5173\u952E\u6218\u5F79\u662F?",
		"id":24092
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u514B\u9C81\u683C\u66FC",
		"indexes":"cpsmzqllsyxngjjxztcd",
		"question":"\u4EA7\u54C1\u751F\u547D\u5468\u671F\u7406\u8BBA\u662F\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u7ECF\u6D4E\u5B66\u8005\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":24093
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u661F\u671F\u4E8C,\u661F\u671F\u56DB,\u661F\u671F\u516D",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzmgxqsmshjx",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u6BCF\u4E2A\u661F\u671F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u5019\u8FDB\u884C\uFF1F",
		"id":24094
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u679C\u65AD\u62D2\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"dhpshytrxnfsqgdwjhwlljzsnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u76D7\u53F7\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u597D\u53CB\u7A81\u7136\u5411\u4F60\u53D1\u9001\u5947\u602A\u7684\u6587\u4EF6\u6216\u7F51\u7EDC\u94FE\u63A5\uFF0C\u8FD9\u65F6\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24095
	},
	{
		"answer":"2\u6761",
		"indexes":"zggdbfdsczlyjt",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u5317\u65B9\u7684\u201C\u4E1D\u7EF8\u4E4B\u8DEF\u201D\u6709\u51E0\u6761\uFF1F",
		"id":24099
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5C11\u5947",
		"indexes":"xlnwlgmjbcwkcdjcwzgdsszddya",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u8001\u9769\u547D\u5BB6\u88AB\u9519\u8BEF\u5F00\u9664\u515A\u7C4D\uFF0C\u6210\u4E3A\u4E2D\u5171\u515A\u53F2\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u51A4\u6848\uFF1F",
		"id":24100
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"sggfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u5DE5\u9B3C\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24101
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7070\u8272",
		"indexes":"bwjqhddgw",
		"question":"\u6BD4\u73A9\u5BB6\u5F3A\u5F88\u591A\u7684\u602A\u7269:",
		"id":24103
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"btcyxkyhdtyqdlytxm",
		"question":"\u4E0D\u9000\u51FA\u6E38\u620F\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u6362\u5230\u540C\u4E00\u533A\u7684\u53E6\u4E00\u6761\u7EBF\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24104
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxdbwqdwlgjl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4EE3\u8868\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u529B?",
		"id":24105
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u7384",
		"indexes":"zgldfqj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u53EB",
		"id":24107
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u987E\u8305\u5E90",
		"indexes":"zglgglmyhbxyyxesldglzdgljghscq",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u201C\u8EAC\u8015\u9647\u4EA9\u201D\u4E8E\u6E56\u5317\u8944\u9633\u4EE5\u897F\u4E8C\u5341\u91CC\u7684\u53E4\u9686\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5EA6\u8FC7\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u5BD2\u6691\u6625\u79CB\u3002",
		"id":24108
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6B66\u529B",
		"indexes":"zgrztznyxdbwqdwlgjl",
		"question":"\u5728\u4E2A\u4EBA\u72B6\u6001\u4E2D,\u54EA\u4E00\u9879\u4EE3\u8868\u6B66\u5668\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u529B?",
		"id":24109
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u662F",
		"indexes":"zQQsgztydqnygQQhxmsyjsdcksgydm",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u540C\u4E00\u5927\u533A\u5185\u4E00\u4E2AQQ\u53F7\u4E0B\u9762\u6240\u6709\u89D2\u8272\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u662F\u5171\u7528\u7684\u5417?",
		"id":24112
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5F00\u5546\u884C,\u5356\u7ED9NPC",
		"indexes":"zyjzjdydwpdjmcqzq",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u5C06\u81EA\u5DF1\u591A\u4F59\u7684\u7269\u54C1\u9053\u5177\u5356\u51FA\u53BB\u8D5A\u94B1\uFF1F",
		"id":24113
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"qlssngzydjn",
		"question":"\u8F7B\u7075\u672F\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24116
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"hjzbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u8C6A\u6770\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":24117
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7117\u6CB9",
		"indexes":"yxngbscydhfhzp",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5E38\u7528\u7684\u62A4\u53D1\u5316\u5986\u54C1\uFF1F",
		"id":24119
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E56\u5317",
		"indexes":"ngdqymyjj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u533A\u6709\u6885\u96E8\u5B63\u8282\uFF1F",
		"id":24120
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u767D\u300A\u5C06\u8FDB\u9152\u300B",
		"indexes":"ssblqxxemfcznss",
		"question":"\u201C\u8700\u50E7\u62B1\u7EFF\u7EEE\uFF0C\u897F\u4E0B\u5CE8\u7709\u5CF0\u3002\u201D\u51FA\u81EA\u54EA\u9996\u8BD7\uFF1F",
		"id":24121
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u897F\u5B89",
		"indexes":"ngcscjsgdhdddc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u57CE\u5E02\u66FE\u7ECF\u662F\u53E4\u4EE3\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u90FD\u57CE\uFF1F",
		"id":24122
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u767B\u4E4B\u56F4",
		"indexes":"xlnygzybsfszhc",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E00\u4E2A\u6218\u5F79\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u6C49\u671D\uFF1F",
		"id":24123
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"xlngsjbsfszsgsq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E8B\u4EF6\u4E0D\u662F\u53D1\u751F\u5728\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\uFF1F",
		"id":24124
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E50\u6BC5",
		"indexes":"zhjcxyzgzqhzjdwcbzskcwzgwqnzzzyztsdwjzzjxlnwbszhj",
		"question":"\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\u51FA\u73B0\u4E8E\u6218\u56FD\u81F3\u79E6\u6C49\u4E4B\u9645\uFF0C\u591A\u4E3A\u7B56\u8FA9\u4E4B\u58EB\uFF0C\u53EF\u79F0\u4E3A\u4E2D\u56FD\u4E94\u5343\u5E74\u4E2D\u6700\u65E9\u4E5F\u6700\u7279\u6B8A\u7684\u5916\u4EA4\u653F\u6CBB\u5BB6\u3002\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u662F\u7EB5\u6A2A\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":24125
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7269\u7406\u5B66,\u5316\u5B66,\u751F\u7406\u5B66\u6216\u533B\u5B66,\u6587\u5B66,\u548C\u5E73",
		"indexes":"syzcnbejdzldsng",
		"question":"\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6700\u521D\u8BFA\u8D1D\u5C14\u5956\u7684\u79CD\u7C7B\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":24126
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u95EA\u4E00\u95EA\u4EAE\u6676\u6676\uFF0C\u6EE1\u5929\u90FD\u662F\u5C0F\u661F\u661F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbscdfyhgjwszw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u548F\u6000\u53E4\u8FF9\u4E94\u9996\u4E4B\u4E94\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24128
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u9C8D\u8001\u513F\u300B",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlpdhj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9891\u300A\u6E21\u6C49\u6C5F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24129
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u5B9D\u4E0D\u5F00\u5FC3",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlszhjcbgyjyssh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9002\u300A\u4E2D\u548C\u8282\u8D50\u767E\u5B98\u71D5\u96C6\u56E0\u793A\u6240\u6000\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24130
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F60\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u4E0D\u7406\u6211",
		"indexes":"xlnjbschhttxyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u97E9\u7FC3\u300A\u540C\u9898\u4ED9\u6E38\u89C2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24131
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u5996\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"cyzsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u6B8B\u9633\u7099\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24133
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A97\u672F",
		"indexes":"jmsgdpsjyhwchylxnscsclhzjngddsgdyqzxjyzzqkybs",
		"question":"\u3010\u5BC4\u5356\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4EA4\u6613\u540E\u5B8C\u6210\u540E\u53C8\u8054\u7CFB\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u7B97\u9519\u4E86\uFF0C\u4F1A\u518D\u7ED9\u4F60\u66F4\u591A\u7684\u4E09\u56FD\u70B9\uFF0C\u8981\u6C42\u91CD\u65B0\u4EA4\u6613\u3002\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4E00\u822C\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24134
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F7B\u4FE1,\u4FDD\u6301\u8B66\u60D5",
		"indexes":"wlpsyxztrymzjnscdnsfcbydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7A81\u7136\u6709\u59B9\u7EB8\u52A0\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u5BF9\u4F60\u5341\u5206\u5D07\u62DC\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24135
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7261\u4E39",
		"indexes":"cszwztxlfsdhssmh",
		"question":"\u4F20\u8BF4\u4E2D\u6B66\u5219\u5929\u4E0B\u4EE4\u711A\u70E7\u7684\u82B1\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u82B1",
		"id":24137
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u848B\u5E72",
		"indexes":"sddwyszybzyjjjjsccsscmzysjldd",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5230\u4E1C\u5434\u6E38\u8BF4\u5468\u745C\uFF0C\u88AB\u5468\u745C\u5C06\u8BA1\u5C31\u8BA1\uFF0C\u4F7F\u66F9\u64CD\u6740\u6B7B\u8521\u7441\u5F20\u5141\u6C34\u519B\u4E24\u90FD\u7763\uFF0C",
		"id":24138
	},
	{
		"answer":"1997",
		"indexes":"ygwfdansznynqs",
		"question":"\u82F1\u56FD\u738B\u5983\u6234\u5B89\u5A1C\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u53BB\u4E16",
		"id":24140
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"jlldsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u60CA\u96F7\u88C2\u5730\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24142
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u76F8\u4FE1,\u4E3E\u62A5",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsyrgsnyffkymffzgjzbnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u6709\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u9AD8\u7EA7\u88C5\u5907\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24143
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u7384",
		"indexes":"zgldfqj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u53EB",
		"id":24144
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F",
		"indexes":"sgsqjgzzds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u5EFA\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":24145
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u664B\u7A46\u5E1D",
		"indexes":"cgzjwgy29wwwhdqzzxds",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u53E4\u81F3\u4ECA\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u670929\u4F4D\u5A03\u5A03\u7687\u5E1D\uFF0C\u5176\u4E2D\u6700\u5C0F\u7684\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24146
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u68A6\u5F97",
		"indexes":"tdzmwxjlyxz",
		"question":"\u5510\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u6587\u5B66\u5BB6\u5218\u79B9\u9521\u5B57",
		"id":24147
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EBD\u7EA6",
		"indexes":"lhgmsczbsz",
		"question":"\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u79D8\u4E66\u5904\u603B\u90E8\u8BBE\u5728",
		"id":24148
	},
	{
		"answer":"30\u65E5",
		"indexes":"blyczmxkzdbghzxsxyzypzjgpzzrqdsrndfzjgblbgzxsx",
		"question":"\u529E\u7406\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\u7684\u53D8\u66F4\u548C\u6CE8\u9500\u624B\u7EED\uFF0C\u5E94\u5728\u539F\u6279\u51C6\u673A\u5173\u6279\u51C6\u4E4B\u65E5\u8D77\u591A\u5C11\u65E5\u5185\uFF0C\u5230\u53D1\u8BC1\u673A\u5173\u529E\u7406\u53D8\u66F4\u3001\u6CE8\u9500\u624B\u7EED\uFF1F",
		"id":24151
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u51AC",
		"indexes":"1977nhfgkhddycgkszngjjjxd",
		"question":"1977\u5E74\u6062\u590D\u9AD8\u8003\u540E\u7684\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u9AD8\u8003\u662F\u5728\u54EA\u4E2A\u5B63\u8282\u4E3E\u884C\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":24152
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u300A\u7F8A\u57CE\u665A\u62A5\u300B",
		"indexes":"z1998ndljfbznjbzbtsft",
		"question":"\u57281998\u5E74\u7684\u201C\u9646\u4FCA\u98CE\u6CE2\u201D\u4E2D\uFF0C\u54EA\u5BB6\u62A5\u7EB8\u88AB\u63A8\u4E0A\u6CD5\u5EAD\uFF1F",
		"id":24153
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"rgwyjAjszwqtdjngjkym",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u6211\u8981\u5C06A\u952E\u8BBE\u7F6E\u4E3A\u5176\u5B83\u7684\u6280\u80FD\u653B\u51FB\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24154
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"xmjsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7EED\u547D\u8BC0\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24155
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62D2\u7EDD\u4F7F\u7528",
		"indexes":"fzgjqwyghgbjwpdjgdbdyrgsntyrjkymfcxjgnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u8F85\u52A9\u5DE5\u5177\u8BF7\u52FF\u7528\u3011\u521A\u56DE\u5F52\u4E0D\u4E45\uFF0C\u7269\u54C1\u7684\u4EF7\u683C\u90FD\u4E0D\u61C2\uFF0C\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u4ED6\u6709\u8F6F\u4EF6\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u67E5\u8BE2\u4EF7\u683C\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24157
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E8E\u8C26",
		"indexes":"qcwjcsslhfsrdxfssgqbpylqbzrjdzzss",
		"question":"\u201C\u5343\u9524\u4E07\u51FB\u51FA\u6DF1\u5C71\uFF0C\u70C8\u706B\u711A\u70E7\u82E5\u7B49\u95F2\u3002\u7C89\u8EAB\u788E\u9AA8\u5168\u4E0D\u6015\uFF0C\u8981\u7559\u6E05\u767D\u5728\u4EBA\u95F4\u3002\u201D\u7684\u4F5C\u8005\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":24159
	},
	{
		"answer":"G",
		"indexes":"scdkjjssm",
		"question":"\u5546\u57CE\u7684\u5FEB\u6377\u952E\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48?",
		"id":24160
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u8F6C\u8D26,\u4E0D\u63D0\u4F9B\u8D26\u53F7\u5BC6\u7801",
		"indexes":"wlpsyxztrymzjnscdnsfcbydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7A81\u7136\u6709\u59B9\u7EB8\u52A0\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u5BF9\u4F60\u5341\u5206\u5D07\u62DC\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24161
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B98\u6E21\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"yxngzysylccjjlhjkrjjdfljjddgjc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u6218\u5F79\u4F7F\u7528\u4E86\u8349\u8239\u501F\u7BAD\u3001\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1\u3001\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1\u3001\u501F\u4E1C\u98CE\u3001\u79BB\u95F4\u8BA1\u7B49\u591A\u4E2A\u8BA1\u7B56",
		"id":24162
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u660E",
		"indexes":"zgldfqj",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u7684\u7236\u4EB2\u53EB",
		"id":24163
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"slthsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u795E\u9F99\u63A2\u6D77\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24165
	},
	{
		"answer":"15",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzjjkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u51E0\u7EA7\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":24166
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u9001\u5979\u9AD8\u7EA7\u88C5\u5907,\u4E0D\u7ED9\u5979\u8F6C\u8D26,\u4E0D\u7ED9\u5979\u8D26\u53F7\u5BC6\u7801",
		"indexes":"wlpsyxztrymzjnscdnsfcbydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u7F51\u604B\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6E38\u620F\u4E2D\u7A81\u7136\u6709\u59B9\u7EB8\u52A0\u4F60\uFF0C\u58F0\u79F0\u5BF9\u4F60\u5341\u5206\u5D07\u62DC\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24167
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u76D6",
		"indexes":"zyyshylyckrjlrcczjwhldhscclxhmgl",
		"question":"\u5468\u745C\u4E0E\u8C01\u5408\u6F14\u4E86\u4E00\u573A\u82E6\u8089\u8BA1\u6765\uFF0C\u8BA9\u66F9\u64CD\u4E2D\u8BA1\uFF0C\u4E3A\u540E\u6765\u7684\u706B\u70E7\u66F9\u8239\u7ACB\u4E0B\u6C57\u9A6C\u529F\u52B3\u3002",
		"id":24168
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54C8\u8428\u514B\u65CF",
		"indexes":"gnzsngmzdyx",
		"question":"\u201C\u59D1\u5A18\u8FFD\u201D\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u6C11\u65CF\u7684\u6E38\u620F\uFF1F",
		"id":24169
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7406\u8D22\u8BA1\u5212\uFF0C\u5E2E\u4F60\u6210\u4E3A\u201C\u7CD5\u5BCC\u5E05\u201D",
		"indexes":"dsjbyxcnbs",
		"question":"\u591A\u5C11\u7EA7\u522B\u4EE5\u4E0B\u624D\u80FD\u62DC\u5E08?",
		"id":24171
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"indexes":"sgsqjgzzds",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u5EFA\u56FD\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":24172
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u767D\u8D77",
		"indexes":"zgsqcjxlksjhmsswzjdqgjlss",
		"question":"\u6218\u56FD\u65F6\u671F\u66FE\u7ECF\u4E0B\u4EE4\u5751\u6740\uFF08\u5373\u6D3B\u57CB\uFF09\u56DB\u5341\u4E07\u8D75\u519B\u7684\u79E6\u56FD\u5C06\u9886\u662F\u8C01\uFF1F",
		"id":24173
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5937\u9675\u4E4B\u6218",
		"indexes":"qwswlfzzzjsdzys",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u8700\u5434\u4E24\u65B9\u4F5C\u6218\u4E2D\uFF0C\u51B3\u80DC\u7684\u6218\u5F79\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":24175
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FDE\u73AF\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"ptyxrdwylbqsxjccrcjjmzcyhlszycbrlpdcjs",
		"question":"\u5E9E\u7EDF\u6709\u5FC3\u8BA9\u4E1C\u5434\u4E0E\u5218\u5907\u53D6\u80DC\uFF0C\u732E\u8BA1\u66F9\u64CD\uFF0C\u8BA9\u66F9\u519B\u5C06\u6BCF\u53EA\u8239\u7528\u73AF\u8FDE\u4E0A\uFF0C\u8FD9\u6837\u66F9\u5175\u5982\u5C65\u5E73\u5730\uFF0C\u6B64\u8BA1\u662F",
		"id":24177
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6253\u5B83\u5F97\u732A\u76AE\uFF0C\u53EF\u4EE5\u5356\u5F88\u591A\u94B1",
		"indexes":"sgxscpbdgwxmzwsmjczbd",
		"question":"\u8700\u56FD\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u65C1\u8FB9\u7684\u602A\u7269\u5C0F\u86EE\u732A\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u7ECF\u5E38\u627E\u4E0D\u5230?",
		"id":24178
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u7384",
		"indexes":"hzywlbsxshsytzszs",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u4E3A\u5218\u8868\u624B\u4E0B\u65F6\u548C\u8C01\u4E00\u540C\u9547\u5B88\u957F\u6C99",
		"id":24181
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD1\u4EE3\u4F1F\u5927\u7684\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6\u662F\u8D1D\u591A\u82AC",
		"indexes":"dxlyljdpsbzqds",
		"question":"\u5BF9\u4E0B\u5217\u97F3\u4E50\u5BB6\u7684\u8BC4\u8FF0\u4E0D\u6B63\u786E\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24183
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u5907",
		"indexes":"cczjlyxszdyxss",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\u65F6\u6307\u7684\u82F1\u96C4\u662F\u8C01?",
		"id":24184
	},
	{
		"answer":"9\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"qsqybfy1927n",
		"question":"\u79CB\u6536\u8D77\u4E49\u7206\u53D1\u4E8E1927\u5E74\uFF1A",
		"id":24185
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u731C\u64C2\u53F0\u6BD4\u6B66",
		"indexes":"cpzwgfxlsyjnmzzdcps",
		"question":"\u5F69\u7968\u5728\u6211\u56FD\u53D1\u884C\u5386\u53F2\u60A0\u4E45\uFF0C\u90A3\u4E48\u6700\u65E9\u7684\u5F69\u7968\u662F",
		"id":24186
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48",
		"indexes":"nzyshzhl",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u9C7C\u751F\u6D3B\u5728\u6D77\u91CC?",
		"id":24187
	},
	{
		"answer":"3",
		"indexes":"czyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u5DDD\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":24188
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u94F6\u884C",
		"indexes":"ngszgyxzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u94F6\u884C\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":24189
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7956\u51B2\u4E4B",
		"indexes":"xlngszggdzmdsxj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u53E4\u4EE3\u8457\u540D\u7684\u6570\u5B66\u5BB6\uFF1F",
		"id":24190
	},
	{
		"answer":"C35",
		"indexes":"xlnxzmymjdcccwd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u9879\u4E2D\u540D\u8A00\u540D\u53E5\u7684\u51FA\u5904\u9519\u8BEF\u7684\uFF1F",
		"id":24191
	},
	{
		"answer":"9",
		"indexes":"szjyxlngxxbsdysyy",
		"question":"\u6570\u5B57\u201C\u4E5D\u201D\u4E0E\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u9009\u9879\u8868\u793A\u7684\u610F\u601D\u4E00\u6837\uFF1F",
		"id":24192
	},
	{
		"answer":"45\u00B0\u548C90\u00B0",
		"indexes":"xlsyhwbjdsnyd",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E92\u4E3A\u8865\u89D2\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u5BF9\uFF1F",
		"id":24193
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u533B\u79D1\u5927\u5B66",
		"indexes":"yxngdxddzzbj",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5927\u5B66\u7684\u5730\u5740\u5728\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":24194
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u871C\u8702",
		"indexes":"xlnzsgldkczy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u79CD\u662F\u53E4\u8001\u7684\u6606\u866B\u4E4B\u4E00?",
		"id":24195
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7898\u5316\u94F6",
		"indexes":"rgjyszlyzbshzwz",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u5DE5\u964D\u96E8\u662F\u5728\u51B7\u4E91\u4E2D\u64AD\u6492\u4F55\u79CD\u7269\u8D28\uFF1F",
		"id":24196
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u957F\u57CE",
		"indexes":"xlnygjgbsybj",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u666F\u89C2\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5317\u4EAC\uFF1F",
		"id":24197
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7C73",
		"indexes":"xlsyzddwdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u957F\u5EA6\u5355\u4F4D\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":24198
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72FC",
		"indexes":"yxnzdwsrsdw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u79CD\u52A8\u7269\u662F\u8089\u98DF\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":24199
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9F20\u6807\u53F3\u952E\u70B9\u51FB\u4ED6\u7684\u5934\u50CF\u9009\u62E9\u201C\u79C1\u804A\u201D",
		"indexes":"zmhlygwjsl",
		"question":"\u600E\u4E48\u548C\u53E6\u4E00\u4E2A\u73A9\u5BB6\u79C1\u804A\uFF1F",
		"id":24200
	},
	{
		"answer":"1972\u5E742\u670821\u65E5",
		"indexes":"________zmjjtywgzfldrdxpfmfw",
		"question":"________\u4E2D\u7F8E\u5EFA\u4EA4\uFF0C\u540C\u6708\u6211\u56FD\u653F\u5E9C\u9886\u5BFC\u4EBA\u9093\u5C0F\u5E73\u8D74\u7F8E\u8BBF\u95EE\u3002",
		"id":24203
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u7384",
		"indexes":"hzywlbsxshsytzszs",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5FE0\u539F\u4E3A\u5218\u8868\u624B\u4E0B\u65F6\u548C\u8C01\u4E00\u540C\u9547\u5B88\u957F\u6C99",
		"id":24204
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u98CE\u884C\u77F3",
		"indexes":"yxnxwpsyhkyzydsjnzjyddsd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E9B\u7269\u54C1\u4F7F\u7528\u540E\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u4E00\u6BB5\u65F6\u95F4\u5185\u589E\u52A0\u79FB\u52A8\u7684\u901F\u5EA6?",
		"id":24206
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u9664\u8457\u6709\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5916\u8FD8\u8457\u6709 [\u7B54\u6848\u9009\u9879\u5982\u4E0B]",
		"indexes":"lgzczysgyywhzy",
		"question":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u9664\u8457\u6709\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5916\u8FD8\u8457\u6709",
		"id":24209
	},
	{
		"answer":"203",
		"indexes":"sjszddyskwy",
		"question":"\u4E16\u754C\u4E0A\u6700\u5927\u7684\u9668\u77F3\u5751\u4F4D\u4E8E?",
		"id":24210
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7384\u5FB7",
		"indexes":"lbzsm",
		"question":"\u5218\u5907\u5B57\u4EC0\u4E48",
		"id":24213
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"yxngzysbsyQQsgd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u662F\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD\u7684?",
		"id":24214
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u7406\u4F1A,\u4E3E\u62A5",
		"indexes":"jkfpsQQyxwywgsdzcskffldyjxysjyzxgmmdczydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u5047\u5BA2\u670D\u9A97\u672F\u3011QQ\u90AE\u7BB1\u65E0\u7F18\u65E0\u6545\u6536\u5230\u81EA\u79F0\u662F\u5BA2\u670D\u53D1\u6765\u7684\u90AE\u4EF6\uFF0C\u9700\u8981\u624B\u673A\u9A8C\u8BC1\u3001\u4FEE\u6539\u5BC6\u7801\u7B49\u64CD\u4F5C\u3002\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24216
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5341\u5E38\u4F8D\u7684\u6028\u7075\u51FA\u73B0\u5728\u5317\u9099\u5C71\u4E2D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u901F\u5230\u8BB8\u5B50\u5C06\u5904\u96C6\u5408\uFF0C\u524D\u5F80\u5317\u9099\u5C71\u8179\u51C0\u5316\u6028\u7075\u3002",
		"indexes":"hjfbdygdBOSSjsmz",
		"question":"\u9EC4\u5DFE\u526F\u672C\u7B2C\u4E00\u5173\u7684BOSS\u53EB\u5565\u540D\u5B57?",
		"id":24217
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u84DD\u7EB9\u7389",
		"indexes":"zQQsgzrgxzxqsyxngstydsdhkyx",
		"question":"\u5728QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u4E2D,\u5982\u679C\u978B\u5B50\u9576\u5D4C\u4E0A\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u77F3\u5934,\u79FB\u52A8\u901F\u5EA6\u4F1A\u5FEB\u4E00\u4E9B?",
		"id":24218
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B5F\u83B7",
		"indexes":"wpdnzdqdplbkmqqqzds",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u5E73\u5B9A\u5357\u4E2D\u5730\u533A\u7684\u53DB\u4E71\uFF0C\u88AB\u5B54\u660E\u300C\u4E03\u64D2\u4E03\u7EB5\u300D\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":24220
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CA1\u6709\u5339\u914D\u5230\u5BF9\u624B",
		"indexes":"QQsgjtzsmqkxcsdwhzdhs",
		"question":"QQ\u4E09\u56FD\u519B\u56E2\u6218\uFF0C\u4EC0\u4E48\u60C5\u51B5\u4E0B\uFF0C\u53C2\u8D5B\u961F\u4F0D\u4F1A\u81EA\u52A8\u83B7\u80DC\uFF1F",
		"id":24222
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"yydljssjgddjssstcdjm",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u9038\u5F85\u52B3\u8BA1\u662F\u8700\u519B\u653B\u6253\u5B9A\u519B\u5C71\u65F6\uFF0C\u8C01\u63D0\u51FA\u7684\u8BA1\u8C0B",
		"id":24225
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u91CD\u5E86",
		"indexes":"zgdwdznl",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u201C\u96FE\u90FD\u201D\u5728\u54EA\u91CC\uFF1F",
		"id":24226
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7EED\u547D\u4E38",
		"indexes":"yxngdjzqhscsgmbdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u5728\u5343\u8D27\u5546\u5904\u662F\u8D2D\u4E70\u4E0D\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":24227
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DF4\u7279\u5C14",
		"indexes":"dgsxbsmtxfshzyfcfdzymds",
		"question":"\u5FB7\u56FD\u9996\u76F8\u4FFE\u65AF\u9EA6\u63A8\u884C\u53CD\u793E\u4F1A\u4E3B\u4E49\u201C\u975E\u5E38\u6CD5\u201D\u7684\u4E3B\u8981\u76EE\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24229
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143\u671D",
		"indexes":"zgdngcdcjlhkoylzdddg",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u56FD\u7684\u54EA\u4E2A\u671D\u4EE3\u66FE\u5EFA\u7ACB\u6A2A\u8DE8\u6B27\u4E9A\u4E24\u6D32\u7684\u5927\u5E1D\u56FD\uFF1A",
		"id":24230
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5343\u8D27\u5546",
		"indexes":"xksddlwdccygzngNPC",
		"question":"\u60F3\u5FEB\u901F\u5230\u8FBE\u53E6\u5916\u7684\u57CE\u6C60,\u5E94\u8BE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC?",
		"id":24231
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8D75\u4E91",
		"indexes":"qwkmjwdfhyhrjyebgzyprzs",
		"question":"\u8BF7\u95EE\u5B54\u660E\u501F\u5B8C\u4E1C\u98CE\u540E\u7531\u4F55\u4EBA\u63A5\u5E94\uFF0C\u800C\u907F\u8FC7\u5468\u745C\u6D3E\u4EBA\u8FFD\u6740?",
		"id":24232
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E94",
		"indexes":"szyjbh",
		"question":"\u201C\u751F\u201D\u5B57\u6709\u51E0\u7B14\u753B\uFF1F",
		"id":24233
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5929\u9E45\u6E56,\u80E1\u6843\u5939\u5B50,\u7761\u7F8E\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"qqzmdblwjs",
		"question":"\u5168\u7403\u8457\u540D\u7684\u82AD\u857E\u821E\u5267\u662F",
		"id":24234
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u518D\u4E0D\u7ED9\u5403\u7684\uFF0C\u4EBA\u5FC3\u6563\u4E86\uFF0C\u961F\u4F0D\u5C31\u4E0D\u597D\u5E26\u4E86\uFF01",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczdsywctsyyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u5BA1\u8A00\u300A\u671B\u6625\u4EAD\u4F8D\u6E38\u5E94\u8BCF\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24235
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E09\u82F1\u6218\u5415\u5E03",
		"indexes":"nygssgyylmdsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u91CC\u9762\u7684\u4E8B\u4EF6?",
		"id":24236
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u81EC",
		"indexes":"srcbjydjrwxsjlqwxlnwbsyjlzl",
		"question":"\u4E16\u4EBA\u79F0\u767D\u5C45\u6613\u7B49\u4E5D\u4EBA\u4E3A\u201C\u9999\u5C71\u4E5D\u8001\u201D\uFF0C\u8BF7\u95EE\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E5D\u8001\u4E4B\u5217\uFF1F",
		"id":24237
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5730\u9762\u53D1\u70EB",
		"indexes":"ngsdzqdyj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u5730\u9707\u524D\u7684\u9884\u8B66\uFF1F",
		"id":24238
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u7FBD,\u5F20\u98DE,\u8D75\u4E91,\u9A6C\u8D85,\u9EC4\u5FE0",
		"indexes":"ngssgwhsj",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u8700\u56FD\u4E94\u864E\u4E0A\u5C06\uFF1F",
		"id":24239
	},
	{
		"answer":"C35",
		"indexes":"xlnygsymkdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u732B\u79D1\u52A8\u7269\uFF1F",
		"id":24240
	},
	{
		"answer":"C35",
		"indexes":"xlngbswglssjxsnymdcqyk",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u6211\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u6C5F\u897F\u7701\u5185\u6709\u540D\u7684\u74F7\u5668\u7A91\u53E3\uFF1F",
		"id":24241
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7389\u73BA\u4E0D\u7F18\u5F52\u65E5\u89D2",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsclsysg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u674E\u5546\u9690\u300A\u968B\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24242
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5927\u6EE1",
		"indexes":"ngs24jqzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F24\u8282\u6C14\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1F",
		"id":24243
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"ngscyd31jtfwyhtfmmhddgjhdq",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u662F\u53C2\u4E0E\u7B2C31\u5C4A\u53F0\u98CE\u59D4\u5458\u4F1A\u53F0\u98CE\u547D\u540D\u6D3B\u52A8\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u548C\u5730\u533A\uFF1F",
		"id":24244
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72EC\u6709\u8854\u6069\u5904",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlbwzfss",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u9A86\u5BBE\u738B\u300A\u81F3\u5206\u6C34\u620D\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24245
	},
	{
		"answer":"C35",
		"indexes":"hcsqnxngfxhxlngdfbsnxndzd",
		"question":"\u6C49\u671D\u65F6\u671F\uFF0C\u5357\u5308\u5974\u5F52\u9644\u897F\u6C49\uFF0C\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E2A\u5730\u65B9\u4E0D\u662F\u5357\u5308\u5974\u7684\u9A7B\u5730\uFF1F",
		"id":24246
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6E38\u4E09\u56FD\u6CB3\u5C71,\u5BFB\u73CD\u8D35\u5B9D\u85CF",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczcryfhjyjrdcesftyz",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5D14\u65E5\u7528\u300A\u5949\u548C\u4E5D\u6708\u4E5D\u65E5\u767B\u6148\u6069\u5BFA\u6D6E\u56FE\u5E94\u5236\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24248
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u65B9\u4E39",
		"indexes":"xlnwmyhdgozbjsjdzjssdch",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u6CA1\u6709\u83B7\u5F97\u8FC7\u6B27\u6D32\u676F\u51B3\u8D5B\u9636\u6BB5\u6700\u4F73\u5C04\u624B\u7684\u79F0\u53F7\uFF1F",
		"id":24249
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6768\u4FEE",
		"indexes":"yryhsjdssyccdzdgs",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4EBA\u4E00\u76D2\u9165\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u8C01\u4E0E\u66F9\u64CD\u6597\u667A\u7684\u6545\u4E8B",
		"id":24250
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u52AD",
		"indexes":"rnygsyplrwdmsplccwzsznclszjxcmss",
		"question":"\u6C5D\u5357\u6709\u4E2A\u5584\u4E8E\u8BC4\u8BBA\u4EBA\u7269\u7684\u540D\u58EB\uFF0C\u8BC4\u8BBA\u66F9\u64CD\u4E3A\uFF1A\u201C\u6CBB\u4E16\u4E4B\u80FD\u81E3\uFF0C\u4E71\u4E16\u4E4B\u5978\u96C4\u201D\uFF0C\u6B64\u540D\u58EB\u662F",
		"id":24253
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5723\u7956",
		"indexes":"kxhddmhs",
		"question":"\u5EB7\u7199\u7687\u5E1D\u7684\u5E99\u53F7\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24254
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u662F\u7684",
		"indexes":"jtcyzddgdddjyhbfjtcydgdddjydm",
		"question":"\u519B\u56E2\u6210\u5458\u7EC4\u961F\u6253\u602A\u5F97\u5230\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u4F1A\u6BD4\u975E\u519B\u56E2\u6210\u5458\u6253\u602A\u5F97\u5230\u7684\u7ECF\u9A8C\u591A\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24255
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u806A\u660E\u4F36\u4FD0\u7684\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"lysllcmngzdsdmssfmd",
		"question":"\u5229\u7528\u6C34\u529B\u6765\u8202\u7C73\u78BE\u8C37\u5B50\u7684\u6C34\u7893\u78E8\u662F\u8C01\u53D1\u660E\u7684",
		"id":24257
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u594B\u8FC5",
		"indexes":"xjszjsddwlgjshygxlnyx",
		"question":"\u60F3\u51CF\u5C11\u81EA\u5DF1\u53D7\u5230\u7684\u7269\u7406\u653B\u51FB\u4F24\u5BB3,\u5E94\u8BE5\u4FEE\u70BC\u54EA\u4E00\u9879?",
		"id":24259
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"ygdwlzdkyydsr",
		"question":"\u4E00\u4E2A\u961F\u4F0D\u91CC\u6700\u591A\u53EF\u4EE5\u6709\u591A\u5C11\u4EBA?",
		"id":24261
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F\u56FD",
		"indexes":"yxnggjbsyQQsg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u5C5E\u4E8EQQ\u4E09\u56FD?",
		"id":24268
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u826F",
		"indexes":"rcmswcbmzlszds",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u79F0\u300C\u9A6C\u6C0F\u4E94\u5E38\uFF0C\u767D\u7709\u6700\u826F\u300D\u6240\u6307\u7684\u662F?",
		"id":24270
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E0D\u76F8\u4FE1,\u4E0D\u7406\u4F1A,\u4E3E\u62A5",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsyrgsnyffkymffzgjzbnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u6709\u65B9\u6CD5\u53EF\u4EE5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u9AD8\u7EA7\u88C5\u5907\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24271
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E1C\u6C49\u672B\u5E74",
		"indexes":"sgyyjdssmsqdsq",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u8BB2\u7684\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\u65F6\u671F\u7684\u4E8B\u60C5",
		"id":24272
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u6E38\u4E09\u56FD\u6CB3\u5C71",
		"indexes":"xcrfbzdfssy",
		"question":"\u65B0\u6625\u71C3\u653E\u7206\u7AF9\u7684\u98CE\u4FD7\u59CB\u4E8E",
		"id":24273
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u7EA6\u9EC4\u660F\u540E",
		"indexes":"yslstdxyjssm",
		"question":"\u201C\u6708\u4E0A\u67F3\u68A2\u5934\u201D\u7684\u4E0B\u4E00\u53E5\u662F\u4EC0\u4E48\uFF1F",
		"id":24274
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BB8\u8D21",
		"indexes":"ssxccbgscxqxdzxhbscss",
		"question":"\u662F\u8C01\u5411\u66F9\u64CD\u62A5\u544A\u5B59\u7B56\u88AD\u53D6\u8BB8\u90FD\u4E4B\u5FC3\uFF0C\u540E\u88AB\u5B59\u7B56\u6240\u6740?",
		"id":24278
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54ED\u51FA\u6765\u7684",
		"indexes":"xhylbdjss",
		"question":"\u6B47\u540E\u8BED--\u5218\u5907\u7684\u6C5F\u5C71\u662F?",
		"id":24279
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7981\u536B",
		"indexes":"ksfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5F00\u5C71\u65A7\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24282
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u6771\u65B9\u6782\u7ECC",
		"indexes":"xlnwsxjbpsx",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4F4D\u601D\u60F3\u5BB6\u88AB\u5224\u6B7B\u5211",
		"id":24283
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B59\u7B56",
		"indexes":"cccjmscbjjys",
		"question":"\u66F9\u64CD\u66FE\u7ECF\u547D\u8C01\u51FA\u5175\u622A\u51FB\u8881\u672F?",
		"id":24284
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D",
		"indexes":"sgyyssdzz",
		"question":"\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u662F\u8C01\u7684\u8457\u4F5C",
		"id":24285
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251",
		"indexes":"xsszbsmlxdwq",
		"question":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB\u88C5\u5907\u4EC0\u4E48\u7C7B\u578B\u7684\u6B66\u5668?",
		"id":24286
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8C6A\u6770",
		"indexes":"adcqsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u50B2\u65AD\u82CD\u7A79\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24287
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u5BF9\u65B9\u53EF\u80FD\u662F\u9A97\u5B50",
		"indexes":"gfbtpspzwwsyxjdmzjxzplrpz1hpzlksqxsqsygssz1ygszmLdxxydzzqkwmyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u9AD8\u4EFF\u6446\u644A\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9A97\u5B50\u5F80\u5F80\u4F7F\u7528\u76F8\u8FD1\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u8FDB\u884C\u8BC8\u9A97\uFF0C\u4F8B\u5982\uFF1A\u201C\u9A97\u5B501\u201D\u548C\u201C\u9A97\u5B50l\u201D\uFF0C\u770B\u4E0A\u53BB\u76F8\u4F3C\uFF0C\u5176\u5B9E\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u6570\u5B571\uFF0C\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u5B57\u6BCDL\u7684\u5C0F\u5199\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u6211\u4EEC\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24289
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u88C5\u5907\u5546\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zxscdngNPCkyjfzydjzrw",
		"question":"\u5728\u65B0\u624B\u57CE\u7684\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u53EF\u4EE5\u63A5\u526F\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u5C31\u804C\u4EFB\u52A1\uFF1F",
		"id":24291
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5218\u7985",
		"indexes":"csbzdxdzlbbxz",
		"question":"<\u51FA\u5E08\u8868>\u4E2D\u7684\"\u5148\u5E1D\"\u6307\u5218\u5907,\"\u965B\u4E0B\"\u6307",
		"id":24292
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u6838\u5B9E\u5BF9\u65B9\u8EAB\u4EFD\u540E\u518D\u6DF1\u5165\u6C9F\u901A",
		"indexes":"fzgjqwywcswlxsyxyrgsntyycdndrjnyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u8F85\u52A9\u5DE5\u5177\u8BF7\u52FF\u7528\u3011\u5916\u51FA\u65F6\u65E0\u804A\u60F3\u4E0A\u6E38\u620F\uFF0C\u6709\u4EBA\u544A\u8BC9\u4F60\u4ED6\u6709\u8FDC\u7A0B\u7535\u8111\u7684\u8F6F\u4EF6\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24293
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u70ED\u5E26\u5B63\u98CE\u6C14\u5019",
		"indexes":"xlnygsyzjwqh",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4E2D\u7ECF\u7EAC\u6C14\u5019\uFF1F",
		"id":24294
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4EBA\u683C",
		"indexes":"ngsyxcg",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u4FEE\u8F9E\u683C\uFF1F",
		"id":24295
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u79D2",
		"indexes":"xlnygdwsysjdw",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u5355\u4F4D\u5C5E\u4E8E\u65F6\u95F4\u5355\u4F4D\uFF1F",
		"id":24296
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u64E6\u9165\u997C",
		"indexes":"yxngxcjyxbfw",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C0F\u5403\u5177\u6709\u897F\u5317\u98CE\u5473\uFF1F",
		"id":24297
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u7F05\u7538",
		"indexes":"xlnggjbszglssdfsg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u90A3\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u4E0D\u662F\u4E2D\u56FD\u5386\u53F2\u4E0A\u7684\u9644\u5C5E\u56FD\uFF1F",
		"id":24298
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u671D\u671B\u4E61\u5904",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczszwtdylby",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5B8B\u4E4B\u95EE\u300A\u9898\u5927\u5EBE\u5CAD\u5317\u9A7F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24299
	},
	{
		"answer":"C35\u57CE\u5E02\u4E89\u593A\u6218",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlqgy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u9880\u300A\u53E4\u610F\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24300
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9B4F,\u8700,\u5434",
		"indexes":"txsfsztxflwnjg",
		"question":"\u5929\u4E0B\u4E09\u5206\u662F\u6307\u5929\u4E0B\u5206\u88C2\u4E3A\u54EA\u51E0\u56FD",
		"id":24301
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u66F9\u690D",
		"indexes":"zglgglmyhbxyyxesldglzdgljghscq",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u201C\u8EAC\u8015\u9647\u4EA9\u201D\u4E8E\u6E56\u5317\u8944\u9633\u4EE5\u897F\u4E8C\u5341\u91CC\u7684\u53E4\u9686\u4E2D\uFF0C\u5EA6\u8FC7\u4E86\u51E0\u4E2A\u5BD2\u6691\u6625\u79CB\u3002",
		"id":24302
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4E00\u6837",
		"indexes":"rggwdmzslsdsmnhtddj",
		"question":"\u5982\u679C\u602A\u7269\u7684\u540D\u5B57\u662F\u7EFF\u8272\u7684\uFF0C\u8BF4\u660E\u4F60\u548C\u4ED6\u7684\u7B49\u7EA7",
		"id":24303
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8EAB\u7A7F\u864E\u76AE",
		"indexes":"whxcjhc",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4F55\u8BB8\u891A\u53EB\u864E\u75F4?",
		"id":24304
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u751C\u9178\u54B8\u82E6",
		"indexes":"qwgmsy",
		"question":"\u537F\u4E3A\u5B98\u540D\uFF0C\u59CB\u4E8E:",
		"id":24306
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4F46\u4E01",
		"indexes":"zsjzhywsrxsdzcywsrzds",
		"question":"\u4E2D\u4E16\u7EAA\u6700\u540E\u4E00\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\uFF0C\u65B0\u65F6\u4EE3\u6700\u521D\u4E00\u4F4D\u8BD7\u4EBA\u6307\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24307
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE",
		"indexes":"ssfmctjlb",
		"question":"\u8C01\u8BF4\u670D\u9A6C\u8D85\u6295\u964D\u5218\u5907\uFF1F",
		"id":24308
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8FD0\u6C14\u7206\u53D1\uFF0C\u901A\u8FC7",
		"indexes":"gjrwkydczfzm",
		"question":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u4EFB\u52A1\u53EF\u4EE5\u591A\u6B21\u91CD\u590D\u505A\u5417?",
		"id":24309
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5251\u4F8D",
		"indexes":"kfcxsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u72C2\u65A7\u51B2\u9704\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24310
	},
	{
		"answer":"5",
		"indexes":"mgdF22mqzdjsydjdzdj",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD\u7684F\uFF0D22\u731B\u79BD\u6218\u6597\u673A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u7B2C\u51E0\u4EE3\u6218\u6597\u673A\uFF1F",
		"id":24311
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u6218\u5929\u4F7F\u5B50\u94ED",
		"indexes":"yxngdjskyzscngmdd",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u9053\u5177,\u662F\u53EF\u4EE5\u5728\u5546\u57CE\u5185\u8D2D\u4E70\u5230\u7684?",
		"id":24312
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9A6C\u5CB1",
		"indexes":"wyfhslsjhcdzdyyyqsyyzhhsyyhshlzlwy",
		"question":"\u9B4F\u5EF6\u653E\u706B\u70E7\u4E86\u8700\u519B\u56DE\u64A4\u7684\u6808\u9053\uFF0C\u626C\u8A00\u8981\u64D2\u6740\u6768\u4EEA\uFF0C\u6700\u540E\u8FD8\u662F\u6768\u4EEA\u548C\u8C01\u5408\u529B\u65A9\u4E86\u9B4F\u5EF6",
		"id":24313
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hfftsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u706B\u51E4\u9644\u4F53\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24314
	},
	{
		"answer":"1223\u5E74\u81F31234\u5E74",
		"indexes":"mgdycxzs",
		"question":"\u8499\u53E4\u7B2C\u4E00\u6B21\u897F\u5F81\u662F",
		"id":24315
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u5BB6\u9891\u9053",
		"indexes":"nsdhrgxyqfwqdsggjdntdygsy",
		"question":"\u4F60\u8BF4\u7684\u8BDD\u5982\u679C\u60F3\u8981\u5168\u670D\u52A1\u5668\u7684\u4E09\u4E2A\u56FD\u5BB6\u90FD\u80FD\u542C\u5230\uFF0C\u5E94\u8BE5\u4F7F\u7528\uFF1F",
		"id":24316
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6709\u94B1\u5C31\u53EF\u4EE5",
		"indexes":"hmdrkyzmcm",
		"question":"\u7EA2\u540D\u7684\u4EBA\u53EF\u4EE5\u5750\u9A6C\u8F66\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24317
	},
	{
		"answer":"C45",
		"indexes":"ysjfsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u7389\u77F3\u4FF1\u711A\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24318
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u5996\u6CD5",
		"indexes":"yxzdbsgyds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24320
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5173\u5BFF\u957F",
		"indexes":"yxzdbsgyds",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u6307\u7684\u4E0D\u662F\u5173\u7FBD\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24322
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u62D2\u7EDD",
		"indexes":"hhjypsjysdftrsxwjxhhydzzqknyg",
		"question":"\u3010\u6362\u53F7\u4EA4\u6613\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u4EA4\u6613\u65F6\uFF0C\u5BF9\u65B9\u7A81\u7136\u8BF4\u5E0C\u671B\u8FDB\u884C\u6362\u53F7\uFF0C\u9047\u5230\u8FD9\u79CD\u60C5\u51B5\uFF0C\u4F60\u5E94\u8BE5\uFF1A",
		"id":24323
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u53D1\u767D\u65E5\u68A6\u5427\uFF1F",
		"indexes":"y5gjdkyscc10gzjdm",
		"question":"\u75285\u4E2A\u9E21\u86CB\u53EF\u4EE5\u751F\u4EA7\u51FA10\u4E2A\u716E\u9E21\u86CB\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24324
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5143",
		"indexes":"mg1787nxfgdjsxfdqlz",
		"question":"\u7F8E\u56FD1787\u5E74\u5BAA\u6CD5\u89C4\u5B9A\uFF0C\u89E3\u91CA\u5BAA\u6CD5\u7684\u6743\u529B\u5728\uFF1A",
		"id":24329
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9AB7\u9AC5\u7CBE\u7075,\u767D\u91CE\u732A,\u90AA\u6076\u94B3\u866B,\u7956\u739B\u536B\u58EB",
		"indexes":"zykndzjgjsdgws",
		"question":"\u6700\u6709\u53EF\u80FD\u6389\u4E2D\u7EA7\u5DE5\u5320\u4E66\u7684\u602A\u7269\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":24330
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u674E\u6E05\u7167",
		"indexes":"hyajsds",
		"question":"\u53F7\u201C\u6613\u5B89\u5C45\u58EB\u201D\u7684\u662F\uFF1F",
		"id":24332
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u989D\u5C14\u9F50\u65AF\u6CB3",
		"indexes":"fyywgwyzrbbydhls",
		"question":"\u53D1\u6E90\u4E8E\u6211\u56FD\u552F\u4E00\u6CE8\u5165\u5317\u51B0\u6D0B\u7684\u6CB3\u6D41\u662F\uFF1A",
		"id":24335
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u770B\u5230\u4ED6\u540E\u6309G\u952E",
		"indexes":"zyhNPCdh",
		"question":"\u600E\u6837\u548CNPC\u5BF9\u8BDD\uFF1F",
		"id":24338
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u97E9\u9042",
		"indexes":"ljjsccylljmcysd",
		"question":"\u79BB\u95F4\u8BA1\u662F\u66F9\u64CD\u7528\u6765\u79BB\u95F4\u9A6C\u8D85\u4E0E\u8C01\u7684",
		"id":24340
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED9\u672F\u58EB",
		"indexes":"hfflsngzydjn",
		"question":"\u56DE\u98CE\u62C2\u67F3\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24341
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u4ED6\u4EBA\u54C1\u597D",
		"indexes":"wsmyxrdckbwdrld",
		"question":"\u4E3A\u4EC0\u4E48\u6709\u4E9B\u4EBA\u7684\u4ED3\u5E93\u6BD4\u6211\u7684\u5BB9\u91CF\u5927\uFF1F",
		"id":24342
	},
	{
		"answer":"500\u5143",
		"indexes":"sygqsxxkzhzrxkzyyczmxzzgbmcydsyyxdfk",
		"question":"\u4F7F\u7528\u8FC7\u671F\u3001\u5931\u6548\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\u6216\u8F6C\u8BA9\u8BB8\u53EF\u8BC1\uFF0C\u7531\u70DF\u8349\u4E13\u5356\u884C\u653F\u4E3B\u7BA1\u90E8\u95E8\u5904\u4EE5\u591A\u5C11\u5143\u4EE5\u4E0B\u7684\u7F5A\u6B3E\uFF1F",
		"id":24345
	},
	{
		"answer":"2002\u5E745\u67081\u65E5",
		"indexes":"cnynqwgksssxdgjqzxcprzzd",
		"question":"\u4ECE\u54EA\u4E00\u5E74\u8D77\uFF0C\u6211\u56FD\u5F00\u59CB\u5B9E\u65BD\u65B0\u7684\u56FD\u5BB6\u5F3A\u5236\u6027\u4EA7\u54C1\u8BA4\u8BC1\u5236\u5EA6\uFF1F",
		"id":24346
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u54BD\u5589",
		"indexes":"hdccsgdw",
		"question":"\u6C49\u4EE3\u79F0\u57CE\u5E02\u5E72\u9053\u4E3A\uFF1A",
		"id":24347
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u660E\u65E5\u5DF4\u9675\u9053",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczlyxjwdyyb",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u674E\u76CA\u300A\u559C\u89C1\u5916\u5F1F\u53C8\u8A00\u522B\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24348
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u8708\u86A3",
		"indexes":"nzczsykc",
		"question":"\u54EA\u79CD\u866B\u5B50\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6606\u866B\uFF1F",
		"id":24349
	},
	{
		"answer":"0.87",
		"indexes":"xlsyxhxsdsnyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u5C5E\u4E8E\u5FAA\u73AF\u5C0F\u6570\u7684\u662F\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\uFF1F",
		"id":24350
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5DE6\u53F3\u76F8\u53CD",
		"indexes":"yxngsysg",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u5C5E\u4E8E\u6C34\u679C",
		"id":24351
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u80E1\u5C18\u672A\u5317\u706D",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczlxzyl",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5218\u5BAA\u300A\u6298\u6768\u67F3\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24352
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u5B98\u91CD\u590F\u537F",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczzjlfhszxjyg",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u5F20\u4E5D\u9F84\u300A\u5949\u548C\u5723\u5236\u5E78\u664B\u9633\u5BAB\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24353
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9999\u96FE\u4E91\u9B1F\u6E7F",
		"indexes":"xlnjbsczdfyy",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u4E0D\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u675C\u752B\u300A\u6708\u591C\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24354
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B9D\u5B9D\u4E0D\u5F00\u5FC3",
		"indexes":"yxngbscc",
		"question":"\u4EE5\u4E0B\u54EA\u4E2A\u4E0D\u662F\u5DDD\u83DC\uFF1F",
		"id":24355
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u72FC",
		"indexes":"mcjqzztzdcszyhlhgzqyzjgxds",
		"question":"\u660E\u521D\u52A0\u5F3A\u4E13\u5236\u7EDF\u6CBB\u7684\u63AA\u65BD\u4E2D\uFF0C\u4E0E\u540E\u6765\u5BA6\u5B98\u4E13\u6743\u6709\u76F4\u63A5\u5173\u7CFB\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24356
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u529D\u541B\u66F4\u5C3D\u4E00\u676F\u9152",
		"indexes":"xlnjsczwwwcq",
		"question":"\u4E0B\u5217\u54EA\u53E5\u662F\u51FA\u81EA\u738B\u7EF4\u300A\u6E2D\u57CE\u66F2\u300B\uFF1F",
		"id":24357
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5B69\u5B50\u968F\u8C01\u751F\u6D3B\uFF0C\u8C01\u8D1F\u8D23\u4EFB",
		"indexes":"fqlyhdwcnrzndjysfyzr",
		"question":"\u592B\u59BB\u79BB\u5F02\u540E\u5BF9\u672A\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u5B50\u5973\u7684\u6559\u80B2\u8C01\u8D1F\u6709\u8D23\u4EFB\uFF1F",
		"id":24358
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6587\u6E90",
		"indexes":"skqsqssxqbfbzywywywjwzwhwswlqgzbyfljfhds",
		"question":"\u300A\u56DB\u5E93\u5168\u4E66\u300B\u5168\u4E66\u7F2E\u5199\u4E03\u90E8\u5206\u522B\u85CF\u4E8E\u6587\u6E0A\u3001\u6587\u6E90\u3001\u6587\u6D25\u3001\u6587\u5B97\u3001\u6587\u6C47\u3001\u6587\u6EAF\u3001\u6587\u6F9C\u4E03\u9601\u4E2D\uFF0C\u88AB\u82F1\u6CD5\u8054\u519B\u711A\u6BC1\u7684\u662F",
		"id":24359
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u59DC\u7EF4",
		"indexes":"zglzwzyjdhssbbqjjls",
		"question":"\u8BF8\u845B\u4EAE\u5728\u4E94\u4E08\u539F\u4EA4\u4EE3\u540E\u4E8B\u65F6\uFF0C\u628A\u5175\u6743\u4EA4\u7ED9\u4E86\u8C01",
		"id":24360
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u6CD5\u56FD",
		"indexes":"nygslhgalhcrlsgzy",
		"question":"\u54EA\u4E00\u4E2A\u662F\u8054\u5408\u56FD\u5B89\u7406\u4F1A\u5E38\u4EFB\u7406\u4E8B\u56FD\u4E4B\u4E00\uFF1A",
		"id":24362
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5370\u7B2C\u5B89\u4EBA",
		"indexes":"zsxozmzcchtsdmztzjms",
		"question":"\u906D\u53D7\u897F\u6B27\u6B96\u6C11\u8005\u6467\u6B8B\u548C\u5C60\u6740\u7684\u7F8E\u6D32\u571F\u8457\u5C45\u6C11\u662F",
		"id":24363
	},
	{
		"answer":"8848",
		"indexes":"zmlmfwy",
		"question":"\u73E0\u7A46\u6717\u9A6C\u5CF0\u4F4D\u4E8E\uFF08\uFF09",
		"id":24364
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u74EE\u4E2D\u6349\u9CD6\u8BA1",
		"indexes":"cbzzhccyzzxzjhxmslzspmttxxdysxyxssmj",
		"question":"\u8D64\u58C1\u4E4B\u6218\u540E\uFF0C\u66F9\u64CD\u4E00\u76F4\u5728\u5BFB\u627E\u673A\u4F1A\u6D88\u706D\u5B59\u5218\uFF0C\u53EA\u662F\u6015\u9A6C\u817E\u5077\u88AD\u8BB8\u90FD\u3002\u4E8E\u662F\u8340\u6538\u732E\u4E0A\u4EC0\u4E48\u8BA1",
		"id":24366
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u63D0\u9AD8\u8B66\u60D5\uFF0C\u597D\u53CB\u7684\u53F7\u53EF\u80FD\u88AB\u76D7\uFF0C\u53D1\u7684\u662F\u6728\u9A6C",
		"indexes":"zbfzpsgjdzbcbdgjwpskytgmxtssdmffzm",
		"question":"\u3010\u88C5\u5907\u590D\u5236\u9A97\u672F\u3011\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7684\u88C5\u5907\u3001\u7FC5\u8180\u7B49\u9AD8\u7EA7\u7269\u54C1\u65F6\u53EF\u4EE5\u901A\u8FC7\u67D0\u4E9B\u7279\u6B8A\u624B\u6BB5\u514D\u8D39\u590D\u5236\u5417\uFF1F",
		"id":24371
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5176\u5B83",
		"indexes":"lgzczysgyywhzy",
		"question":"\u7F57\u8D2F\u4E2D\u9664\u8457\u6709\u300A\u4E09\u56FD\u6F14\u4E49\u300B\u5916\u8FD8\u8457\u6709",
		"id":24372
	},
	{
		"answer":"C48\u7684\u716E\u9152\u8BBA\u82F1\u96C4\u526F\u672C",
		"indexes":"ggdzqctmybssysd",
		"question":"\u5173\u516C\u7684\u5750\u9A91\u8D64\u5154\u9A6C\u539F\u672C\u662F\u5C5E\u4E8E\u8C01\u7684?",
		"id":24373
	},
	{
		"answer":"28\u5929",
		"indexes":"rldpfzzbddtqhszywzccnrdpfqbgxycxyjjdzsj",
		"question":"\u4EBA\u7C7B\u7684\u76AE\u80A4\u603B\u5728\u4E0D\u65AD\u5730\u8131\u53BB\u548C\u751F\u957F\u3002\u4E00\u4F4D\u6B63\u5E38\u6210\u5E74\u4EBA\u7684\u76AE\u80A4\u5168\u90E8\u66F4\u65B0\u4E00\u6B21\u9700\u8981\u5C06\u8FD1\u591A\u957F\u65F6\u95F4\uFF1F",
		"id":24374
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u5468\u745C",
		"indexes":"sqqlrjz",
		"question":"\u8C01\u5A36\u4EB2\u8DEF\u4EBA\u7686\u77E5",
		"id":24375
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u56FD\u4E3B",
		"indexes":"xyyzhdjqrwkyzngNPCjsrw",
		"question":"\u60F3\u8981\u4E00\u76F4\u83B7\u5F97\u91D1\u94B1\u4EFB\u52A1,\u53EF\u4EE5\u627E\u54EA\u4E2ANPC\u63A5\u53D7\u4EFB\u52A1?",
		"id":24376
	},
	{
		"answer":"\u9634\u9633\u58EB",
		"indexes":"fgzysngzydjn",
		"question":"\u5206\u5149\u65A9\u5F71\u662F\u54EA\u4E2A\u804C\u4E1A\u7684\u6280\u80FD?",
		"id":24377
	}
]